Two middle school Satan worshipers try to enact a terrible plan.
And then we look at the conspiracy that is called "God Was Raped" today on Dead Rabbit
Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host, Jason Carpenter.
I'm having a great day.
I hope you're having a great day too.
This is the season finale for season 2.
So after this we're going to be taking a week long break.
I hope you guys stick with me.
You guys should be seeing notifications in a week.
What is that?
November 5th is when I'm taking my break.
So seven days after that, November 12th.
Hey, yeah.
So we'll be back here on November 12th.
I hope you guys have a great time.
I just needed some time off there.
So you know, yesterday's episode was pretty fun.
I had a lot of fun with the paranormal porn stars and they actually hit me up on Twitter
and they said thanks for the shout out.
And that was really cool.
And if I ever needed any help, I'm plugging the show and I said let the same, you know?
So I didn't know this at the time.
I went and they had some YouTube videos up and I was watching them.
Now they did have the Spirit Box thing, which we've discussed before.
They did have a clip of a curtain moving and it appeared the windows was closed.
So you know, at least they're putting content out there.
They're putting ghost hunting content out there.
So that's cool.
We'll see what comes of it.
I would really like to see them.
And that's one thing I messaged them is I hope you guys find some proof of ghosts because
again, I'd like to see some good proof of ghosts.
And I'd also like to see them send up the paranormal groups that have been operation
for decades to get beaten by this group of newcomers.
So that would be, that's not a pun either.
That would be really cool.
So but yeah, yesterday was fun.
We had ghost baby and we had paranormal porn stars.
And if I had planned stuff out better, probably would it be this way because last night's
episode was a lot of fun.
This night's episode is quite grim.
One of the stories just kind of fell in my lap.
And the other one I'd been working on for a while, it's one of, it's a conspiracy iceberg
story.
So I had to do more research on it, but we're going to go ahead and present it.
And it'll, it'll be a good way to end the season.
But it's just a little bit darker than yesterday's episode.
Actually before we get started with the first story, I want to let you guys know how much
it means to me that you guys are enjoying the show.
I love the feedback.
It's growing faster than I could have ever imagined and I'm really humbled to think that
so many people are into this show.
It's really, really great.
And I'm getting art from people and I'm getting kudos from people and it's just an amazing,
it's been an amazing ride so far and we're just getting started.
We are just getting started with Dead Ravvo Radio.
So let's go ahead and jump into the first story here.
Now the first story just happened on October 24th.
This is very, very recent.
And I just found out about it today.
Now what it is, I guess this is, this is kind of lighthearted.
I think it's funny, but it's pretty grim if you really kind of step back and think about
it.
So at Bartlow Middle School, which is in Florida, a student got wind of something and went
to a teacher and said, "Teacher, I think something bad is going to happen today."
And the teacher goes to the principal and the principal calls in the school resource
officer, which I think is just a term for like a security guard or a cop.
And they start looking for these two girls who hadn't been in a class.
So they were looking for them anyways and they find them in the restroom.
I'm assuming it was a girls restroom.
That's totally not clear, but they were definitely in the restroom.
And what these girls had planned was terrifying.
So the girls got arrested and the police went through their text messages and they came across
what they had heard from the student was that these girls had a plan.
They were going to attack students as they came into the bathroom, the smaller students
because of course serial killers can't take on real threats.
They're going to attack students who came into the bathroom.
They were going to stab them and then drink their blood and eat their flesh.
And then once they got to say, the article says up to 15 students.
I don't know why that's such an arbitrary number, but once they got to a certain number
of students, they were then going to throw body parts outside of the school and then
kill themselves.
That was their plan.
Now these two girls aren't being named.
I'm sure that'll change because even the slender man girls, the girls who tried killing the
other girl to get into slender man's mansion, their names eventually leaked.
So I'm sure these girls' names will leak as well.
But so that was their plan.
And when they got arrested, the cops, you know, obviously were interrogating them and
they said they were doing this for Satan.
So they had this belief that this was some sort of offering to Satan.
And I've talked about Satan worshipers in the past.
There are two types of Satan worshipers.
There's people like this, these girls.
And then there are people who are called themselves Satan worshipers or more, more, probably more
aptly Satanists, which basically they're just humanists.
There are people who believe in the pleasures of the flesh, but even they have fairly strict
rules about animal sacrifice and human sacrifice and things like that.
So when you hear about Church of Satan, that's not what they're, they're not referring to
lunatics like this.
The Church of Satan is an actual legitimate religion.
And I went over that on my anti-cosmic Satanism episode as well.
But I think it's important to make those distinctions.
These girls had a very, very limited view of the theology of Satan worship and also
piss poor planning.
So I left out a key detail.
I said that they found the girls in the restroom and then they were arrested by the police
and you're like, well, that's it.
Girls are allowed to use the restroom, right?
That's not, they were caught with weapons in the restroom.
Now the weapons they had were butcher knives.
That's fair.
I mean, you can plan on stabbing people and eating their flesh.
I could see bringing butcher knives to the party.
They also had a pizza cutter.
Now despite the word cutter in the term pizza cutter, when have you ever even been able
to cut a pizza properly with a pizza cutter?
You always just like, oh, oh, you just really got to go at it to get through that crust.
They really, I mean, that's the level of planning that went into this, that with two girls, they're
11 and 12 years old.
They thought that you could use a pizza cutter to one kill a person and two to cut them up.
I don't think a pizza cutter, you would have to sharpen that so sharp for that to be effective
in any way, shape or form.
And then even then, listen, if you're going to do like a mass murder thing like this, you
may not want to do it in a restroom because as you're chopping up one body, someone else
is going to walk in.
That's just the way it is.
And then you got to chase that person and now you run through.
I'm giving tips to young murdering girls, but terrible plan.
Absolutely terrible plan.
I've always had this theory and we read about this a lot in failed school shootings or school
bombings or school stabbings or school cannibalism.
There's always a student, not always, but most part there is a student that comes forward
and reveals the plans.
I have a theory.
I call it the 21 Jump Street theory.
I believe that all over America in high schools, there are maybe not all over America, but
I believe that in some high schools, there are actually undercover agents who look for
this stuff.
Because I noticed this trend back in the early 2000s where you would have three kids, you
would have two kids caught for trying to blow up a school and they would get ratted out.
I don't want to use that word yet.
Ratted out by a third student.
And let me say this right now.
Don't ever shoot up a school or anywhere.
It's terrible.
I said you're throwing your life away.
But I've always had this theory that because we do this with terrorists where we'll have
a guy show up and he's like, "Hey, you want to buy this bomb from me?"
And the terrorists will go, "Yeah, sure."
And then the feds come in and arrest them.
Or someone will go in and he'll find four guys and say, "You know what?
I really hate the government.
You know what we should do?
We should blow it up."
You should print out plans to build a bomb and you should run a truck and you should buy
the supplies and it's all a government thing.
And the question always is, would those four guys have ever thought about building a bomb
on their own without the agent coming in and selling it?
And I've wondered about that off and on over the years about these.
Obviously, there are real school shootings and they're absolutely tragic.
But I've always wondered if they have operations like that in high schools where an undercover
agent goes to a high school, identifies kind of like the loner kids and starts getting
them talking about, "Oh yeah, we should shoot up the school.
We draw plans and they get them all excited about the idea and then the agent goes, "Those
are the two kids who are planning on blowing up the school."
And the feds come in and they arrest it and it's this big deal.
If they are doing that, I can understand on one hand that they may figure these kids are
going to blow up the school anyways.
Our agent didn't actually make them make these plans.
On the other side, it's possible that they weren't going to blow up the school and they
got excited about the idea.
But once you get to the planning stage, you've crossed a lot of lines and that's where a
lot of these guys get caught.
Now having an undercover agent at middle school might be a little bit tricky, but in
a high school, I could see that happening.
In a high school, I could see an undercover agent going in, pretending to be one of the
outsiders, and checking to see if anyone else is on the fringes.
If anyone else is ready to blow and they just get enough information and then they report
them.
So I don't know.
The other theory, I mean obviously that's a conspiracy theory and I have absolutely
no evidence to back any of that up.
It's just a hunch.
It's far more likely that three kids start planning about something and then one gets
cold feet rightfully so because it's a horrific act.
Or the kid or kids who are planning on doing this thing, they have big mouths and they
end up telling somebody and then that person again rightfully so rats them out.
Now I'm not trying to use the word rat as a derogatory here.
That's just...
What's the other word?
Informs.
Yeah, I just can't think of another word for it right off the top of my head.
So yeah, these two middle...
Could you imagine if that had happened?
Could you imagine the horror and shock if their plan had been successful?
Two middle school girls eating up to 15 kids as they wandered into the bathroom one at
a time and then killing themselves on the front step of the school.
Could you imagine the sheer horror that the world would have to deal with when faced with
that kind of evil?
It would have been beyond shocking.
So I'm glad that they got caught and I'm glad that it was put to an end very quickly and
peacefully and don't bring a pizza cutter to a murder scene.
It's not going to help you one way or the other.
So the next thing I want to talk about, if you thought that story was dark and it was
fairly dark but it had a happy ending, not for the girls, they're screwed, but...
The next story comes from our conspiracy iceberg.
It's something that I've gotten a lot of requests on and it's fairly dark because the
imagery is fairly dark.
The ideas behind it are dark.
And it is the phrase "God was raped."
God was raped appears on some of the earlier conspiracy icebergs.
And very quickly people were throwing out ideas for what it was.
But God was raped really only has maybe two or three hypotheses of what that phrase actually
means.
Let's go ahead and break it down and I'll give my analysis or what I think is going
on.
So the first one is that there's God and then there's other cosmic beings.
And God was raped by one of these other cosmic beings.
And we are the product of that.
Humanity is the product of that rape.
He basically gave birth to us.
And that's the reason why God is such a dick to us over the years, over the millennias.
Because we're basically like his rape children.
Now while rape does play a large part in some mythology, the Greek gods raped an awful lot.
You know, I read that one, I read that theory and I was like, "I think there's more to it."
Because there would be nothing to really back that up in that God was violated in that way
by another cosmic being.
You'd have to imagine that there was a cosmic being on God's level or even more powerful.
And because when we're saying God, we're really restricting ourselves to the Western idea
of God.
So Judaism and Christianity and Islam.
So I don't really think that that's the case.
But it's an interesting note.
And again, I'll touch on this later, but I don't necessarily think God in that sense
has turned his back on humanity.
Now the second theory is a more interesting one, because there is a little bit of biblical
basis of this one.
That is the idea that, so we know when, let's back up for a second, so the story of Sodom
and Gomorrah.
So a quick paraphrase of the story of Sodom and Gomorrah.
So Abraham was pleading with God.
God was basically like, "You know what?
I'm done with the city of Sodom, because there are two separate cities."
And I was like, "You know what?
I'm done.
I'm so done.
It's just such a wicked place.
Everyone is super rude there, and they commit a bunch of crimes, and they don't treat foreigners
with any respect.
I don't like it.
I don't like it at all."
Now Abraham was like, "God, listen, you can't destroy the city."
And basically God goes, "Okay, tell you what.
If you can find me 50 righteous people in that city, I'll spare it."
And now Abraham starts to basically negotiate with them, and he's like, "Tell you what?
What if I can only find 40?"
And so God goes, "Okay, you know what?
40.
If you can finally 40 people, I won't destroy it."
Then Abraham goes, "What if I can only find 30 people?"
And so they negotiate it down to 10 people.
So basically if God says, "If I can find 10 people in this town, then I'm good.
I won't destroy it."
And then God sends his angels into the city of Sodom, and when they show up, their disguise
is normal people.
When they show up, Lot is sitting outside the gate, and Lot's like, "Oh my God, dudes,
you dudes are rock.
Why don't you come into the city and we'll hang out and I'll show you how good this town
can be."
So they go to Lot's house, and they're just chilling in there.
And what happens is a bunch of dudes show outside and start banging on Lot's door, and
they're like, "Lettison, let us in.
We want to bang the dudes that just came in your house."
And Lot's like, "No, no, no, no, no.
You don't understand.
These people are special."
And people are like, "No, dude, we want to have sex with them.
Let us in."
And then in one of the most curious parts of the Bible, Lot says, "So Lot is there with
the two angels, his two daughters, and his wife."
And Lot goes, "Tell you what, guys, there's your poundin' on the door, like the walking
dead."
Lot goes, "Tell you what, you cannot under any circumstances have sex with these two
dudes who just came in from out of town.
However, I have two virgin daughters.
I will gladly give you if you leave these guys alone."
What?
That's such a weird thing.
But see, the thing that gets lost a lot in the story of Sodom, one of the things that
made God very mad, it was a big part of Sodom's sin, according to the Bible, was the fact
that they were rude to travelers, that people would come there to visit and they would get
stabbed or stuff stolen from them or raped or all sorts of stuff.
And that was a thing.
Like if somebody comes into your home or comes into your city, you should treat them as family.
So the fact that Lot was saying, "You can't hurt these travelers," because Lot didn't
know they were angels, Lot said, "You can't hurt these travelers.
You can't hurt these travelers."
And Lot says, "Listen, they're in my house.
I cannot let you hurt them.
They're from out of town and they're in my house.
You can't hurt them here.
Have sex with my virgin daughters."
And that was considered because he was basically those, it's so bizarre.
It's such a weird little aside.
But the fact that the city of Sodom they were being rude to outsiders was actually one of
their biggest sins.
So anyways, and you know, the rape, that is part of that too.
So what happens is the angels eventually end up blinding the people outside, using their
powers to blind the people outside.
And at that point, God was like, "You know what, Lot, take your family, get out of town,
and whatever you do, don't turn around.
Just leave.
Don't turn around and watch what's happening."
So Lot and his wife and his two daughters take off out of town, out of Sodom, and the city
is, by all accounts, just nuked.
It's vaporized.
And Lot's wife turns around and looks and she turns into a pillar of salt.
So she's gone.
And people have thought, "Well, maybe there was some sort of nuclear blast, because what
else would turn a person to salt?"
Well, I don't know, but looking at a nuclear blast sure won't turn you into salt.
And then of course there's an even odd, you know, cap to this story.
Lot passes out at some point and both of his daughters have sex with him and give birth
to his sons, their grandkids.
So it's to keep the family line going, because the mom was dead, so the two daughters seduced,
well, didn't seduce him.
Basically, they raped him.
He was asleep.
There's a lot of rape in this part of the Bible.
Now, the story, I paraphrase, basically, Genesis 18 and 19 for you, but this is where the God
was raped story comes from.
So God says, let me read you the exact passage here.
So this is Genesis 18, "And the Lord said, because the cry of Sodom and Gomorrah is great,
and because their sin is very grievous, I will go down now and see whether they have
done altogether according to the cry of it, which is come unto me, and if not, I will know."
So what's interesting about that is that God's saying that he's going to visit Sodom.
This is from the King James Version.
So and then we finish out 18 where he's having this debate with Abraham over how many good
people he has to find.
And then when we go into Genesis 19, it just starts off with the two angels showing up
outside of town.
The theory is this, that in the original version, if you look at the original translations of
this, is that it was God who went into Sodom, and the story ended up a little bit differently.
So that God visited Sodom, and he saw the wickedness.
He was at Lot's house.
The guys were banging on the door, and they raped him.
And then they say, one of the theories is that then the story got changed.
So it was God said, I'm going into town, but the angels went into town.
The angels got raped, and God destroys the city.
And now the version that we see in the Bible is, God says he's going down, but he sends
his angels down instead.
They don't get raped, and God destroys the city.
Now we do know when we look at stuff like the Council of Nicaea, the Bible has been
edited by man.
And books have been deleted from the Bible that they feel didn't really fit the vibe that
they were going for.
This is a good way to put it, as good as any.
So the idea that there are parts of the Bible that have been modified is not a very controversial
idea among most theologians.
I did try looking up other times when angels blinded people.
So I looked for another part of the Bible where an angel used the power of blindness
over people.
And I personally couldn't find one.
It may be out there.
The other character who definitely does get blinded is Saul.
Eventually he becomes Paul when he becomes the father of Jesus.
And actually, so what happened with Saul was hunting Jesus and persecuting Christians,
and he heard a disembodied voice say, "Why are you persecuting me?"
And Saul's like, "What the hell?
Where's that coming from?"
And the guy's like, "I'm Jesus."
And he blinds Saul, and then eventually Saul becomes Paul.
His vision is restored, and it's like, now he can see the real, he can see the beauty
of God and the beauty of Christ.
Now the Holy Trinity, God is Jesus, and Jesus is the Holy Spirit and all of that stuff.
So the only people who I've seen, and I could be wrong on this, that have the power to blind
people in the Bible is God or Jesus.
And again, if somebody wants to correct me on that, I'm 100% behind being corrected on
that.
So it makes the story of the angels having the power to blind the crowd outside a little
weird.
So we have two things.
I mean, I'm going to go into the city, and we have a bunch of people being blinded, which
we've seen God/Jesus do that in other parts of the Bible.
Is it possible that the Bible has been modified, that it was God who went into the city of
Sodom himself, and almost was raped?
Is it possible that the Bible has changed so much that God did go into the city, actually
get raped, and then blow up the city?
You know, it's not like Sodom and Gomorrah were the only cities where evil was happening.
God really had a beef with these towns.
Like it really, really stuck in his craw that these guys were operating the way that they
did.
And if God takes to physical form, I guess that is possible.
So, but then again, if he has the power to blind people, I don't really think they would
be very effective rapists, especially if he can blind a whole group of them.
But the phrase "God was raped" may just be based on the idea that God was in the city
of Sodom and he was almost raped.
And I think that theory holds more weight than the first one, because now we have biblical
text we can look at.
Now, I'm not a biblical scholar.
I'm not a theologian.
I don't speak Latin or Greek or Hebrew or any of these things.
And this is something that people could go, "Oh, no, no, no, you're real off-basist."
And again, I'm totally open to feedback.
But I think that may be where the theory God was raped came from.
But, when I was researching this, I came across something very sad.
And this interview was in 2005.
So it definitely would predate the iceberg by, what, six, seven years.
So there was a young actress named Pamela Senna who was raped.
And she gave this really interesting interview.
So let me go ahead.
So this was an interview that was going on.
And I'm going to start off with a question and then her answer to it.
So the question, so basically she believes that during the rape she left her body.
She had a little altar to God placed in her house.
And during the rape she kind of disembodied herself and she walked over to the altar.
Now, this is the question.
You explained that she left her body to walk over to the altar where God lived in your home
and repeatedly pleaded with him to help you, but to no avail.
Clearly up to this point you believed that he existed and that he could help you, but
the torture didn't stop.
So do you feel that he could have helped you, but chose not to?
This was her answer.
Before the rape, I believed in him absolutely.
So much so that when I reached that moment of realization of being absolutely powerless,
I had the out of body experience that I wrote about in the book.
Whatever small part of me believes that praying to God was redundant was explained to me by
my mother, who believes that God was in that bed with me, crying at the potential for human
cruelty, that God was also being raped with me, so how could he help me?
There's some part of me that believes that.
I think that is an interesting little piece of this puzzle.
And it's the idea that God was raped because he's raped when anyone is raped.
He dies when anybody dies.
He hurts when anybody hurts.
He's happy when anybody's happy and so on and so forth and so on.
And I think that's the key component to, again I'm not trying to name a particular deity,
and that's why I've kind of set this about all kind of Western religions that believe.
And even I think if you were a polytheist and you believe that there is just pantheon
of God's, is that the problem that a lot of people have with religion is they go, "How
could God have let babies die of AIDS in Africa?"
But I think that's not the point.
I think the point is that he's dying with those children as well.
It's not that he's immune to our suffering.
He suffers with us.
So this young woman was being raped in her bed and he was there with her experiencing
that because technically you're his child.
So the same way that any parent would suffer seeing their children suffer, that's God but
he has the ability to unfortunately be there in those horrible moments.
So God doesn't let little babies get AIDS and God doesn't let people get raped and God
doesn't let all these horrible things happen.
God experiences those things on that level if you believe in that.
And I know not everybody believes in that.
But I think that's the key.
Technically yeah, God was raped.
God was raped every time any person was ever raped or beaten or bruised or hurt or whatever.
So it's an intro.
I started off looking at this phrase and I was really clued in onto the story of Abraham
and Law and Sodom and Gomorrah and the angels and all that stuff because I'd heard that
story growing up.
But I think Pamela Sinna's interview is more accurate to that phrase.
Yes, God was raped because she was raped and God is with her.
And that is how you can take a cosmic omniscient being and break him down to a level that
we can understand.
So he's all powerful.
But in that moment, he's just as vulnerable as his children.
Which I find mind-blowing, honestly.
So that's where I...
If I had to say what that phrase means, the kind of cool, interesting way to look at it
is that God went to Sodom and he got raped and he blew the cities up.
And if we could find...
That's something that we could actually track back.
If we could find someone who could read Hebrew or someone who could read Latin, they may
be able to go through and go, "Oh yeah, there is some weird other parts of that text that
don't really make sense."
But I think that the idea that God not was raped, but God is raped, and God is killed
and God is...
You know, God has stuff stolen.
God gets his Xbox stolen because you're like, "Ah!"
God has walked out of his house and looked and his bicycle lock was broken.
I think that's a more interesting way to kind of break down such a powerful character.
So I think that's what the phrase, "God was raped" means on the iceberg.
But it doesn't mean that I'm 100%.
If you guys have any feedback or any other ideas about it, I'd love to hear from you.
And lastly, I know this episode is running a little bit long.
But I promise you zombies.
There's some zombies.
Crystal from Twitter.
I suggest turning down your radio.
We're gonna go ahead and get started here.
But before we do, just want to let you guys know, Dead Rapper Radio Daily, Paranormal Conspiracy
and True Crime Podcast.
You don't have to listen to it every day, but I'm glad you listened to it today.
Have a great one, guys.
Okay, so we're back.
Now, again, if you've been listening to...
I had to take the song out.
I performed a rap song here.
So Dead World Part 1 and Dead World Part 2 is the story of a young...
A story of...
No, he's not necessarily young, I guess.
But it's the story of a man and his daughter trying to outrun a group of zombies in Sacramento.
I ended up taking both of those songs out of the podcast because they do contain a instrumental
that I do not own now.
And I explained this on the earlier edited episode, Dead World, when in the hip-hop world,
a lot of times people rap over other people's beats.
It's kind of a normal thing.
But when you start to get into the corporate world of podcasting and things like that,
you don't really want to mess with copyrights.
Now, the songs have not disappeared.
They're available on YouTube, and I'm going to include the YouTube link and the show notes
if you want to go check those out.
I really like them.
I thought they were really cool, but maybe you don't like rap.
Maybe you don't like me rapping, or maybe you don't like both.
But anyway, so I did want to take that out because, again, I just wanted to stave off
any trouble in the future.
I didn't want to be way deep into the podcast and get a copyright claim notice and so on
and so forth.
And I think if you've gone through the archives, this is going to be the last time we're going
to do anything like this, you may notice things where I say, "Here, let's listen to this clip
and no clip plays."
That's because I ended up taking the clip out because I didn't want to get...
And again, in a court of law, it totally would have stood up as fair of use because I would
play a clip and comment on it and critique it and things like that.
But I just didn't want to bother with the hassle.
So we're going through season three forward.
We're not going to be doing that.
We're just going to be discussing things.
It didn't really add a ton to it anyways.
The song did, I think, but yeah, we just want to be in the clear with all of our copyright
stuff.
All of our art we own, the intro and outro song we own.
Every song that you hear on the show we either own or it's stock music.
It's free music that I find.
So yeah, sorry, it's a little bit of an anticlimatic for such a great episode.
I really like this episode, so it's kind of anticlimatic, but I hope that you enjoyed
it nonetheless.
If you want to check out the music, click the YouTube link before.
Now I'm going to go back into the future and I hope you'll join me then.