It's too hot for YouTube week. These are all the stories that I put off telling because I knew YouTube
Wanted to allow them anyways first off
There's a cheese out there. They would have allowed this story, but I have to do an introduction story and it's a good one
There's a cheese out there. That's so
disgusting
It's illegal to eat and
Then we meet a man who believes that the Jewish people came from outer space
with one mission
To protect us from cryptids today on Dead Rabbit Radio
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host Jason Carpenter
I'm having a great day. Hope you guys are having a great day too. I had a great weekend
I hope you guys had a great weekend too. Coming at you live from the new studio
The haunted closet that is the name of the studio and it actually is a haunted closet and I have some even more improvements
I have some sound balancing stuff
So I hope this sounds even better than it did last time
We're making improvements to this show because this show is going to be around for a long time
And the reason why the show keeps growing is because of patreon supporters like Sam everyone give a round of applause to Sam
He is walking into the Arab command playing a little piccolo
And all these kids are following him and doing these dances and something like that. We're like hey Sam
Why'd you bring all those kids to the not even now? Why do you have a bunch of kids following me? He's like I'm the fight Piper
I love that episode. I actually don't know if you love that episode
But he's the fight Piper and the kids are just like what are we doing here?
And we're like, we'll have to feed you guys and we'll get you home to your parents soon
But Sam until then the kids are now part of this crew and Sam
You're gonna be our captain our pilot this episode if you guys can't support the patreon or if you don't kidding
Have children in mass. That's great. Don't do that second thing. But if you don't support the patreon
Help get the word out about the show. Tell your friends. Tell your family talk about it online
That's what we need you to do to help the show grow now Sam
Go ahead and fire up. We've got all these kids. We're gonna need some of our big vehicles
Let's hop in the dead rabbit dreadnought
We'll put it in your little kid arms to work as they're rowing in the galley
You're gonna be the captain of this dreadnought. We're leaving behind dead rabbit command. We are headed out to
Sardinia
Being in the big old drum the kids were like my arms hurt
I'm like only a thousand more miles kids. We're almost there. So we all get off of this boat
We give the kids some some fruit juice. They'll need those electrolytes for the journey back and
Sam is leading us into a small village in Sardinia now Sardinia is actually an island in the Mediterranean
It's off the coast of Italy. We're here to taste the delicacy
It's called kazoo Martzu
It's supper. This is great. It's supper time not only a supper time. It's some kids birthday
They use this for birthday celebrations and wedding celebrations. It's a delicacy
Everyone lives this and I have my little napkin tied around my neck and I have my fork in my knife
And I'm like come on guys. Let's run. Let's go get some Kazoo Martzu
And we sit down and they bring out a big block of cheese
Mmm-hmm. You love the smell of cheese
I say to you as the smell is not hit your nose yet and you look down at it and it's like
Melted cheese in the middle of this wheel of cheese kind of like queso you guys love queso, right?
I'm already taking three or four bites. Yum. Yum. Yum. Just dig in guys and you're looking at each other
Sam is hijacking the boat to leave leave us all behind Kazoo Martzu. It's illegal
This cheese cannot be purchased to come out be eaten probably can't be transported
You just roll in a wheelchair on the road cops are chasing after you Kazoo Martzu literally means putrid cheese
Now they've been making this cheese for thousands of years
They're actually trying to get it made not illegal the people of Sardinia goes this is a traditional food
Haggis is disgusting right a bunch of people eat disgusting stuff. Why can't we eat Kazoo Martzu?
We've been doing this forever and the government's trying to get the the European Union. It's illegal in the United States as well
You can't even eat it where it's made they can bust you there
It's like it's like a black market thing although the local cops aren't gonna kick down your door because you're eating this
Disgusting food they might kick down your door to eat some as well. This is what you do now
We're all in farmer outfits Sam is teleported back to the group. He's like great
We're milking a sheep get that nice warm body temperature sheet milk right out of the other
Then we take it back and you cook it
That sounds normal right there's nothing wrong with drinking sheep's milk and
You know that's how normal cheese is made but you cook it you get the curds all together you make a normal block of
Percogno
One of the two who make one of those that sardinians are looking at us like great. He's gonna butcher everything
The word butcher
You take you make a normal wheel of Pekino and you go ah
Monza Monza and they're like not yet not yet
You then take this wheel of Pekino and you cut the top off of it
So you know like cheese gets kind of waxy on the outsides, but we want to expose the gooeyness of the insect
You cut the top off of the wheel you take it off and then the flies show up
You like that perfect you thought it was actually a fly flying around you
They'll land on the cheese and then they start going that's my time to shine
And they start laying eggs and
The way that this cheese is made is the the people eat this
People have eaten this for thousands of years the flies lay eggs on the cheese
The eggs hatch circle of life
maggots come out of them
The maggots then begin eating the cheese they digest the cheese and their little maggot tummies
And then poop out a little bit of that cheese
They sound like that but you can hear them
Then you let this process go on and on and on for two to three months
So it's not just like one maggots pooping on your cheese
This is actual quote from Wikipedia by the time it is ready for consumption
A typical kazoo mart zu will contain
thousands of these maggots
So it's not just one which would be bad
I'm not saying if you're ever eating spaghetti and there's one maggot in your spaghetti
You're like, ah Jason said this is a problem, right?
Disgusting either way so these little maggots they're about they're about eight millimeters long and these little maggots
It's like one-third of an inch. They're super tiny, but you can see them
They're a little white translucent maggots and they just kind of eat through cheese and they make it soft
They make the inside of the cheese super soft. So it is kind of like queso
Sorry if you're eating queso right now. You're looking for maggots
And you go Jason listen, we all know that cheese is just like old milk
It's like curdled milk and stuff like that it you let it turn orange or I didn't look about cheese was made
I'm just
Remembering some of the Sesame Street I saw back in 1979 the cheese is old milk
Like this is just an added part of the digestive process and sure I don't appreciate
Maggots in my food and you say
But you know, it's it's really no grosser than just leaving milk out overnight or again
Whatever Sesame Street said in 1979. Okay, let's get ready to eat some kazoo Marchu
So we each get our own wheel because we're clients
We each get our own wheel and I'm already scooping it in yum yum yum
And you see me I'm put it this is how they traditionally take it they take scoops of it
They spread it across a piece of flatbread and they eat it. So you see me I've been doing that and you notice
When I put a little bit on the flatbread I then kind of cover the top of the flatbread
I'm like holding almost like I'm eating food in jail and don't want anyone else to steal it
Like that's weird. Why does he keep covering his food? Is he afraid like rains gonna fall on his food?
You look up the sky perfectly clear and that's when you're looking down at your own kazoo Marchu and you realize
The maggots are still in the cheese
You are supposed to eat the maggots
That's part of the delicacy the people do this when you eat it you spread it across the flatbread
You'll cover up the top of the flatbread so they don't jump off of you and land in your face
Or maybe you're like I don't want to lose my delicious maggots. You don't want them to jump
You're licking your hand. You're licking your other hand. You're not getting away from me maggots
Yes, this is the end of season 13 the last week is going out with a bang get ready for season 14 soon
Licking the maggots right up your hand. It's actually considered the cheese is considered ruined
It's unhealthy if the maggots are dead in the in the cheese, which that should go just go without saying if there's ever dead maggots in your food
It's unhealthy
but
If let's say you don't like maggots, let's say you're one of those weirdos out there
Let's say you're one of the 2% of the human population who doesn't like to eat maggots
You can't wait for the maggots to die naturally because that's gross
What you can do is you can take you spread some cheese and you put it on a cracker and then you put the cracker in a zip lock bag and
Then oh did I mention these?
These maggots can jump up to six inches. I didn't mention that. That's why you have to protect it
I think I said they could jump I didn't think I said they could jump half a foot
So you spread it on this cheese you put it in the zip lock bag you close it and as the maggots are suffocating
You will see them jump off of the cheese and hit the sides of the zip lock bag
You'll hear it go. I'm not making this up. This was in Wikipedia. They go
There's so many maggots per piece of cheese that you're gonna hear it a couple times and once you're done hearing the pitter-patter noise and the zip lock bag
You're good to go. All the maggots are dead now. You just have to reach into a bag full of maggots
Now you just have to stick your hand into a zip lock bag full of dead maggots to retrieve your price
This is so disgusting and people love it over there. I actually watched it was really cool
I watched two
YouTube clips on it in between me watching hours of unpractical jokers for the past week
I was able to watch two YouTube clips on this one was a Gordon Ramsay show. I guess called the f-word
And where he sends people out he sends people out to eat disgusting food
He he did it at the ending he had and they're like, yeah, it tastes really good. It didn't necessarily
Tasted good. They said that it had a smoky type of spicy taste
And the one guy says the aftertaste stays with you for hours and Gordon Ramsay goes
You gotta told me that before I took a bite
But you can get it. It's it's illegal. It's like black market food
But you can't get it and the reason why it's illegal is because it's unhealthy to eat maggots
Can you believe it? Can you believe what science is trying to tell us these days?
Ah, I hate when politics gets into science
Supposedly the egg heads back at NASA want to try to convince me that eating living maggots is harmful
It actually causes something called myapsis
my isis and
It's where you can get you can get it anywhere in your body. They say normally it's accidental
Sardinia normally it's accidental because of poor living conditions. You'll get maggots in your eyeball
You'll look maggots in your ear. You'll get me eat maggots is the most likely one
You're eating unsafe food and it could take a while like it's not like I'm it's not like you eat a magnet later
The night you're like a Martha Martha. I don't feel so good. What's what's wrong? Well?
Disgusting food we got from Italy and oh it could take six months because the maggot has to like go in there
It hatches in you it starts laying more eggs
It'll get in your intestines these bugs will get in you and I know it sounds like body horror
It sounds disgusting, but it's true. They actually have different types of I should have done it
She's an adventure. I mean I should have done an interactive adventure on this one
They had these different forms of my isis you can get and most of them were just kind of boring or inconvenient
I mean all of them led to your death
They weren't treated, but I thought the creepiest one if you picked any number you get oral
My isis and what that is is that's when you get a maggot in your body that hatches and then begins to spread and lay eggs
And a little flying your butt. This is a hundred percent true oral my asses or oral oral not oral like you know hearing oral
I'm so glad the season's
Oral my asses I need a break you get these in you you can actually you'll be sitting there in your chair
Martha's reading the newspaper and you'll be sitting there
And you're like six months six months after you ate this disgusting food you'll feel crawling in your skin
These wounds they will not heal by the way
Wounds will not heal without medication or a kick-ass Lincoln Park song you feel crawling
Inside your body because they're actually crawling in there. You'll be sitting there watching the prices right one night
Martha did you hear that noise?
Wow, what are you talking about this guy's hitting the buzzer and prices right no not that noise
You'll hear them buzzing in your body that should
In your body
And you'll have a smelly discharge
But I'm telling you if I'm feeling stuff crawling in my skin these wounds they will not heal
Buzzing in my body this time that it's real. I don't care about the smelly discharge
I would be like throwing that at people so if you've ever eaten
Disgusting cheeses you've ever been to Sardinia or if you just happen to be having a conversation with someone in the street
And you accidentally swallow a fly go to the hospital
What if the doctor please and get it checked out you might be totally fine? It's not it doesn't happen every single time
But if you do eat this cheese, there is a small chance. There is a maggot in your intestines
waiting
For its big break to be part of a Lincoln Park song Sam
Let's go ahead and call in that carpenter copter. We're leaving behind Sardinia the children can find their own way home
We give them the keys for the dead rabbit run not let them take care of themselves
They end up in a Lord of the fly situation. I will check in on them later, but take us out of Sardinia
We are headed to New Mexico
Last week we did a promo read for happily actually watch that movie. It's decent. It's decent. It's a good rental
I would definitely check out happily. It's weird like I said it was it was weird
I also had the opportunity to get a sneak peek of another movie the other day
This is the first time I've read a promo read for a movie that I've already seen this movie. This movie is dope
Do you like board games and murder?
Then the dark comedic thriller murder Barry win is for you
critically acclaimed on the festival circuit and winner of best feature at Phoenix fear con
Murder Barry win centers on three aspiring board game designers who have to dispose of a body
With few options available. They turn to their game for guidance the premise of their game
How to murder someone and get away with it
Pre-order now when you'll receive the original deck of cards is featured in the film for free
Details at murder Barry win.com. It's really good. It's really really tense. I laughed out loud in a couple moments
I normally don't like dark comedies. It's good. I really really enjoyed it
I actually want to go more into it in the future
But check out murder Barry win. They're doing pre-orders right now
Check it out. I'll put the trailer in the show notes and I'll put the pre-order thing on the show notes as well
Very very well done movie and patreon supporter and good friend of mine a longtime friend of mine Carson
Worked on this movie. That's how I found out about it and I reached out to them. I said hey
Do you guys want me to help you out with this movie? They sent me a free copy of the movie
This is director Michael lovens first feature length film
So I expect a lot of good stuff from both Michael and Carson in the future really really quality work
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
I
Got it cut out now. Ah this haunted closet is so hot by the way Sam turn around this carbon helicopter
Just hang a left or right whichever direction we're headed in we're headed to El Paso, Texas
Let's get started because I'm gonna warn you right now. It's not the most coherent conspiracy theory
Again another shocker a conspiracy theory. That's not coherent. We are in El Paso, Texas, and we're walking around downtown
We're eating popsicles because it's so hot
And then out of the corner
Dracula jumps out. Oh, you thought it was daytime, didn't you?
No, it was nighttime and then we're scared and samples out of steak and I was like bro
Not yet, and then we hear blah blah blah blah blah blah blah and we turn around and
There is a giant slime
Moving through the city and then
Now that that that that that that that that that that that it's not techno music craft work hasn't entered the scene
We see a giant man-eating plant with hands that have like little
Plant things on them to go and snap snap snap snap snap
And I'm like, oh my god
This might be the end of Dead Rabbit radio
We're surrounded by some of the worst cryptids the worst cryptids Dracula slime and a giant plant and then all of a sudden like a
Power Rangers beam from the sky
And we see three dudes just standing there. They all look at each other and
They go, huh? They take power ranger poses and
They go, don't worry guys. We got this
We're Jewish and then they start karate chop and it's like a freeze frame guys back to karate chop a
Slime Dracula's running in fear the plant is getting ripped in half
Did you know according to the Reddit account anonymous tips X or his username now is deleted?
But he used to be known as anonymous tips X. This is where we are
The very beginning is where it already starts to lose cohesion
either one Jewish people came from outer space all of them or
Not that or not that they simply live in space from time to time
Which would be pretty dope. I'm glad that I'm from earth, but if I could vacation in space, I'd be down to do that
The and the Jewish people they have two missions in life
one
To protect us from gang stalking. Did you know this?
Did you know that every single gang stalker and the entire Western hemisphere at least
So if you're down in Chile, you're being stalked. There's all pockers. We're gonna look at you weird
Oh
Like what or if you're in Alaska and you're fishing your ice fishing and fish you're gonna look at you weird
That fish that alpaca they were both from El Paso, Texas
Every single gang stalker in the Western hemisphere is from El Paso, Texas if you think you are being gang stalked
Look around for some Southwestern art
You see Coco Pelle on a car driving by gang stalker. You see a man in a cowboy hat
You're probably watching
Dynasty or a rodeo or are herding cows right now, but those people are also gang stalkers. So that's good to know, right?
It's good to know now anonymous tips X has actually crafted this map
And it sucks because the images when he deleted the count the images are gone
I'm gonna try to find a way to find them. I thought I had him saved on my computer
I have I might have and if so I'll post it and I'll put it in the show notes
I might actually take me a couple days or maybe someone can use the links. I tried going through internet archive
We'll see what we can do, but let me try to give you a visual here. You're really not missing much
It's basically just really bad Photoshop, but he has a map of America
So we know that the gang stalkers come from El Paso, Texas and the Jewish people are here to protect us from gang stalk
But I also got to let you know a little bit more about the United States
Let's take a geography lesson according to anonymous tips X Oregon is the home of the second horsemen of the apocalypse
Which looks like cloud from Final Fantasy? That's just
That is the most sane one on here. That's what Oregon Oregon is the home of cloud from Final Fantasy
According to this source according to our source
California is currently overrun with white supremacists
who
Also is the bad guy from Resident Evil Nemesis
They're actually you've ever been walking through California. You've seen a white supremacist
maybe
These are the identifying factors
Is he 8 feet tall? Is he 8 feet tall?
Does he have a giant glowing red ball in his chest to show his weak spot is one of his arms an organic blade if
You if you've just seen a bunch of people walking around shouting white power. They're probably not white supremacist
However, if they are a video game character in the shape of a bio weapon leave
Go go away right now and they're all over California governor Gavin Newsom white supremacist
Resident Evil Nemesis boss. You didn't know them Montana is the capital of hell
Texas which is where we're at right now
Texas is guarded so not everyone in Texas is this person Texas is guarded
The whole state is guarded by leather face that makes the most sense out of all of this stuff
Illinois is protected by a German
Named I didn't know this guy was German. I mean I've never really watched these movies, but I don't think they ever went into his ethnicity
I don't think they're ever like oh that character
Illinois is protected by the
Illinois is protected by the famous German Michael Myers from the Halloween series
Like did I really watch those movies, but they're like ah, yes
He's he has a sister and he broke out of insane
And his mother's from Germany. Did they ever is that ever part of the origin story for Michael Myers?
There's another famous germ this guy actually might be German based on his name
But again, I don't think it was implicit in his origin story Ohio is protected by another German named the famous
Freddie Kruger or Frederick Frederick Kruger was probably his original German name
Frederick Kruger best origin story of any horror villain ever. I love his origin story
His mother was assaulted by a thousand maniacs in an asylum and he was born from that act
That's a perfect horror story origin
But again, I don't think and they're like half of those inmates were German like I don't think that's part of his origin story
New jersey not
German new jersey is actually protected by a famous dutch man
A famous dutch character first off who wants to be protected
Who wants to be protected by freddy kruger for new jersey? It's the famous dutch
Guy jason vorhees
Very very famous. I knew he was dutch actually. I remember
I was taking a class in dutch cinema history and they're like the famous dutch character ever was not dutch from predator
It was dutch from it was the dutch man from brand 13. Everyone's all what?
Neither of those characters are actually dutch
Florida is protected by a which if I had to choose to live in any of these states
Any of these states, right? None of those guys are protectors leather face not a protector
Michael Myers freddy frederick kruger jason vorhees not a protector if you live in florida
You're protected by blade dude. Wesley snipes blade. What first off he would wreck
He would easily wreck all of those guys
He might have a problem with freddy kruger because he's the most magical but dude blade versus leather face
It's not even a contest leather face is just a fat dude with a chainsaw. I want to move to florida, dude
I want to move to florida because blades watching over me
Now this is a map of the united states, but canada is included. I know I have a lot of canada listeners
We're not gonna leave you guys out canada
Canada you're protected by a tiny guy with a knife
I didn't recognize the photo
I didn't recognize what it was from. They just show the entire country of canada
There's a little like a gnome with a knife like a little goblin guy with a knife. So eat it canada
We got blade in america. We have blade. It's official ladies and gentlemen. This is just the mind of anonymous tips x
We're really just getting started here because the jewish people are not here to protect us from jason vorhees because luckily
He's the protector if you happen to live in the state of illinois. Don't worry
sleep easy
A mass murderer with a machete is watching over you as you sleep
But see the jewish people are here to protect us from gang stalkers if you ever have problem with gang stalkers
Find someone who's jewish and say hey, dude
I'm pretty sure that alpaca's following me and they'll turn and they'll look and they'll be like
I got you covered
And then you see me you're choking the alpaca out. Uh, let him go quit gang stalking this man. I'll let him go
It says
They're also here to protect us from cryptids and before I go any further I should
Give you this little lifestyle tip before we continue here because I see this in my notes
According to anonymous tips x you should eat three eggs a day. This is a public service announcement in the middle of his ramblings
This is literally where he dropped it as well. You should eat three eggs a day
but
Only three eggs a day. You can't eat any more than three eggs a day
his source for this information
Famous video game you guys may remember this video game moment
Avid video game players are going to be like, oh dude. I remember where I was at when I saw that cutscene
In metal gear solid 4
There's a scene
Where they're frying eggs
There's three eggs in the frying pan
Moving on
Moving on from metal gear solid 4 so we we have we're done with the public service announcement
Let's continue on with the story the jewish people are here to protect us not only from gang stalkers
but they're also here to protect us from cryptids and
Little did you know you thought that you would just be able to go? Hey, you know, I'm jewish
I can I go cry to chop Dracula a bitch upside head. No you idiot. It depends on where you are jewish
Where you are jewish?
Very complicated mythology we have here if you are jewish in algeria
It is super specific jewish people in algeria
They were sent here
to fight giant scorpions
uh jews in kyrgyzstan
They're here to fight the winged tiger
Which
That's pretty dope right like both of those you're fighting giant scorpions
You feel like jason and the argonauts the winged tiger is actually a cryptid that's supposed to exist in the takla moklin desert
That's kind of a more dour existence
You have your bar mitzvah. You're like, oh, this is dope, dude
And then your parents realized sorry son
You gotta go live in the desert for a while. You can't come back until you kill the winged tiger. Oh mom
Jews in venezuela. They're the ones one in our beginning intro story. I didn't make those. I didn't make those cryptids
I don't know where
The jews in venezuela
They are the ones that fight giant man-eating plants
In the jungles of venezuela a giant man-eating plant it's it's so full it can barely move it already ate a bunch of dudes
But out of the jungle
There's a jewish guy hiding me on a tree and he walks up and he just
Crotty chops this plant on the back of the neck doesn't have neck crotty chops him right on the stem
I don't know if the implication is that if you're not jewish
You can't fight these things because I think I could take on a man-eating plant
I left the word giant out. I left the word giant out when I said that
But I think I could do it fighting winged tigers fighting man-eating plants. This is dope jews in norway. What do they get to fight?
They actually this is so bizarre
This is even weirder than that stuff if you're jewish in norway you have to travel to laos
Because apparently there's no cryptid in norway for the jewish people to fight you have to travel to laos and there
You're like all right, dude. I'm not gonna fight like some float and demon head and we're gonna flight some like
suck monster from the swamp
jews in norway hunt pedophiles in laos
Which is noble work. Don't get me wrong
But if you knew
That all your other jewish buddies were crotty chopping giant scarfians
And you were just like arresting some 43 year old dude and be like i'm sorry man. I'm sorry. Don't tell my family
You'd be a little disappointed again. You're doing good work. You're doing good work for the community for the world at large
But your buddy your buddy just beat up a winged tiger
jews in hawaii
They get to fight churufe
Which is a volcano monster
that's
both awesome and that's all that's that
At that point you're like why i've been born in norway
I can see myself fighting. I can see myself fighting a man eating plant. Maybe a giant man eating plant. I can see myself at least
Maybe with the right equipment being able to take on a giant scorpion or a winged tiger
How do you fight a volcano monster?
Like
If he has no organs you can't stab it
You can't really push it anywhere the whole fight is you just like slowly
Ambling away as you're getting closer and closer to the sea
I guess the implication is if you're jewish in hawaii
You have the ability to find a volcano monster. You can't be burned by heat. Maybe i don't know
I'm not jewish. I'm not jewish on hawaii. If you're jewish in hawaii, let me know
Jewish people in singapore was also one of the people who saved us in the beginning of the episode
They fight giant slimes again. That's a very abstract
Creature to fight but they can do it
Jewish people in singapore are able to fight giant slimes. We're back in canada
You have the tiny man with the knife protecting you jews in ontario canada to be specific
They fight giant turtles
So after what the last two groups fought giant slimes, which you know, they're slow moving but again
No noticeable weakness volcano monsters. No noticeable weakness. I was like, oh, that's dope
I can kill the giant turtle
I mean sure it could just like bring its arms and legs and head into the shell and I just kind of waited out
Or i'm just poking it with a little knife
I'm paring a little knife from a little goblin guy. I could fight a giant turtle the jews in ontario canada. They have it pretty good
I found out later on because they're I had to do additional research for this
I found another image he posted when he says giant turtles. He's actually referencing the teenage mutant ninja turtles from the michael bay movie
I'm sorry much. I'd rather fight a giant slime and a volcano monster at the same time than rafael
Screw that so anyways canada is just not a good place to live according to this guy jews and chekelsavakia
I'm gonna give you guys a second
Can you guys guess what the jews and chekelsavakia fight?
I don't know why i'm giving you
I don't know why i'm giving you a second. I can give you an hour. You'll never figure it out the jews and chekelsavakia have one enemy
The face on mars
So, okay, let's bring this do I even have to break this down
Do I even have to say it can't move it can't die
It's just a structure and you have to go there now apparently again
I don't know if the jewish people are hanging out in space every once in a while. They're from space
Super unclear not like everything else is super elusive, but how do you kill the face on mars? They just stand there. They just erode it. They're just going
Blowing on it they're like hey it's your turn you gotta come up and blow on the face
For a hundred years eventually it'll be eroded away
Jews these ones make sense jews and romania they fight dracula
Jews in egypt they fight the mummy just the one not all of the mummies just the famous mummy those make sense
Those make sense
Frankenstein is also a target on this list. Uh jews have to fight frankenstein
But for whatever reason i can't figure this out jews and ethiopia fight frankenstein
I don't even think frankenstein knows why he's in ethiopia. Huh?
What so so
Used to be in european castle
Now where am i just watching all these people walk around he's in the middle of a small town
He's trying to figure out exactly. I got struck by lightning now here
And then there's a jewish guy walking up behind him. What do you use to kill?
He's the frankenstein is the easiest guy to kill. He's just stitched together body parts just give him a good push
I guess fire is what makes him scared
But i mean like a bullet to the brain can kill him and jewish people in india
fight igor
India has a population of about a billion over a billion people. I don't know how many people there are jewish
But it's not none. It's not one. It's probably just probably like a couple thousand ten thousand jewish people in india
Maybe more because the population is so large. They all beat up igor every single one of them shows up
Every single day igor the assistant
The hunched back assistant to dr. Frankenstein
At least frankenstein can like try to hide in the jungle seven foot tall corpse trying to hide in the jungle
igor is just a dude
Getting the crap kicked out of him every single day in india
By at least again, I don't have accurate numbers, but at least 10 000 people
at the very end of this photo presentation that he presented on reddit
It's just a picture of a fart green fart
And I think that's the best way to sum up this whole story
So that is the saga of anonymous tips x and that's really the start of
our
Band from youtube week this story. I've had it for a couple months. I really wanted to cover it. I thought it was so funny
Just this bizarre rambling of this guy
It's from the gangstalking subreddit the gangstalking subreddit has so much potential
It's not as funny as I thought it was gonna be
There was one guy he was talking about his reddit post was gangstalked by x
Kids flying monkeys
Not x kids not like they were abducted by professor xavier. He's gangstalked by his x by his kids
And by flying monkeys. I was like dope dude flying monkeys. Like does this actually think fly does this guy?
That's crippling mental illness actually see flying monkeys. Haha. That'll be hilarious
No, there was no flying monkeys in it
It would have been sucked to be gangstalked by your kids first off
You would find out that your kids were from alpesto texas
They're like, that's weird and then secondly, how would you get away from them? They're just always there. Are we there yet?
Are you there yet? Are you there yet? They're calling you as you're driving to work? Ah
But it's so funny because I wanted to cover this but when I do put stuff out on youtube
It just attracts great people. I've gotten a lot of great listeners a lot of great friendships
But all the weirdos youtube attracts all the weirdos as well think about it this way when you listen to the podcast
It's like a nightclub. You kind of have to know where it's at. Someone shows you
Tells you about it. There you go to the nightclub. But when you put it on youtube is like a city park
Anyone can show up any search term could have someone just stumble across it
This is one of those stories that's real fun to look at and kind of look at this guy's madness
I knew if I put it on youtube
I was just going to get inundated with a bunch of weirdos and a bunch of
Normie tear conspiracy theories about some screenshot. They saw
Regarding Jewish people or I saw watch this six hour documentary and it'll answer all
I just want to talk about fun conspiracy. I first off I've researched all that stuff
I may sound like I'm poo pooing it, but I've researched all those screenshots. I've watched those documentaries
I've done that stuff. I've been doing conspiracy theory stuff for 20 years
Can't we just have fun with these conspiracy theories? So I wanted to say I'm glad I saved this one
I always figured the youtube channel was going to go down at some point and it is back up but I'm debating on
What we're going to do in the future
But this is a this is the type of story that I know that I could share with an audience
And we could have a good laugh at it. So hope you guys enjoyed this story
This is one that I've been sitting on for a long time and really hope I can get the graphics up at some point and share them with you
But the next time someone does say, you know
Jewish people blah blah blah blah blah you should turn to them and say, you know what?
I'm thankful for my Jewish brothers and sisters
If it wasn't for them Igor would rule India
And just walk away just walk away have no response to anything else and
I think we all need to give a little shout out to
To Frederick Kruger. He is truly doing the Lord's work all of those monsters
All of those monsters Frederick Kruger and Michael Myers. I always thought they were evil people
See doesn't this story show that you may think someone is evil, but they're not
Just because they carry a machete or a chainsaw
Or have a huge body counts and have murdered people across multiple movies. They're not evil. They're the real heroes
I think that's the moral of this story one
Don't post everything on youtube two. Don't judge a book by its cover and three if you are ever
ever
Gangstalked
Be prepared to take a trip to El Paso, Texas because if you want this terror to end
You have to go
To where it all began
DeadRabbitRadio.com is going to be your email address. You can also visit us up at facebook.com/DeadRabbitRadio
Twitter is @DeadRabbitRadio
DeadRabbitRadio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast. You don't have to listen to it every day
I'm glad you listened to it today. Have a great week guys
Don't have to listen to it every day. I'm glad you listened to it today. Have a great week guys
You
(upbeat music)
[MUSIC]