An old-timey ghost realizes sometimes the best way to hurt somebody is to hurt their pocketbook.
We say goodbye to a legendary and feared author.
Then we meet a young woman who met her soulmate and couldn't wait to begin a new life with the one
she loves the most. But then an alien appeared and told her, "You can't get married today on Dead
Rabbit Radio."
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host Jason
Garmenter. I'm having a great day. Hope you guys are having a great day too. I hope you guys got a
lot of cool plans for this weekend. We got so much stuff to cover. First off, let's give a
shout out to our Fan Art Friday submission. This one actually we used to use a lot until we went to
the Ash Black logo pretty much across the board and now we're doing the Fan Art Friday. So this
is from John. Long time listeners of the show will remember this artwork used to be all over the place.
So John, thank you so much for... I think on YouTube you'll still see it a lot too, but John,
thank you so much for sending this art in. Really, really appreciate it. And then let's give a shout
out to one of our Legacy Patreon supporters, a longtime listener of the show, our Forrest Finn
correspondent coming into Dead Rabbit Command right now. It's Beatrice Lava. Everyone give a round of
applause to Beatrice. Really, really appreciate your continued support for the show. She's also my
TikTok consultant. I've been trying to do more stuff on TikTok. I'm just limited to the amount of
time. I'm not doing dances. Before you guys all go check out the TikTok channel. It's not me doing
Fortnite dances. I'm trying to take episodes and shrink them down to a minute. And I've been really
good with it because I know that's what you guys love most. You guys want the episodes to get
shorter. I'm taking stories and making them a minute long. Getting really good at it. It's just a
matter of time of putting the pictures together and stuff like that. We're gonna do a lot of TikTok
in the future. And Beatrice has really helped out on that front. So Beatrice, let's go ahead and
toss you the keys to the Dead Rabbit Durgible. We're gonna leave behind Dead Rabbit Command. We
are headed out to North Carolina. Beatrice is expertly flying this vehicle. She's done it before.
We're headed out to Caribus County in North Carolina. Specifically, Old Skin Flint's Mine.
This is actually, I think, the last holdover of... I had that ghost theme week. And then it spilled
over until the week after it. I was just happy I was able to find all these ghost stories.
This one also takes place in North Carolina at a mine. I could have all fit him into one week,
but it was too much haunted mine for a week. This story is really awesome. I just didn't want you
to guys be like, "Oh, me oh, mine." Too many ghost stories. Do you like that? Do you like the Friday
puns? John's like, "Give me my artwork back." We're landing in Caribus County the year 1799.
And that was when a 12-year-old boy found a big rock in the water. There's a bunch of rocks,
but this one was gold and shiny. "Paul, look at what I found. I found this rock." And the dad goes,
"Oh, that's kind of cool. My kid obviously has some weird fetish for rocks, but we'll deal with
that in the future. Right now, why don't we use that rock as a doorstop?" And then one day,
a dude was walking by and he goes, "That's weird. How come this door has stayed open?"
They're like, "Well, if you look down, if you crane your neck down, you'll see there is a door
stop there." And the guy goes, "Ooooh." And he realizes this doorstop is a hunk of gold.
This is when the first gold rush in America started in North Carolina.
You guys are like, "Jason, you should have given us this information last week when you were talking
about all these North Carolina goldmine stories." The problem was that information was in the notes
for this story. It wasn't in the notes for those other stories. So this guy goes, "Tell you what,
I'll give you $3.50 for that doorstop." And the guy's like, "Yeah, sure. That's a lot of money back
then. I mean, that's a lot of money right now." And so he pays it, but then eventually the homeowner
finds out that that rock, that shiny gold colored rock, was actually gold worth $3,500 in old
timey money. So that's like Scrooge McDuck bucks. So eventually he's able to track down the guy.
I think he did get some more money for that doorstep. But a bunch of other people started
coming into the area of the first major gold rush in American history. North Carolina was the leading
producer of gold until 1848 when gold was discovered in California. And people go, "North Carolina,
pew! This place sucks!" But before people realized that North Carolina wasn't where it's at,
you had people from all over the world come to North Carolina to try to strike it rich.
They didn't have a rule, though. No slaves were allowed. No slaves. This is interesting. I didn't
have thought about this because if you thought, think about it. The gold rush was during slavery
times. California wasn't a slave state, but North Carolina wasn't. They had a rule. No slaves were
allowed in the mine because they were afraid that they would hide gold. Can you believe this?
They were afraid that slaves would try to purchase their freedom, try to purchase their freedom and
the freedom of their friends and family by finding gold and then coming back out of the cave and
being like, "I don't work for you anymore. You have a big chunk of gold." They couldn't allow it.
They couldn't allow these people to actually, you know, be people. So no slaves were allowed. So
they had to import labor from around the world and people wanted to come. They wanted to try to
make money. Enter Jonathan McIntosh. He's the owner of the McIntosh mine. 450 foot deep mine.
It seems to be doing pretty well. Lots of gold is coming out of it, but it's not enough for Jonathan
McIntosh because despite him saying, "Oh, we got the best timber in the world. We got the best,
we got the best other stuff that makes a mine function. You want dynamite? Our dynamite is
dynamite." Everyone in the mine knew that Jonathan was a liar. They'd go down there and they'd see
the wood. It wasn't rotting, but he would use very, very new timber. So it wasn't strong enough.
He had seen that dynamite explode and they weren't impressed. It was just like regular dynamite.
They knew that Jonathan was selling them a bill of goods. Like he wasn't actually
putting money into the mine, which you don't go down there to be bedazzled, right? They weren't
worried about the fact that it wasn't the jazziest place to work. They weren't about their own safety.
They could tell he was cutting corners. So people were like, "I don't know." So as the mine got deeper
and deeper, it was harder to find people to go down there. There's a local miner named Joe McGee.
He's an expert. He's been doing this all of his life. The first tunnel he crawled out of was his
mother and he hasn't stopped crawling through tunnels since. And he knows reputation of McIntosh
Mine. It is not safe. But no one else is going deep into the mine. Jonathan calls up Joe and says,
"Hey, listen. I got a deal for you. You go into my super safe mine at the deepest point and start
digging and doing your mine magic and then everyone else will go down to join you because
you're such a cool guy, Joe. You're so cool. Everyone will follow you." And Joe goes, "Listen,
I know the story is your mine is not safe. You cut a bunch of corners, but I will do it. However,
if I die, you have to pay my wife $1,000." Today would be the equivalent of about $30,000. So it's
pretty good life insurance policy. Actually, that's kind of lame for life insurance policy.
Anyways, Joe goes, "If I go down there and I die, you have to pay my wife $1,000." And Jonathan
was kind of shocked. How dare he say his mine isn't safe? What are you talking about? I mean,
I don't go down there myself. I wouldn't let any of my friends and family down there. But
it's totally safe. And in fact, it's so safe. I want you to know if you die, whatever that is,
I'll give your wife $2,000. Joe goes into the mine. A couple days pass. Hey, you don't remember
that guy, Joe? We used to kick it with all the time. He was a really good miner and all that stuff.
Yeah, yeah. Have you seen him lately? Uh-uh, no, I thought he was hanging out with you. No,
I wish he was pretty cool. A couple weeks go by. Hey, dude, what are you doing, man? Oh,
sorry, I thought you were Joe. I thought you were super cool. I don't really care about you.
But speaking of Joe, have you seen him? No, dude, no one's seen Joe for weeks. Not even his wife.
Joe must have left. That's the only thing when you think of, I mean, we do know that he's working
in a super dangerous industry, but maybe he just left and left his wife. Oh, okay. Now,
nobody knew about this arrangement, this life insurance arrangement, except for Joe's wife.
And Joe's wife went to Jonathan McIntosh and said, "Hey, you know, pretty sure my husband's dead.
He's not going to run away. He was in your mind and he told me that he told you. He could only do
it, you know, the thousand, you know, rewind the podcast a little bit, remember that part?"
And Jonathan goes, "Oh, I did say that, but he didn't die. Nobody's found his body
and he probably just left you. You're kind of busted. You're kind of busted and he left you,
so I don't have to give you any money. It was if he died, I gave you the money,
not if he like cheated on you or something like that. Slams the door in her face.
One night, a minor who was also a good friend of Joe, here's a knock on his door.
And standing there is Joe McGee's ghost. He thought it was just Joe McGee. He thought he just
really cheated on his wife. No, it was his ghost and he's floating there. He doesn't say if he has
Casper legs. Doesn't say if he's eating a bunch of hot dogs like Slimer, but he is. He's inventing
the hot dogs so he can eat them. He's floating there and he tells his friend, "Hey, dude, you won't
believe what happened to me." The friend's like, "Let me guess, you died?" Yes. What was the giveaway?
The fact that I have Casper legs? Why do I keep saying Casper legs? Casper actually had legs,
but you know what I mean? Like a little wavy ghost body. He's like, "Listen, forget that anachronism.
Forget what's going on with that host." I died in the mine, dude. I went down there and that
jerk Jonathan had fresh timbers, like the freshest. Like these were amoeba trees down there and they
collapsed. I was killed in the mine. Joe says, "Listen, I'm gonna tell you where my body's at in the
mine so maybe you can give me a proper burial. I mean, I am buried. I am buried by tons of rock,
but you know, bury me in the soil where it's a little nicer." And, "Hey, do you know? I don't know
if I told you about this. I probably should have told more people about this, but I arranged for
a life insurance policy. Did my wife ever get any money?" And the friend goes, "No." He didn't. The
ghost is like, "Ahh, Dagnabbit." Then he just turns and he slowly floats away. It's interesting that
he didn't go visit his wife, right? It's interesting that he goes and visits his friend and asks him
all this stuff. He could have went to his wife first or last even. I mean, like, "Hey, honey, I'm not
home. I'm just the ghost. But hey, did you get that money? Also, I love you." Like, he never visits
his wife, but he does visit this dude. But before he floats away, he turns back around because I
forgot to see until I read a little bit more of my notes. He turns around, he goes, "And
I cursed the Macintosh mind forever, forever, forever, forever." And then he gets tired of saying that. He
says it for like 30, 40 minutes. Then he turns around and floats away. Jonathan's minor friend gets
some other minors together. They confront Macintosh. They go to his house and this basically formed a
lynch mob and they want to know what's going on. Jonathan admits to this. He says, "Yes, okay. Oh,
you got me. You got me my bad. I sent this expert minor down in the mineshaft and yeah,
sure, the timber might have been a little new." And he died and I realized that he died pretty
early on. So I did the noble thing. I just told everyone he was a cheater and he left his wife.
And he is forced to give the wife this $2,000. And the minors were able to go down and locate
Joe's body and give it a proper burial. Into the story, right? Not as far as Joe's concerned.
Because what happens is minors are still working in that mine. They're like, "Yeah,
the guy did. The owner of this mine did murder someone and tried to rip off his widow. But,
you know, works, work." As they're working in this mine, they would see Joe's ghost floating through
the darkness. He's like putting gold back in the mountain. They're like, "Joe, come on, man."
You know how long that took? He's like phasing it through the mountain. He's
like, "Oh, man."
you