When a man is confronted by aliens from another world, they order him to do the unthinkable.
And then we travel to the United Kingdom to meet a couple of friends who are out smoking
a little bit of weed and enjoying some fresh night air.
Little did they know their lives would forever change when the phone rang today on Dead Rabbit
Radio.
Hey everyone welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Sesa Garmin and I'm having a great day.
I hope you guys are having a great day too.
I hope you guys are having tons of fun doing whatever you're doing.
Let's go ahead and get this episode started.
Let's go ahead and introduce one of our Christmas livestream contributors coming into Dead Rabbit
Command right now.
Everyone give it up for Jonathan Bellach.
Woohoo!
Yeah come on in.
Come on in buddy.
He's shaped like a big old bell walking in ding dong.
Jonathan you're going to be our captain, our pilot this episode.
If you can't support the Patreon, if you can't support the show financially, I totally understand.
Just help spread the word about the show that really, really helps out a lot.
Now Jonathan let's go ahead and toss you the keys of the Jason Jalob.
We're leaving behind Dead Rabbit Command.
We're going to drive all the way out to Mexico.
Jonathan's driving us on out.
There we got the AC on full blast.
We're just kicking back and enjoying the ride.
Specifically we're headed down to La Palma O'Oxka.
La Palma O'Oxka.
People right now are looking at maps.
They're like that's not how you're granted.
Well luckily we're not going into that town.
We're going near it.
It's December 1st, 1979.
We're near La Palma Oxka and a man is stumbling out of the darkness.
He's just covered in blood.
People are coming out of their homes because he's like freaking out right.
He's wailing in pain and fear.
People are like oh man that sounds like terrible.
Let's look out our window.
See what's going on.
The suit's covered in blood and he's freaking out.
And they noted like that would be alarming enough right.
If you heard someone wailing in pain and he looked out your window and he saw a man walking
through the darkness covered in blood that would already be bad enough.
But it doesn't take long for the townspeople to realize that most of the blood is a little
bit on his shirt, a little bit on his arms.
But most of his blood is below his waist.
So that should give you an idea of where the story's going.
Let's travel back in time to just the day previous.
It's 5pm November 30th, 1979.
There's this worker.
We don't have his name.
We don't have the name of this unfortunate soul but we'll go ahead and call him Jerry.
Jerry's working at a local palm grove.
And he's using his machete to cut down weeds.
Shop, shop, shop, shop.
And the weeds are just falling everywhere and then he just keeps chopping.
He's like, I'm doing a good job.
I'm a big boy.
Chop, chop, chop, chop.
Chopping them up.
And then all of a sudden these eight tall men just kind of walk up on him.
Now I'm going to tell you that I found this story on ThinkAboutToDarkStone.com.
That's not the whole story.
You were like, Jason, wow.
You're really hurting for material.
Oh, that's my, oh my God.
Anyways, that's not an EVP.
That's just someone who doesn't own a muffler.
This guy's, oh, where is, oh yeah, I found this on ThinkAboutToDarkStone.com.
They got it from Robert E. Bartholomew who wrote a book called UFO Lore.
I actually couldn't find any proof of that book existing.
I found a bunch of other books written by Robert E. Bartholomew.
We'll talk about him in a second.
He's very famous in the study of UFOs and mass hallucinations and ghosts.
He's been consulted a lot about the Havana syndrome thing.
We'll talk about that in a second though.
He is an expert in the field of parapsychology though.
But I couldn't find a book called UFO Lore.
But so remember that.
I want you to remember that this comes from UFOology, the way I'm going to tell you the
story.
These eight tall dudes walk up to Jerry and they were described as having dark skin, not
dark green skin, not dark skin with scales.
They were just darker skinned people than Jerry.
They were wearing green goggles.
I don't know if those are normal, right?
And they had communication devices.
So that could either be a little badge from Star Trek or Wokitalki.
And they were all brandishing a style of weapon that Jerry described as a machine gun.
In quotes he described them as "machine guns."
So I'm having a hard time figuring out if this, I believe the story's probably real.
But I don't know if he was confronted by eight unusually tall, unusually dark, unusually
green-goggled aliens who had futuristic weapons shaped like Earth machine guns and communicators.
I mean, that's so vague.
But he believes that they were aliens.
He believes that he was confronted by these aliens, right?
And these aliens are speaking Spanish.
These aliens are speaking the language that is of that area, right?
And these aliens/men with machine guns, they order Jerry to cut off his own penis.
And he does.
Chops it right off.
And then wanders around the darkness for hours on end until finally he walks up to La Palma
Oxyca and he's moaning and wailing and he's holding his crotch probably in one hand.
In the other hand, I wonder if they let him pick up his penis.
I wonder if he was allowed to carry it.
Oh, my hands getting tired.
I've been carrying this all night long.
You put it in your pocket at a certain point, right?
But I don't know, we don't have a lot of follow-up to this.
Whole bunch of questions to this story, right?
Because definitely when I saw this, that is the whole story now we can start dissecting
it, no pun intended.
He drops his penis off.
These aliens showed up and they made him drop his penis off.
What's interesting about this story is one, we've never come across a story like if this
is UFO related.
Because it was in a book, it was in a book that doesn't exist called UFO Lord by Robert
Bartholomew.
Bartholomew who again is a very famous name in parapsychology and mass hallucination.
He's the guy, he's done a lot of speeches.
He wrote a book about the Havana syndrome.
That was where the ambassador, US ambassador staff in Havana, Cuba started to get sick
and you saw headlines all over the world about a sonic live and there was being used against
our ambassadors and he just chalked it up to mass hallucination.
Maybe it was, I'm paraphrasing, right?
I didn't read his book book.
He goes, "If this same sickness had overcome a bunch of steel workers in the middle of
Idaho, we never would have thought it was any sort of weapon."
He's written a lot about mass hallucinations.
He's written a lot about ghosts and UFOs.
He has all these books out.
It seems to be more of a skeptic.
I don't know what book they're referring to.
There is no book called UFO Lord but I always like to use the term Lord.
I can't think of another time that an alien forced a human to mutilate themselves or another
person.
That would actually be kind of interesting.
I mean, I wouldn't want it to happen to me but like for her.
I don't know.
You see that in horror movies and stuff like that where like the alien goes, the alien's
basically jigsaw.
He came all the way from across the galaxy to be like, "You think you can cut down the
palm trees?
But what do you hold in your palm most of the time?"
Tip-top, Jerry.
That's never happened, right?
That's never happened.
I can't think of another time where an alien forced someone to mutilate themselves.
Now it could be that the reason why.
Maybe that's how cows are getting mutilated.
The aliens are coming down.
They're like, "You got to drain all your own blood."
The cows are like, "What?
How is that even possible?"
They're just thinking really hard.
Their eyeballs pop out and then all their blood disappears.
I've never came across anything like that in the lore.
I think it's most reasonable to think that this guy was doing his job and just some dudes
showed up on machine guns and they're like, "Yo, chop your dick off."
And he's like, "Huh?"
Even that's pretty weird, right?
I know humans are sick.
I could see that happening, but you'd be like, "What?
Fine.
I guess if you have a machine gun to your head, you might do it."
It's weird because was he implying that they telepathically made him chop off his own penis?
Or what?
And then what did they do afterwards?
He chopped his penis off and then he ran away screaming and they're like, "Okay, now
what do we do?
It's fun for about five minutes, but do we do it again?
Do we go out of the town and get drinks?
Who knows?"
So bizarre story.
Absolutely bizarre story.
Did aliens come down and make a guy chop his penis off?
Was it aliens?
Was it a group of people, just normal humans with goggles, making people chop their dicks
off?
And if so, are they still out there?
They're right behind you right now.
You're like, "Huh?"
You turn around and you only see seven tall dudes.
You're like, "Whoa, that was close."
And then you turn back around and the eighth one's chopping your dick off.
What if this is?
What if this does happen more often?
Right?
We don't hear about it because the people, then the aliens are like, "Ah, yes, good
start.
You've chopped off your genitals.
Now chop off one of your arms."
And he chops it off.
He's like, "Oh, can I stop now?"
And the aliens are like, "Hmm, let me see.
I don't like the way your liver is looking at me."
You're like, "Ah, chopping your liver out."
Jonathan, fly us out of Mexico.
We are headed all the way out to the United Kingdom.
Jonathan, we're in the United Kingdom.
The year is 2009 and it's nighttime.
We're going to meet a young man named Keith.
He's 17 years old and he's hanging out with his friends in the United Kingdom.
He tells us this.
Now, Keith isn't his real name.
He doesn't use real names.
Well, we're going to meet three friends.
Keith, Randall, and Michael.
Those are the names that I'm going to give them.
And they're out smoking some weed in this deserted field.
It's kind of like right next to a tennis court.
So you're sitting there, you're smoking weed and just enjoying the beautiful night air
of Britain.
And all of a sudden Randall gets a phone call.
He gets his phone.
Hello?
Keith said right when Randall answered the phone, he started flipping out.
He just began screaming as loud as he could into the phone.
Now Randall was sitting down.
They're all kind of sitting down while they're smoking.
And Randall flops his body backwards and begins just screaming into the phone.
And Keith and Michael are completely taken aback by this.
Keith goes, "I've never heard someone scream like that before."
Ever.
It was this loud, piercing scream and he was just spouting off gibberish.
They couldn't make any sense of what he was saying.
And at the same time, he was writhing around on the ground.
His entire body is just contorted and twisting and he's rolling around on the ground and
he's just screaming.
Keith put it like this, quote, "I can't even really describe how bad this was.
The noises he was making were disgusting.
I can't even try to explain it."
Keith says even thinking about it, he wrote this post anonymously, but he goes, "Even
thinking about it now, all these years later, it makes me physically ill to remember the
noises Randall was making as he was rolling around on the ground just screaming."
And then his eyes started to bug out and he begins to laugh.
He begins to laugh so loud that the cacophony of laughter is now replaced to screaming and
his eyes just seem to be protruding from his head and then all of a sudden Randall completely
stops making noise.
He's not screaming, he's not laughing, and in a very comb manner he takes his phone,
puts it into his pocket, gets up, walks over to the tennis court fence and starts climbing
it.
Once he gets to the top of this 10 foot fence, he jumps off head first into the ground, breaks
his neck, and dies.
They obviously called the police, right?
They obviously needed to get some sort of assistance for him, but when the police show
up, he's already dead.
Died on impact.
The police show up and the ambulance shows up, takes the body, takes it away, and Keith
and Michael are just dumbfounded and they're telling the cops what happened.
And the police just completely write it off as a stoner kid having an accident.
"No, no, I mean, like, yeah, we were all stoned and stuff, like everybody got this phone call
and like you went crazy and you mean like how sometimes people can have bad reactions
to weed?"
"Well, yeah, yeah, yeah, but it was more than that."
Like he was screaming and then he started laughing.
"Well, you mean the way that people laugh when they're like, "Yeah, yeah, obviously,
but it was more than that."
Like, I don't know what happened, but he, like, it wasn't just an accident.
Something happened.
But the police just completely filed it as dumbstoner kid does dumbstoner thing.
So there was no real investigation into this and what would you investigate, right?
The phone?
You're going to have the cops start doing a search for Samara?
Getting search warrants for all the local VCRs?
I mean, like, what are you going to do?
Now, after this happened, Randall's family moved away pretty soon afterwards.
And Keith and Michael, it really messed him up.
He said Michael started doing ketamine.
He started self-medicating and he's not the same person he used to be.
He pretty much rotted his brain out with drugs.
Keith goes, "I started taking Selexa.
I started taking an SSRI drug."
Okay, it just wasn't really working for him apparently.
He did stop it.
He says, "Most of the time I try not to think about it, but ever since that day when I get
a phone call and it shows a no, a number or block number, I never answer it."
It's a fascinating story.
And if you think about it, let's say that this phone call went out to 10 people at the
same time.
Let's say that he wasn't targeted or 100 people or 1,000 people across the world and
50 of them answered it.
50 of them go, "Hmm."
And out of those 50 people who actually took the call, let's say all 50 of them killed
themselves, how many people would just be racked up as a suicide number, right?
And you could have people be like, "No, that guy would never kill himself."
And the officer goes, "Listen, all we know is that your boyfriend jumped off a 10-story
balcony."
So, I mean, you can say all day long that he didn't kill himself, but there was evidence
of no one else in this room and your boyfriend's at the bottom.
I don't know why the cops are being so rude to this girl, but you know what I mean?
Even if it was somebody who you'd be like, "Dude, I can't believe that guy would ever
kill himself," that would be the only thing you could realize.
Oh, an accident, right?
Someone getting the phone call and laughing hysterically and then walking into the bathtub
and spilling water all over the ground and then slipping around.
You know what I mean?
It would be creepy and it would be effective, right?
And I gotta wrap this up soon because I could just go on and on about this, but there's
that idea that you can hack the human brain.
There's actually been a lot of talk about this recently.
You can hack the human brain.
We think of it as we have our thought patterns.
We have our soul.
We have these ideas that we march forward, but it's electrical impulses that are carrying
all that stuff back and forth.
What if you could disrupt the way that the brainwaves were working, not magically, but
there was some sort of code, despair code type of thing that actually makes the brain
go loopy and makes you kill yourself?
And again, most of these deaths would just be chalked up to suicides or accidents.
There was two witnesses to this one and the police totally didn't investigate it.
And if those kids hadn't, or if Keith himself hadn't posted this online, then we never would
have heard of it either.
So how many other people suffered from that phone call that night or since?
Are these phone calls still going out there?
Is someone still auto-dialing numbers?
And when you pick up, you go mad.
It's a terrifying idea because we all have to communicate with each other.
And if there is a disease that is spread as a meme, as a communication, as a form of media,
the chances of you getting it are, I mean, it's incredibly high.
Whether or not you have, if you have a cell phone, you'd be incredibly susceptible to this,
but some people don't have cell phones.
Well, you have a home phone.
Some people don't have home phones.
Well, you know, okay, Amish man, you'll get a letter in the mail.
Like how do you avoid a curse or a disease that's spread via media?
Because we know how to protect ourselves from airborne diseases.
We know how to protect ourselves from, you know, skin-borne diseases and monkeypox.
Geez, that's terrifying.
You got monkeypox running around, but I know how not to get monkeypox.
But imagine if there was something out there that was spread via media.
That's always been a trope in the paranormal horror community that there is.
I've done episodes that I thought were cursed.
I still released them.
You can't avoid communication.
You'd have to be a monk in a cave to avoid this signal.
Now obviously, you're not having these mass die-offs because of these phone calls, but
it didn't matter for Randall and his family and for Keith and Michael who saw this and
went to some serious mental trauma themselves.
The only thing Randall did wrong that day was pick up his phone.
And that was enough to kill him.
The police report may say dumb stoner kid does dumb stoner things.
But to Keith and Michael, they know the truth.
That a insanity-fueled death is just a phone call away.
Dead Rabbit Radio at gmail.com is going to be our email address.
You can also go to stepinfacebook.com/DeadRabbitRadio.
Tiktok is @DeadRabbitRadio.
Dead Rabbit Radio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true prime podcast.
You don't have to listen to it every day, but I'm glad you listened to it today.
Have a great week guys.
Bye.
(upbeat music)