A woman who loves horror movies so much, she decided to star in one.
Are you smart enough to avoid stranger danger?
And then we meet a man who claims if you can find an episode of Good Morning America that
aired in the year 2017, you could overthrow the reptilians who currently rule the world
today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Carpenter.
I'm having a great day.
I hope you guys are having a great day too.
I hope you guys are having lots of fun and I mean that all the time.
I really do hope you guys are doing awesome.
First off, coming into Dead Rabbit Command is someone that I know is awesome.
Walking in, one of our newest Patreon supporters, give it up for Chris Padmos.
Everyone give a round of applause to Chris Padmos, a little bow, a little curtsy if you
have a skirt on.
Chris, you're going to be our captain or pilot of this episode.
If you guys can't support the Patreon, I totally get it.
Just help spread the word about the show.
Really, really helps out a lot.
Chris, are you ready to do this?
Chris, I'm going to go ahead and toss you the keys to the Jason Jalopy.
We are leaving behind Dead Rabbit Command.
We are headed all the way out to Sydney, Australia.
The reason why we're in Australia, specifically going to St. Clair, that's in Sydney, Australia,
is 2019.
And then we're going to meet a woman.
Her name's Rita Calamari.
She's 57 years old and life is going okay, but she has a bit of a problem with her adult
daughter, Jessica.
Jessica's 25 years old and she is obsessed with horror movies.
Man, I do love myself a good horror movie.
Love horror movies.
But there's a difference between like, I will go out of my way to watch a horror movie.
I will.
But I've never done this.
I've never done this and this is what I find so interesting because I'm obsessed with horror
movies so there is a bit of a bond between me and Jessica, but she takes it a little
too far.
One, she's obsessed with horror movies.
Specifically she watches the Texas Chancell massacre movies over and over again.
And that's a mixed bag.
There's some really good ones.
A new beginning.
It was fantastic.
Now, what she, and she watches the Jeepers Creepers movies over and over again.
Those were less good and they were made by Known Pedophile, which makes them unwatchable
in my book.
And so, Jessica is watching these horror movies.
I love horror movies.
She loves horror movies.
But she is threatening to murder her family.
I mean, I did that once on that one Thanksgiving.
She is constantly threatening to kill her family members and that was alarming.
But then, they weren't reporting her to the cops because she's just like, why I ought
to?
She's like holding a butcher knife and stripping with chicken blood.
They're like, "Ah, she was threatening to kill the family but the family wasn't calling
the cops."
She then started calling random people.
She would just pick up the phone, dial a random number and when someone picked up, she would
threaten to cut their heads off.
So that's alarming.
That's the last thing you expect.
And your phone reachers are like, "Oh, I hope this isn't some salesman.
I hope this isn't someone who's going to take up a bunch of my time trying to get me to
change my cable provider."
And it's some woman saying, "I know where you live.
I'm going to chop your head off."
You're like, "Ah, she did that 100 times a day constantly."
So those people are calling the cops.
I don't think it was the same person over and over again because she was dialing the
number randomly.
But I'm sure she got.
She's doing this 100 times a day.
I'm sure she at least a couple times got the same person.
They're like, "Ah, now this is not a job again.
Trying to watch Jeopardy."
So the cops are now like, "You can't do this, right?
You can't do this."
But they're aware that she has some mental issues.
I don't really think you can lock people up for that.
Well, I guess it is threatening people, but they knew that she had some issues.
You know, what are you going to do?
The police are a little worried about it.
The family is worried about it.
But the mom, Rita, is like, "I can take care of this.
I can take care of this."
So she goes to where you would go, right?
When you need professional help, your child has some mental issues.
But they're watching Jeepers Creepers over and over again.
She contacts a medium.
She contacts a she-wolf medium, a she-wolf half-linked spirit who can communicate with
the dead.
She says, "Your daughter is possessed by a demon.
And for $3,600, I can exercise the demon out of your daughter."
And Rita goes, "Well, you know, that's a lot of money.
But why don't I make it stabbed in the back anytime, anywhere?"
So she pays like half up front.
Half up front, the other half, when I see a demon leave my daughter's body.
And the she-wolf medium gets the money and then shocker, right?
The most unbelievable part of the story, it was a fraud.
She didn't do any...
Can you believe that?
I know, I'm shocked.
The paranormal community, we're all aghast that there's one person who's a fraud in this
entire community, ripped her off $1,800, did nothing.
July 20th, 2019 is when this all comes to a head.
The police are called to this house.
They've been to this residence before.
They know it's gonna have something to do with Jessica.
And as their police cruisers are driving out the road, do, do, do, do, do, they see their
red and blue lights illuminating the front yard of Jessica's house?
And they see her running around the yard.
They're like, "Great, it's a 101.
Jessica, Jessica is running counterclockwise in the yard, over."
And they get out of their patrol cars and they're walking up and they see Jessica running
around and then they see her.
She's holding Rita's decapitated head.
When the police are walking up to her, she then shot puts her mom's head through the
air and it lands in her neighbor's yard and kind of rolls for a bit.
And then she just sits there and points to the head, standing there silently pointing
at the head.
When the police went into the house, they found the rest of Rita.
She had been stabbed 85 times.
And at one point, the knife broke and Jessica got up and got another knife and continued
to stab her mom again.
They found that happened a couple of times.
There were a few broken knife blades in Rita's body and she kept getting new knives so she
can continue stabbing her mom.
What finally prompted her to go insane and kill her mom?
Well, she was insane before that.
But what prompted her to just completely lose it at that time?
Everything else that had gone on, why did she finally snap and kill her mother?
Because her mother realized something that day.
Jessica is dangerous.
I have to take her to a mental hospital.
And when she told her daughter that they should go to the hospital to take care of her, her
daughter murdered her.
When she finally realized how dangerous Jessica was, it literally was too late.
Terrifying story coming out of Australia.
And again, it's one of those stories that's, it's one of the easiest stories to happen,
right?
Somebody loses track of reality and snaps.
And she obviously had this long descent.
Sometimes it can be someone doing too many drugs.
Sometimes it can be someone who has a history of mental illness or someone.
The scariest ones are the people who have no struggles at all and just snap.
Because if it can happen to them, it can happen to the rest of us, right?
So just a terrifying story about a mother and a daughter, the mother hoping till the
end that she could save her daughter, but the daughter had other plans.
Creepy, creepy story.
She actually was found guilty of manslaughter and she'll be sentenced.
I wonder if she's been sentenced yet?
I have this story ready to go for a while.
Let's take a look.
Yeah, I typed this story up a while ago and I'd been waiting, kind of putting it off,
but I liked it.
21 years.
She got a 21 year sentence.
It's interesting when you look, I forgot about her horribly distended face.
I'll have to put a picture.
She looks like a muppet from the dark crystal.
And it's not her fault, right?
But she looks like HR Puffinstaff's niece.
And I find that odd because her face almost looks inhuman.
Right now, there's someone listening to this podcast and they're like, "Jason, it clearly
looks like me."
No, there's some, you can even have someone who looks similar to her.
I'm putting the picture up.
I'm going to put the picture up.
You can obviously have someone that just popped up out of nowhere if you're watching the YouTube
channel.
People, I mean, that looks photoshopped.
That looks photoshopped.
It doesn't look human.
The reason why I'm bringing that up isn't because I'm like, "Ew, gross, she's ugly."
Because I'm not necessarily saying she's ugly.
She just doesn't look like a person who belongs to the human race.
But I'm wondering, like, if it's like demonic possession.
You see what I mean?
Is there a demon captured in this photo?
Because there's other photos.
She doesn't look that terrible.
It's, um, yeah, creepy.
Is that another picture of her?
Yeah, she's just kind of weird looking.
Again, sorry if you've already written your Jessica Calamari/fiction with you and her,
but yeah, she looks weird.
Anyways, Chris, I'm going to go ahead and toss you the oars to the Dead Rabbit Robo.
We're leaving behind St. Clair, Sydney, Australia.
We're going to row all the way out to Roseville, California.
Splash!
Row in our way over there, Chris, the courageous captain, making sure we safely get across
the high seas.
This story takes place around 2001 in the affluent suburb of Roseville, California.
It's up in Northern California.
You have to live in around that area.
I never live in Roseville.
It's a bunch of preppies, but I live in Citrus Heights and North Islands and Orangeville
and all that stuff.
But anyways, I've done a ton of episodes on that.
The entire town is cursed and haunted.
This story, Roseville, California, around the year 2001, there's a five-year-old kid walking
down the street and then all of a sudden, a van pulls up next to the child.
The window rolls down.
When a young man sticks his hat out of the window and goes, "Hey, would you like some
candy?"
"I got candy in my van.
Would you like to get in the van?"
And the kid goes, "Candy?
Sure!
That sounds fantastic!"
And then their memory goes blank.
This was posted online by someone known as SpecificPurpose7419.
And they were saying, "I have this clear memory of a van pulling up when I was about five years
old candy in the van.
Typical stranger danger thing and I got in the van and I don't remember anything that
happened after that.
But my family does.
So what happened was at some point I brought up this memory.
Hey, because I remember a stranger pulling over and getting me in the van and my dad goes,
"Oh dude, you remember that?
Oh, that was so long ago."
And this guy will call him Steven if that's Israeli and he's just got Steven.
"Well, what do you mean?
You remember me getting kidnapped?"
And then I forgot.
Dad goes, "No, no, no, that's not what happened.
You weren't kidnapped."
You see, what happened was you and your siblings were a bunch of dummies and you were the most
gollible of all.
And me and your mom were afraid that you were going to get kidnapped.
So we wanted to scare you straight.
So we got a friend, a family friend that you didn't know and we had him pull up in the
van and say, "Would you like some candy?"
And you got in the van.
And then it was all just a stage thing.
It never happened.
It wasn't a real kidnapping.
It was fake kidnapping.
And Steven's thought about this answer for years and it doesn't make sense to him.
He explains, "If my dad is telling the truth, why do I only remember the beginning?"
I'm sure I'm five and a little kid, but why wouldn't I?
And at that point, I don't feel like I'm in trouble.
I'm getting candy.
You figure the most traumatizing part would be the back of the van opening up and my
dad and my mom saying and they're yelling at me because I was dumb enough to get in
a car if someone I didn't know.
Why do I only remember the first part and not the second part?
It's written in a way that I think Steven is intimating that they don't really believe
the father's version of events.
And I, at least that's the read I get from it.
Because the, you're thinking, I really got kidnapped and I completely blinked it out
of my mind because I was a kid and my parents, when they got me back, they just said, "We're
never going to talk about this."
Law enforcement could have even said, "Listen, the kid's young enough.
They may not remember this.
Let's not talk about it."
But I guess the police, they're like, "What about a trial?"
And the cop's like, "Shhh."
No.
No, we don't want a trial.
We don't want a trial.
I guess that doesn't wash, but the parents could have said, "You know what?
We're just not going to talk about it."
It really happened, but we're not going to talk about it if he ever asked us to pretend
it didn't happen.
Because people do go through traumatic stuff as kids and don't remember it.
Or they've blanked it out in some way.
I mean, on the one hand, if your kid gets kidnapped, you don't want them to forget the
experience so they don't get kidnapped again.
But on the other hand, you don't want to put a giant poster of the kidnapper on the kid's
bedroom ceiling.
And I'm still out there, his voice boxes.
You get him to record all of his best kidnapping sayings.
Boo!
I'm right behind you.
They put all these voice boxes all over the house.
Kids are like, "Oh, there's a gray area between those two."
Never acknowledging that it happened.
And then continuing the kidnapper's work while he's in prison.
There's a huge gray area there.
But I find, and so a bunch of people responded to this and they said, "Actually, there was
a big wave of fake stranger danger stuff, dateline NBCs, dunce, things like that, Oprah
did things like that."
Other people said, "That happened to me."
It's not unusual.
I could see parents doing that.
I think it would be a funny, practical joke.
You're like, "Take them out, sight city limits.
Let's see how long we can get this."
They're on radio.
You're like, "Just keep on driving.
I want to see how long I can terrify my child."
There's two ways to read this.
One, this kid's dad was hilarious, right?
This kid's dad not only was hilarious enough to get started in the first place, but then
laugh about it years later when the kids all traumatized me like, "Uh, I have this weird
memory I can't make out."
I think it was kidnapped and then the dad laughing at him.
Or, something super traumatizing happened to him and the entire family's decided to
cover it up.
That's creepy because there's family secrets where the family's like all together and they're
like, "Thicker thin will never say where the gold is buried."
Then, there's the thicker thin will never tell Steven where the gold is buried.
You're a member of the family and if you're being boxed out from that, there's a family
secret about you that you don't know of.
That's some like, V.C. Andrews type stuff.
So a creepy, creepy story.
It's either very funny or the family's keeping a horrific event from them.
I guess the question is, if that happened to you when you were super young, you get kidnapped
and horrible stuff happens, would you want to know?
Or would you not want to know?
Yeah, it would be interesting.
They go, "No, it's so traumatizing.
If we started telling you about it, you're going to have all these horrible nightmares
and stuff like that."
A true mystery to us, a curious tale.
But to this person, it's the most important conspiracy they may ever have to unravel.
Very, very interesting story.
Chris, I'm going to go ahead and toss you the keys to the Carpentercopter.
We are leaving behind Roseville, California.
You're headed all the way out to Hollywood.
[imitates carpenter]
Yesterday we did an episode about whether or not the show, the secret of Skinwalker Ranch,
is cursed by simply watching the show or knowing someone watching the show, could you go insane?
Interesting.
I really like that episode.
But what if television couldn't be used to just spread a spell?
What if it could be used to actually overcome the evil that infests this world?
Well, that's what we're going to be talking about today.
We're going to be talking about someone who actually believes they have discovered the
key to destroying the reptilian control of this planet.
The reason why we're at Hollywood is we're about to watch a taping of the Jimmy Kimmel
show and the audience is like, "Yeah, woo, Jimmy Kimmel.
Yay!"
And some guys I call, I thought this was the Jimmy Fallon show.
Half the audience gets up and leaves.
So there's a lot of space for us to spread out, right?
We're sitting here.
And a couple of us are still clapping.
Jimmy Kimmel comes out on stage and he's like, "Hey, everyone, welcome back to the Jimmy
Killin' Kimmel Show or whatever it's called.
I don't know if it's like late night with Jimmy or whatever."
He's doing all that stuff.
And in the back of the theater, we see a man.
He's kind of like, has a hat on and a trench coat.
We're like, "That looks super suspicious."
He's kind of like, his eyes are shifty.
And that man, I guess I'm even super-ail intent about saying that he's going to show up with
the Jimmy Kimmel Show and do anything crazy, but that man is actually trying to expose
the reptilian agenda.
So there's a series of posts online about, there's a lost episode of Good Morning America.
This was the episode that aired on April 22nd, 2017.
And this was written by a user known as JB Stout 7.
He was watching Good Morning America on April 22nd, 2017.
And so I'm going to let his words paint this picture for us.
He's watching it with his mom.
Both of them were watching Good Morning America.
"I remember watching the episodes that day.
It was very, very odd.
And I did see the weird beans.
That meme is pronouncing the word like human beans.
He didn't see a bunch of pinto beans walking back.
And I did see the weird beans walking around in the background.
The clips of lizards.
Them talking about trying to figure out what was going on.
I remember Harry Styles performing.
Would you really remember who the musical guest was if you were watching television
and sort of reptilians?
Real life reptilians are walking in the background of Good Morning America.
And they're like, "What's going on?"
"I don't know.
The holographic matrix must be offline again.
You numbschool."
And then he's like, "Oh, that's fascinating.
Alien life is real."
But I wonder who the musical guest is.
Apparently Harry Styles performed that day on Good Morning America.
And then so you have Harry Styles.
You have Lizardmen.
And then he also goes on to say, "You see at some point a bald man in a silver jumpsuit
walk around in the background."
So I'm assuming that's either a literal man who's bald, who's wearing like a silver jumpsuit,
or supposed to maybe be an alien, a space alien with a bald head in the silver jumpsuit.
I don't know.
But anyway, so that happened on April 22nd, 2017.
Now according to JB Stout, that video is the only one, the only episode of Good Morning
America that is not available on Discovery Plus.
Now I was not able to fact check that.
It would have cost me $7.99 a month to fact check that.
And I thought about doing the free weekly trial.
If you use the subscriber code DeadRabbitRadio, you get 20% off.
But I thought even if I do sign up for this free trial for $4.99 and you cancel within
seven days and you get your money back, I might find that that episode's not there, but
I'd have to go and see if these episodes, if there are other episodes missing, right?
If it literally is the only episode that's not streaming on Discovery Plus, that would
be shocking.
I'm sure there are other episodes missing.
And this is why.
You could, Jason, how can you be so sure?
You gotta fact check this guy.
He does make another statement.
He says that Jimmy Kimmel and Ellen DeGeneres were the most searched Google terms on April
22nd, 2017.
And it was because people knew something was up.
So they all Googled Ellen DeGeneres.
Ellen DeGeneres, Jimmy Kimmel, Jimmy Kimmel.
They were trying to figure out what they saw.
I could fact check that.
I looked into Google trend history.
Those were not, it was some like football teams.
And when I say football, I mean soccer.
I don't even know why.
I don't even know why I misspoke.
That was like the number one trending topic in the US.
There's some other stuff.
People on Ellen DeGeneres were not in that top 10.
They definitely weren't number one.
But you're like, Jason, wait a second.
Wait a second.
So let me get this straight.
Good morning, America.
Here's an episode about reptilians and bald people featuring hairy styles.
What does any of that have to do with Ellen DeGeneres or Jimmy Kimmel?
Why are we in Hollywood?
Why do you force me to watch the Jimmy Kimmel show?
Okay, so here's the timeline.
This is how it all ties together.
I'm not saying that it's logical.
I'm not saying that it makes any sense or that it's true, but April 21, 2017, Jimmy
Kimmel's son was born.
Son was born with a little congenital heart defect, but he's okay.
Totally fine, but did have to undergo surgeries.
JB Stout believes that was some sort of coverup that his baby was totally fine.
What really happened was the baby was born totally fine.
A telepath showed up on the set of the Jimmy Kimmel show and started to affect Jimmy Kimmel
and started to mess with the Ellen DeGeneres show.
And so people who were watching their shows being like, oh, I can feel the words in my
head.
They're coming right at me and the telepath was affecting.
This is all happening on April 22.
The telepath was also affecting good morning America, and that's why the reptilians were
visible to us.
So there's no physical evidence if you watch the Jimmy Kimmel show on April 22, 2017, or
the Ellen DeGeneres show on April 22, 2017.
But if you watch the Good Morning America segment that day, you will see the reptilians.
This telepath is starting to pierce through the aliens' communication, and he believes
that reptilians control the media.
So this telepath, is the telepath flexing?
Is the telepath showing the reptilians what it's capable of?
Is the telepath actually trying to disrupt these segments?
Is the telepath Jimmy Kimmel's son?
I mean, I don't know.
It doesn't really explain where the telepath comes from.
Or the motives of the telepath.
But that is this conspiracy theory right now, the Jimmy Kimmel conspiracy theory, that there's
a telepath that is maybe at war with the reptilians, maybe in league with the reptilians, we don't
know.
But if you can find the copy of Good Morning America for April 22, 2017, you may be able
to prove once and for all that reptilians are slowly taking over the planet.
Now yesterday's episode, we ended it up by saying if you look at what we know in the
lore, the conspiracy theory makes sense.
The conspiracy theory was the television show, The Secret of Skinwalker Ranch on History
Channel is cursing its viewers.
If you break it down to its components, that is believable in the paranormal world.
This is a conspiracy theory.
I think this is a great companion piece to that.
Because you can break it down its components and it's the same thing.
Reptilians, people controlling the media, telepathy, mind control, government censoring stuff,
having to disappear, lost media.
All this stuff, it's components, the Hollywood conspiracies, it's components we can break
down as part of the lore.
But this conspiracy theory is different.
This user, their previous posts show someone in need.
They are, they have several posts online about being plagued by intrusive thoughts.
Thoughts that aren't their own.
Thoughts one would assign to a telepath, maybe.
They say they get lost in intrusive thoughts, disturbing sexual imagery, violent imagery
popping in their head.
They complain of racist thoughts, clouding their judgment.
In a later post they start talking about hearing auditory hallucinations, they've gone beyond
intrusive thoughts.
And not only are they hearing auditory hallucinations, JV Stout is hearing auditory hallucinations
speaking of damnation.
You're wicked.
You're going to hell.
He closes that post out with quote, "I'm just worried that my mind is too far gone and there's
nothing I can do to heal and get close to God."
Unquote.
So is this the story of a man who's gripped with intrusive thoughts and possibly other
mental health issues?
And he's projecting those thoughts out into the world, reshaping what he sees to be part
of a broader conspiracy theory.
But if you take this conspiracy theory and you break it into pieces, it's still the pieces
themselves make sense, but the overall narrative doesn't.
And because we know this man suffers from auditory hallucinations and intrusive thoughts,
this conspiracy theory feels heartbreaking.
It feels like we're reading the manifesto of a man who thinks he's cracked reality,
but he's most likely in desperate need of help.
There's a difference to it.
There's almost a darkness to it.
Reptilians and telepaths and all that stuff, sure that's feasible, but when it's crafted
by a mind that's pleading for some sort of respite from the mental issues they're suffering,
you can see that in the writing.
You can see that in the theory itself.
This is one of those conspiracy theories that it's more terrifying if it's not true.
Because we can all imagine reptilians running around and telepaths fighting a secret war
against them, and that all kind of comes with the territory.
And if it's not true, it's really the story of a man, a real life human being who needs
guidance and help in this world.
And I'd rather live in an insane world than be insane and live in the real world.
Live in a world that's turned its back on me.
I would make up stories too.
Because in that make-believe world I've constructed, at least people listen to me.
DeadRabbitRadio.com is going to be our email address.
You can also do this up at facebook.com/DeadRabbitRadio.
TikTok is @DeadRabbitRadio.
DeadRabbitRadio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast.
You don't have to listen to it every day, but I'm glad you listened to it today.
Have a great one, guys.
[MUSIC]