A minister has a bizarre way to pass on God's blessings.
If you were driving down the road and saw a sexy woman,
would you try to hug her? That's the whole story. And then we take a look at the story of the faceless.
Is there any truth to an old Native American legend about a man who was so vain he lost his face?
And does it have terrifying implications for us all today on Dead Rabbit Radio?
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host Jason
Garvin or I'm having a great day. Hope you guys are having a great day too. I hope you guys had
an awesome weekend this whole week. I'm gonna tell you the most depressing, dark stories. No,
just kidding. Just kidding. Last week we did cursed episodes. I hope you guys are still around. I'll
check my download numbers to see how many of you guys got possessed by demons and are now listening
to other podcasts of it. That's what the demons want. You have to listen to my podcast. No,
I've decided to take a bit of a break from the super depressing stuff. Thanks for indulging me
last week. Speaking of indulging me, weird segue, coming into Dead Rabbit Command, pushing in a
giant hot fudge sundae that we're all gonna eat, it's Mikey Radmaker. Mikey Radmaker. He's making a
rad sundae for us right now. He has on an old soda jerk costume. He's like, "Hey everyone,
he's scooping us out ice cream." Mikey, you're gonna be our captain, our pilot this episode,
and apparently also the first new service as food. You guys can't support the Patreon or if you're
lactose intolerant, that's fine too. Just help spread the word about the show. Really, really
helps out a lot. Mikey, oh dude, I'm so hungry for ice cream right now. I'm so hungry for ice cream,
but I'm eating it in my imagination. Mikey, let's go ahead and toss you the keys to the
hair hang glider. We are gonna leave behind Dead Rabbit Command. These hands are all slippery from
the ice cream. Oh no! Falling to his and all of our depths because he's our pilot. Mikey, after
you wash your hands and dry them, let's get you in the hair hang glider. We're leaving behind Dead
Rabbit Command. We are headed out to South Africa.
Now, I have to say this. I put this call out on my Twitter feed and I put it out on YouTube.
Somebody may have recommended this story to me. I'm pretty sure somebody did. I don't remember
who. I keep track of all my correspondence, but I get recommendations through Facebook,
through Gmail, through the Patreon email, through YouTube, through Twitter, through Instagram,
and I checked all the stuff. I couldn't find out who sent this to me. So if you recommended
this story to me, I will make amends to you. I'll be able to prove as well. You can't just
say that you did it. I'll be able to go through my documents, but I'm pretty sure someone recommended
this story to me. I don't think I would have stumbled across this one, but you recommended
this story to me. We'll make amends, so don't worry. I'll take care of you, but I couldn't wait on it
anymore because when I started asking people, "Hey, does anyone know who recommended this?" Everyone's
like, "No, just tell me the story that sounds super interesting." We're in Guiani. That's in the state
of Limpopo in South Africa. So the hair hang rider expertly piloted by Mikey lands us in Guiani.
We're actually landing right in front of sevenfold Holy Spirit ministries. It's a church and the
doors open up. We walk and we see all these parishioners sitting there and they're like,
"Hallelujah, singing the songs, singing the songs of praise." It's like this whole musical number.
They're all choreographed. They have this special thing going on. Mikey knows all the dance moves.
We're like, "What? We didn't know you were part of the story." But that's not the whole dance move,
whole choreographed dancer team. That's not why we're here, as entertaining as it is.
In the very front of the church, we see a man laying on his back and everyone's like,
"Give me the praise. Give me the praise. Give me the praise. Doot, doot, doot, doot, doot."
And we see, walk out onto stage, whatever that part of the church is called. It's not like I was
raising the church or anything. We meet Pastor Christ Penelope and he's like, "Doot, doot." He's
like, "Shitting fireworks out of his fingertips." And there's a man just laying there on the ground
and Pastor Christ Penelope is kind of doing a little dance. I don't know. I don't know.
I don't know why I've turned it into that Steve Martin movie, a leap of faith. I don't know why
I turned it into like a revival movement. It could just be super solemn. The point is,
is that Pastor Christ Penelope, I don't know why I'm trying to make it so exciting. The story
itself is so bizarre. It doesn't need all this razzmatazz. There's a guy laying on his back
at the very front of the church and Pastor Christ, everyone's sitting down now. They're all quiet.
Pastor Christ Penelope comes out and he goes, "I'm going to bless this man. This man is in need.
This man is in need of some miracles." And Pastor Christ Penelope starts to squat
and gets down, gets those quads working, gets those thighs working. He sits down and we're like,
"What in the world?" And I'm like, "Wait for it. Wait for it." And he keeps getting lower and his butt
is getting closer and closer to this dude's head. Specifically, we're actually seeing a lineup. It's
almost like we can gauge it from where we're at. The anus of the minister is starting to line up
perfectly with the man's mouth. It's like playing one of those crane games and right when he, yep,
yep, phew, locks in. Now instead of winning like a plush prize, we all of a sudden hear a
"This is a real story, by the way. This isn't something I made up." He farts right in the dude's
mouth and everyone's, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. Everyone's clapping and celebrating the fact.
This is not a one-off occasion. Pastor Christ Penelope believes that his farts are holy.
There are photos of this, by the way. I don't have to keep saying that a lot of times.
There are photos of this. There are photos of Pastor Christ Penelope looking right at the camera.
It's not like a candid photo. It's not some weird thing he's doing in the back. He's looking right
at the camera. There's a man laying on the floor and he's just sitting on his face. There is a
wait period to get farted on. There's so many people who want this that you have to sign a list.
And if, like, let's say you're sitting like you're like, "Oh, I'm dying. I only have two months to
live." He's like, "Well, three month waiting list." People who are sick, I think, get to the front
of the line, but local business leaders, people who are starting their own businesses, people who
are bidding on contracts, they will have to wait up to two months before this man will fart in their
mouth. It has to be this man. I mean, you could probably pay someone on the street to do that.
And some people would probably do it for free. But this man, his farts are blessed. They're holy.
And some people will bring stuff with them that he can also fart on. There is a division in the
church, though, because you have people who love it. They go, "Listen, when he farts on you, you
don't even smell it. It's like magical." And then the other people go, "I don't care whether or not
you smell it. It's still gas being expelled, body temperature gas being expelled from the orifice
of one man on to me. Whether or not I smell it, it's disgusting. It'd be the same thing if someone
just came up and breathed right in my face." And they're like, "But he doesn't have bad breath.
That doesn't matter. It's still gross." The church is divided. Some people think this is a blessing.
Other people go, "I think I'm going to have to find another church. You know, I don't have a high
list of qualifications for my next minister. I only have one question. Do you fart on people?"
And because of this article, that someone may or may not have recommended me, which is the true
mystery, really, not whether or not this man's farts are holy. I think we know the answer to that.
They are. But who recommended this story to me? But this story did give me this amazing quote.
There was a news article for thedailysun.co.za and has the great quote where there was a
parishioner being like, "Nope, nope. This is the quote. Quote. That's not what I signed up for.
I needed prayers, not fart." I don't think in that woman's entire existence she would ever have
had to say that sentence out loud. I definitely thought that I would never read it, but I love it.
So funny because in one of the interviews he keeps going, "Go to my Facebook page. Everything is
explained on my Facebook page. Go to my Facebook page." I went to his Facebook page. It wasn't funny.
I expected it to have a bunch of jokes. I don't know actually why. He has a little green cartoon
gas clouds floating around his head. I didn't mean jokes, but I thought it would have more fun
material. No, it's just about human suffering and people praying and things like that, which I'm
down with. Not the human suffering thing, but I get the power of prayer. I think that's important,
the power of mindfulness and connecting to the other and all that stuff. I get that.
I do have to say this. It's possible, right? Like in a world where Bigfoot and aliens and ghosts
and all that stuff exist, in a world where the CIA like tests whether or not people can do remote
viewing and Russia is trying to figure out the secrets of telepathy and the men who stare goats
and all that stuff, and people having bizarre powers, it's possible out of 7 billion people
plus more than that through the course of human history, one of us has magical farts.
Like it's not a long enough timeline. It's going to work. One of us has blessed farts.
It's no more ridiculous than a psychic. If you just look at the plain facts of it,
it's no more ridiculous than saying I can communicate to your loved ones
by the rap rap rap on my table. It really isn't. It really isn't. If in the 1860s,
two sisters in their house realized that they could communicate with the dead through farting,
back then, and there was a whole spiritualism movement involving farting,
and now here we are in the year 2021, and this guy in South Africa goes, "Oh, it's so weird. I can
bless you by asking God, and then I hear a rapping on the table." People would be like, "Well, that's
stupid. Everyone knows the paranormal communicates through farts?" So it's- I don't think so. I don't-
I think this guy just likes farting on people. But to be fair, I could be wrong. He could be a
mutant. He could be blessed by- not necessarily a mutant, but he could also be divinely blessed by
God. Who knows? I'm leaning towards neither of those. I'm leaning to him just farting on people.
Mikey, let's go ahead and hop in the Carpenter Caboose. We're taking a train out of
Fartsville, South Africa, and that's how it's going to be officially named now.
Dude, wouldn't it suck to go to that church and to have built that church with your own bare hands
and helped establish that? This dude comes in and starts farting everywhere,
and that's how it'll be known. Mikey, let's get in the Carpenter Caboose. We are leaving behind
South Africa. We are headed out to Brazil. Chugga chugga chugga chugga chugga chugga chugga chugga chugga chugga chugga chugga chugga chugga chugga chugga chugga chugga chugga chugga chugga chugga chugga chugga chugga chugga chugga chugga chugga chugga chugga chugga chugga chugga chugga chugga chugga chugga chugga chugga chugga chugga chugga chugga chugga chugga chugga chugga chugga chugga chugga chugga chugga chugga chugga chugga chugga chugga chugga chugga chugga chugga chugga chugga chugga chugga chugga chugga chugga chugg
saying that Campos Gerais in Brazil chugga chugga chugga chugga chugga chugga chugga chugga chugga
We're all jumping off the Carpenter Caboose. The year is 1983. We don't have a specific date,
which is odd, because we have a bunch of other specific information for this story.
But the year is 1983. It is 830 at night. And we're walking down the street, and we see a man
named Joaquim Antonio-Louise riding his bike ahead of us.
He has a little car that has the sound of the car, the little baseball card in the spokes.
He kind of rounds this curve, and that's when he sees a woman standing on the side of the road.
830 isn't that late. It's kind of dark depending on what month it is, but it's not.
Super late. If you just saw someone standing on the street corner at 830, it wouldn't be
why is he on the street corner? It's in the middle of nowhere in this rural area. He's a farmer.
So maybe it would just be weird to see anyone out around that time or in that area.
But he sees this woman, and he immediately goes Big Bad Wolf from the Looney Tune cartoons.
His eyeballs are all pretty. He has a medical condition. He was on his way to the hospital.
He's like, "Oh, I better get these eyeball things checked out." And the fact that I keep making
sounds like fog horns, I gotta get this checked out. He turns the corner, he sees the girl.
She is thick, as the kids would say these days. She has a voluptuous body, a tight skirt,
big plump, juicy legs. Really? What podcasts has this become?
A good one. This podcast says this is a sexy, curvy woman standing by the side of the road
wearing a short dress and a blouse. And she has a light blue belt tilted slightly to the left.
So he jumps off the bike and he starts approaching this woman and she's just standing there.
It's 830 at night. He walks up to her. He feels compelled to go towards her. Now she's a very
attractive woman. Very, very attractive woman. Sounds attractive, right? Belt tilted to the left.
That's all I need. That's really all I need. He's walking towards her. He feels compelled.
He wants to get to know her. He wants to talk to her. Figure out, you know,
do I like you? Do you like me? But you guys heard the intro. He just really wants to hug her.
He doesn't know why, but he really wants to hug her. Total violation of social norms. But
while Keem's not thinking, he's just drawn towards this woman, he stretches his arms out
and he goes to wrap them around this plump lady. And then all of a sudden, she jumps away. Now,
not like she just kind of jumps a couple of feet back and she goes, "Uh-uh-uh." She goes from being
right in front of him to being 500 meters away, which is actually one-fourth of a mile. That
sounds more dramatic. I don't know how big a meter is. And then she jumped again
and became a little, a little dot in the sky. Ding. I don't know if it made the animated noise
and a little sparkle. He actually gets completely terrified by this. He never expected, no one would
expect this. Woo! She jumps away. He actually got on his bicycle, rode home, and went to sleep.
I don't know how you would sleep after that. Either way, I'd be afraid she'd come and jump
on my house for me trying to assault her. That story was reported in the Revista Brasileira de
UFOologia, which my Portuguese isn't that great, but I'm pretty sure that's the revised Brazilian
UFOologia book or something like that. I got it from ThinkAboutItDocs.com. They got it from them.
It's an interesting story for a couple of reasons. One, we've seen stories where people feel compelled
to go towards cryptids and aliens. It's almost like a hypnotic thing. They're kind of swayed
into something. He may have been under some sort of mind control. She could have just been super
sexy. And he's like, "I want to get to know her." And as he's walking towards her, then he's just
like, "I'm just going to grab her." Which, don't do that part. Don't do that part, right? Now,
when you have someone you like, don't just try to hug them on the first meeting. I don't get that.
I don't get that. I know people like to hug the first time they meet people. That's always weird
to me, especially at 8.30 at night. You can do it. It's 7pm. That's fine. But in the middle of nowhere,
it makes it even weirder. He doesn't know this woman at all. He's just walking up to hug her.
Story's bizarre. And then her jumping. Actually, that's the most bizarre part. I'm not like, "Oh,
yeah." And then, by the way, she also did an inhuman feat. So, cryptid alien? I think alien,
because she's had the belts. I mean, a lot of humans wear belts. I'm not saying there's 7
billion aliens on the planet. But a lot of times, I don't think of many cryptids who have belts on.
But there's a lot of sexy cryptids, too. So, that's kind of… it's an interesting story. I mean,
it was reported by this UFOology association, but alien? I'm leaning more towards alien than cryptid,
but still, just a weird story all around. Moral of the story, don't hug people. Never hug. Never
hug anyone again. Just let your baby lay in the crib and go, "Uh-uh, you might jump away."
That's the first moral. And I think that's actually the only moral. I don't think there is a moral.
He goes to hug a woman, she jumps away, he gets on his bike and rides home. Rides out of
the fields of Campos de Ries, Brazil, and into the hearts and minds of all
Dead Rabbit radio listeners. And you know who else is a powerful jumper? You know who else is
really good at jumping? Superman. March 18th on HBO Max. Batman and the Flash and Wonder Woman.
And who's the other guy? Aquaman. Team up. In a world without Superman. Who will prevent
Darkseid from taking over the planet? They will. Watch. Zack Snyder's Justice League. March 18th.
Only on HBO Max. Rated R. Cross my Superman sound effect. You like that? I like that. I
don't even remember the names of all the guys. Mikey's just super embarrassed. He's like,
"Seriously? This is the episode I'm on. You're reading a bad promo." Mikey, go ahead and call in
that carpenter copter. We are leaving behind Campos de Ries, Brazil, and we are headed back to the
United States. Specifically, we are headed out to Minnesota. And as we're headed back there,
Mikey, hit that time travel button. We are leaving the present day and we are headed back
to ancient Minnesota. This is long before the European settlers came to America. This is long
before it was called America. This is the time where the natives ruled the continent. We're
going to land this carpenter copter and we're walking around this frigid cold field of Minnesota.
We're walking around and we see a village in the distance. It's getting dark. Mikey, thanks for
landing so far away. We see the flames of the village in the distance. We're walking towards them.
Apparently, there is a story among the Lakota Nation of a man known as the Faceless One.
He's basically a boogie man that you would tell your children about to keep them in line.
"Don't go out after dark or the Faceless Man will get you," Grandpa says. "Take out the garbage or
the Faceless Man will get you. But Grandpa, it's dark outside. Take out the garbage. Take your chances.
Faceless Man's right there. Do your homework." They're like, "I get it. Let me guess. Faceless
Man's going to give me. Yes. Yes, you've learned well, young man." Here's the legend. There once
was a member of a tribe who was the handsomest man in the land. We'll call him Barney. Barney is
super good looking and he's so good looking that there are even women and other tribes who are
like, "Oh my god. Did you read the newspaper today?" Barney is so hot. How is the headline of
the newspaper? The Barney Times. It's publisher Barney. They're like, "Oh my god. He's so hot."
Women from other tribes are wanting to get with Barney and he's just like kind of in the beginning.
He's like, "Oh, you know, that's really cool. I'm glad that I'm blessed. Some dude farted on my
face when I was a baby. Next thing I know, I'm super hot." But as time went on, he wasn't so humble.
He started to become very, very vain and he's like, "Yes, I am super hot, dude. I read the newspaper
as well. I am super hot." And he starts to basically believe the hype. Women from other
tribes are trying to get with them. Rivals don't like him. People in his own village don't like him
at a certain point because he's such a jerk. He's so conceited and there's this old medicine man
working in the village. He's making old medicine. It doesn't work. They just humor him. The young
medicine men are much better. He's making medicine and Barney is always like, "Yo, you suck. You suck."
He's just yelling into the dude's house, "You suck." He's like, "Man, I'm just trying to make my medicine.
You suck, dude. Your medicine sucks too." He would constantly make fun of how old and ugly this
guy was and the girls, "Hehehehe." Apparently he's dating the crypt keeper. The girls are just going
along with it because, you know, they're in love with this dude. And the old medicine man's like,
"Oh, I'm gonna get that guy one day. If only I can move more than one mile a day. I'll chase him down."
"You suck. You're super ugly, dude. Barney rules." The old medicine man's like, "Oh, man,
this existence sucks." But he knows something. He knows medicine and really implied he's like a
witch. He's like a wizard, right? Like old medicine men like Shaman. Like, okay, let's take a break.
Why is this guy picking on a man who has magical powers? Because it's not like he's like crushing
up berries for people who have headaches. That's part of it. The other part of it is he's like
going on vision quests and stuff like that. He's having vision quests where he's like beating up
Barney. He's turning into a wolf and eating Barney. Why would you mess with a Shaman? So this medicine
man's like, "Okay, I'm done. I'm done with this." But he lets it go on for a while. I think he figures,
you know, eventually Barney's going to mature or he's going to get killed in some raid. One of the
two. But eventually he's just done with it. So one day when Barney's walking through the village
with all these girls and Barney's like, "Hey, what's up old man? Oh, not you. Not you. You're
going to die soon because you're super old." Medicine man goes, "What? That doesn't even make sense.
I mean, I'm up right now, but anyway, that doesn't matter. You're right though. I will die eventually
because that's how things happen. All things die." Well, medicine man goes, "Listen, when I die and I'm
going to die soon." Yeah, you die soon. He's like, "Okay, get it done. Get it done. That clean me about
my death. I'm going to take your face with me. I'm going to die and I'm going to take your face off."
And the dude's like, "What? That's super stupid. Like, that's not going to happen. I mean, it's not
like I don't believe in all sorts of spirits and curses and things like that. What you are saying
will not happen." The old man's like, "Okay, we'll see." A couple weeks later news passes through
the village. The Barney who issued the Barney Times comes out. "Old man dead. He was ugly as
hell," says Barney. And Barney goes, "Oh, you know, that knew he was going to die. I made fun of him
a lot that he was old and he was going to die and my prediction came true." He's looking around for
the next person, the next ugly person in the village to make fun of. He's like, "Ah, figure that out
tomorrow." The next day when Barney wakes up, he has no mouth. He goes, he goes, "Okay, I feel like
I have no mouth. Let me check with the nose." The nose is in there. Wait a second. I remember
having two eyes. Do I have two eyes? No. His face is smooth. I don't know if he had ears,
because technically that's not the face, but it's not like you'd be like, "Well, at least I have my
ears." I mean, he has immediate problems. Like, he can't communicate. He can't breathe. He can't
eat. He has a super smooth face. He jumps up and he runs out of his house. He's like, "Oh,
and people go, that is obviously some sort of demon. That's obviously some sort of monster.
That man with no face and ears or not ears, but they chase him out of the village."
Nobody can understand what he's saying. He leaves. They never see Barney again, but the people
of this village aren't very smart. They don't put two and two together. A faceless man runs out of
Barney's house a day after he was cursed to lose his face. Everyone goes, "Oh, I don't know."
They put out one more issue of the Barney Times. Where is Barney? That's a collector's issue if
you still have a copy of it. And that was the end of Barney. But the faceless man supposedly is still
out there and he waits in the darkness for you. He wants your face off. He wants to steal your face
and wear it because if he doesn't have one, maybe he can have yours.
Now that's a really interesting boogieman legend. I came across it. I was reading this Reddit thread
about Native American legends, Native American horror stories, and I found some really cool ones
we're going to be covering. This was written by Skull Kid 00. Now they said it was a Lakota legend.
I actually tried verifying that this is true. Not that it's true. I'm not like typing in faceless
man. Did it happen? I'm trying to find archives of the Barney Times. I was trying to find out if it
was a real Lakota legend. I was able to find that other tribe has a legend about why corn husk
dolls don't have faces. It was basically the same thing. Once one of the gods created a corn husk
doll and they put a face on it and it was animated and it walked from village to village. Everyone
said how beautiful the doll was and it became super vain and eventually got punished by having
its face removed. That's why when you make a corn husk doll now you don't put a face on it because
punishment is basically like a punishment for you to have a doll with no face and have it be
super spooky. But like I said in the intro, the implications for us today. I'm not... this is
really interesting because when I read this story by Skull Kid 00, an interesting boogieman story
has a moral to it. It would totally scare kids. Having your face ripped off. It's spooky being
having like a totally flat face. It's with no features. It's so inhuman. It's creepy. Tell
that story to nine-year-old kid. They are going to take out the garbage. But then I thought about
it a little bit longer. Let's put our conspiracy caps to wrap this episode up. This is really creepy.
What if this is real? And not in the sense that the story of Barney is real,
but the story of something out there taking our faces is real. You have it in Europe with the
Faye. You have it in Europe with them stealing the children and replacing them with the
Faye children. So we raise them and we think it's around the changelings. We discussed the story
a couple weeks ago out of Morocco where you had Jin replacing human children with the Jin children
to grow up in our world. And you have a ton of legends of shapeshifters and people assuming
other people's shapes. You have the skinwalkers. You have them imitating people's voices. You
have all these legends. You have a lot of them in America. And then you have others sprinkled out
through the rest of the world. Let's take a look at this. This is really kind of spooky.
What if, conspiracy cap fully on, that when people go missing, truly go missing and are found again,
it's not them? Think about it this way. 600,000 people go missing in the United States each year.
And that number is true, but it's a little off. It's a little lacking more information.
600,000 people go missing, but by the end of the year, only 85,000 of those cases are still active.
That's a huge amount of people, but most people are found in very, very short order. 95% of the
600,000 people, they're runaways. 0.8% of them are non-custodial parents taking children. 0.1%
is what we think about when we think about a missing person. 0.1% is someone who is not
related to the person taking them from one location to another. I don't know how many of those are
found again, but out of the total of 600,000 people by the end of the year, 85,000 people are still
out there. The rest of the other 500,000 have returned home. What's really bizarre about this
is that in the European Union, and it has double the population of the United States, 10,000 people
go missing each year. Double the population, 10,000 people disappear each year. Who's to say
they come home? They do on paper, and they do in reality. Somebody runs away, they're gone for two
weeks, and then they come back, or they're picked up by the police, or they go stay at a friend's
house, and their friend tells the parents, "Hey, we know where Judy is." But in that time where they
leave their home, they are replaced. The whole thing about the faceless man, and boogeyman in
general, it's about enforcing rules. Don't go out late. Don't, either like I had the joke about
taking the garbage out, boogeyman or that type of thing, go to bed, or the boogeyman's gonna get
you. It's all about enforcing rules. Running away is the ultimate rule break. You're leaving behind
the social psychological network that's built up at home, and breaking all the rules by leaving
and throwing away that command, throwing away those rules. You run away, you get on the bus,
you get three blocks away, and you encounter something as you're turning down a dark alley,
and you're found a couple days later. You return home willingly, the police pick you up, whatever.
But it's something wearing their face. In that brief time where they're not
around people who would know them when they're interacting with strangers,
that would be the time that some sort of supernatural force could learn, could perfect
the ins and outs of their body language. So by the time it does go back home,
it blends in perfectly with who Judy was. And if we're talking about stranger abductions,
if we're talking about people just being snatched off the street and never seen again,
and that's, and I'm even focusing on just the quote unquote "benign" missing people, the people
who run away. I'm not even focused on the people who get snatched out of their house,
and then they're returned, and they're like, I don't know what happened. Some guy, he broke in,
he was wearing a mask, he took me down there, and then there was an Amber Alert, and I get found.
But what if these people aren't being found, but replacements of them, doppelgangers,
the real them is still out there somewhere, if they're alive at all. If something like the
faceless man was stealing people's faces and wearing them. Now there's only one of them,
but who's to say that this legend is canon? Who's to say that this legend is not the story of just
one but a race of cryptids, a race of beings that steal your face and wear it and become you,
and no one's the wiser? No one except for one group of people. I talked about them in episode 59
of the podcast, I'll put it in the show notes, but in brief, these people have brain damage.
These people have undergone trauma. These people suffer from something known as
Capgras Delusion. It's the idea that they can look at someone that they've known their entire life,
and think they are a replacement. They're an android, they're a double, they're not the person
that they knew them to be. The person they love, their wife, their child, has been removed somehow,
and they're looking at this double. And is that person being dragged off to the hospital?
The guys show up in the suits and they drag you off into the funny wagon, but according to Daffy
Duck cartoons, that's how they used to do it. As they are being sent to a mental institution,
and they're screaming, "That's not my wife, that's not my wife, that's not my wife,
the wife is befuddled." No one can figure it out, the authorities just figure he must suffer
from Capgras Delusion. The wife may not even be aware of when she went missing when she was three,
for four hours. She was at the park with her family, and she walked into the brush, and they
couldn't find her for hours and hours and hours, and the whole town panicked. There she is, but it
wasn't her. The real her disappeared into those bushes forever, and a perfect replica waddled out,
to the point that she doesn't even know she's a doppelganger. That is all being said with Conspiracy
Cap fully on. I'm taking a real-life medical condition and tying it into Native American myths,
but it's still creepy to think that the United States has six times the amount of missing people
than the entire European Union and half the population. It could be something about our culture,
it could be something about the way we treat our youth that makes them want to run away,
that thinks they have a better chance outside of their own home, or it could be that this country
is stalked by dark creatures. This land actually has entities that are not found on other places
on the planet. This land has something in the darkness that's not just snatching kids out of
houses, but sometimes just whispers through the breeze. You're better off alone. You need to leave
your house. You're better off alone. And these whispers gather and grow in the minds of these
young people until they pack up, leave the house, and step out of the safety of the light,
and into the unfamiliar darkness of the outside world. That might sound far-fetched,
but on Friday I'm going to cover a Native American spirit that does exactly that,
who whispers in the darkness, who is so powerful that in the modern day, people have called for
the police to investigate this spirit. So it's not my imagination to think that a spirit
can whisper through the darkness. Friday we're going to cover one that actually does it,
but this one doesn't want to simply take your face and replace you. It wants to do something
much, much worse. How's that for a tease for the rest of the week?
GoodRabber Radio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast. You don't
have to listen to it every day, but I'm glad you listened to it today. Have a great one guys.
[Music]