Giant rats terrorize Iran. A couple brings their kids to church and things do not go well.
And then we talk about the great fires of 1871. You know about the Chicago fire.
It's a nursery rhyme, I think. But do you know about the other fires in America?
That same day. That's important. That is the same day.
More death, more destruction, and all the fires may have been caused by something out of this world.
Today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
[music]
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host Jason Carpenter.
I'm having a great day. I hope you're having a great day too.
I'm putting together some stuff for our New Year's Eve episode.
And I know most people will be listening to this one on New Year's Eve. So technically it's the New Year's Day episode.
But we will be having some stuff come out.
Now, other than that little note, oh and I have a special episode. I have a regular episode coming out for New Year's Day.
And then I have a special episode. It's actually, it's a behind the scenes story of the creation of Dead Rabbit.
You're thinking, "Jason, that's a little ridiculous. You've only been around for six months."
However, I want to know that type of stuff. I love director's commentaries and stuff like that.
It'll be a bonus episode. Just be sitting there for you if you want to listen to it.
I really go into depth about how the show was created. Some of the obstacles I've overcome.
My least favorite episode. The episode that almost made me quit the show. I talk about that.
I talk about my favorite episodes. The episodes that I think have had the most impact on the growth of the show.
And then I talk about a controversy. And the time the podcast was almost canceled.
Not because of me, but because of some issues going on behind the scenes.
So all of that stuff will be in our bonus episode. You'll get your regular one and then you'll get a special bonus one as well.
So, let's go ahead and get started here. So first off, let's go ahead and start talking about Iran.
So, right now, so apparently, I didn't know this, but apparently Iran has always had a rat problem.
Rodents. Giant rodents. And they've constantly been poisoning them.
And eventually when you poison a rat so many times, it stops working after a certain point.
I guess 75% of the rats in Britain are immune to what would it be called?
Well, rat poison, obviously, but I'm sure it has a technical name like raticide or mouseicide or whatever their genus is.
That's probably listed in there as well.
But anyway, so Iran has been trying to poison the rats and is, you know, fairly successful, but rats develop an immunity to poison.
That's just something that happens, apparently.
So then they began, no joke, they began irradiating them.
They're like, well, if the poison doesn't work, no one's immune to radiation.
Let's just basically like irradiate their homes.
Now, yes, that is the setup for every 1950s movie ever.
And Iran is now experiencing a 1950s movie because the rats are as big as cats.
They're giant mutant rats.
And Iran, the government of Iran has said they're mutants.
They've mutated from the radioactivity and now they're huge.
And I guess they're having a lot of snow melt off over there and it's flooding the rats' nest.
So the country is just awash in rats.
Big, smelly, all wet because the water came in their homes.
Rats are disgusting.
I remember once I was walking down the street here in Hood River at like four in the morning.
And I'm walking in between two restaurants.
Well, I'm not like literally like walking in an alley between them, but I'm walking on the street and on one side,
I'm not going to name the restaurants because this is really, I think it's gross.
On one side of the street's one restaurant, on the other side of the street's this other restaurant,
and I'm walking down the sidewalk and I see the biggest rat I've ever seen.
It was the size, it looked like the size of a 12 pack of soda.
It looked, okay, maybe that's a bit of an exaggeration.
Okay, but an 8 pack of soda.
And it crawls out of the sewer of one restaurant, lazily walks across the street and crawls into the sewer of the next restaurant.
And I was like, I'm never eating there again.
That's disgusting.
Of course I did indeed.
He keep eating at both of those restaurants, but it was pretty gross to see something that large and it was just wet and gross, man.
So anyways, imagine that, but the two restaurants is the entire country of Iran.
Now, the Iranian government is like, they're mutants.
These rats have been mutated by radiation.
They're giant.
And scientists have said, you know, because scientists are kind of like, they're party poopers.
They're like, that's not how mutations work.
You can't just irradiate an animal and it gets bigger.
This isn't a 1950s movie.
It's probably just because they've just gotten big.
These are survival of the fittest and the biggest rats are the kings.
And you know what a rat king is?
This is disgusting.
I know I keep going off on tangents here, but a rat king, some people say they don't exist.
Again, scientists are party poopers, but a rat king is when so many rats get caught in a tunnel, like a sewage tunnel, that their tails get tied together.
You know how like you'll throw like three power cables in a box and then like an hour later you come back and they're all tangled up?
Imagine that, but 100 rats and their tails get tangled together and they begin just rolling through the sewer because the rats at the bottom are like, I can't breathe underwater.
And so they'll push the ball so they get to the top to catch a breath and the rats on the bottom will be like, so it just goes over and over again.
Basically, it's the real life equivalent of gelatinous ooze from D&D.
They just roll through the sewers, eating people.
They don't live very long, but only if they live to be like five minutes old or whatever.
It's still quite terrifying.
So back to the story that I'm trying to tell, the rats in Iran are so just like vicious and huge that the Iranian government has said, we don't believe you scientists.
We believe that these guys are mutants.
And how do you stop a mutant?
Not with getting your own team of mutants.
No, they have a team of dedicated snipers that now just hunt giant rats.
Last count that I saw, they had already killed 2,000 rats.
But these, I mean, that would kind of be a cool job because you're just doing what you love, shooting stuff, and you become a better sniper because of it because they're, you know, smaller than a human.
A rat the size of a cat is probably a good as a target to get good at shooting people in the head.
So, I mean, that's kind of grim.
If we ever go to war with Iran, they're going to be like super good at crack shots because they're like, man, I've been shooting Wamp rats in the desert since, okay, that was a stupid joke.
Okay, but anyway, so Iran, I do wish you luck.
I hope you take care of your giant rat problem.
And I'm on your side.
I'm not politically, but I'm on your side.
I think they're mutants.
Don't listen to the scientists.
Scientists say that Pluto is not a planet.
So what do they know?
I know it's a different branch of science, but it's all the same, really.
Our next story is part of new news.
So this one's going to be a quick one and it's kind of bizarre.
Well, the whole thing's bizarre, but it's also bizarre how it ends.
So we're in the magical weird year of 2004.
I'm learning, oh, and I looked, my new news folder still has like 200 other stories that I have to go through and find out if they're worth doing anything on.
2004 was a banner year for weirdness.
It's turning out.
We're in the city of Rochester, which I believe is in New York, but maybe it's near New York.
I'm pretty sure that's where Professor Xavier School for Gifted Youngsters was.
Was in Rochester, but I could be wrong.
But we're in the city of Rochester.
It's 2004, that magical, magical year.
This couple comes in to a church, bringing their three kids with them, a nine-year-old, a seven-year-old, and a two-year-old little baby person, right?
They walk into church.
It's nighttime.
And, you know, in New York, I think in big cities, you can have churches that are open late, or maybe they're 24 hours a day.
I don't know.
But usually there's like nuns walking around.
I'm assuming this is a Catholic church.
I've actually never seen a Protestant church open, like, really later than the service, maybe a little bit after.
But anyways, they walk into a church of a denomination I do not know.
There are nuns there and the Protestants are like, "Why are you here?
This is the Southern Baptist Church."
And they're like, "Sorry, we're lost and we needed to pray."
Anyways, the point of the story is that this couple walks in with their kids, and they're kind of looking around, and no one really pays them any mind.
They don't look like super weird, but they're a little sketchy.
There's something about them that's kind of making people pay attention to them.
Maybe it's just six cents.
So, what happens is one of the workers at the church, one of these nuns who's in the wrong church, is standing there, and she--
I hope it's nuns.
I have no idea.
But anyways, it's just, I might not say church workers.
Maybe it was the bingo person.
They hear the woman say to the husband, "Let's go make the sacrifice."
And then they kind of mill about the church for a while.
And at this point, the church workers are like, "Okay, they didn't seem super sketchy, but they seemed kind of sketchy."
And now they're talking about making a sacrifice, so they call the police, which is probably a good thing, especially for what happens next.
The police show up, they begin questioning the couple, take the couple back to the station.
And when they're talking to the woman, she says, "They were going to sacrifice the kids in the church, the nine, the seven, and the two-year-old.
It was their plan to go there, kind of look around, check the place out, and then sacrifice them."
It's interesting because I wonder what their plan was with the other people there.
I wonder what they-- like, were they going to sacrifice them to?
Like, was there just going to be this long receiving line of sacrificial offerings?
Or were they just going to do it so quick and then not worry about it?
Because her logic was this. This is what she told the police.
She said, "Jesus sacrificed himself for her, so she was going to sacrifice her boys to free her soul."
Which, her interpretation of the Bible is a little off, because technically, according to the Bible, when Jesus sacrificed him--
I always get so funny, I always see a listener drop when I start talking about Jesus, but it'll only be 10 seconds.
According to the Bible, Jesus sacrificed himself to save your soul, and then he doesn't go, "Hey, man, pay it forward."
Like, there was no collateral added to any part of the Bible as far as that goes.
But for whatever reason, she had it in her head saying, "Well, he sacrificed himself for me, so I'm going to sacrifice my kids for--
to free my soul." It's very, very odd.
And what I think is interesting about this type of behavior is that she may have had that delusion, but the husband was going along with it.
So, it's just weird. I don't know if there was, like, drugs involved or something like that.
So, now we're in the year 2018, 14 years later, and so I'm like, "Well, what happened?"
No follow-up to the story, no sentence, no conviction, nothing like that.
Which makes me think that the charges are revocated, or she went to get mental counseling.
Because technically, she didn't commit a crime. I mean, you could say child endangerment or something like that.
But as far as I could tell, she was never charged.
Now, that doesn't mean she wasn't. It could just be that the news didn't cover it after certain point.
It was just another crazy person in Rochester.
But, yeah, weird story. Weird story.
And it's a good thing those people were paying attention to what was going on, because otherwise, it could have gotten--could have gotten bad.
I mean, understatement, three kids sacrificed, but, yeah, it could have been pretty sucky.
Okay, so the next story we're going to look at today is...
Oh, yeah, this one was really interesting, because I came assembled across this on accident, really.
I don't even know how I found it.
But we're in the year--let's hop in the Carpenter copter.
Carpenter copter is actually pretty sturdy. You can handle these time warps.
So 2004 is not really a time jump. We just kind of like turn our heads lightly and we're back in 2004.
But when we're going way back in time, we want the Carpenter copter. We want to ride in style, and it can handle any sort of time warp.
So...
[imitates carpenter copter]
I don't know where we found that time warp. We were just at the airport.
We slowly lifted off the ground slightly, disappeared back in time.
But we are going back in time. We're going back to the year 1871.
So when this helicopter appears out of nowhere, everyone's like, "Oh my God, it's a giant demon. It's super loud."
And the pilot looks like he's really terrible at flying that thing, whatever it is.
[imitates carpenter copter]
And we land and we jump out of it. It's a specific date. It's October 8th, 1871.
Four days after my birthday, which would probably matter if I was born 100 years earlier than I actually was.
So we're in 1871. It's October 8th.
We're in the Midwest. I think it's the Midwest. It's like Chicago and Michigan and stuff like that.
Wisconsin. So that's close.
It's Illinois. I think that's more East. But anyways, it doesn't matter. We're in that area.
And we land next to a farm and we go and we see this woman milking a cow.
And you guys all know the story. The Great Chicago Fire rushed through the city.
It destroyed 3.3 square miles of the city.
It left 100,000 people homeless, which was one-third of the population at that time. 300 people died.
It just raised the city. And the kind of joke explanation was the cow kicked over a lantern in Miss O'Larry's barn and it started the Great Chicago Fire.
That was an old nursery rhyme. And I think most people who hear the term "Great Chicago Fire" are like, "Oh, yeah, the one where the cow kicked it over."
Now, apparently the fire, they did say started in that barn, but it didn't have nothing to do with the cow kicking it over.
And everyone that got tons of news coverage and they're like, "Oh my God, like 3.3 square miles of a major city burned to the ground.
100,000 people homeless. 300 people dead. This is the most horrible fire tragedy that America has faced yet."
But we're going to travel just a bit, just a little bit over to Michigan.
Now it's the same day, the Great Michigan Fire. And you know, they're probably like, "They don't have internet or television."
But they're like, "Man, I heard something really bad happen in Chicago. I don't know how, but I know it because I don't have a newspaper or a television."
But I know it. The Great Michigan Fire spread across three cities, three different little townships, raised just...
That's a machine gun noise, but...
Crackle, log, that's a fire noise.
Crackle, crackle.
You're like, "Jason, I get it. You're quitting the sound effects. Something's on fire."
In Michigan, 3,900 square miles burn. Now it's not entire city squares, but you would have a city or a town, it's probably a better term for it, just...
I don't know why I'm doing gunshot noises.
Go up, it would cut swaths through forests, just lighting everything up.
500 people or more killed across these three communities.
And the reason why they go or more is because the place had...
There was a big lumber industry, so you had a lot of lumberjacks there, people moving to that area specifically to cut trees down, and then they would move on.
So they don't know how many people died in the forest. They're like, "And it could be higher than 500."
Because we had people there cutting trees down that weren't members of the community, they're just kind of like migrant workers.
So it could be higher than 500. So it definitely a bigger fire than Chicago, as far as square miles, and more people died.
But the problem was that everyone was focused on Chicago because it was a big city.
So people... Well, the people in Michigan were focused on the fire right in front of them.
But nationwide, people were like, "Oh my God, did you hear about Chicago?"
And Michigan's like, "Hey, remember me? They're still covered in soot."
And the people were like, "No, did you visit Chicago? Why do you look like you just walked out of a fire?"
And they're like, "Ugh."
But on the same day as the Great Chicago Fire, as the Great Michigan Fire, in Wisconsin, we're going to hop in the Carbenter Copture because we want to go here and visit this place.
We want a first-hand account of Pestigo Fire.
Pestigo was a community in Wisconsin, and it was like this town, I think. It was, again, a good word for it.
And it kind of looped around this bay.
You had this water thing in the middle of it, a lake, is probably the scientific term.
The community wrapped around like a horseshoe.
On October 8th, 1871, Pestigo Fire starts.
Now, starts out in the field and rapidly grows.
And the reason why is there was a cold front coming in, and it created very, very quickly what's known as a firestorm.
Now, a firestorm is a very specific scientific term, not just the name of a movie starring Howie Long from the '90s.
Firestorm is a very specific scientific term.
Superheated flames at least 2,000 degrees Fahrenheit.
So if it's only 1,999 people are like, "Pfft, go back to school. Get to 2,000." But if it's at least 2,000 degrees Fahrenheit,
and it has winds of 110 miles per hour, or stronger, it doesn't heck and be over that.
That is what is considered a firestorm.
So it's moving incredibly fast. You can't out-drive that, especially not like in a, like a Hyundai or something.
You would, I mean, you're 110 miles an hour, and it's 2,000 degrees, even if you were in a car that say was going 120 miles an hour.
By the time you started to put distance between you, your tires would melt.
And they didn't have cars back then, so it doesn't matter. They were just totally boned.
It torched everything.
A fire tornado appeared and hit a train, knocking the train cars over.
Now, that might be a little dramatic. The train wasn't moving. It wasn't like, "Keep going, keep going."
It's like, "Chucka, chucka, chucka, chucka." And there's like this tornado chasing, and they're like, "It went too close."
It was just sitting still. I should have made that specific from the beginning. It was just sitting there.
And fire tornado, pfft, knocked stuff over, knocked over a train car.
Now, 1,875 square miles burned.
So, bigger than both of them. Wait, was that bigger than both of them? Now I have to double check the Great Michigan one.
Oh, no, it was smaller than Great Michigan one. Okay, so...
But still, first is the worst, second is the best. 1,875 square miles burned.
So many people died. They don't know. They're best guests.
So, in Chicago we had 300, and in Great Michigan we had 500.
The Pashtego fire, between 1,500 and 2,500 people, dead.
It happened within like minutes. You have this huge death toll.
Because the fire was moving super fast, and it was just cutting everyone down.
And this is the interesting thing. Well, it's not interesting. It's quite dark.
So many people died, and the fire... there weren't enough people left to identify remains.
So they just started throwing them in a big pit.
Entire families and neighborhoods and communities... no one was left to say, "Oh, that's Joey, and that's Margaret, and that's Malcolm," or whatever.
There was nobody left to say, "Oh, yeah, I know that guy," because they all needed someone to go, "Hey, I know that guy," and they were just all burnt to a crisp.
Some people said, because you know there was that water in the middle. Some people go, "Hey, I got an idea. Let's hide in the water."
And that's a good idea, if the flames are coming.
But it was also October in Wisconsin. So some people jumped in the water and they survived, but other people died of hypothermia.
I talked about that on a previous episode about ghost boats, where the boat was on fire on one end, and it was covered in ice on the other end.
It was going down the Tagahoochee or whatever. That you had your choice. You could either burn or freeze to death.
And that was the same thing here. You could jump in the water and risk freezing to death, or you could stay on land, and it was 100% chance of burning.
Now there was one anecdotal story. A young girl saw a cow jump in the water, and so she jumped on the cow and held onto its horn until the fire passed.
I think that story is totally fake, because I don't know how good swimmer's cows are. Plus I'm a little iffy whether or not cows have horns.
Anyways, they might, but I don't think they're strong swimmers. I don't think that is a skill that cows are normally known for.
Now, this was tragedy, obviously. And there's not a lot of funny stuff and a tragedy.
However, I did read a story about a man, his neighborhood, went up in flames. His house went up in flames, and he ran into the smoke to save his wife.
He didn't slip on banana peel. It's not that type of funny, but that actually would be pretty funny too.
But he runs into the smoke to save his wife. He grabs her, he picks her up, he runs out of the smoke, he runs down the street, he gets away from the fire, looks down.
It's not his wife, it's another random woman, and he began wailing. Wailing, because he knew that meant that his wife died in the fire.
Now, that sounds like something he would see on a loony tune. Bugs Bunny runs, well there's no loony tunes where a giant fire kills everybody, but Daffy Duck runs into a house to go rescue.
Does he have a girlfriend? Well, it's Danny Duck. And instead he runs out and he's holding Bugs Bunny in a wig, and he hears the horrible cries of Danny Duck dying in the flames.
And then they cut to just a roasted duck sitting on a plate and he's wailing. I call BS on that story too. It sounds horrible, but I call BS because how would that story be related to anybody?
Either the guy is sitting in a bar and he's like "Yeah, you know the biggest regret of my life." One day I ran into a burning building and saved the wrong woman.
The other people at the bar would be like "Well yeah, that's kind of sad, but you saved a human life." So he wouldn't tell that story.
I don't think the woman would tell that story because then she'd be like "Yeah, one day I got saved, but he saved the wrong woman. I should have burned horribly in that fire."
And I don't think a bystander would have known what was going on. So there's really no one to relay that story. I think it's, again, anecdotal.
But, another note, before I get on with the conspiracy theory, because I'm not just going to talk about people dying horribly in fires, the government, so everyone was more focused on Chicago, but the US government,
steadied the Pashtego fire and they said "How can we make this fire happen artificially as a weapon of war?" So they steadied wind patterns and they steadied burn stuff.
They're like rubbing charcoal between their hand and they're like "Yep, okay, now I know how to build a perfect weapon." They're like "Seriously dude, you just rubbed some charcoal between your hands. He's all tasting it."
Yeah, let's go to the lab. So anyways, when they started building incendiary bombs, they looked at the model for Pashtego to see what would be the best environment to drop them in as far as structures and as far as like weather, what would work best.
Because firestorms happen, but they're kind of rare and they're super dangerous, so it's not like you want to be out there in the field steadying them.
So when they started firebombing Dresden and Tokyo during World War II, they modeled the bombing patterns and stuff like that from what they knew from the Pashtego fire.
If you can take the power of nature and turn that into a weapon, you're nearly unstoppable. That's something Cobra Commander does, but anyways, so the US government did that.
Let's get to the crazy conspiracy thing though. At the time, again, people focused on the Chicago fire and I should also say that Pashtego fire, all of their communication devices burned down, so they weren't able to get out the message that hey, we have this big fire.
So looking back, researchers, armchair scientists, things like that, came up with a theory. They're like, how could you have these huge fires all happening on the same day, starting on the same day, across such a large geographical area?
If they were closer, you could say Embers from Chicago went to Michigan and Embers from Michigan went to Pashtego and there was even more fires in America that day, but none of them hit that level.
So people started to come up with a theory, meteorites. Now, at the same time, there was this comet that used to exist, it's completely dead now, but at the same time, there was a comet that had been flying around, it showed up every six years, it was called Bela's Comet,
and every time it got back, it got a little more small, broken into two, and then broken even less and stuff like that.
But 1871 was when the comet was supposed to come back. Now, they hadn't seen it the past two times, I believe, that it had come by, and so scientists were like, oh, it must have completely broken up, because we already knew that it was starting to fragment.
But the theory is, is that chunks of it crashed into Earth, and the pushback, and started these fires. There was basically like a shotgun blast of fires hitting across America.
The pushback, the scientific community, has said, interesting because there's a lot of dispute, and then the other people have pretty good arguments.
The debunkers are saying, well, meteorites aren't hot when they hit the ground, you can actually walk up and pick one up.
Now, that's a lie, because I saw the blob, and you can't touch those rocks. Actually, wait, no, that one was super cold.
That's not right, because I've seen other movies where the rocks come down and they're super hot, and they go, ow, actually no, even those movies, they go, ow, it's so cold.
Anyways, scientists point one, they come down, they're so cold, I saw the blob, it's too cold to touch.
But the pushback, the other guys were saying, the commentarians will say, they're saying, well, that's true, but it's only cold a millimeter deep,
and it's only cold if they're of a certain composition, so we don't know for sure that all of them do this,
but the ones that people run up and touch, or the ones that contain blobs, are cold, however, they could be hotter.
So the debunkers go, well, comets are ice, so it can't actually fall down and set fires, so another point, debunkers.
The commentarians said, actually, we know that the Beale Comet passed through an asteroid belt and started bringing asteroids with it,
and we don't know what those were full of. They said they could have been full of methane, which would be explosive,
or this other chemical that I don't remember, started with an A-C-E, that is also explosive.
They said, the comet itself may have disintegrated, it may never have shown up to Earth,
but it threw these other asteroids at us like a shotgun, and they just hit across America,
and people at the scene of the fires said preceding the fires, you saw fireballs coming down.
Now, I take that with a grain of salt, because they probably had a lot of smoke in their eyes,
and really the chances of them looking up and then seeing a bunch of fireballs coming down,
I think probably stuff was on fire, and they may have seen fire stuff, but who knows?
Because they don't know why so many fires started on that same day,
and what's interesting is a lot of the debunking articles were like, it was really dry, it was a dry season, which is true,
or is the month of October well known for having a bunch of fires?
I mean, I guess we had all those wildfires in Los Angeles, not more than a couple months ago, but I don't know.
I think about it, it was cold enough in the water that you could die of hypothermia,
but you could also have a massive fire going on on the shore, so that's where the temperature thing kind of throws me off.
So did the breakup of a comet cause these massive fires? Can it happen again?
I don't have the answer for either of those questions, but I think they're interesting questions,
and I think it's crazy that all these fires, and again, I just highlighted the three of them,
there were a lot of other minor fires, and in Canada, but there was in multiple states, like I think Iowa had a fire,
like you had this stuff, this big circle, not close enough that embers could fly from one state to the other,
but close enough that if nature took a giant shotgun and filled it full of asteroids and comet bits and just went pfft,
close enough to do some serious damage.
So who knows? We won't know actually until it happens again, and hopefully it never does, but we will see.
DeadRabbitRadio@gmail.com is going to be our email address, you can also hit us up at facebook.com/deadrabbitradio.
Twitter is @jasonoeparpenter. DeadRabbitRadio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast.
You don't have to listen to it every day, but I'm glad you listened to it today. Have a great one, guys.
(upbeat music)