My home may become the setting of a new horror movie as I've realized something is
living in here with me and
Then we meet a man who during the times of COVID
Does not wear a mask outside
But what happens when the voices in his head tell him he has to?
And then we meet a young woman who was simply trying to get a good night's sleep
Instead she wakes up and finds herself surrounded
In a darkness blacker than black today on Dead Rabbit Radio
Hey everyone welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host Jason Carpenter
I'm having a great day. Hope you guys are having a great day too
Hope you guys are having tons of fun out there in the sun or in the snow
Or maybe you're in like a little igloo, but I hope you're having fun no matter where you're at
Someone who always has fun someone who always brings the party going to the igloos coming into Dead Rabbit Command right now is one of our
Thanksgiving livestream
YouTube donators give it up for Nicole Magenta everyone give a big round of applause for Nicole do a little bow
If you can't support the patreon that's fine too. I totally understand that just helps spread the word about the show really
Really helps out a lot now you guys have heard the intro
We got a ton of stuff to cover this episode so Nicole
I'm gonna toss you the keys to the Dead Rabbit Dune buggy. We're leaving behind Dead Rabbit Command
We're headed all the way out to my place
Nicole driving us out over the dunes back to my place apparently I live in the Sahara so I've lived here for about 11 years in this place and
In those 11 years, I have never I've never written a mysterious word on my wall and then repaint it over it
I've lived here for 11 years and about three days ago. I'm sitting here. I'm hanging out and I look over and I see
clearly a
Word written on my wall that's been painted over
Starts with an S can't see the other letter looks like maybe a T in the middle
That's larger than the rest of the word can't see the letter after that and then the last letter appears to be R five letter
word S maybe a T and an R and
I'm looking at that and I'm thinking here's the logical explanation. I
Just recently replaced three light bulbs in my apartment which right there
I never even made the connection that that could be paranormal related because electrical right I just replaced three
Light bulbs in my place in like the past week and I replaced old CFL ones with those new LED ones
So the lighting has changed in the apartment
and
So the logical explanation was this was written here before I moved in and I never really saw it with just the way the light
Interacted with my place
Now that if she's light bulbs I can clearly see it plus I used to have more
I used to store more stuff on that side of the but I don't anymore
But I stopped storing stuff there a couple weeks ago. So why is it appearing now?
That brings us to the paranormal answer right that brings us to the paranormal answer
I've talked a lot about my apartment being haunted on this show
I'll try to find some episodes to put in the show notes
But I've mentioned it so many times about my apartment being haunted, but it's been a long time since I've had anything
substantial happen here
But like I said, I was talking to old friends and I said hey, do you recognize this on the wall?
And they don't they don't remember seeing that before
So did something right on my wall did something some force come in and right on my wall
And I got to say when I looked over at it. I immediately knew what that word meant. I immediately was like are you kidding me?
Because it's either a trick of the light it could be absolutely nothing could be a painter drying off his paintbrush
It could be always have been there and it painted up this word back then which would still be concerning
I'm looking at that and I go if it says anything that says Seder
saty r which are the half-horse
permanent erection nature gods that
Just ran around banging animals and women and I swear I swear out of all of the paranormal creatures
I could possibly meet
That is the low that's the lowest I do not want to hang out with the dude with a permanent erection
I'll let me back up here. I hope he just wants to hang out right?
He's manifesting into this universe with a giant horse erection. I'm out. I'm leaving
So you only get one good horror movie in you right like you never hear about anyone who escaped from the serial killer and then
Got got trapped in a haunted house and had to do an exorcism you get one good horror move
So people get none and that's probably the best thing
But if you are gonna have one you get one can my horror movie not be
Come on movie not be about a Seder running around my apartment
That'd be so annoying. Maybe it's a Harry and Henderson's thing
Maybe we teach him how to and maybe teach him how to not bang animals and random women and he teaches us
the values of love
How much he loves banging animals in random women?
So anyways, I will keep you updated on Seder gate if the word continues to appear then
Moving if I start to make horse noises very very accurately on this podcast
I might have been taken over by the Seder, but I will keep you guys updated on this possibly totally natural phenomenon or a
Very disap... very very disappointing haunting. Nicole, I'm gonna go and attach you the keys to the dead rabbit dirgeable
We're gonna say goodbye to my place. See you later, bro. And take us up up and away and we're headed out to
a small town in suburban America
The reason why we're headed out here is I recently came across this post online
This person starts off I say and I want to get all the political stuff out of the way
I'm neither pro mask or anti mask
But this story involves masks, so just I just want to make it clear to everyone
I do not care about your opinion on a mask this story involves masks. So that's how the poster of this terminal plan
Layed it out. I don't care about your opinion
I'm let me just talk about masks for two minutes. They go on to say so I have a mass exemption
That's why I really don't care about it. I can't wear one anyway, so I'm constantly having to deal with that
So what happened was a few weeks ago this guy. Let's call him Terry
So Terry explains the story a couple weeks ago
He's sitting at home with his mom and his dad just hanging out watching the old boob tube
They actually were probably all doing their own separate thing with headphones and smart devices, but
He's sitting there and all of a sudden he hears a noise coming from the kitchen and he turns and he looks and the kitchen is empty
He's just staring off in there
What he hears is the sound of a group of people talking in his kitchen his empty kitchen
He looks at his mom and his dad and they don't seem to be bothered by it. It's almost like they can't hear this very very loud
conversation
Now Terry can't place what the voices are saying
He just you know how you kind of hear that rumble like when you're in a club and you're in the bathroom
And you can still hear the noise from the club on the other side of the wall. It's like that
He hears this sound. He can't understand what they're saying, but he knows their sound and
He said it sounds like it was coming through an old PA system. It wasn't clean. It wasn't crisp
It was staticky crackling
But it was voices
On December 3rd 2021 so just a few days ago for us Terry sitting in his computer working
And he hears a voice a singular voice this time
Whisper in his ear
It's a voice he recognizes as someone familiar but
He can't place it
He's heard it before but he doesn't know who it comes from and this voice says clearly in his ear
Wear a mask
He didn't have his speakers playing he had no headphones on he was sitting there quietly in his room and he heard a voice go
wear a mask
Now
This thread after he posted this it immediately became what he tried to avoid it became an argument over
Masking and mask mandates and pro-mask and anti-mask and
He wrote tired of hearing about that we just want you wrote ghost stories even when we're reading them online
So but that was what they were trying to avoid that's what happens
But then a lot of the other posts and I will agree with this a lot of the other posts were
You might want to go to a doctor and get that checked out and I agree even though we talk about the paranormal when you do have
Concerns about your sanity or your hearing voices or maybe you think you're sane, but you are hearing voices are hallucinating
Yeah, it doesn't hurt to go talk to someone. I can almost guarantee that it's stress. I when I'm really stressed out I hallucinate smells
Auditory hallucinations happen. I will smell raw garbage raw
smelly sewage
When I am
Really really stressed out first thing I do is look make sure there's no Arby's around me and I go okay
So it smells not coming from there. It must be
Conn's there's no other place that smells like raw sewage other than my imagination and America's least favorite roast beef restaurant
So it's probably stress you can you can hallucinate voices and stuff like that get it checked out
But looking at the conspiracy theory angle here
I recommend getting checked out before you listen to the next five minutes of this podcast because I'm gonna go real deep into some
paranoid
delusions
You could go with a dystopian
idea
That this is the first test of a system to beam messages into the people who don't do what the government says
Like what if he's not the only one experiencing this?
auditory hallucination
What if the government has now realized everyone who's not doing what it says and
They can beam these messages into people's heads
Until they follow what the voices say
Far-fetched. Yeah, would the government do it over masks? No, but if you were simply testing out the technology
Just to see what the long-term ramifications are
What better time to do when people are already fearful
So you monitor so many see they're not wearing their masks in this sector of town and that sector of town the amount of information
Private companies have on us is mind-boggling and the government just scoops that stuff up. They know where we're at
They know what we're wearing. They know what we're doing
And by all appearances they tend to leave us alone, but what if that's not the case like what if this is a trial run?
There's been a long-standing
Long-standing history in the conspiracy theory community in schizophrenia, and I'm not saying that as an insult
I'm not saying schizophrenics who are conspiracy theorists or conspiracy theorists who are schizophronyx when deep conspiracy lore
There is a lot of talk
I don't know how much proof there is proof is a slippery word in conspiracy
But a lot of talk that a lot of people who are quote-unquote crazy are driven crazy by the government or private institutions
There are they hearing voices because they have schizophrenia or do they have schizophrenia like symptoms that are induced
by a powerful adversary
That's classic conspiracy theory lore going all the way back to the 60s where when you got metal fillings in your teeth
You could pick up Russian radio waves like that was a common trope
That's how you trolled conspiracy theorists back when I was growing up 80s 70 80s 90s stuff like that
The tinfoil hat and the picking up the radio waves on their teeth. Oh when I said that I know a lot of older listeners a lot of listeners my age
They go I remember that that was really popular now. It's a flat earth
You're just a flat earth there are things like that Q and I you're just a Q and on guy
And that's how they dismiss you back then it was you get radio waves from the Russians in your teeth. So
The idea of hearing voices is it a I'll tell you this right now medically if you do hear voices
Please go get it checked out. I'm not saying that the government's trying to take you over
I'm saying definitely go get that checked out 99.99%. It's a medical thing that can be treated. I want to make sure I say that
But the other point zero zero zero one percent is this and this guy's a test for that
And we can also be we can have our conspiracy cap on and be a little more optimistic
It's possible that by not wearing a mask this particular gentleman may be
Going to catch something in the future and it's a time traveler or an angel, right?
I mean, I guess that's kind of I explain this entire dystopian future. I'm like or angels
It could be a warning to for him to wear a mask for an upcoming event
Maybe there'll be a maybe there'll be a very vicious pipe fight going on and he will choke on the cream
Unless he has that mask on so I don't know it's probably just a stress
I would recommend going to the doctor if you if you do start thinking the government's talking you
I hope that I didn't put it in your head and be prepared for that pipe fight Terry
I think was your name that I gave you
But whether it's biological or paranormal or more time traveler or an angel
Definitely an interesting story. Nicole. I'm gonna toss you the keys to the world famous carbon recovery
We're leaving behind this boys bedroom. We are headed all the way out to blue Springs, Missouri
On September 25th 1981 in blue Springs, Missouri, there is a 15 year old girl trying to fall asleep
It's 10 p.m. The Sun has set
Little owls are like hanging out on trees doing their thing this 15 year old girl will call her Margaret
Now I hate that name this 15 year old girl will call her
Michelle
Michelle is laying in bed. She's trying to go to sleep and she hears a sound coming from her closet
She's she's trying to fall asleep and it sounds like there's a squirrel in there. I don't know much about Missouri
I barely know how to pronounce it, but
That's super bizarre if that's that's not normal in any other part of the United States, right?
I'm not the only one he's never woken up to a squirrel in my closet and
To not be surprised because she just goes on I'm gonna go back to sleep
If I found a squirrel in my closet, we would become the best friends, dude. I would be feeding him nuts
I'd be like getting like peanuts and stuff
I'd be getting him like walnuts nuts
He never had before almonds and we'd like hang out in the closet all day long back
That would be dope and he'd be one of those pets that you wouldn't have to like potty train because he would go
outside and poop outside and then
You also sew my clothes you can mend to my jacket with his little tiny sewing hands
So I would jump up with joy if there was a squirrel in my closet
Even if I was trying to get to bed, but she tries to go back to sleep and then she starts to hear the sound of paper crinkling
There's more like the matrix disintegrating but she's hearing that sound and
She realizes okay squirrels
Jason has a squirrel fetish. She watched too much rescue Rangers back in the day
But she goes squirrels aren't squirrels aren't known for their paper crinkling abilities
And at that point she begins to hear voices in her room and actually didn't plan this
I sometimes pull these stories randomly. She all I did not plan that she also hears voices like it's a big party going on
But this is not coming from the kitchen or somewhere else. This is coming from her bedroom
now she's laying there on her
left side and
She's kind of looking into the left side of the room. She's laying there and when she hears all of these voices
She's thinking about getting up and walking to look out the window because she's thinking it must be coming from outside
Obviously there's nothing in her room and
Right as she's thinking that right as she's thinking about getting up off that bed. She hears of I didn't I forgot these stories are so similar
Right when she's thinking about getting out of bed. She hears a voice clear as day in her right ear
It says a whole sentence, but she only understands the last two words the gun
She immediately rolls over to face the noise within a split second she's in a pitch black void
She's flat on her back and her right arm is extended all the way out and up
She's completely paralyzed
She says the room is so black she looks up and she can't see the tips of her fingers
Her whole body begins to hum with a painless electrical cure and
She starts to levitate off the bed
She's spinning around
Right this part sounds kind of fun other than the horrible things that are going on she begins to slowly spin like counterclockwise
above the bed
So as far as she's concerned, she's an absolute pitch black void at this point
There is nothing around her, but she feels her body slowly spin around and
Then once she is realigned with the bed once the head is aligned with a pillow
The paralysis is done and she falls to the bed her body still feel without electrical current
But she can move and the first thing she does is she grabs her phone
Grabbed her landline phone. This is back in 1981 and when she picks it up. It's a dial tone. It doesn't work
Michelle jumps off the bed and is now standing in this void
But it still feels familiar to her it still feels like her room
So she begins running towards where she knows the door is and when she gets to the door
It's gone
Instead is a pitch black tunnel leading into oblivion
Michelle steps backwards and looks at this tunnel that is so
Black so dark so devoid of anything
It is blacker than the void that surrounds it. It is impossibly dark
Michelle screams and
Her voice is nothing but an electronically distorted vibration coming out of her body
*Dramatic music*
She throws her hand over her mouth in shock
No, no one intended. She throws her hand over her mouth in shock
And then she's back in bed
Laying on her left side
The room has returned to normal
Her voice has returned to normal
The time is 10 10 p.m. I
Got a story from think about a docs calm one of the best repositories of UFO paranormal lore
They got it from the National UFO Research Center, which also is compiles all this information really really good database
If you're into this stuff, which you should be because it's totally awesome
So this is the third time on this show
We have covered a similar story about someone waking up in their room being this pitch black void and I'm
It's that's really interesting to me
It really really is and there have been other black bedroom stories have come across recently that I haven't covered because it's kind of just the
Same thing we've talked about and I'm starting to wonder how common this event is
Now fair enough. They could just be dreaming. It is a phenomenon called the black bedroom
It takes place at night in bedrooms where people are known for sleeping and dreaming. That's a true
But we've now covered three stories on this show about people who get up and they're moving around their own bedroom
And it's pitch black. They can't see anything and the walls seem impossibly far. They can't get out
I'm starting to wonder how common this is
Because this shows
just how
This is a common theme this week
We talked on Monday about how the giant came to the vulgar region in Russia and it was making the people feel sad and it was kind of
Affecting their moods and it was causing miscarriages and I said then that shows how powerless we are in the face of these beings and
This kind of good. I don't know why I'm finding these stories all of a sudden
I don't know why they're popping up
Maybe it's to warn me that I will be powerless to stop the satyrs lust
But we had this story now as well
Where there was nothing she could do to prevent this
Once it was in action everything was moving so no pun intended like clockwork that there was no way she could break out
Until they wanted to let her go
She's lost in this void she can't speak she can't feel she can't see
Powerless powerless
But one thing I didn't intend was the similarities between the two stories
So let's put on our conspiracy caps and wrap it up like this
What if other people who are trapped in these black rooms?
One common theme among these black rooms is that you can't get out of them. You can't find the door
But what if some people do and they walk through that?
unbelievable blackness
Into eternity
They may show up that they just died in their sleep
Their lifeless body still laying in bed. They went peacefully
But what if a darker answer is still out there as
They fly through the void
Screaming in electrical pain
Their voices are heard
Across the globe
It's the sounds of madness
The sounds of humans crying out
Lost souls seeking new lost souls
Misery may love company
But madness
Demands it
DeadRabbitRadio@gmail.com is going to be our email address
You can also hit us up at facebook.com/DeadRabbitRadio
TikTok is @DeadRabbitRadio
DeadRabbitRadio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast. Don't have to listen to it every day
And I'm glad you listened to it today. Have a great one guys
[Music]
[MUSIC]