A trio of short ghost stories from an otherwise beautiful part of the country.
And then I tell you about one of my own personal ghost hunting experiences and how it almost
ended in tragedy today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Carpenter.
I'm having a great day.
I hope you're having a great day too.
I always say I'm having a great day.
Mentally I'm having a great day.
I've been in a lot.
I woke up man.
I was sore.
My leg hurts.
My back hurts.
My neck hurts.
I don't know what I was doing in my sleep last night but man everything is just super
stiff.
I've been using some CBD salve.
You know it has like the THC and the CBD in it.
Everyone's like oh it's perfect.
It's so great.
You just put it on your skin and all your pain instantly goes away.
It's great.
It's okay.
There's my sales pitch for it.
It's just not what I thought it was going to be.
I thought it was going to be a little bit stronger but you know I guess any port in
a storm right.
So as I twist and turn my body trying to work out the kinks let's go ahead and get started
with the first story here.
Now the first story we're still in ghost week so we got some cool ghost stuff for you.
The first story is we are going to Santa Barbara County.
Now Santa Barbara County is in California and that's pretty much all of the intro I'm
going to give it to you because I don't want to get into the history of Santa Barbara County
because it's not really that interesting.
It might be.
I don't know.
But actually was there a Saint Barbara?
I thought Barbara was a woman's name and I thought saints were men.
Maybe I should look into that.
But I'm not going to right now.
We're going to take a look at a couple stories here.
One of them is terrifying.
Actually no two of them are terrifying and one of them is tragic on a metaphysical level.
So first we're going to visit Santa Cruz Island.
So we're going to hop in the Dead Rabbit Robot.
You take an oar.
I take an oar.
Shhhhhh.