a bus that wanders the streets of Philadelphia, but only picks up those who really need its help.
And then we take a look at one of the first cases of cattle mutilation in American history.
Did a rancher named Alexander Hamilton actually see an airship abduct a cow right in front of him,
only to dispose of the carcass the next day, today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host Jason Carpenter,
I'm having a great day. Hope you guys are having a great day too. I'm still on vacation,
I'm still using my travel mic here. Seems to be doing pretty good, but yeah, I pretty much just
slept today. I've been thinking, oh dude, when I'm on vacation I'm gonna do so much research,
I'm gonna get so much stuff done. I've really just been sleeping and playing Mad Max, the video
game Mad Max, which is pretty cool. I like beat 'em up games. There's not many of them out there,
but I'll wake up, I'll play Mad Max for a couple hours and I'll be like, okay, now I'm tired,
I'm gonna go back to sleep. And when I wake up, I'll do the show, I'll do so much reading for the
show. Then I usually wake up, eat lunch, and take another nap. I don't like being this unproductive,
I like being a productive person. But tomorrow, tomorrow I'll get so much research done for the
show dude, so much. But that being said, I do got two great stories for you today. The first story
is a really interesting one, and I'm gonna take you along the path that I took when I found it.
So let's go ahead and hop on board the Carpentercopter because we're going to Philadelphia,
Pennsylvania. It's always sunny in Philadelphia, is the new season coming out? I usually had new
episodes ready to watch with my brothers before I came out here. I guess they're taking like a
year and a half off now. Anyways, let's hop on board the Carpentercopter flying over to Philadelphia.
And we have to land, we can't enjoy this story from the air, we have to kind of get down. So we
land, we're walking on the streets of Philadelphia. Now, hopefully you're depressed, or I'm depressed.
One of us needs to be depressed, which is a sad state of affairs. But we're sitting there,
it's late at night, we're in downtown Philadelphia. We're both just like, hmm, little storm clouds
over our heads. Depressed, sad, neither of us know what is coming next in our life. And that's when
we look down the street and we see a bus. It looks like every other bus out in Philadelphia,
but instead of on the sign, on the electric sign that shows where the bus is headed,
it just says SEPTA, which is the name of the bus organization down there. It's like Southeast
Philadelphia Transit Authority or something like that. I don't know, I just pulled that out of my
head. So I'll be shocked. It's probably fairly close, but anyways, so SEPTA is like the bus
organization down there. Now, we kind of look at each other and go, hmm, now we're new to Philadelphia,
but we think it's weird that the bus doesn't list where it's going. We have that much knowledge.
And then we wait for the bus to come to us and it just sits at the corner there idly,
cold, filly winds wrap around us. And then we have to stand up and we start walking towards the bus.
The bus just sits there. But we feel if we don't get to the bus in time, we're going to miss our
chains. So we begin running through this empty street in Philadelphia. And finally we reach the
bus. The door slide open. We step on board and we see the bus driver. He's just sitting there,
cat pulled down over his eyes, kind of staring ahead. We assume we can't see his eyes. He's
looking ahead, cat pulled down over his eyes. And he kind of motions to us to pay. But if you can't
pay, you get the feeling it'll be okay. This bus ride is still for you. And then we just take a seat,
sit down on the bus, we look around. There's a lot of people on the bus. All of them look depressed,
all of them look lost. And the bus just, I don't know what sound effect that was. It's lost in
the bubble gum factory apparently. The bus begins to drive off into the depths of the city of Philadelphia.
I think we need to take it to the maintenance shop. So here's, this is where this story comes
from. This is an urban legend in Philadelphia right now. And pretty much what I said, you'll see a
bus when you're down on your luck, when you think that you can't go any further, you can always go
downtown. It's half the song when you're done. No, that's when you're feeling alone and there's
nowhere to go. You can always go downtown. That's that song, right? It's not if you're horribly
depressed and you don't know what's next. You can always, I think that should be a remix. I think
it should just be about a guy at the end of his rope trying to figure out, oh my god,
my wife left me, my dog's dead. Let's go downtown. Okay, so anyways, anyways,
now the song's stuck in my head and hopefully it's stuck in yours too. That'll make you more depressed.
Anyways, so the story is this bus in Philadelphia, when you're down on your luck,
you'll see it, it will never come to you. You see it, but you have to run to get on it. And when
you get on it, pretty much what I said, and it's full of people, and the story is this, the bus
will drive you around the city for an indeterminate amount of time, but and it, you can't get off
when you want to. It will drop you off when and where you're supposed to get off. And where you
get off is where you can start getting your life back together again. They say when you get off
the bus, you have a vague recollection of seeing other people on the bus and you go, that was weird,
I was on the bus and there was like a politician on there. There's a couple hobos. And even though
you may recognize them on the bus, when you get off the bus, you just have vague recollections. You
could never name anyone you actually saw on the bus. The legend goes that some people never get off
the bus, that they just stay on the bus for the rest of time. And there's even stories that if you
stay on the bus long enough, you'll be dropped back off where you got on, but back in time before
your troubles even began. Some say that there's a bus like this in every major city in the world,
but people don't notice it because it's not the bus they're looking for. And these buses just glide
through the streets trying to help people find the answer that they're looking for, find a new
beginning, find some peace. Now it's interesting, so I've read about that. I was looking up on
Urban Legends, different Urban Legends around America. I came across that and I was like,
this is gold. This is such a great story. And I do what I normally do. I start clicking on the links
and start investigating all this stuff. And what I found out was, this is so interesting, there's a
ton of websites that list this as an Urban Legend in the city of Philadelphia. But what it actually
is, it's a short story. It's a short story on this guy's blog. It's about one page long.
Pretty much entails everything that I told you. And that's it. What? And you're like, well Jason,
thanks for Jason's fiction corner. But this is what's interesting about this. Think about it.
When I told you that story, I'll bet you anything you have the same feeling here in it that I did
reading it. It is so, I don't want to say like realistic, I mean, assuming that in the world of
paranormal, this is something that one rings true to sounds incredibly comforting. It's a very cozy
Urban Legend. And I remember reading it and thinking that's a beautiful Urban Legend. Like,
that's a beautiful kind of creepy story. But like, no one gets trapped. It's something that's
totally beneficial. And because we get lost in the hustle and bustle of the city, whether it's a
major metropolis or just a small burgh, you get used to all the sights and sounds and everything
in your particular area and the idea of something kind of roaming the streets and you never noticing
it. But if you needed it, it would be there. It's a very comforting thought. And the guy who wrote
this wrote it as a short story, the wandering busts of Philadelphia. But I think the reason why so
many people have latched onto it as being some sort of true story is because it's oddly compelling and
oddly believable. We want to believe it at least. I did. I definitely think that this has transcended
the short story. It'll always be remembered now as the Urban Legend, which, you know, kudos to the
author. I didn't write his name down, but kudos to the author for writing that because that it will
now become part of Philadelphia legend. Kids will tell that, maybe not kids, because it only really
appeals to young people, but people in their 20s and older, they can they can appreciate that type
of thing. An ability to either go back in time before your troubles began or if not that dramatic,
just be when life feels like you don't know where to go downtown. When life feels like you're in a
dead end and you don't know what's coming up next and you feel powerless, there's a universal power
out there to help guide you to where you're supposed to go, where fate wants you to. Very,
very compelling story. And again, touches on that thing where I love it when we can find an Urban
Legend and find out where it started. This story will be re- this, I don't see this Urban Legend
going away anytime soon. I only see it growing, actually. And I would imagine in the next couple
years, the author being like, "Well, you know, there's a hint of truth. Like, I could see that
happening because it does sound real and it sounds comforting and it sounds like a paranormal event
you would actually want to have happen in your neighborhood." As opposed to most of them, which
are just ghosts kicking in your windows and stuff like that. I guess most ghosts don't kick in your
windows. Maybe you lived in a bad neighborhood. Actually, that's a good question. What about
like people who are like drug dealers who are shot in the street? Do their ghosts continue to sell
drugs and like break into cars and stuff like that? What if a good maybe 3% of all random vandalism
in cities is attributed to ghosts tagging buildings and stuff? I wonder if you spray painted a ghost
if you'd be able to see them. I wonder, basically, they work on Little Rascals physics. We throw
blanket over them and you see a ghost. Anyways, I'm not going to do a whole segment on this,
but I was reading the news recently. I guess some idiots out on the east coast have figured out that
I don't know if you smoke it or inhale it or turn it into some sort of powder, but people have been
ingesting wasp spray to get high. I've read a couple articles about it and they have the same
quote from some government official saying, "You can do wasp spray once or twice. You'll be fine,
but when you do it the third time you'll have an allergic reaction and you might die." I read
about it a couple days ago and they were like, "Yeah, dude, it's a crazy new thing. Kids are
smoking or doing wasp spray." I can't even say that word right. Wasps. I can't say,
is there a singular, right? Wasp. Wasp. Okay, wasp spray. Kids are doing wasp spray.
Everyone's looking at this official China given press conference. He totally pauses and he's like,
"Can I say it singular? Is there a wasp?" Everyone reporters just standing there with the cameras.
And finally, he gets on with it. "You can do it once or twice, but the third time it'll kill you."
And the first time I saw it was people were doing it and then just today I was reading on Judges
Report that three people have died from using wasp spray as a meth alternative. Apparently,
it like amps you up and causes your hands and feet to swell and I'm like,
knowing a lot of meth addicts. I don't remember having gigantic hands and feet.
Okay, so that's, I'm not going to do a full story on that. And part of me thinks it might not be
true. Part of me thinks it could be some sort of moral panic that no one's actually doing this.
The news articles could be wrong, which has happened in the past. I want to believe that people
aren't so stupid that they're like, "Man, I don't have any meth, but I have all of this wasp spray."
Like I want to believe people aren't that dumb, but I don't know, I could be wrong.
But let's go ahead and move on to our next story. We're going to hop on back on board the carpenter
copter. Come on, get on board. Pulling you off the bus, you're like, "No, I have to go back in
time. I have to go back in time for everything." Went wrong and I'm like, "Get on the carpenter
copter. Get on the copter dude. Just can pull you on." You're like, "No, my future.
They're on the carpenter copter." We take off and we're going back in time.
We're flying around now. We're in 1897. We're flying over Kansas.
Anyways, we still got the song "Downtown Stuck in Our Head" as we're landing.
And we're going to go to a meeting with a man named Alexander Hamilton. No, not that Alexander
Hamilton, not the rapping forefather, but this Alexander Hamilton was a rancher. Kind of a step
down. I wonder if he had any cool dance moves. But we do know that he is a member of this club,
this speaker's club, and he's a rancher and he has a very famous name. Now, he's at this speaker's
club and we're here listening to him tell this story. Now, he's already told this story all over
town. He actually had this story written up as an affidavit with some of his closest friends.
One of them was like a member of law enforcement. One of them was an attorney. One of them was a
judge. It was signed by nine people, close friends of his. It was registered with the postmaster in
town. Alexander Hamilton swore up and down this story happened and we're sitting in this meeting
as he's retelling the story to us. And Alexander takes a sip of brandy. Alexander, did they have
Jack Daniels back then? Alexander takes a sip of whiskey. That's better. Sets it down and goes,
"Well, you know, gentlemen, you've all heard the story, but I'm going to tell it again for our new
friends who just came through a time portal." I don't know why he sounds like Barack Obama,
but anyways, Alexander goes, "But here's the story. Here's the story." So me and my friends were out
wrestling up some cattle. Wait, no, we're ranchers. We already have cattle who don't wrestle them up.
But it was a dark night. It was 10 30 p.m. I remember that specifically. And quote, this is one
of my favorite quotes from this whole thing, quote, "I arose thinking that perhaps my bulldog was
performing some of his pranks, but upon going to the door saw to my utter astonishment an airship
slowly descending upon my cowlot about 40 rods from my house." Now there's two important things in
there. One, what he's saying is, he heard a bunch of noise in the backyard or his friend yard or
whatever. Went outside and he saw what he described as an airship. And he goes on to describe it as a
cigar shaped vehicle, which is one of the classic shapes of UFOs. We have the flying saucer,
we have the triangle, we have cigar shaped ships. This one was 300 feet long. Now he uses the term
airship, which makes you think like a dirgeable. That was the term back then for UFOs or would be a
term for UFOs, an airship. So he walks outside to his utter astonishment. He sees a 300 foot long
cigar shaped vehicle floating over his ranch and he describes as having a dark reddish color.
That's the first important thing to take from that quote. But I also like the fact that he heard a
bunch of noise outside as cattle were running around. And he said, he thought that perhaps my
bulldog was performing some of his pranks. Who does he have an animated bulldog? Does he have that
little bulldog from those Hanna-Barbera cartoons that's like lighting firecrackers and throwing
you on and blowing up cows and stuff like that? He's like replacing their water with oil. I guess
those aren't pranks. Those are more like murderous acts. I think those are more like animal cruelty.
But the idea that he goes, man, my cows are freaking out. May oh, it's just a bulldog
performing some of his pranks. That might be a translation error, even though both are written
in English. Maybe pranks meant something different back then. Although I like the idea of a bulldog
in this story stalking around Alexander, who's basically he looks like a 2D drawing going.
But more importantly for this story, he goes on and he goes, now I looked up into the sky.
Night was all over the place. It was black. And I saw this airship. But oddly enough,
my voice has changed. But in one of the meetings, like that is weird, his voice did change. It's
almost like you forgot what voice he was doing before. Alexander is like, ignore that. I'm looking
over this airship and I see a carriage underneath it, underneath the cigar. And it had quote,
"Six of the strangest beans I ever saw. They were jabbering together, but we could not understand
a word they said." We're all like, okay, okay, Colonel Sanders. That's interesting. It's weird.
The aliens might have changed your voice. Now he says they were jabbering together and they
couldn't understand a word they said. They're also like up in the air. I don't know how many,
people on a hot air balloon, I don't ever look up and go, oh, that's so sweet.
He proposed to her. You can't really hear people. Plus it's windy up there. It's not windy down
where you're at, but the words, when you talk, all your words get stuck on the wind and they go
forward. People can't hear. That might be the worst example of physics. But think about it,
if someone's standing in a blimp, in a windy, windy blimp and you're speaking, technically,
aren't your sound waves being washed away with the wind? The sound waves don't come out like a
bubble. They come out right in front of you and then you're talking into the wind. Maybe the wind
doesn't have anything to do with it. Maybe the fact that you're just 100 feet up can make it a little
hard for people on the ground to hear. Anyways, so he sees this thing that may or may not have been
a blimp, but it was definitely an airship and it definitely had six of the strangest beings I ever
did see. And then a rope falls out of the airship and wraps around the neck of a two-year-old cow.
So the cow's like freaking out. Everyone, Alexander Hamilton standing there, he's shocked,
shocked that someone could last so that good out of an airship. And then the rope starts getting
pulled up and the cow's flipping out. The bulldog's all of a sudden going, "Oh, this prank got a little
too real." He runs off. Cow gets lifted up into the ship and Alexander Hamilton's like, "What?"
and shaking his fist at the airship as it flies away. Now, the next day, that's an odd enough
story. It would basically be one of the first reported cases of a cattle abduction. But the next
day, a farmer over, like a rancher, a couple ranches over, gets a hold of Alexander, sends over
his cartoon vulture to go and tell Alexander, Alexander and his cartoon dog go over to his buddy's
house and they see the cow's hide, legs and head just laying in the field. And the rancher knew
it was Alexander's because of the brand on the hide. Now, Alexander Hamilton swore up and down the
story was true. People were kind of like, "Well, maybe, but I don't know." He ends up getting,
making a notarized statement that's signed by all of his buddies saying, "This happened. Like,
you guys trust me? This happened. I saw this. Judge signs it. Law enforcement guy signs it.
Attorney signs it. Registered with a postmaster. Put into his official record." And everyone's like,
"He saw the very first cattle mutilation in recorded American history. Cow, he's
visually seen a cow get abducted onto an unidentified flying craft and then dropped off the next day
with all of its guts taken out." Now, I talked recently on an episode about this documentary film
crew that, it was a really good episode. It was a really good story too. The truth was almost out
there, I think is the name of the episode on Dead Rabbit Radio. There's a documentary crew that got
invited by the US military to make a documentary on a UFO landing. And then the last minute,
the government said, "No, no, no, we don't want you to do that." And then the documentary did
come out, but it lacked some of the information that the government promised them. In that
documentary, it's hosted by Rod Serling. He said, "There's a story about a man named Alexander
Hamilton who witnessed one of the first cattle mutilation things." I thought, "Oh, that's,
I got a bunch of stuff from them." And I'm like, "That's awesome." So, and that documentary was
released in the late 70s? And I researched it and I found the story. And what's interesting again
is they mentioned this on the documentary. I looked it up. I found out about the story. And
when you look into it though, this is a very controversial UFO encounter. Very, very controversial
UFO encounter. Because what happened was it was all in part, people were like, a lot of people
thought it was actually Alexander Hamilton, the wrapping forefather, but it turns out that it
was just this guy in this rancher. But people still go, "This is one of the very first cases of cattle
mutilation recorded." And we have this signed affidavit from 1897 before the whole UFO flap.
We have someone talking about this. Fate Magazine, which covers paranormal stuff. It's basically,
it's a monthly magazine. I don't know if they're still monthly, but anyways, it's a magazine that
covers like psychic powers and aliens and ghosts and Loch Ness monsters and all sorts of stuff.
Basically, it's like a print version of Coast to Coast AM or something like that.
They are not known as skeptical by any means. They talk about all sorts of weird stuff that I think
is ridiculous. They ran an article about this encounter and they said, "It's fake. The story is
not true." And they say, and people got really, really upset. And they go, "Listen, the story itself
was told by a man named Alexander Hamilton." And even they were saying it, there may be a hint of
truth to it, but here's the problem. Here's the problem with this story. Remember how we landed
in that meeting the first time Alexander Hamilton was telling us this story? Alexander Hamilton
belonged to a group that had speaking engagement. They'd all get together and they'd talk to each
other just like the Friars Club. But this was called, this group was called the Liars Club,
where they would come up with the most ridiculous stories and try to convince other people or
tell them to each other and think about, like, what's the most ridiculous story you can come up
with? And this was one, and so here's the problem is that it is most likely, it is most likely,
that he made this story up for the Liars Club and everyone who signed the affidavit were also
members of the Liars Club. It wasn't like they were walking around town with Liars Club jackets.
Nobody knew that these guys were totally into this thing, but he was a member of a group called
the Liars Club. Fate Magazine also said in 1943 there was an article in a Kansas newspaper called
The Buffalo Enterprise, which said that this woman said her mother knew Alexander Hamilton back in
the day. You know, they were a little freaky. He's wearing this leather jacket with a cow head on it
all of a sudden. He was a man about town wearing this cow skin. She's like, hmm, I'm picking up what
you're putting down. And he's like, you're abducting cows? She's like, no, that's weird. He tells her
the story. And she's like, now that quip makes sense. But no, maybe me and you could have a little
abduction story. I don't know where I'm going with this. Anyways, the point is this woman's elderly
mother knew Alexander Hamilton back in the day and he admitted to her that it was a hoax. And this
girl, this woman says, oh yeah, my mom used to bang Alexander Hamilton back in the day, super freaky
stuff. He's really into leather. And the reporters like this is gross. But he admitted that it was
a hoax. Now that was an article that was published in 1943. He didn't really gain any traction.
Fate magazine dug that article up, also found out this guy was a member of the Liars Club.
And they said this story was most likely 100% made up. It was made up as part of the Liars Club
tradition, which I believe. And so here's this. This is what I think is most interesting about
this story is that if we accept that this story is made up and we'll get into whether and we'll
get into another side of it in a second. But if you can imagine this story is made up, which it most
likely is, it almost perfectly matches up to what we know of modern catamethylations. And so here's
the thing. We've seen this before. Somebody tells a lie. You can you see this a lot with mass panics.
Someone could be like someone could start having some sort of mental breakdown and it'd be like my
skin's itching. I can't saw my skin itching. I can't oh my skin's itching everywhere. Is there
something in the air? I don't know what it is. I was fine at home. I'm itching, itching. And then
other people in the room will kind of start itching too. So people are fairly suggestible as a species.
This story was believed to be true and a lot of people still believe it to be true.
It was believed to be true though. It wasn't disputed at all for over 100 years. What are the
chances of someone making up a story and then it perfectly matching modern day alien abductions?
It's it's quite unlikely. What the more possible, what actually the more logical answer is,
is this guy made up this story and then other people basically when they came across bizarre
encounters in their own farms or ranches. You remember the story their grandpappy told them
about a cow getting pulled up into a UFO dumped off the next day. And then that rancher tells that
story and says yeah my cow they found just found his guts hanging out or all blood was drained from
his body or whatever whatever the thing is. It is most I kind of mean relation is one of those
things that I really have a hard time believing in. I do believe cows die obviously they're not
immortal beings. And you could come across the cow's body and be like that's weird.
Like that's not a normal wound for a cow or that's weird that this may a lot of times too they'll
say the body was drained of blood. How does the farmer know that there's absolutely no blood in
the body? None. Zero. None. Because there's a big difference between being drained of blood like
having blood drain out of you and all the blood is gone. There's a huge difference between those two.
Same thing with 9/11 they'll talk about the building's fall at freefall speed.
But then they'll say they fell at near freefall speed. Huge difference between the two things.
Sorry to throw the 9/11 thing in there. Huge difference. Freefall would suggest internal
detonations. Near freefall would suggest structural damage to a building. And the building's fall at
near freefall speed. But to the average person you just hear near freefall you think whoa that's
super fast. That's super fast. Same thing when someone says they're drained of blood sometimes
they'll be specific. When someone says drained of blood you would assume there's no blood left in
the body. Sometimes they'll use they'll say there was no blood left in the body with these
catamethylations. But how does Joe Hick Farmer know there's no blood? Does he do the dissection
there himself? And if you tell me they're sending these things off to labs to be tested on like to
they take them to a cow corner and he's like yep there's absolutely no blood in this cow's body.
I don't believe that for a second. I think what happens these cows are dying for whatever reason.
Natural causes, heart attacks, poor diet, whatever it is. Broken heart couldn't catch the bus.
It makes far more sense there is a natural cause to it than to think to logically think about this.
An alien craft appears over a farm abducts a cow using technology. This was rope level technology.
This was some great rope level technology because he wasn't thinking tractor beams. That was way too
sci-fi to even imagine back then. But and again that's such a bizarre detail that that matches up to
the stories we hear today but tell me what's more logical. A cow dies of natural death and it has some
weird predator wounds on it. Eyeballs are missing, tongue are missing. There's some blood missing.
Or an alien ship showing up. A vehicle that we don't understand shows up.
Abducts a cow using technology we would consider is magic. And then drops the cow back off within a
range you can find it. It doesn't that makes no sense at all. Why would a UFO abduct a cow,
do medical experiments and they just throw them out the out the UFO near you? Why don't they just
why isn't the ocean why isn't the mariana what is it marinara? No the mariana why isn't that deep
trench in the ocean full of cows? Because that's what you that's what someone would do if if you
go and you kidnap a cat to do medical experiments and on you don't then throw the cat back on the
street to be found unless you want it to get caught. But see think of this is this is the extrapolation
of that. You can't have a story of cattle mutilation if you don't find the cows. It doesn't work.
So logically the aliens would be abducting the cows and either incinerating them,
destroying all evidence that they are ever taken or dropping them off in a location that no one
would ever find them. I.e. two-thirds of the planet no one has the ocean. But that doesn't work for
the myth of cattle mutilation. You have to have the cattle be found and you have to have it be found
by someone who goes that's weird that cow went missing. Or that's my cow. It can't just be a
cow in the middle of the forest. That would be weird if you were walking through a yellow stone
and there was just a cow with drained of blood. If there was just a cow in the forest that would
be weird. So I think that this story really shows that to me at least. I mean I went into it thinking
oh this is interesting but once I found out this was fake I go this is just more proof that all
cattle mutilation stories are fake. And I think they were all based off this original lie. This guy
told this story that he thought was funny and it ended up creating a worldwide phenomenon
just like flat earth. Just like flat earth. Because to a normal person the idea of aliens
abducting cows and then discarding their remains near where the body was taken is ludicrous.
Just like to a normal person the idea of a flat earth is ludicrous. But cattle mutilations are so
widely known now as like a quote unquote legitimate thing. That I think this bodes. I think this shows
what's going to happen with flat earth. Flat earth is just going to keep growing and growing and
growing and growing. Flat earth I really do believe was either a meme like the new resurgence of flat
earth was either a meme or some sort of PSYOP some sort of government psychological operation
to see how stupid people could be. And it's gotten out of hand. I think it's one of those two things.
I think it's like my little pony wasn't a thing until some people decided to meme it into being a
thing and then it became this phenomenon for like four years. I think that's flat earth and I think
that's cattle mutilations too. I think this guy made this story up and it got out of control and
people actually believe it's a legit thing. They find a they find a dead cow. It's nose and tongue
are eaten out. It has less blood in it than when it was alive. Shocker I know. But all that being said
there is the slight chance the slight slight chance that Alexander was telling the truth.
But the problem is is that this is a real life version of the boy who cried wolf. If you belong
to a group called the Liars Club and you see something fantastic no one's going to believe you.
He may have had that affidavit written because he knew people want to believe him. He had to go
that extra step to be like I swear all my lives gentlemen. I swear all my lives this happened
and everyone's just kind of like okay Alexander you know last time you tricked us your dog was
pulling pranks. It's terrible. Oh my cows are dead. He's throwing fireworks at him. It's like I know
I know when I punished good old Rufus I punished him. But I threw some through some turpentine
on him. He doesn't exist no more. But is the thing. This is true gentlemen this is true and
everyone's just kind of rolls their eyes. Now there is a chance that yes this really did happen
to him but the reason we just have to look at his past and go he lied he lied as a hobby.
Why should we believe this one? And if that's the case if that's the case the fact that the
very first cattle mutilation in the United States is tied to a no one fabulous fabulous fabulous
does discredit the whole thing. It really does. I just don't believe in cattle mutilations
other than any sort of human involvement. I just have never bought into the idea of aliens abducting
cattle and then discarding the bodies. I don't have a problem with the idea of aliens or aliens
abducting people or aliens abducting cattle it's just the whole phenomenon of them them dropping
them off with their guts ripped down. So I think that's totally ridiculous. I think people are
finding weird things and trying to figure out a way to explain them. But you have to wonder if
this story was true if this story was true. Alexander Hamilton wakes up that night and he
hears his dog pulling pranks and as he's throwing on his pajamas and getting a shotgun he walks out
into his yard and there he sees that giant cigar shaped craft that rope curl out of the ship and
wrap around that cow's neck and it begins to get lifted up into the sky. You have to wonder
Alexander Hamilton must have been thinking if this story was true Alexander Hamilton must have been
thinking two things. One, this is the craziest thing I've ever seen and two, no one is going to believe me
that this is true.
[Music]
DeadRabbitRadio@gmail.com is going to be our email address. You're going to also hit us up at
facebook.com/deadrabbitradio Twitter is @deadrabbitradio.
Dead Rabbit Radio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast. You
don't have to listen to it every day but I'm glad you listened to it today. Have a great weekend guys.
[Music]