Has an insane man discovered the way to guarantee a ghost is left behind when you die?
Then we travel to a small town to meet a young man whose life is kind of on the skids.
Things just really aren't working out for him.
So when he's taken a little vacation in between jobs to hang out with his friend and his friend's
family, he's hoping it'll be a nice quiet getaway.
But turns out he's about to get into a bar brawl with the cryptic today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
[Music]
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Garvener, I'm having a great day.
Hope you guys are having a great day too.
We got a ton of stuff to cover so we're gonna get started right away.
First off, coming into Dead Rabbit Command right now is one of our legacy Patreon supporters
walking in.
Give it up for Mikhail Malone.
Woo!
Everyone give him a big round of applause, voice them up on your shoulders.
He has a fear of heights, that's why we're doing that.
Mikhail, you're gonna be our captain, our pilot this episode.
If you guys can't support the Patreon and totally understand, just help spread the word
about this show.
That really, really helps out a lot.
And just a quick reminder, May 14th, I will have this.
I built this up like it's some giant thing.
It is.
I will be at the McMinnimin's UFO Festival.
It's the second largest UFO festival in the United States, but who's counting?
In McMinnville, Oregon.
That is where I'm gonna be at.
I'm not a speaker, but I'll have a vendors table.
So I'll be out there.
I'm gonna have a little museum of some haunted items.
We're gonna have Mikhail Malone on the tallest ladder in the city just to watch him freak
out.
And yeah, come on down.
Check it out.
Meet me.
And look at some haunted stuff that I've collected over the years.
Assuming again, there's a big, there's a big flaw to my plan.
I have to transport a bunch of haunted and/or cursed items.
Several hours.
Several hours on a road trip.
So I mean, assuming the car doesn't blow up into flames or get abducted by aliens or
we get possessed by ghosts along the way, who knows?
But assuming we're able to make it there safe and sound with a menagerie, I think we'll
be safe because I have all of these haunted items in my apartment.
And even though I'm constantly suffering from these really weird medical problems, I will
be there.
Assuming that I'm still alive, I will be there on May 14th, 2022.
Check out the vendors area and meet your favorite paranormal podcaster.
Me.
Hopefully.
You're like, "Aw man, I thought ArtPel was gonna be here.
I thought his ghost is gonna float around."
Anyways, that was kind of a bummer way to end my promo.
Mikhail, let's go ahead and toss you the keys to the Jason Jalopy.
We're gonna leave behind Dead Rabbit Command.
We're headed all the way out to Southern California.
There's no haunted items in this car because this car is not insured.
I definitely don't want to get a car accident in the Jason Jalopy.
We're headed down to Southern California.
I believe it's been so long since we visited this man.
I believe he's still in Santa Monica, but I don't have that in my notes.
I've covered this guy a lot.
I'll put the episode in the show notes.
It's everyone's favorite homeless video game designer who wants to wear your skin and attack
your children.
Give it up.
Dude, I don't want to applaud for this guy.
He is a lunatic.
We're not gonna give him a round of applause, but we're gonna drive through, again, Santa
Monica, I think.
We're just gonna walk up to a random hobo and be like, "Are you the video game designer?"
He's like, "I'm whatever you want for five bucks."
We're like, "Oh, okay."
So Max Kramer, he is a homeless video game designer who is just, he's gone insane, but
he also knew how, and he's still alive.
We have, I have so much more to cover about him.
I've really been spacing it out because I don't want to just do this dude.
I got other stuff.
I got Ghosts and Alien Invasion and stuff to talk about.
Max Kramer's still alive and he did have a pretty big web presence with his Jewish car
machine website.
He believes, and in short, that we're all in the simulation.
Well, he's in the simulation.
We're all NPC character.
This is a very common conspiracy theory.
But to be fair, he was one of the first people to be, to be screaming this theory out on
the street corner.
He believes that he's one of the few actual player characters, blah, blah, blah, blah,
blah.
We got a bunch of episodes on him.
I'll put him in the show notes.
The reason why I want to talk about him here is because it's not just, we're not just gonna
look at some of his crazy rantings, we will.
Right?
I found this super bizarre connection.
I've been doing a bunch of research lately and while I was researching it, I kept going
back to this particular set of weirdo stuff.
And let's go over a couple of them I have here.
Oh, and I want to give a shout out to Oogs.
Oogs is the person who originally sent me the Max Kramer stuff.
So thank you so much for sending it over Oogs.
He said he has these random thoughts things and I found a couple that were funny or weird
and recently due to recent research I've been doing, one of them is just, ugh, it's terrifying.
But let's look at one of the weird ones first and strap in because this weird one is, okay,
so here we go.
This is one of his random thoughts.
I know I have odd random thoughts, right?
But this one, this is one of his random thoughts.
What if a female sex organ of an insect was, you're like, just stop, I don't want to hear
what a crazy homeless person, I don't want to hear the rest of that sentence.
I don't want to know what a crazy homeless person thinks about female sex organ of an
insect, you're like, nope, I'll be back tomorrow, click.
That is important for the rest of the sentence, I don't know.
What if a female sex organ of an insect was transplanted into a male human's body to give
birth, you stuck around that long and you're like, nope, still don't want to know, you
came back from the podcast and you're like, oh maybe this is a short segment, nope.
What if a female sex organ of an insect was transplanted into a male human's body to give
birth to grasshoppers?
Would the offspring, let me stop right there, let me stop right there.
The real question is, my random thought would be, first off, are bumblebees as succy as the
loony toons made me believe?
Secondly, I would go, how does a bug have babies?
I'm assuming they lay eggs and I'm assuming the eggs come out of some sort of bug uterus,
but I don't know.
I've never cared to look it up, I've never ever concerned myself with this.
What would happen if you took an insect's sex organ and put it into a human body, male
or female, he specifies male, let's say I took a grasshopper's uterus and put it in
a man.
My first question would be, would that work?
Could a dude be like, oh, nine months, nine months, he's like, come at you little darlings
and then a bunch of little grasshoppers jump out of them?
You choose the body part that they're coming out of, but would that work?
Would the human body be able to provide the nutrients?
Clearly not, Jason, clearly not, but what if you put it in just the right spot?
What if you took it out of the grasshopper right before the eggs were coming out?
Maybe two or three eggs had already popped out and then you like slide it into a dude's
armpit.
These two in fart noises, with his armpit and eggs are shooting out?
That would be my question, is could you do it?
Could you possibly get a grasshopper uterus put into a human male and have it still be
viable?
That would be my question.
And to me, if someone asked that question, I would be like, well, I don't know.
I don't know, and let's never find out the answer.
Let's not look it up.
I don't want to see photos of this.
But that's not Max Kramer's answer, and I might have more abnormal thoughts than like
say the average person, the NPC, you non-player characters, not you.
You're one of the good guys, you're one of the players, but so the rest of those normies
out there, they would never think of a disgusting thing like that.
So would it be viable, would be my question, from like a scientific slash weirdo point of
view?
That's not even, Max Kramer just assumes that it's viable.
That's not even what Max Kramer's finished sentences.
His whole thought is, what if a female sex organ of an insect was transplanted into a
male human's body to give birth to grasshoppers?
Would the offspring consider the male human to be female?
As their mother?
That is so weird.
His question is whether or not it's scientifically possible or viable or how bugs have babies.
It's would the baby grasshoppers think the man was a woman?
That is an interesting question.
We can't only a mad man would ever figure it out.
Would the grasshoppers instinctively think, oh this must be a woman because I came out
of them.
So I mean to say stuff like that's weird, that's bizarre, that's insane, it's almost
underselling it, right?
And he actually, I guess I probably should have given you some more info in the beginning.
He has this weird delusion that he thinks that people are constantly trying to turn
him gay and that sexy black people are actually Asians in disguise trying to turn him gay.
That's all, you'll find those episodes in the show notes and all over his website as
well.
So he has these weird sexual feelings to begin with.
And I didn't think about that when I started thinking about putting a grasshopper uterus
in a man.
I think that's where he's coming from.
How would this affect the man's sex or the way that people view the man?
Would they view where the grasshoppers view was a woman?
I mean that might be part of his sexual hang up as well.
He's constantly talking about black dudes trying to trick him into having gay sex with them
and then him finding out they're actually Asians.
He's like, "Oh man!"
But that, despite the fact that he talked about that for 10 minutes, that's not the
reason why I really wanted to talk about him.
That was entertaining in and of itself, but that was just one of his random weird facts.
The reason why or, sorry, I misspoke.
I misspoke.
That was not a fact.
That was one of his thoughts.
Please do not ever think, even though this is the number one science podcast in El Salvador,
please do not ever think that I once said it is a fact that you can remove one that
insects have uteruses, but two that you can remove it, put it into a man and it would
give birth.
Not a fact.
A thought of his, not mine.
But then, here's another one that he came up with.
And I read it.
I read like this grasshopper one.
I've had these sitting in my files for like three or four months, because I was like,
"Yeah, it's weird stuff, but you gotta find a good place to put it."
Like, are you gonna put it in the armpit?
Or are you just gonna leave it in the grasshopper?
And I left it in the grasshopper.
I just had it sitting here for a while.
And then recently, I've been going to this website called Shadowlands.net, which is just
a ton of ghost stories, because I think the show needs more ghost stories.
We just don't have enough ghost stories on the show.
So I've been really aggressive about finding ghost stories.
I'm just talking about training grasshoppers then, because I noticed when I was going through,
I was just starting alphabetically.
So I'm going through Alabama's, all these hauntings and things like that.
A lot of hangings.
A lot of hangings down there, a lot of racially, you know, charged hangings, a lot of Ku Klux
Clan, a lot of Southern lynching of Black men.
There's a lot of hanging ghosts in Alabama.
And that should really, I mean, just through the numbers and through the tragic history
of that state, should come as no surprise.
So I'm reading these and I was like, you know, hanging ghosts, hanging ghosts, hanging ghosts.
I was just reading so many of them, but I was like, that's pretty common.
I've talked about hanging ghosts out on Dyer Lane in California.
I've never seen one, but in California, we had, because lynching was also just mob justice
and hanging people, executing people by hanging has been an official mode of killing people
for probably since the invention of the rope.
So Alabama just had them back to back to back all of these, you know, Ku Klux Clan hangings.
They're just popping up.
So, but I started to think about just 30 years of paranormal research I've been doing.
I'm like, this is not uncommon.
Hanging ghosts is very, very, very.
And you think about it because you have a lot of times it's an injustice, right?
It's a mob doing it.
But even when it's a state run execution, there's still just such a tragedy of grabbing
someone dragging them into the tree and hanging them because it's so, so let.
So this is what's super interesting about that.
That's actually a great segue for what I'm getting at.
Max Kramer says this quote, the historical execution of people hanging seems to be a
way for the executioners to be respectful of God.
As if it is as though the victim, one of God's creations, is sent back to him dangling on
a rope, a metaphor of a baby and its umbilical cord.
And I saw that.
I put it, that's gonna be my new thing for my notes.
I put it in the grasshopper, put it in the grasshopper uterus.
I saw that.
I clipped that out with a bunch of other random thoughts, put it away.
But when I was reading all of these hangings, all of these lynchings, right, in Alabama,
where they're using the tree, they're using the tree out in front of the plantation, they're
using the tree on the edge of the forest, they're using the tree, they're using the
tree.
And people to this day say you can go down there and sometimes you'll see a body hanging
from the tree.
I started to think about it and I go, not necessarily that Max Kramer was right, but
he might be more right than even he thinks.
There may be something actually to the act of hanging that seems to bond the body to
the location.
There do seem to be a couple of caveats.
It seems to be related to people being hung from a tree or in a place of residence.
And you go, Jason, where else would you hang somebody from?
Well, this is, I don't, I don't, maybe, maybe I ate too many bagels this morning and I'm
in a carb fog.
But I'm thinking this is so interesting because the state, right, when the government wants
to hang you, they build a scaffold and they hang you, they'll then disassemble the scaffold.
It's like the whole part of the construction of the scaffold is part of the process of executing.
And it's very, very creepy to watch this thing be built over the matter of days.
You know, obviously, like the sentence has been rendered, you know, the date of execution
and you would sit there in your jail cell in your old time in Western town as they're
building a scaffold.
Now when Europe, they might have, because they had, you know, they had these magnificent
cities and stuff like that, they may have had, I know they had like hanging squares
and things like that.
But even then, I don't think you would keep the scaffold up all the time.
You weren't hanging people every single day.
So you wouldn't be like, well, you know, I really liked, I really liked you to have
your vendor booth, but you know, the scaffold and they're like crows are constantly picking
at it and they're getting like pieces of flesh out of the twine of the rope.
I'm pretty sure they disassembled those as well.
But yeah, when the state does it, they'll build the scaffold and then they'll remove
it and there's nothing for the ghost to attach itself to.
But when you're hanging someone from a tree that is alive, you're using this living thing
to take a human life.
It's sucking the energy in.
It's taking the form of this man who, again, in a lot of cases, unjustly hung.
It's just leaving that mark, leaving that psychic mark.
And in a house as well, it would make sense that a haunting would hang around in a house
because it is a place full of life as well.
It could also already be full of a lot of chaotic energy and it's tapping into that
as well.
And then, for the state execution method, the scaffold disappears, there'd be no way
for the ghost to appear.
So just an interesting thing and we do see so many hanging ghosts.
What's interesting is when you look at ghost lore in general, when a lot of times when
like kids die, or this is a really cheery episode for Monday, but kids die, people get shot,
stabbed.
Sometimes the hauntings are left behind with a final scream.
You know, someone gets stabbed to death, you'll hear like a scream at three in the morning
every so often the woman's getting stabbed to death and stuff like that.
But a lot of times you'll, someone will jump off the top of a building, die, and then they'll
see her ghost walking through the hallway.
Or kids will drown in the pool and then you'll see phantoms of the kids running around the
pool.
It's never the kid floating in the pool dead.
But with a hanging, they are almost always still hanging as a ghost.
People burned to death, are seen sitting in their favorite chair, people poisoned, are
seen looking out the window.
But people who are hung are often seen, their ghosts are often seen still hanging.
And I never ever ever really considered that until today.
When I was doing all this research and reading all, I mean it's just such a tragic history,
right, of the south of these issues with people getting hung.
I'm reading all of this stuff and I'm kind of putting this all together and while I was
reading that I was remembering Max Kramer's thought.
Maybe the act of hanging, there's something about it that is, it is so cradle to grave.
We all have an umbilical cord, right?
We are all coming out of our moms, not our breast-offer moms, but we're all coming out
of our moms.
We all are attached with an umbilical cord.
Cisarian, whatever, however you're popping out.
I'm not going to discriminate against you.
What?
Oh man, that's a Cisarian baby.
Don't hire her.
But the umbilical cord, I'm wondering if the cord is severed and we come to life and then
the cord remains as we die.
Is there a connection between that, between the life and the death?
It's so perfectly mirrored.
It's scary how perfectly it's mirrored.
And they always say, right, people who are insane, sometimes they can see past the universe,
they can see past the rules that we all set up, that we all follow physics in a certain
way, we follow this, da-da-da-da-da.
But then people say that, but then you meet people like Max Kramer who wants to wear your
skin and sneak into your house and do horrible things to your children.
And you're quickly reminded that insane people sometimes are just completely insane.
And they say insane things.
But maybe they're half right.
Maybe while they're doing these horrible things to your family, someone like Max Kramer
is so insane he can just ramble for so long that eventually he says something that's so
profound and so terrifying that most of us just missed it.
The act of hanging could be the complete opposite of birth.
And that is why when people die hanging, for the most part, their ghosts are still hanging.
Because if you're going to be a ghost, that might be the worst.
I once said being a bathroom ghost is the worst.
There was a ghost in a Burger King bathroom somewhere in California.
I said this might be the worst haunting.
The worst place to be in a burger- empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty,
empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty,
empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty,
empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty
empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty,
empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty,
empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty, empty