New information involving yesterday's story.
We're gonna go more into detail about a young girl's ghost being spotted at
Nettleton High School. Then we travel to LA to take a look at another specter that
seems to be trying to interfere with the lives of the living. And then we take a
trip all the way out to Arizona. Is there any truth to the story that there is a
building in Arizona that's unique architecture actually reveals when the
world will end. Today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
[Music]
Hey everyone welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your
host Jason Carpenter or I'm having a great day. I hope you guys are having a great
day too. I'm recording this episode pretty early in the morning because this
heat wave that is going on I hope you guys are all beating the heat very well
but someone I know who never gets cold. I don't know why they didn't tell me this.
Everyone give it up for one of our newest Patreon supporters.
Kree MasterCycle. Oh yeah come on in buddy. Come on in. Kree MasterCycle. Kree
MasterCycle is actually one of my friends on TikTok and he has a really cool
channel on there. I'll put it in the show notes. He reviews Cologne. He's constantly
doing these art projects. It's really cool. Something that I'm not aware of
right? I don't go around smelling different things and going like how can I
put that in a bottle? But he has a pretty cool TikTok channel where he's doing
stuff like that. Kree Master you're gonna be our captain or pilot this
episode. If you guys can't support the Patreon I totally understand. Just help
spread the word about the show that really really helps out a lot. Now Kree
MasterCycle let's go ahead and toss you the keys to the new vehicle. I just came
up with this. Give me those keys back. I'm gonna toss you the I'm gonna throw it
at you. The bunny bike. The bunny bicycle. We're gonna get on this. We're gonna sit
on the handlebars. He can't see over us. He's like go ahead and pedal us all the
way out to Arkansas. It's going a journey. That's almost a little way across the
country. Getting a good workout in there Kree Master. Bottling your own sweaty
scent. Yesterday's episode we talked about Neddleton High School. The
Ghost of Raider Gym. And it's so funny. I really really loved that story when I
was editing it. I was like oh this is really cool. Like this is going to be a
nice spooky one. And like I had said in that episode if you haven't heard it
basically a ghost story in a gym. Sightings of a phantom girl. You could
hear people screaming in the darkness sometimes. And then one of the most
unique features was there was a tree. Well there wasn't a tree. Because then this
wouldn't be unique. These students were there late at night. They were hearing
screaming in the gym. And when they went into the gymnasium they saw leaves
falling to the ground. And I go you know it's super rare as far as paranormal
phenomenon goes. To have living organic matter just manifest. We've had coins
manifest. We've had things disappear and reappear in houses. But living matter. No
I said that's rare. I couldn't think of another time that that happened. And I
also said on that episode that I was in touch with. Nettleton television. It's
the student run. Program at Nettleton where they produce two documentaries.
About Raider Jim. About the ghost of Raider Jim. So I was talking to Nettleton
television about it. And then when I finished the episode. And it's so funny.
I don't usually do this. I don't usually do this. I usually just let people find
the episode on their own. But Nettleton television was so good with giving me
information. I thought they might want to know how this turned out. So I sent them
the finished episode. And we got some additional news. And this is weird. Okay so
I send this over and I talked to the teacher advisor Craig. Craig Miller.
Thank you again for your help. And after everything was said and done he goes oh
you know it was a really cool episode. And it was kind of spooky. But some of the
stuff has been confirmed fake. It's very very interesting. They're very interesting.
So let's take a look at this. According to Craig Miller. He said and this is
super and I want to be very clear with you guys because this is just part and
partial of doing paranormal research right. You're going generally when you're
a scientist and you're researching atoms and stuff like that you're like oh I
just read this great paper on how molecules fly around atoms and then you
do all this extra research and then you find out that that scientific paper was
fake. It doesn't happen. No one's like putting fake bones in the ground waiting
for you to dig them up and then you know you're like oh man I thought I made a
new dinosaur. No it doesn't happen but in paranormal research it does happen a lot.
He goes I only kind of know what I've heard but apparently this is so funny
because I said how rare it was to have a tree with leaves. Apparently that's fake.
He goes talking to a former choir teacher. He had heard that some of the
students had made up the leaves detail. Now that didn't happen. He goes I want to
confirm that. He's actually going to do a little more digging but I wanted to be
honest and fair. I just found out this information last night. He said I know
one of the students who initially came up with this story about the leaves
falling and then they said I'll reach out to him to confirm whether or not it was
a joke on their part. So we'll see what comes of that but it's so interesting.
Remember I'm saying this is super rare. I've never seen anything like this before
and it's possibly fake. Probably fake really. I think we can move it out of
the possible. So the probably and then we have the story that the country music
star Moose. What was it? I don't remember his foot. It was Jim Moose. He talked about
that he had seen the ghost. He didn't know it was a ghost at the time. He had seen a
young girl walking through the hallways of Raider Jim. They broke in late at
night and he's watching this girl walk. Apparently apparently that was fake too.
But what's interesting about this is that what happened was they made this
documentary the original one that goes to Raider Jim and then this country
musician. I'll look up his name real quick here. Hold on I got to go into
yesterday's notes but this country musician was watching that original
documentary and then contacted the school and said oh that's so weird. I didn't
know that the place had a reputation of being haunted. I saw a ghost as well. I
saw a ghost back in 1980-1981. His name was Jim Brown. Jim Moose Brown. So
anyways Craig Miller said Moose saw the original documentary then Moose
contacted us. We shot a new update to the documentary and once that documentary
came out someone said oh that was a prank. We pulled on Moose. He was not a part
of it. Years ago we wanted to scare Moose and his friends who broke into the
gym so they dressed someone up as a girl or was a girl. I don't know what the
thing was but it was a fake. They had a friend disguised as a ghost and to walk
around all creepy. Now apparently Moose then heard that story that it was fake
and absolutely denied it. Said no that's not what it was. That's 100% not what it
was. I didn't see a friend. I didn't see someone dressed up as a girl ghost. What I
saw was paranormal. What I find so odd about all this stuff right is that it
may be fake. It may be fake. Right some of the stuff may be fake. All of it may be
fake but I found this in different parts of the internet. And if you were going
to if your objective was to scare Moose and his friends if you listen to that
ghost story all the all the girl did was kind of walk slowly around the gym and
the two other friends never saw it. Just Moose. Now that's more of like a
psychological terror. That's a long con. Right because apparently he never really
told the story to anyone. He might he told his friends hey I just saw someone in
here we're gonna get caught. He didn't even think it was a ghost. He just saw a
girl walking and thought that another student had gotten in there. So what
that's kind of a lame scare. It's weird. So I'm questioning because again I am a
conspiracy theorist. Was what Moose saw fake? That's theory one. Or Moose saw a
real ghost. That's theory two. Or Moose saw a real ghost and there is an active
thing going on in Edelton High to actually suppress the ghost story. So then
they made up the debunking. Here's the thing I'm a conspiracy theorist and by
nature. And so I have to ask myself was the ghost a fake right? Was it a joke? It
wasn't a very good joke right? Because they didn't get super scared. The other
two guys didn't even see it. It's more of like a psychological terror just kind of
walking through the darkness. Not like she chased them away or yelled boo or
anyone jumped out to scare them as well. So you have that. You had a student
prank or Moose saw a real ghost. Now Craig goes listen that at first
documentary those people they were telling those stories. Like he's like I
don't have an explanation for everything. I'm putting words in his mouth. He
didn't exactly say that but he goes you know I don't know what to think as far
as those stories go. Let me pull up his exact quote here. He goes as for the
stories in our original documentary I just don't know. It's like Charlie Daniel
said there's some things in this world you just can't explain. So I don't know
and this is just part and parcel of working in the paranormal research
community. I'm not mad right? I'm not mad. I like that story and I wanted to
update it for you and this kind of makes sense when I go this is I've never
seen anything like this before. That makes me think that now that it was
fake the leaves coming down because it doesn't match paranormal lore. But did
Moose really see a ghost? Is this a cover-up? Are they now kind of backtracking
Craig's? Like come on Meg what are you talking about? My high school? There's no big conspiracy theory going on here. It's so funny Craig was so good at
responding to me even like late at night. There's a big time difference between
Oregon and Arkansas. He was so good at responding to me the back of my head I
thought he might be a ghost. He might be a ghost honing a lab at Nettleton High
School because I was like dang this guy's on top of things and I'm like emailing
stuff at like 10 p.m. West Coast time. So I'm not saying you're a ghost officially
but anyways I wanted to give you guys an update. I do think this story is really
fascinating now that we know parts of it are fake or maybe fake. It's actually a
little more interesting because very rarely do we get confirmation that
stuff's fake and then it kind of lets us go. That's why we never see that in any
other paranormal stories because it was made up. So but we'll see he's gonna get
in contact with a student who talked about the leaves. See if we get more
information on that. Moose is adamant that he saw a ghost. Craig says I believe
his friend who said that it was all a joke. Super super interesting story
nonetheless. We talked about that for a little bit longer than I thought we would
so cream master cycle let's go ahead get you off that bike. We're gonna tushy the
keys to the Jason Jalopy. We're leaving behind Arkansas and Nettleton High School.
We're headed all the way out too. You know what we had enough ghosts. Let's
let's say that ghost story for tomorrow. Go ahead and take that Jason Jalopy all
the way out to New Mexico. Cream master cycle is driving us on. We got the
air conditioner at full blast and we're headed back to the year 1974.
Specifically at September 1974 and we're headed towards a little town no one is
Hobbes. So near Hobbes, New Mexico there's a farm and at this farm you have
this little farmhouse and a couple chickens. You know how the song goes
right. Cluck cluck here to cluck cluck there cows probably I guess there's
different types of farms. Like if you have like a bunch of okra or if you're
growing like wheat it doesn't necessarily Jason come on what are you three? Not
every farm has a cow like there's dairy farms and if you're a dairy farm it's not
like you're like oh it's time to go pull them grapes off the vine. No it's
different types of farms you're like yes Jason I'm aware of how businesses work.
So anyways I don't know I don't know if this guy had a
cluck cluck here and a cluck cluck there it's a farm. We're back in the year
1974 and this farmer is driving his pickup truck home on the road again.
No copyright violation if I make the tune wrong. He's driving this pickup
truck down this dusty path back home and as he's getting closer to his house he
sees a site he's not used to. He's like what I don't have any cows where is that
Moo Moo here and a Moo Moo there coming from. He looks up in the sky
this massive UFO is in the sky just this huge disc is flying overhead.
Jason you really don't learn your lesson you just found out that you did a whole
second on a story that was fake and that just involves someone walking through a
gym now you're having a giant UFO in the middle of the day.
Flying overhead and it's so big that not only has his attention his wife and his
daughter because he's almost home. His wife his daughter and apparently a
neighbor was visiting at the time they came running out of the house and they
looked up and they saw the disc flying overhead as well. Now he's driving his
pickup truck and he's like literally on the path down his driveway
headed home and he's like driving and he has his head like craned out the window
he's kind of looking up at it because at this point it's right over him and then
all of a sudden the bottom of the UFO opens up and this farmer and his entire
pickup truck or beam the board it starts to float off the ground oh no the brakes
don't work steering wheel doesn't work and he starts to ascend into the belly
of this UFO. The wife the daughter and the neighbor are all watching this all
watching this entire vehicle get abducted by a UFO and once the pickup
truck is completely inside the UFO takes off. Apparently the wife called the
police that would be what you would do right you want to be like oh maybe
he'll come back later. She called the police the police investigated this and
according to the story this event was covered up by local authorities this you
if you want to check this one if you want to find out the farmer's name or the
exact date or anything like that you can't the story was covered up by the
local authorities. Now this story I have a sneak and suspicion I talked about the
story before it sounds vaguely familiar but I also read stories a long time ago
and have them in my notes I'm kind of waiting for the right time to talk about
them so I might have covered it before if I did I apologize but I'm iffy on that
and it's fascinating enough that I wanted to talk about it again I got this
story from thinkaboutadocs.com they got it from a book called Situation Red the
UFO siege by Leonard H Stringfield what's interesting is in the world of
UFOology there are a few different factions and this faction the UFO siege is
I really feel under underserved in the sense that the aliens are here to do us
harm the aliens are not here for good purposes you had a big buildup in the
70s and the 80s where the aliens were connected to new agee so I really go
back to 60s 70s 80s the aliens were connected to new agee they're gonna
cure all of our diseases they're going to help mankind ascend to a cosmic
brotherhood you'd see that in books like childhoods end by no one pedophile
Arthur C. Clark all but that episode of the show notes I guess I should I guess
I shouldn't say no an alleged pedophile Arthur C. Clark so as a state doesn't
sue me a childhoods end was about the cosmic brotherhood you see a lot of
that stuff nowadays it's kind of a mishmash where you have the reptilians
trying to take over the world or you know the gray aliens doing cattle
mutilations or abducting humans but you still have a good contingent of the
Gaia calm new age belief that aliens are here to help us and books like the UFO
siege is saying that's not the case that's actually not the case you have
aliens that are trying to do us harm continuously do us harm and I like
showing stories where we are more defenseless against these things right
you would think if you were in a pickup truck you could outrun this thing but
I mean they can abduct the whole pickup truck in front of witnesses in the
middle of the day you always hear the stories the big thing people go of
aliens are real how come they always visit some drunk farmer in Missouri at
3 a.m. there's hundreds of not thousands of stories that aren't that but
that's kind of the easy way to dismiss it it's an easy way to dismiss it and we
have this big push towards UFOs UAPs let's get the military to tell us what
they finally are and when you look at reports like this sue me this report
this reports to you but whether or not a tic-tac UFO was flying around the Nimitz
battle group back in 2017 yeah that's cool right but it didn't
abduct anybody right it didn't abduct anybody it didn't change and I'm not
saying for it to be real they have to abduct people but a lot of there's a
new push there's a new push towards a very dry clinical look at aliens used to
me that there are our space brothers because we were locked into this cold
war and it seemed like we were gonna kill each other and it was up to the
aliens to save us and then as we get into the 90s as the cold war starts to end
basically people stop looking outside their borders and within their borders
for the enemy the enemy within and we became very conspiracy focused and
obviously things like 9/11 even made that even worse so now the aliens are a lot
of them are reptilians they're part of this new world order they're trying to
take over the planet and things like that but you still have the big new agee
movement now you have aliens as the oppressors taking over and then you
have aliens in a very dry clinical way like if a tic-tac was flying around the
Nimitz battle group was it a gray was it a reptilian like it's so interesting
like now when journalists talk about it now it's just so kind of dry the same
way you would talk about oh we're testing a new laser cannon on a plane it
doesn't really go into any of the sociological issues of alien life but
I wanted I wanted to talk about that because again it shows that raw power
of alien life if it is out there and you'll never hear you'll never read
that article on MSNBC.com or Fox News anything like that it's too wacky it's
too goofy it's almost like they're trying to take the sci-fi sheen off of the UFO
phenomenon and they're like here's something we don't understand here's a
tic-tac you know okay who's driving it like what type of alien do you think is
driving it do you think it's C3PO like let's talk because you can't talk about UFOs
without talking about the sociological part of it as well so very very
fascinating this is a really interesting time to be into UFOs to be in the
paranormal because you're seeing more people talking about it but they're
talking about it in a different way than we're used to so very very interesting
story if it's true and if it's not if it's not or if I covered it already I
apologize but Cream Master Cycle we're gonna go ahead and leave behind Hobbes New
Mexico they're like will you help us find my husband we're like nah we got
something else to talk about Cream Master Cycle fire up the carbonic
helicopter we're headed all the way out to Arizona this is a story that just
like the nettleton high school story I started off by finding it on shadowlands.net
and the more I dug into it the better it got that's generally how these things
work right the more you dig into it and if you're able to find more information
about it this story is absolutely insane started with the local urban legend but
by the end of the story you might believe in the legend yourself we're headed
out to Tucson Arizona well near there where you're like oh I have family there
I'm gonna stop and say hi nope say in the carbonic helicopter we're actually headed
out to the area of the Santa Cruz River we're looking for mission San Xavier
del Boc and this mission was built between 1783 and 1797
it was like how did it take so long to build a building it's 14 years people
are just praying in there there's no roof they're like totally getting rained on
it took them 14 years to build this building and today it's a big tourist
attraction like religious tourist attraction I don't think people are
going out there and like taking photos of themselves maybe they're praying and
stuff like that I don't know why a non-religious person would go here I'm
not saying you have to worship Mickey Mouse and go to Disneyland but apparently
people visit it but I don't think it's just random people walking around but
they should actually everyone should stop by this mission everyone should
stop by mission San Xavier del Boc because it may give you a clue of what
the future holds this mission is reportedly haunted by a monk the ghost
of a monk he's like always floating around and stuff like that it's like oh
no one build a roof and it got rainy in here and I got pneumonia and died and
there his his ghost is kind of floating around and then also it's like a mission
building remember in school we had to build those little Adobe missions I
don't know I was in California but we had to build missions for a school
project we had to like make the little Adobe brook not life-size missions
really Jason that was a pretty brutal school you're like making I was like oh
kind of please learn math today they're like no you have 50 more Adobe bricks to
make we'd make little dioramas I remember doing that a lot as a kid this
mission had like different buildings kind of like a mission complex so you
had the main church itself and you have these other outlying buildings in the
same area apparently one of these buildings in the past caught on fire and
a none and five school kids were burned alive at the schoolhouse they tried to
get out they didn't and finish their dioramas the fires come when she's like
nope no one's leaving till your homework stem they're like ah anyways you there's
reports that you can see her ghost leading five children away from that
area it's no longer there the structure is burnt down but the main reason you
know there's other ghost stories as well hearing voices stuff like that but the
main reason I wanted to cover this story this is so cool this is so interesting
is outside of the mission there's this giant facade on the front of the mission
right it's this giant kind of ornate designed a piece of work it's above the
main door and it's it's quite huge it appears to be really big in the
photographs I'd say it's a couple feet by a couple feet I'd say it's probably
bigger than me right and it's all like this ornate work and all like these
little curly thingies and little leaves and stuff like that and then on each
side all they'll be photos in the show notes if that's not enough of an image
in your mind there'll be photos in the show notes on each side because you know
it's like supposed to look beautiful so it's very symmetrical on each side at the
very edge of the left and the right part of this facade is this curly little woo
and inside that is a mouse and then standing outside the woo is a cat and
people it's weird like people have talked about this historically like I didn't
just find this on ghost websites I was looking up the history of mission San
Xavier Dale Bach as well they said we don't really know why the cat and the
mouse artwork is there because it doesn't have any religious significance the
other thing like the main image in the facade outside of all of the little
intricate things is there's a picture of Jesus crucified which is what you would
expect on a church right but the cat and the mouse doesn't really have any
biblical significance the cat is the only domesticated animal that is never
mentioned in the Bible cats were very common in the area because you know like
Egyptians are constantly like had cats around according to Prince of Egypt by
Dreamworks you'd have cats they knew what cats were cats are not named in the
Bible at all so there's no religious significance to a cat and a mouse I
think mice are in the Bible but they're the ones who sewed Jacobs code of many
colors the cat and the mouse has no religious significance why is it there
and this legend popped up basically according to reports the monk the monk
that it kind of has an ominous presence his ghost that wanders the estate he
tells this story the cat and the mouse are symbols of the end of the world if
the cat ever catches the mouse the world is about to end like what like I mean
it's frozen in time it's actually carved into stone and the monks like are you
doubting me I'm literally a spirit I'm floating around in front of you you can
see through me are you doubting me but you can look at these and I was thinking
like oh that would be cool actually move do you see a little ceramic mouse running
around you're trying to feed it ceramic cheese they're frozen in time it's a
sculpture but apparently according to this legend if the cat ever catches the
mouse then the world's about to end which is good news for us because it
would actually take forever for an inanimate object to catch another
inanimate object but I'm assuming as we're coming closer to the actual end of
all human reality the death of the universe due to paranormal means that
cement can move as the demons are pouring out of hell and the angels are
pouring out of heaven there's a massive battle across all time and space I'm
pretty sure that pretty sure that a facade at a mission in Arizona could do
something a little wacky but that's the idea if the cat catches the mouse in the
world's about to end I saw that I really liked it I took a bunch of notes on it I
started to research it I go what a cool urban legend but again as I dug more
into this place this is absolutely insane this is absolutely insane you guys
may be wondering why I have the cover art that I do for this episode it's
the picture of Jesus crucified on the cross right and you're like yeah I can
kind of see that if you guys you guys are driving the car right now that's
what it is but he's in such a weird position if you look at this facade
you'll see that Jesus is crucified but he's not like crucified up on the cross
his hands are spread out and he is them nailed to the cross and then he's in
this weird sitting position like you can actually see him kind of slouched down
and sitting and even that looks kind of uncomfortable because it's like the cross
is in front of him so it's this weird thing so his hands are crucified and
then he's sitting down and his waist goes behind the cross I've never seen
crucifixion like this before I've been to a lot of them I'm actually a 3000 year
old vampire I've never seen crucifixion or crucifixion art like this before so
his arms and his torso are in front of the cross as you would expect but he's
slouching down and then his waist and his legs are like wrapped around the
bottom of the cross very very weird and honestly though when I first saw it
didn't think anything of it I didn't even really notice that that was part of
the motif I was looking at trying to see if the cat caught the mouse as I started
looking into just trivia about the mission I found this website Tucson.com
did an article mission san Xavier del Boc 11 things to know and it was quoting
all these different facts about the mission inside the mission there is a
sculpture a statue of st. Francis Xavier should make sense he's the founder of
the mission and he's sitting in a glass case now what's interesting it used to
be a rumor that it was a mummy usually be a rumor that it was a mummy you have
it definitely get me to go to a mission any religion that has mummies I'm down
you have a certain I'm a worshiper of set you have this statue of st. Francis
Xavier in this glass case and it's just it's weird looking so people thought it
was a walk around with his arms out brains brains are like ah this it was not
originally a statue of st. Francis Xavier originally it was a statue of
Jesus crucified on the cross and what happened was about 50 miles north you
had of the Tuma Kokori mission that was set up in Arizona way back in time but
by 1849 that settlement was constantly getting attacked by Apache raiders so
they had to start moving stuff in their monk hat they're like dude we got to go
so as they were moving all their stuff from 50 miles north way back in the
1800s they had this giant statue of Jesus crucified it broke it broke they're
trying to move it down to mission san Xavier del Bach which had already been
established it was built back in 1797 so now we're 50 years in the future and 50
miles away they're bringing down this statue of Christ crucified and on the
journey his legs break off and they go you're gonna need those you're gonna need
those on a statue of Jesus so what they do is they took that statue and made it
up and like kind of like decorated it and changed it a bit and turned it into a
statue of st. Francis Xavier sitting down so that's the statue that's in there
now so my question to you is this facade that's sitting on mission san
Xavier del Bach this mission that was built in 1797 how in the world did they
design it to show a picture of Jesus with his legs broken off if you look at
that picture the way that he's sitting there's like the crosses blocking his
waist and first off why is Jesus sitting on the cross right that's just that's
just number one why is he even sitting down on the ground but that facade as
far as I can tell that that facade is as old as the mission they have been doing
restorations and things like that but I would be surprised if when they were
restoring this mission they go you know what we should do we should change the
facade to show the fact that Jesus got his legs broken off on this 50 mile
journey
it's possible right it's possible that he wanted to be truthful in their
advertising that our Jesus doesn't have legs you come to mission san Xavier del
Bach but again tonight with Jesus with no legs in the church they turned it into
a statue of st. Francis Xavier sitting down in this weird position because it's
kind of hard to sit down when you have no legs so did the facade tell the future
because the image is clear it's a picture of Jesus on the cross but his
legs are separated from his body there's no other way to read that picture
and I can't think of another picture of Jesus crucified on the cross where he's
sitting like that was it restored over the years to show that it would be weird
to show statues break all the time right if you had a big drawing of Venus the
Milo and then her arms broke off you wouldn't be like great then you would
erase the arms that the art would remain the same did the facade tell the future
about the statue of Jesus being crucified breaking at that same point and if
the facade told that relatively minor fact that something that was gonna
happen 50 years in the future if the facade could detail that could it then
not tell us when the universe is going to end so forget your doomsday clocks and
your green button forget the soothsayers on the internet constantly
talking about two more weeks and the world will end the real gauge to tell
whether or not the end is nigh may actually be sitting in Arizona an image
of a cat trying to get at an image of a mouse frozen in stone it does not
quickly move depending on political leaders it does not quickly move depending
on the geopolitics of the world or the emotions of the person making the
prediction the only thing that can move these items the only thing that can get
the cat close to the mouse would be God himself the only person who can warn us
about the destruction of the universe is the only person who can destroy the
universe
DeadRabberRadio@gmail.com is going to be our email address you can also hit us up
at facebook.com/DeadRabberRadio. Tiktok is at DeadRabberRadio. DeadRabberRadio is
the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast you don't have to listen
to it every day but I'm glad you listen to it today. Have a great one guys!
[Music]
(upbeat music)