Three girls walking on a country road, discover a creature, and possibly a government cover-up.
And then we look at Paul Adams' greatest invention. You thought the Yon Machine was a
magnificent piece of technology/therapy. Today we look at the food replicator. And
you can build it yourself, today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host Jason Carpenter.
I'm having a great day. I hope you are having a great day too. We've got some cool stuff to cover,
some cool stories, but first I wanted to talk about this briefly. We have a Discord setup. A lot of
people have been requesting to get a Discord setup. A lot of people have been requesting to get a
Discord setup, and it is set up now. It was set up by Barfee Man 362 on YouTube, so I appreciate that.
I'm going to stop in every once in a while. I can't promise I'll be there every day just because
I'm always doing research and working my jobs and doing the show, but I will be stopping by. But it's
also a good place for the fans to hang out. I know something that a lot of podcast listeners have
said is said, you know, I listen to the podcast, but I have to go to YouTube to really be part of
the community. So hopefully this will mitigate that. It'd be a cool place to kind of hang out,
be civil towards each other. I think everyone kind of gets along with this group. And so again,
thank you Barfee Man 362. And then I have a buddy, he's Earbud on Twitter. He surprised me today
with a built, he built a desktop computer for me. He saw the laptop I was using because he knows me
in real life. He goes, you use that laptop for everything. And I was like, yeah, this is like,
this is my podcast laptop. This is my work laptop. This is laptop I watch, you know, the office on.
This is kind of what I have. So he built me this super dope desktop computer. It's easily the fastest
computer I've ever owned. And that's what I'm recording the podcast on right now. And it actually
sounds a bit smoother. I'm still trying to fiddle with the audio, the mic volume and stuff like
that. But to me, it already sounds a lot smoother just because it's a better sound card. Still got
my laptop to watch the office on and to do all my research on. But thank you, Earbud. I honestly,
I don't feel like I deserve it. It's this amazing gift that he just dropped off today. And but I
and I told him, I said, really, this will help take the podcast to the next level. My plan now
is to do and it's in the future. It's not coming up anytime soon. But I want to do a video for
Friday's episode. And for the podcast listeners, I know that it sucks when you listen to a podcast
and they're like, Oh, look at this cool thing we're watching in a podcast listener can't see it.
I hate that. I absolutely hate that. So the Friday episode won't be any different to the podcast
listener at all. I'm not going to be like, Hey, now let's watch this five minute YouTube video
while I'm totally quiet. But to the YouTube users, you'll be able to see video. It will also allow
me to do I've talked about doing Twitch. I want to play some scary games, find some spooky games,
maybe even do like like terror readings and Ouija stuff. So I told I mean, this this computer
is exactly I think what the show needed just the technology bump up is so high. So thank you,
your but again, I don't feel like I deserve it. But obviously, you feel that I do and that is very
humbling to me. Yeah, it's just amazing. So I think we're going to see a lot of really cool
technological leaps coming for the podcast. I think it would be cool to play like some spooky
games and talk to you guys on a Friday night. Because that's really my time where I'm not doing
any podcast stuff and I'm not working Friday nights is kind of like from seven to three in
the morning. It's totally mine. Everything else belongs to something. So let's go ahead and get
started with the first story. Oh, fuck. Oh, carbonated water just exploded all over me. And
it's freezing cold. I wonder why I did that. Oh, because it's a block of ice underneath. That's
why it's pressure build up. I think it's going to explode. I got a hair hold on the year 1996.
The country Brazil, we've actually it's funny. We've been to Brazil a lot on this show more
than I would have thought. It's really, really interesting because it's something that's not
normally covered in UFO or Bigfoot or Cryptid or anything allure. Tons of stuff happening down there.
So we're in Brazil once again. And I have no problem with it. I think it's probably a lovely
country. I've never been there. Too many aliens. So this story is actually a request from Gabriel
on YouTube. He was the one who recommended the story for me. It's quite funny, quite weird,
and it has a lot of odd twists and turns. The year is 1996. The countries Brazil were specifically
in a region called or a city called Varghina. Varghina? Varghina. We'll call it Varghina.
I already I lose Brazil listeners every time I do a Brazil episode. But anyways,
we're in the country of Brazil, Varghina. Three young girls walking down the road. It's dusk.
Still a little light out, but it's on that teetering between darkness and day. You guys know what dusk
is. I'm setting the mood. These three young girls are walking on the road. They see something in
front of them that concerns them, not someone. They think that what is walking in front of them
is the devil. They later described this creature as kind of having a wobbling
gate moving unsteadily in front of them alongside the dusty road. It's five feet tall, large head,
very, very thin body, little limbs, little spindly limbs wobbling back and forth.
Had V shaped feet, like a duck's foot. Just kind of an odd detail. Brown skin, large red eyes.
Girls ran away, went and told their mother, "We saw the devil. We saw the devil."
Mom's like, "It's so funny because the mom's like, 'No, you didn't.' The mom's like, 'You girls are
stupid.'" These girls who were eight ranged in age between 14 and 22. Two of them were sisters,
so they went back to their mom's house. They told their mom this story, and the mom's like,
"No, you didn't. That's super dumb. You guys are idiots." But anyways, the daughters convinced her
to just go out and check the scene. "My mom, my mom, go check the scene." So the mother goes out there,
and which is kind of ballsy actually. If I had three daughters and they ran home and they said,
there's a lot of hypotheticals in this one, but if I had three daughters and they ran home and
told me they saw the devil, I don't think my first inclination would be to go out and be like,
'Prove it!' and then to go out into the twilight to find this creature. But anyways, she did.
The mom goes there and she noticed two things. Three things. She noticed a strong smell of ammonia.
She noticed some footprints, which apparently matched the V shaped feet. And there was a dog
in the area. I don't know why the dog is a detail that she noticed, unless she's like,
"Harry the Spy," and she's just like, picking up clues randomly. But the strong ammonia smell
and the V shaped feet do make sense. What happened was that then this panic started in the town.
The story spread very quickly that there was an alien or the devil in town. And I think most
townspeople were like, I think most people in town were like, "Five feet, tiny little arms,
weird, you know, like giant head." It was probably an alien. It probably wasn't the devil.
So you started getting this rash of UFO sightings in the area. Other people were like,
"I saw a UFO in this area. I saw this strange light." One farmer said,
"A UFO flew over his property and hovered there over his cattle." I think this story is completely
made up by the way. Not the whole story, but this particular part. This farmer says, "I came out,
my cows were acting all weird. They weren't as talkative as they normally are. They were kind
of like looking down at the ground. They weren't engaging with me." I noticed there was a UFO
floating above them that it floated there for 40 minutes. No photos, really dude. You didn't even
bring a sketch artist out to draw a picture. 40 minutes is a long time for you to not be able
to go get your camera. But anyways, that story is completely ridiculous. But there were other
UFO sightings in the area. Culminating in a big story where apparently an alien collapsed on the
side of the road. And it was at night time. This alien is just collapsed on the road, sick or
something. And that's what the original people, the original girls after they got over the devil
story said. It looked like it was sick. What we saw the way it walked, it looked like it wasn't
healthy. But anyways, there's this other alien sick on the side of the road. Maybe the same one.
We'll find out. Three military trucks pulled up, put the body in the back, took it to a local clinic.
So it didn't take it to like a Area 51 S hospital underground. They took them to a like 24 hour
med clinic and dropped it off where it was treated. And you think that's ridiculous, but multiple
people saw more than one alien in the clinic that night. They're like, "I know that story's stupid
that the military would just drop an alien off at a 24 hour express med, but I saw an alien there.
I absolutely saw an alien there." So the story spread like wildfire through the town. So the
Brazilian military investigated this. Brazilian military is like, "We should look into this.
Let's see what happened here." Here's the thing. This is it. They're findings for what happened
over that period of time in 1996 is either absolutely true or the worst cover-up I've ever
heard. Because you're not like men in black when they like scan you with that little beam in your
eyeball and I know that's not real life, but you know they'd scan you with that little eyeball
thing and then they'd give you a fake story. People say UFOs are swamp gas or the plan of venus
or stuff like that. All of that stuff is for... This sounds like the worst cover-up ever, but it's
most likely what really happened. So the military investigated and first off they said, "Listen guys,
those three military trucks that were driving on the road that night, that it was a schedule drive,
those trucks go through that area all the time around the same time. Like that is a normal,
we didn't pick up anything on the side of the road." The people go, "Well okay, well what about
the... what about the alien that the girl saw walking down the road?" So this is what the
Brazilian military had to say about the original sighting. This is from an article here. "In regards
to the wasteland creature, an official inquiry led by the Brazilian military authorities concluded
in 2010..." So this is 14 years after the event, they really did look into this. "Concluded in 2010
that the Silva sisters had actually come across..." So this is what the military concluded was walking
by these girls. "...had actually come across a homeless, mentally unstable man nicknamed
Mudhino, covered in mud. Can you imagine the military investigator who's been working for
the government for 15 years? He thinks he's investigating a possible alien sighting and
when he starts interviewing people around town he consistently sees a muddy homeless person
walking around unsteadily with red bloodshot eyes because he has a drinking problem and he's
probably quite skinny because he's homeless and mentally unstable and I can imagine the
investigator every time he's interviewing somebody and he's like, "So you swear that you saw the
Shiofo over your cows and they're like, "Yes, yes, he sees Mudhino walking in the background
all unsteadying." The investigator's like, "God, man..." And then some people go, "Okay, yeah, we know
Mudhino, we know him. He does have an abnormally large head, skinny little body, brown skin,
which is just a mud covering him. But how do you explain the aliens that we all saw in the clinic?
How do you explain that?" And at that point the military goes, "We have an answer for that as
well. We came to that conclusion in 2010 as well." Apparently they traced it back. Now again, this is
either a terrible cover-up or the absolute truth. But the military says we traced back the sightings
to the clinic. We went to the clinic, we talked to them, we went over records. Apparently two...
This is the military said, two dwarves, two little people were in there who were expecting to give
birth. Not both of them at the same time, but it was either like a routine checkup or it was a
like a... what are those things where they check out the baby? Prenatal visit, something like that.
So you basically people who were hearing all this UFO flap and then they walk into a clinic
and they saw just two short people, one with a big old belly, and that was the big alien sighting.
Now it's one of those things like because of mass delusion, I could see people jump into that
conclusion when they see something out of the ordinary. They see these little people and they're
like "Ah aliens!" So yeah, that's the story of the alien of the town that I can barely pronounce.
I have to say this though, how mentally unstable and muddy do you have to be to be confused with
an interdimensional creature? I kind of want to do a story on this guy. If anyone has any
information on Mudino, I'd love to hear it because that just sounds absolutely bizarre. Why is he
covered in mud? Is it a decision he made or did he just fall into a mud puddle and never took a
bath? Like what is the origin story of this guy? And what is up with his feet? I gotta look into this
guy. I swear there are, I think a cool place to look, this might sound kind of cruel and savage,
but I'm sure if you wanted to find some cryptids, hang out with the homeless. Not saying that they're
cryptids, but if I was like a skinwalker, if I was some sort of like half-human hybrid,
that's where I'd hang out. They got bigger problems to worry about the fact that your eyes
roll back into your head when you sleep or that you have like eight tongues or you're eating the
flesh of you know the living. They got bigger problems to worry about. If I was a cryptid,
I would hang out with the homeless. I actually should look into that. Are cryptids feeding on
the homeless or just blending in with them? Interesting. Okay, but before we get into that
story I just came up with. Let's go ahead and move on to our next story. So this was the original
request I got from Ramsay via email. He said, "Jason, you gotta look into this guy. He's an
inventor and you gotta look at this invention." I started looking around the site and the first
thing that popped up that I saw was the Yon Machine. I was like, "I want to cover him,
but I'm going to break it up into two because the Yon Machine, that was the last episode of Season 3.
I love that episode." And the one that Ramsay specifically wanted me to cover was the food
replicator. So I've always kept it on the docket and now it's time. It is time to tell you about
an invention that will change your life. It changed his. It definitely changed his.
So a brief overview of Paul Allen. He's a man. He's probably like in his late 60s. Actually,
actually he may not be around anymore from the look of his blog, but at this time he looked to
being about his late 60s maybe. It's really hard to pin down his age. Just a couple photos of him.
He invented the Yon Machine. You are the Yon Machine. By yawning you can relieve your stress.
I recommend listening to that episode. He also invented something and I curse, I curse God and
I curse the world that I live in that this link is not working. I'm looking at his website of
all of his inventions and one of them is called Paul's Squirrel Academy. And then you just click
on it and it goes to a 404 page somewhere and I was like, no, like how why was I born onto a
planet where I don't have access to what Paul's Squirrel Academy is? I can only imagine the insanity
that used to be behind that link, but it is no more. We will not, that phrase belongs on the
conspiracy iceberg. If anything that I've covered belongs on there, that does. Paul's Squirrel Academy.
What does it mean? Is it a literal academy or are there squirrels walking around with little
top hats or little, what are those little graduation caps? Is it a metaphorical academy?
Like how we each have a squirrel inside of us and the academy helps us. I don't know that phrase.
If anyone ever edits another conspiracy iceberg image, please put Paul's Squirrel Academy on
there because that is just, that is a lost conspiracy. But unfortunately I exist in the
timeline where Paul's Squirrel Academy doesn't exist, but we are left with the food replicator.
Now the food replicator is exactly what it sounds like. Paul Adams, is Paul Adams or Paul, it's
Paul Adams. I think I called him Paul Allen earlier, but it's Paul Adams. He has invented a food
replicator and it will cost you maybe eight bucks to build and just 20 years off your life,
just letting you know. Very, very simple. Here it is. Two, two tin cans. So any invention that
starts off with two tin cans, you know is going to be gold. You know that is an amazing invention.
That's a shark, that's above shark tank. That's like DARPA level technology. Two tin cans. They
have to, you should write this down. You guys are going to want to do this. They have to be food-based
cans. So they have to be cans that previously held food and they have to be the same. So you
can't get a can of Denison's Chili and then a can of raviolis. You have to get two cans of Denison's
Chili and then give the chili to me. Y'all eat it. You then empty out the cans, you wash them down,
take off the wrapper and there you go. You have the first part of your science fiction device
known as the Food Replicator. This is real, by the way. This is, I should say that he's been
doing this for years, eating this, eating this food. Well, again, he might be dead now, but we'll
get to that. Two matching tin cans. Clean. Some circular magnets. You'll need those as well.
One lead with two alligator clips. So you'll need a little wire and then two little alligator clips.
And two identical plastic or glass bottles. That's all you'll need to really start making this food.
You're going to take the two tin cans, you clean them out. You're going to take the magnet. He
spends a long time describing how magnets work and I'm thinking, who is this for? Fourth graders?
Like, who doesn't know how magnets work? The reverse polarity of magnets, he goes on and on.
Anyways, no duh, dude. You take the magnets and you completely cover the bottom of one can
with the magnets. So you take the can and you make sure that they're all facing the same way.
Which obviously, but anyways, so you take a bottom of the can, you put the little circular
magnets down, you cover as much of the surface area on one can with the magnets, and do the same
thing to the other can. Then you use the alligator clips and you connect them via the wire, and now
you're done with the Food Replicator. That's the actual device itself. Then you are going to take
your bottles and you're going to fill them up full of water. But Paul is very, very specific.
It can only be tap water. No other water will work for whatever reason. You can't use any other water
but tap water. Fill it full of tap water. Fill both bottles full of tap water. So now you have two
bottles, your source bottle and your replica bottle. In your source bottle, put food in it.
I'm almost done. I'm sure this is probably boring, but in your source bottle, you put food in the
water and you swish it around and put it under one tin can. And in the replica bottle, you don't do
anything to it. You put it under the other tin can. So you have to be fairly small bottles of water.
Wait 10 minutes and then drink out of the replica bottle. You have just drank the food
from the first bottle, from the source bottle. And you're thinking, "Okay Jason, this guy is
this wacky invention. Ha ha. You told us some stupid instructions and that's the end of the
episode, right? That's kind of boring." No, because I wouldn't waste your time with that. It is funny
to look at this recipe for this device, but what it gets insane because so he makes this device
back in 2004. And he has blog posts going for years. Now we start, this is where we start to see
the insanity sink in. This is where we start to see that this guy invented this machine. I'm not
necessarily calling him insane, but just the bizarre thoughts that got wrapped around this.
In 2004, when he invented the machine, he was having some blood pressure problems. He was having
some health issues. And he decided to invent this machine to help those health issues. He was a little
overweight and his blood pressure was high. And I think it started initially that he was trying to
lose weight, but you gotta eat something. His blog then goes, there's two levels of the blog.
There's the interactions with himself and interactions with other people and the food
replicator. The interactions with himself, every blog post, he lists his blood pressure. And you
can actually watch it go up and down over the course of months. And his weight, he loses 20
pounds incredibly rapidly. And he wasn't a super big guy to begin with. He was like 195 in the
beginning. And then he's down to 170. So he drops 20 pounds fairly quickly, which is fine. It's good
to lose weight, but you need to eat stuff. He is getting most of his meals from the food replicator.
And when I say put, when I first read this, I was like, Oh, put food in a bottle of water.
I was thinking, you know, put like a piece of meat in there. And then it gets transmitted
to other water. He put, he's putting breath expiritos in his food replicator. He's constantly
talking about taking omelets and making an omelet and only eating a part of it and sticking the
rest into a bottle of water and then drinking the replicated omelet. He's like, Oh, I feel so good.
I've eaten this omelet. And then the next blog post is blood pressures up. Like it's just insane.
It's totally nuts. And he's doing that. And then as the year like the months go on, he starts being
like, I woke up this morning and I'm not hungry, but I'm like kind of hungry. And I made toast with
butter and I ate it. It was the most delicious thing I've ever eaten because he's starving himself.
And then there's this weird, weird pattern emerges where he starts talking about how much he loves
Panda Express. And he starts going to Panda Express and eating chow mein. And then he gets sick
because he's eating a bunch of carbs and he's been starving himself through the food replicator.
And he can't figure out what the problem is. So he drinks an omelet the next morning. It's
absolutely bizarre. And the whole time he's watching his blood pressure go up. So here is,
oh, again, this is, this is, this is, I want to read off a couple of his sample blog posts here.
This is February 10th, 2004. So this is very, very recent from him building the food replicator.
I had the urge to exercise today. That's good. Exercise is good. I always think exercise is good
thing. So I've been bouncing. So I've been bouncing on the mini trampoline, what? For a total of a
couple of hours. So now I imagine this guy just, and is on a mini trampoline for hours,
for hours. I have so much energy since I drank that burrito. This is so good.
This is, this is actually the same day, February 10th. All I had eaten of real food today by about
4pm was half a cup of orange juice, apart from drinking water as usual. I'd had a few squirts
of yesterday's burrito and so on. So I didn't feel particularly hungry. But the idea of some toast
and cheese was appealing. So again, like he's constantly like talking about eating other food.
It's not working. But he swears by it. And also the phrase, "A few squirts of yesterday's burrito"
is not appetizing in the least. That's what I say after I've gone to Taco Bell and I'm headed to the
bathroom. Ah, I gotta drop off a couple squirts of yesterday's burrito. That's disgusting. So anyways,
but he loves squirting, eating squirted burrito. So, and he then decides to share his miracle
invention with the world. He puts the invention online, but he's like, "No, it's not gonna
end." He starts trying to get his friends to take squirts of water into their mouth. So he has one
buddy who's pretty game to it, and Paul starts giving him squirts of coffee. So it's just regular
water that's been infused with coffee. And his buddy's like, "Oh yeah, fine. Probably don't,
don't shoot me. Don't kill me at work, please. Don't, please, Paul. I'm on your side." And then
there's this, there women pop up every once in a while in his blog post. There's this woman,
a friend of his he's hanging out with, and he's like, "Here, take some of this water." Which, I mean,
ma'am, you have terrible common sense. If a man goes here, take a squirt of this enhanced water,
and you do it. She takes the squirt and he's like, "I wonder what she'll, I wonder if she'll taste
the omelet in the, in the water." And anyway, she comes home from work and he's like, "Did you notice
anything from the water?" And she's like, "Well, not really, but I did crave an omelet later." And
he's like, "Success! Maybe I put the idea of cheese in her head." This is totally wrong, by the way.
And then he finally tells her what his invention was. He goes, "You know that water I gave you
was actually replicated omelet in a bottle of water." And he goes through the process, because
he didn't tell her at first. He just said here, "Have some enhanced the water." So he tells her
what it was. And then later on that night, he goes, "Would you like some more?" And she's like,
"No, I don't. I don't." And even he's like, "I think I creeped her out. I think I scared her from my
invention." But, so he's now trying to share it with other people. But then we talk, now he's a
true scientist because he starts experimenting on himself. He has this weird post on February 15th.
Where he talks about his pornography and masturbation addiction. And he's going on about how
it's, okay, so this is the year 2004. He's like, "I have this huge collection of pornography and
I masturbate all the time and I don't know what to do." And then he goes, "Sometimes I just want to
delete my collection, but then I think, no, I can't." And he goes, "I have all these pictures and I'm
thinking pictures. Pictures? How old is your computer? I get like 2004 wasn't the highest level
of internet, but who has pornographic photos? Like, did people still have those back then?
Am I, am I that like removed? Like, it was video, we had videos then, right? When was the last time
someone looked at a pornographic photo on there, just a photo on their computer? So anyways, he has
this huge collection of pornographic photos. What are you, photos? Anyways, I came. He has this huge
collection of pornographic photos on his computer and he's chronic masturbator. So as a scientist
would do, he thinks, "I bet you the food replicator can solve this." And he talks about a phrase he
once heard, says, "If you're having a problem with something, you don't have enough of it yet."
He doesn't source who said this quote. And it sounds like a terrible, terrible quote,
because basically if someone has a heroin problem, you could say, "Well, technically,
you don't have a heroin problem. You have a problem with not having enough heroin." And be like,
"Oh, yeah, you're right. That is my problem." He repeats this phrase multiple times throughout
his website. If you're having a problem with something, you don't have enough of it yet,
which is quite bizarre. I could see that applying to like money and love, but anything else,
masturbation. So he's thinking, "Maybe it has something to do with my semen. Like, I'm releasing
all of this. This is so gross because now this guy is in his late 60s, early 70s, and he's basically
just jacking off all the time. His mini trampoline is super slippery." And he goes, "I am jacking off
all the time, but maybe I need more semen because I have a problem releasing semen." So he jacks
off into a bottle of water and puts it in the food replicator and drinks the replicated semen water.
Now, I mean, come on, dude. Come on. Like, if the invention doesn't work, it's just very,
very unclean. It's unsanitary. You're jacking off in a bottle. But if the invention does work,
you're drinking magical jizz. Anyway, so he begins drinking his own replicated semen
for pretty much the rest of the blog. Like, I was looking through blog ratings and it'd be like,
"Today I drink some semen." So his photo is on this blog. It's his real name, his address is on
there. I can't imagine any business associate ever stumbling across this thing and being like,
"Hey, Paul, can I see you in my office today?" You're not. You're not. The water during the
work is when he's semen in it, right? He's like, "What? No, no." Fingers crossed behind his back.
Salt water. But anyways, so the madness continues. So he starts doing in February. He has pretty
consistent updates on his blog. But on June 28th, everything kind of takes a turn. There's only
like a blog post every month or every few months after that. And the blog posts are saying, "All
the blog posts say is, 'I'm still alive. I'm not dead yet. I'm still alive.'" He's just like letting
us know that he's not dead yet because he started to have, he thought he had a heart attack.
Like, short, like a couple months after building the food replicator because he wasn't eating enough
food. And he was taking vitamins via the replicated water. So he would buy vitamins and he'd take
some of them. But most of them, he would drop in water and drink the replicated vitamins.
He started putting like silver in the source bottle and then spraying the replicated silver all over
his body to get rid of germs, like crazy, crazy stuff. And the last update to the website was
2015. Now, in 2015, he had gone back up to his weight of 190, 195. So he did start putting weight on
again, but he hasn't posted anything that I've seen since 2015. So it is possible that he has passed
away at this point. Or he's built his new replicator he was talking about. On March 17th, he talks about
his friend saying, "You know what? I'd really like to replicate a haughty, 20-year-old haughty."
Paul's like, "Hoo hoo hoo hoo! Hmm. Let me think about that." Here's a quote in his own words,
"Which gives an interesting idea." The guy was joking, by the way. The guy who said he'd like to
replicate a 20-year-old haughty was joking. He didn't realize he was joking to a supervillain.
He didn't realize he was joking to a supervillain on a shoestring budget.
"Which gives an interesting idea. What if you got two 55-gallon steel barrels, added the magnets
and a wire between in the usual manner and put a person in the input barrel?" What? So some guy's
cracking a joke and Paul's like, "That actually might work. We might be able to replicate a human
being." Or turn him in a water. See, that's what I know. You're just going to turn him in water.
So then he goes on, "There would need to be the usual electrical connection between the
cans and the person should be barefoot and touching the bottom and should probably also touch the
side of the barrel with his hands." What? So now you want to replicate a dude? Like, the other guy
was talking about like a chick, but you're replicating a guy now? That's a weird turn, Paul. Bizarre.
Okay, but anyway, that kind of threw me off. "What would be the result?" he asks. "What would be the
result of taking squirts of a replicated person?" And then he says, "I have no idea." Luckily, he does
say that basically you put a person in a 55-gallon drum and then you take a giant water bottle,
like an Alhambra water bottle, and you would suck some of them out and turn them in water,
and then you could drink the person, drink the person's essence, and he starts to say,
"Maybe I could use this like if someone's fighting with me or someone's angry with me or I don't like
them. I could take their essence and drink them because," he repeats the phrase, "if you have a
problem with something you don't have enough of it." He's thinking, "Maybe if I have a problem with
someone because I don't have enough of them, but if I drink them they're inside me, so I have all
that I need." That's his rationale. Now, he goes, "Obviously I'm not going to be able to get this
person into a 55-gallon barrel, especially if it's somebody who doesn't like him. If it's somebody
who doesn't like Paul, he's not going to be tricked to come in over to his murder dungeon
to hide underneath a barrel." But he does have a helpful tip for that. What you can do is you can
get a non-digital photograph, a lock of their hair, or some of their blood. He will drink
the blood of people who he's having trouble with. He will put some of their blood into a container,
replicate it, and then drink the water. This guy is, I mean, come on Paul, come on. You're already
drinking your own C-A-A. I wonder why he didn't say I'll just drink their semen too, but anyways.
And then, depending on your point of view, this is either a creepy way to end it or a heartbreaking
way to end it. I personally think it's a little bit of both. But in his blog post where he's trying
to figure out if he can replicate a human being and drink them, he says this. Another interesting
experiment to be done. He says it's like he's wearing a smock covered in blood with a little
doctor's mask all bloody holding a butcher knife. And he's talking specifically about taking hair or
blood or photographs of people and replicating them. Another interesting experiment to be done.
I'll try it with some photographs of people. I'll start with a photograph of my daughter
who hasn't contacted me for four years. She doesn't like me. And I don't even know where she is.
She does know my address though. So basically this guy is suggesting drinking his daughter.
That's super creepy.
DeadRabbitRadio.com is going to be your email address. You can also hit us up at
facebook.com/deadrabbitradio. Twitter is @jasonocarpenter.
DeadRabbitRadio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast.
You don't have to listen to it every day. But I'm glad you listened to it today. Have a great one, guys.