A grim discovery.
Stardoles scientists. And then we travel to Reading, California to investigate whether or not a cult is taking over the city.
But this isn't any cult.
It's a cult that can raise the dead today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
[Music]
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host Jason Carpenteror.
I'm having a great day. I hope you guys are having a great day too. I hope you guys had a lot of fun today.
Let's go to Poland. Let's go to the year 2013
Poland.
Bing! We're magically there. Carpenter copters in the shop. We're just walking around a bunch of trees are surrounding us.
We're hanging out with a bunch of bat researchers. These guys are hunting bats. So we're there. We have rifles.
We're like, they're like, no we're not hunting bats like that dude. You lunatic swark.
He's showing up with shotguns to blow these, blow these bats away. We're like, oh, I thought that's what we were doing.
We put our rifles and shotguns away. They're like, no we're observing the like migration pattern.
Then we just kind of zone out as they kind of tell us what they're actually doing with the bats.
But while they are looking for the bats, this is what happened. True story here. They're hunting bats.
They're searching for bats and they know that the bats tend to hang out in this underground
abandoned nuclear bunker, which is probably the four coolest words you can put together.
And so they're in there. They're shining their flashlights and the bats are like
And they're like all flying out all dramatically. There's some guy in the corner being like, oh today's the day both my parents were killed.
There's actually a thing called the Bruce Wayne syndrome in the bat research community. They don't let orphans
work with bats because they're afraid what's gonna happen. It's an actual thing. Don't Google it. Don't look don't look it up
But it's called the Bruce Wayne
What did I call him before the blue? It's not the Bruce Wayne syndrome. It's the Bruce Wayne Claws. They have it at universities. Bat
universities. They don't they when you go to apply for this joke's taken too long. You guys got it. It was dumb
Let's just keep going here. A bunch of bats flying around some guy in the corner going hmm. What scares a criminal?
And the rest of the bat researchers are like again
Another vigilante was born on this research trip as well, but as we're watching the bats fly around
something
Unexpected happens. Not the birth of a crime fighter. No, they expect that at this point when they're walking around this bunker. They hear a
Now like what is that noise like we get it? There's leaves and stuff on the ground
They're making the noise and who wasn't a goblin story doesn't involve a goblin coming up behind them
And they were never seen again. No the crunching noise was from them walking around
They're like that's weird and they're looking around making sure none of their co-workers are eating rice Krispies. None of them are
They're walking on ants and they're like, okay big deal. Huh? You know me finish. They're walking on
one million ants a
Million ants in there they went in there to steady bats and instead they found a colony of one million ants and
in a pitch dark
Nuclear bunker and they're kind of scratching their heads and they're like
I wonder what what all these ants are doing in here
Wonder what they're also scratching their heads because bats keep landed in their hair
But they're like why are a bunch of ants in here? So they went and got some ant dudes
They went and got some ant scientists to come to this bunker
They go back to the university and they're like hey, yeah, we did all our bat stuff
But you guys might want to go check this place out. And so this is what this is terrifying. This is terrifying
So they go there. They're looking at ants. This is what they surmised
This is what they've figured out is that there's no queen down there. And I like that's weird
So this isn't an actual like ant colony because that'd be fine million ants big giant colony
They're living here, but here's the thing. There's no queen which means they can't reproduce
Every ant down there is from someplace else. There's no food at all people aren't dropping sugar cubes down there
There's no Eminem wrappers. There's nothing. So the ants are surviving by eating other ants
There's no light down there. It's pitch dark. That's why the bats loved it so much
But the ants, you know, they can do darkness. They live underground, but you know, they like a little light
They like a little sun sun on their back
No food
Not having food or being able to procreate is more important than their ability to suntan
But for me, I wouldn't want to be trapped in the dark all the time
I wouldn't want to have to eat other humans and I do like procreating as well
But those are the three biggies. So the scientists are like how what is going on here?
They don't have a queen these aren't these ants weren't born here. Where are they coming from?
They don't have food down here. So why would they be in here in the first place? And as the scientists are like, hmm
Stroking their chin and ant falls on their head. They're like, hmm
Where'd that come from? They flick it into the darkness and they hear it immediately being eaten by other ants
Hmm now that I've gotten rid of that ant now I can think about where are these ants coming?
Another ant falls on its head. He's like hmm the ants are
falling through vents
Around the nuclear fallout shelter. Now. I know what you're thinking because I was thinking the same thing
Why would you build a nuclear fallout shelter that had vents kind of defeats the purpose you're like oh
We're safe now. It's time for me to breathe in some of that sweet sweet it radiated dirt
But apparently there are vents. Maybe there's some sort of weird filtration system that's broken down since
1960 when these things were built but ants are falling from the surface into this bomb shelter
So what's happened what they imagine and there's a million down there
So what has happened is over it. They're not all alive a bunch of them are like half eaten
So basically it's probably 500,000 and then 500,000 half bodies
But the ants are falling through the vent into pitch blackness on top of hundreds of thousands of other ants
And just be like where am I? Oh my god
I just up there to get a suntan
Eating a little bit of a pair getting ready to procreate with the queen next thing I know
Pitch blackness and he can feel his comrades crawling all over him. Ah get off of me get off of me
And it's basically sink or swim because you fall down there those ants are starving
So if you can't immediately start fighting for your life bite people with your pinchers
You are snapped in half by one of your own clan because all of these ants
actually were from a
ant hive
ant colony on the surface
Because they ended up the scientists goes
This is our theory that these ants are actually from the surface from this other colony that's right by here
They built a bridge out of the bomb shelter back to the surface and when the ants would found the bridge and they crawled up
They got to the colony. They were immediately accepted back into the colony
so all of the ants that were falling down in there were from the same clan and
You you came super close to being food like that
Most of them probably did become food and the ants that were stuck down there. They had no queen
They had no social system all they could hope for was for another sweet sweet brother to fall through that chute
So they could gobble them up and the scientists decided to leave the walkway there because they're like this is going to be an ongoing
Problem ants are going to keep falling through here and now when they fall through here
They'll be in there for a little bit and then they'll find the bridge and they'll be able to walk back up to the surface
totally fine
But one thing they noticed as they were leaving there was a group of ants who refused to take the bridge up
They wanted to continue to live their life in darkness looking for a family member to fall through that hole
Gobble them up
I find this story terrifying
That story super creepy. I think you and it's 100% true. There are still a bunch of ants down there
I completely review they're like I don't want to live by the Queen's rules anymore. I'd rather commit cannibalism than be part of the system
Man, I'm not a cog in the machine. I'm a cannibal
I don't think I'm shocking anyone to say if that same type of situation happened with humans if there was a thing where humans were
Falling into a giant pit the first couple humans would be like oh no
We're trapped in here and you have a couple people go into shock and a couple people just kind of die
But other people would be like we're gonna survive no matter what and as more humans kept falling in there
Eventually, they'd be like we don't have any food
We're gonna eat the newest humans and then eventually human would fall down there who was stronger than the existing humans
And he would eat him in retaliation create a new social order and you would have an entire
Eventually over enough time you would have a culture that was built for the darkness that was built for cannibalism
And if people were like Jason, this is the dumbest analogy ever
You're saying there's a pit big enough for like 60 or 70 people to fall into
And they immediately devolve into cannibalism, you know what I'm saying
I think it's creepy because I can definitely see the same thing happening now before we move on our next story
I just want to remind my dear listeners a couple different ways you can support the show you can support us on patreon
It's in the show notes
We have a merch store in the show notes if you can't do either of those that's totally fine
You can give us a review anywhere you listen to the podcast or you can promote the podcast let your friends know you listen to the
podcast all four of those things help the show
So so much they really help the show grow
Now let's go ahead and move on to our next story
So we're leaving behind the forest of Poland before we start walking out of the force you're like Jason
You really don't have any ants in your pocket. I was like no man. No don't I pull my pockets out. You're like your other pocket
I'm like a pull the chance come out of my back pocket. He caught me. I'll see you guys later
I throw a bunch of sugar. I'm like replicate and call me your queen and then we
Disappear you walk through a portal. We're in Reading, California
So we're now in Reading, California, and you and I are walking down the street. I do you see me just scan on the ground
I'm like where my ants where my ant brothers. You're like Jason. Stop looking for ants. I was like
We're walking through Reading. You're literally holding my chin up
so I can't look at the ground and we see a giant church in the middle of the city and it is Bethel Church and
You're like so why did you bring us here? You're not taking me to church. Are you you're not gonna pray to the great ant God?
I was like no no no no no I'll do that later Bethel Church
They have a huge music ministry big internet presence and a huge somewhat say
Outsized presence in the city of Reading the city of Reading has
90,000 people in it and this church claims to have about
11,000 members so that's over 10% of the population of Reading
Attends this church
At that point a police car drives by behind us and like that's weird. I'm like, yeah, it is weird. Let's walk
Let's keep walking through the city here. This church has been around for quite a while and their claim
They have several claims to fame. They do have this big music ministry, but that's really not what we're gonna talk about today
They have some beliefs that some would consider unusual now. I've talked about this before on the show
I'm a Christian myself
There's a lot of people who believe that my beliefs are unusual that Jesus died came back from the dead three days later that
You know Moses part of the Red Sea those are all things. I don't believe the book of Genesis. I think is a total
Metaphor I don't think that the story happened literally like that as you get farther in history. I believe the New Testament
I believe that these things happen so and I believe the book of Revelation is a metaphor as well
So but so I just to let you guys know where I'm at and you could say well Jason
That's ridiculous like you're telling me that you believe people can actually come back from the dead and and I'll say yes
That is part of my faith that I believe people can come back from the dead. However
I think there's a limit to it now
Here's the thing there are
That and that's a key detail to this story because I want you to know where I'm coming from with this story
Because I'm going to be start mocking some of these guys beliefs and this is always interesting thing when you cover religion when specifically when a
Believer covers religion at what point does a belief become
completely bizarre to a lot of people the idea of someone being crucified being
Put in a tomb and then coming back three days later is
Completely impossible and to me. I'm like, yeah, maybe it may have happened. I believe it happened
So when these people when Bethel ministry begins preaching that they can bring people back from the dead
It raises a lot of eyebrows and not only raises eyebrows in the secular community
But even in the religious community we go what?
That's happened like two maybe three times in the Bible
Jesus brought a dude back to life
Jesus himself came back to life and there's probably something else that happened in there that I'm not aware of it's a big book
But it's super rare. So when a church shows up that basically says you can do this too if you join us
Just as it's basically revenge of the Sith. It's really what Palpatine promised Anakin Skywalker
He could do but this is real
This is a real place and Bethel has this thing called the Bethel school of
Supernatural ministry and other people have called it the Christian hog warts
And so you're like dude if that's why you brought me to Bethel so we could stand outside of a cult like church and
Then go and visit their school of supernatural ministry. I'm totally down. You're like converting Christianity
I'm like no no no no no no no no it's not as cool as you think it is
I mean, it's cool be whatever religion you want, but don't don't change your life just because of a cool name of this school
So I looked into it of course
I thought about attending it and you have to be in readying to do it
I was hoping they had online classes or something like that
But I also imagined you were like flying around shooting laser beams out of your hands. That's what it sounds like
Supernatural ministry gives you two powers. They're both fairly lame
One is the ability to heal people and you're like Jason. That's not lame doc. I'm a doctor
I listen to your show you calling me lame first off. Yeah secondly
Yeah, sure healing people would be cool
But when someone says they have magical powers and the power is basically can be replicated by a bandaid
That's not a magical power, bro
so they believe that they can heal people by laying hands on them and
They have the power to preach again not a superpower
You can take a speech 101 class in college and get that power as well now
They may have other powers in there some people are saying that they know how to walk through walls one of the big things
They do and before you get excited. They can't they can't do that
But they also do this thing called grave soaking it's where you lay on the grave of a
Previous Christian religious prophet type of guy and you can soak up his energy
Apparently that was something from the bible as well
I mean the bible has a lot of weird stuff in it
but
They think you can do this now again back in the bible moses is thrown sticks down and they've become snakes and and all sorts of stuff
There's stuff in the bible that happens that doesn't happen in real life anymore
So the fact that in the bible they're able to do something doesn't mean that you can be able to do it now
But that's one thing bethle teaches
That if it was a miracle in the bible, it's good now
You're like jason who cares these people are just walking around and they're telling people that they can heal people and they can lay on a grave
I mean, are they bugging you now? There's also been allegations that bethle church is
Taking over redding california. They're getting into the police forces. They're getting into the mayor's office into city council
They allegations of them getting sweetheart deals
Because they're starting to gain political power and I have to say to that like I don't endorse that
I don't think it's a great idea, but that happens everywhere
Every everywhere does that and it's unfortunate
But when if you if you have a small group of people and small being relative, you know
There's 11,000 of them in a city of 90,000 but when you have a group of people you have to do one of two things
You can create a community or you can take over an existing community
And we see examples of that happen on the internet. We see subcultures infiltrate existing forums and websites
And within a matter of months, they've taken over
That forum or that website or they start their own and we see this in cities or as well
Scientology has done this to clear water. Disney has done it to like orange county. You see corporations do it
You see religions do it. You see cults do it. You see political organizations do it
This is just something that human organizations do. I don't endorse it
But whenever someone tells me group x is slowly taking over this community
I always say I always have the same reaction. Well, that's just what people do
I don't endorse it and that might sound like an endorsement
But if it was happening in my community, I would if I and we did have that actually up here in the dows
We had the raw niches before I moved up here. However, you pronounce it
We had that colt in the dows that was trying to take over the raw niches
And I know i'm mispronounced it again and they ended up sprain
Like e.coli all over the the salad bar
I've never covered that on the show because it's such a well known
I remember reading about it when I was a kid in california
It was one of the biggest I think it still is the biggest biological attack from a terrorist group in united states history
But the church taking over a city allegedly
Telling kids they can go out and spend a bunch of money enjoying this college
And they'll get these supernatural ministry powers the powers to talk and the powers to heal
And they've been walking all over the city whenever they see people in wheelchairs
Their stories of these kids surrounding them and being like walk walk walk in the old lady wheelchairs
I was like, what are you talking about? There was a story going around that some kid had an asthma attack
And they wouldn't call 911 they were trying to heal the kid and the kid ended up having brain damage
I saw that story get passed around a couple times. I could find no
News articles on that you figure that would have been a big news story unless
Even if they've infiltrated the news organizations of redding
I think that story would have gotten out there was another story about a guy
Who fell and or was pushed off of a cliff by a member of this
Supernatural ministry school broke his back and bashed his head in
And they didn't call an ambulance for six hours because they were trying to find him to heal him and he sued them
And then the judge said you can't sue them because they legally don't have to call the cops and he lost the case
But he appealed it and now he's actually going to try to sue him again
You want to go out you want to pray in the street? Totally fine. You want to tell people you can bring people back from the dead?
Whatever. It's not going to happen. It's totally bizarre
But whatever all of that stuff being said the reason why I know about Bethel church
The reason why I really came to my attention was because of olive
Now olive was a little girl
This all happened super recently
December 14th 2019 olive hyal highly genthal olive highly genthal two years old
stops breathing
and dies
The mom kailey
She is a member of Bethel church. The whole family is a member of Bethel church, but kailey's a member of the church
She is in their music. She's done music with them as well
So her recordings have been out there and things like that very very active in this church
She posts on instagram after her daughter dies
And i'm going to read this instagram post for you. We're asking for prayer
We believe in a jesus who died and conclusively defeated every grave holding the keys to resurrection power
We need it for a little olive a line
That's her middle name
Who stopped breathing yesterday and has been pronounced dead by doctors
Absolutely tragic story. Absolutely a heartbreaking story
And if it was just there, yes family in need. We need prayer
Please be here for us as we're suffering from the loss of our daughter all of that stuff
But this is where we continue. We are asking for bold unified prayers from the global church
To stand with us in belief
That he will raise this little girl back to life
Her time here is not done and it is our time to believe boldly and with confidence
Wealed what king jesus paid for it's time for her to come to life
So that caused
a lot of controversy
online
But not at first at first actually this instagram post that went out to people who are supportive of Bethel church and people began
praying for olive and putting it the hashtag wake up olive
And the belief was if like she just said enough people prayed that jesus and all of his power and majesty would bring
This two-year-old girl back to life
And started to spread around the internet starts trending wake up olive wake up olive
Just the those three words just the combination of words is chilling
Wake up olive
Day three if you're not familiar with biblical stories jesus died on the cross according christian faith three days later
He came back to life
They went to go visit him at the tomb and the the big boulder that was blocking his tomb was moved away
Jesus was no longer in there
There's a couple angels chilling in his tomb and they're like hey guys, you're too late
Jesus is out. He's taking care of business. So knowing that now it's december 17th. It's three days after all of his passed away
Kaylee starts her instagram post that day
Day three
Is a really good day for resurrection
Oh man, and I I get it. I get it. This family has lost a two-year-old child
And you're hoping for a miracle
I totally get that and I think you guys realize that i'm not busting a bunch of jokes
I totally get where that's coming from day four next day instagram post starts with
Day four is a really good day for a resurrection
I found out about this because
The when the controversy kicked in because now we're on day four people are beginning to get wind of this and saying this is
This is suffer this is extending the suffering of this family and the family is like no no no no
Like this can happen the church believes that people can be brought back from the dead today
There's a huge musical concert going on people are out celebrating praising the lord praying for olive to wake up
December 20th
They start planning the memorial service the miracle did not come
olive will not be resurrected
I don't want to criticize this family for wanting a miracle
I don't really even want to criticize the church. I think the church probably is more at fault for
Putting this belief in people's heads that people can be brought back from the dead
But I don't want to spend the last few minutes of today's podcast
Wagging my finger at someone who has religious beliefs different than mine. It's a tragic story
It involves a church that has bizarre beliefs, but not
They're not telling people to go out and commit jihad. They're not telling people to go out and blow up abortion clinics
They're not telling people to do these unspeakable acts
They're basically have a belief that's weirder than my belief that's weirder than
You know two billion people's beliefs
But not by a massive long shot
The reason why I wanted to cover this story is because we look at paranormal. We look at conspiracy theories stuff like that
What if
It worked
What would happen to human society if it worked?
We've had stories of people getting frozen in ice. They've been clinically dead for five hours
They're thawed not frozen in ice but frozen. They're not a block of ice. They're not captain america, but people who have been frozen
They're clinically dead. They're thawed out. They're back to life
We have stories like that people who have been brain dead a longer than we thought you could survive being brain dead coming back to life
We've had miracles
but
Being dead for three days that has only happened once and again
You could argue whether or not that even happened back then but what would happen to human
society to belief
To the way everything is structured
if
this
worked
Could you imagine the news that day it would filter out slowly
From the town of redding. Olive was alive
Most people wouldn't even know the backstory at this point three days in the controversy really hadn't started
But you would start to get wind in the news
A miracle it happened
And you could say well people who don't really follow religious news
They probably wouldn't know about it
But if your church succeeded in bringing back someone from the dead you would make sure everybody knew
There would be doubters. There would be skeptics
There would be people going to redding to see if it was actually true and you'd have the local coroner
Local police officers saying no, it's true. She had passed away and now she's back to life. Look at her and you would look
There's a young girl playing in the yard
Now here's the thing. There are already suggestions. We've talked about them early in the episode that the church of bethle has taken over
The city of redding
So skeptics would go that that's impossible
There was no way this girl could have come back from the dead and we know this church is infiltrating
The pillars of power. So who's not to say they already own the coroner? They already own the police department
It has to be fake. This can't have happened
But the story would still get out there that a little girl died and after three days of intensive prayer
She came back to life
It would change
everything
It would change the entire course of human history
Because not only would you have proof that it's possible to die and then come back three days later
Not only would you have proof of a faith of a billion people on this planet?
You would have proof that it could happen today
You would have proof that all the ministers all the clerics
All the rabbis of the world could talk about miracles all they wanted
But there was one church in redding, california that could actually raise the dead
What do you think would happen to every other religion overnight?
If it was proven that this group of 11,000 people had the key to immortality
They had the way the truth and the light
Their prayers
worked
Somewhere out there
In the infinite sea of alternate realities
Olive came back to life
Somehow some way
A miracle existed in the infinite expanse of time and space
She came back to life
And society completely restructured itself
Because a little girl defied death because the church worshiped and prayed so hard
That all notion of science all notion of
Established religions was broken over the course of three days
In that reality
So close to our own
Olive is alive again
In that reality that's so close to our own
Every religion has just formed into one the one religion that can provably work the church of bethel
In an alternate reality so close to our own
You have a church that doesn't work on infiltrating local government
But has already infiltrated the governments of the world
Bringing olive back wasn't just about restoring life
Into a two-year-old girl
Bringing olive back was about proving that bethel was the one true religion
Was proving that only they had a direct line to god
Performing the greatest miracle of the modern age
Proved that the church of bethel
Was the only true religion
One world
One religion
One miracle
And in that reality so close to our own
It's the perfect place for another biblical figure to make his appearance
The antichrist
Appears in that world
Not all miracles
Come from god
Dead rabbit radio at gmail.com is going to be our email address
You can also hit us up at facebook.com/dead rabbit radio
Twitter is @dead rabbit radio dead rabbit radio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast
You don't have to listen to it every day, but i'm glad you listen to it today. Have a great one guys
[Music]