"Would you attend a university that openly admits that some of their dorms are haunted
by a dead child?"
They put it in their brochure, they talk about it a lot, it's kind of weird.
And then we travel to Algeria to attend a wedding of a young couple.
When the soon to be bride is sobbing all day long, her father thinks that it's just wedding
day jitters.
Little does he know that she's been possessed by a demon.
Today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
"Hey everyone welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Carpenter, I'm having a great day.
I hope you guys are having a great day too.
I hope you guys are staying warm because I'm not.
I'm actually in the haunted closet recording this episode wearing thermals, a jacket and
a little fuzzy hat.
It's so cold and this episode will last exactly as long as I can stay warm.
But someone who's always warm, warm hearted at least.
Walking into Dead Rabbit Command right now, let's give it up for one of our Christmas
livestream contributors.
Everyone get on your feet and give it up for vexing.
Woohoo!
Yeah!
Walk on in, walk on into Dead Rabbit Command vexing.
Really, really appreciate all your support.
The Christmas livestream was awesome yesterday.
They had so much fun hanging out with you guys.
Vexing you're going to be our captain, our pilot this episode.
If you guys can't support the show financially, I totally understand and really do.
Just help spread the word about Dead Rabbit Radio.
That helps out so much.
Also had a ton of fun with yesterday's Christmas livestream.
That was really fun.
I love hanging out with you guys and if you guys aren't aware, I did drop the full audio
tracks for the intro and outro music.
Atlantis attacks and Bella Royale.
You guys have been asking for them for about four years and if you go to deadrabbitradio.lipson.com,
you can actually download the tracks onto your hard drive.
They're up on YouTube.
You can listen through your podcast app but you can download them if you go.
They're totally free.
You can go to deadrabbitradio.lipson.com to download them to your hard drive.
A lot of fun.
We're coming up to episode 1000.
Don't know if I'm going to do anything special?
Probably not.
Probably just being on the episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
But to me that is special because I love this show.
Vexxing, let's go ahead and toss you the keys to the dead rabbit dirgeable.
We're going to leave behind Dead Rabbit Command.
Fly us all the way out to good old California.
California, the land of surf and sun and not 17 degrees weather and ice storms which
is what's happening where I'm at.
We're in California.
Specifically we're headed down to San Rafael.
We're going to visit the Dominican University of California.
This is really interesting.
A lot of times I peruse the website theshadleands.net.
It's just a repository of ghost stories.
It's how I spend my Saturday mornings, honestly reading the news, then hopping over there,
hopping over to thinkaboutadox.com, trying to find good material for you guys.
And I came across this story very brief.
Like most of the stuff on theshadleands.net it's generally just a couple sentences.
In San Rafael there's the Dominican University and at that school there is a ghost known
as the blue boy who supposedly drowned in a bathtub.
It goes on to say some students say they have seen wet footprints near the site of the haunting.
It's a pretty generic description.
It doesn't describe life after death.
It doesn't describe a haunting vision of what awaits us all.
But other than that it's on the ghost website.
You see a lot of that stuff.
If you saw that appear on the New York Times you'd be like, "Wait, what?
But as far as on the ghost website."
Now here's this really caught my eye because I read tons of ghost stuff all the time.
This caught my eye because I myself have seen a blue boy ghost.
And it was hands down one of the most terrifying paranormal experiences I've ever had.
I've talked about it before on the show so I'm not going to go into a ton of detail about
it.
I'll put the episode in the show notes.
Just for context, I've seen what I can only describe as demons and demonically possessed
people.
I've seen shadowmen.
I've seen these huge black two dimensional dogs walking down the street.
These are all in previous episodes.
I'll put those episodes in the show notes as well.
You're like, "What?
This is my first episode, dude.
Are you like a huge meth head?"
No, I'm not that.
But I've seen things of that meth head see.
I've seen all sorts of crazy things in my life.
But the blue boy was the scariest of them all.
I remember I was driving through Orangevale, California.
That's where I used to live.
I used to go ghost hunting all the time.
Gas was 98 cents a gallon.
Oh man, it was beautiful.
Drive around.
Me and my buddies, we'd drive around.
We'd go to haunted places.
But anyways, I was doing this one by myself.
I was driving down this road in Orangevale.
I don't remember the exact name of the road.
I could find it on a map, but I'm not gonna.
It's too cold and I don't want to spend time looking it up on Google Earth.
It's in the Orangevale area.
It's pretty small.
It's a couple streets past Hazel.
It's going down this residential neighborhood.
And I was all by myself.
It was probably like 2, 3 in the morning.
And I see...
All of a sudden it was in front of my car.
Like I want to say it stepped in front of my car, but that wasn't the case.
All of a sudden, something was in front of my car.
It was about...
I'm really bad with kids' ages, but I'd say the kid was maybe like between 7 and 9.
I see a boy, a blue boy, standing in the middle of the road.
And it was very interesting.
I mean, that's interesting in and of itself, right?
This is the problem when you get jaded when you're researching paranormal stuff all the
time.
You're like, "Hmm, on a scale of 1 to 10, that's a 5.
A phantom of a child standing in the road."
It was more interesting than that.
I saw him.
He was dressed in clothes, right?
He wasn't wearing caveman clothes.
He wasn't necessarily wearing pioneer clothes.
If I had to guess the time period of the clothes, I'd say somewhere between the 60s and the
90s.
He's wearing like a shirt and jeans and stuff like that.
Pants, maybe.
Slacks.
Here's the thing.
I wasn't too interested in what he was wearing.
I'm driving down the road all of a sudden.
I'm just trying to classify it in some way.
I'm like, "What?
Those shoes don't fit you, young man."
I'm driving down the road and all of a sudden this boy is standing in front of my car and
I hit it.
I hit this boy.
What happens is he basically passes through my car as you would imagine a ghost to do.
I'm driving and this blue boy is now standing in the middle of this road.
Let me finish describing him.
I'm kind of getting off track.
I guess I'm going to spend more time talking about this than I thought.
It's hard to tell a short version of the story when you ran over a ghost because it's more
than that.
I'm driving down the road and this boy, his skin is blue, his clothes are blue.
But there's also this blue glow attached to him.
It's almost like there are shades of blue that make up his clothes and his face and
his hair.
His blue-ish.
You could tell that at one point when he was alive, it was probably black hair or dark
brown hair.
Now, how's the blue?
It's tint.
It's like someone took an X-Acto knife and cut out reality around him.
There's this blue, a lighter blue kind of outline around him.
This glow.
It's super interesting.
You could see it would be like someone just etched it out and what you're seeing behind
him is a bright blue shining through.
He's glowing blue.
He's blue.
I hit him with my car and I remember I'm driving and it just happened so quickly.
Let me stand my fingers better than that.
Happened like that.
I drive through him and I look in my rear view mirror and now he's sitting in my backseat.
I freaked out.
I kept driving.
It happens so instantly, but I remember it kind of taking my breath away a bit.
I see him in my backseat.
Then he disappeared.
It wasn't like I didn't then drive to my grandma's house and I was like, "Well, welcome home."
He's still sitting back there and he's like, "No, I want to go to Dairy Queen first."
I was like, "Ah."
I hit him.
He appears in the back in the rear view mirror and then he's gone and I drive home and I
think it was the next day or a day later.
I mean, obviously terrified me.
When I go back home, I think it was the day or two later.
I don't recall.
This story would have happened back in the late 90s.
I drove back out to that area to kind of get an idea of what it looked like during the
day and there was a creek.
I thought, "Oh, this could be true or it could be part of the imagination process."
You don't know.
With paranormal research, you just don't know.
I got the feeling that he had drowned in that area.
Now, it would be kind of hard for a nine-year-old to drown in a creek.
Not impossible.
Don't test it.
Don't be like, "Jason, I went out of five nine-year-olds.
I kidnapped three of them drowned."
Yes, you are right.
Don't test it.
It wasn't like a tiny creek.
It wasn't a raging river, but I just had the idea that this kid died in this creek.
I don't know.
Maybe he got hit by a car and fell in the water and he's unconscious and he drowned.
It's disturbing either way, but anyways.
That little jerk, that little blue boy haunted me for a long time.
Like I would see him around me.
I was terrified of him.
It was a malicious spirit.
It was definitely not something you'd want to hang around.
I remember I worked at Godfather's Pizza back in the day.
It got so bad.
I worked at Godfather's Pizza back in the day and I was talking to my friend Jackie
and I think Josh was there and then our boss, Jeff maybe?
What's his name?
I don't remember.
Jerry?
Anyways, we're sitting there.
We're talking at Godfather's Pizza and I see the little boy, little blue boy.
Wasn't a customer?
Wasn't just any nine year old that was freaking out.
I was like, "No!"
I see him raw.
It was the weirdest thing the way paranormal activity happens.
They're not tied down to our physical laws.
I see him basically, there was a little hallway back where the bathrooms were.
I see him right there.
We're probably a good like maybe 10, 15 feet away from this hallway at least in the bathrooms.
I see him kind of standing at the entrance of that hallway and then in a heartbeat he
was right in front of me.
Like my mind perceived him running but the time he just instantly was in front of me.
I'm standing there with friends and my boss and all of a sudden I scream.
I go, "Ahh!"
They saw a ghost, they saw a ghost right at me.
It was like 8pm.
It wasn't even that late.
I was terrified.
I was like, "This is the type of spirit that can ruin your life."
This is the type of thing where you're like trying to deliver pizzas and he's like tripping
you.
You're like, "Oh!"
Well even he doesn't even have to trip you.
He doesn't have to tie your shoelaces together.
He just appears in front of you.
You're carrying pizzas and he's like, "Boo!
You're gonna throw your pizzas."
And that's just pizza related.
Imagine if you were applying for another job because you got fired, you get drop in pizzas.
You're in an interview for a job and the blue boy is standing behind the boss and he's
like, "Nah, ah, ah, ah, don't hire this guy."
Like what?
Come on man, give me a chance.
Let me get a job here.
He's like, "No, don't hire him."
And the boss will be like, "Who are you talking to?
I will give you a chance."
Why do you keep looking over my shoulder?
Why have you peed your pants three times?
In a 15 minute interview, I was like, "Oh, the ghost."
This ghost could really mess with you.
If he's making you scream in public, a grown man, scream in public, what else could he
have done?
Eventually I stopped seeing the blue boy.
I really should look up, I'm gonna find that street because I will have to be in the cold
here for a second because it's not fair.
Let me see if I can pull it up here real quick.
Because it's not fair to tell a story like that and go, "Ugh, I don't remember where
it took place.
Really?"
Let me find my grandma's house and then I'm gonna kind of goof off.
So I think it was...
I can give you like a street or two.
I know there's a lot of people in Sacramento who listen to this podcast.
It's funny.
My grandma's house looks great.
The people who took it over are really good.
I think, okay, so there's...
It was one of three streets.
I can put it on that.
It was Philbert, Chestnut, or Walnut.
But anyways, yeah, if you're out in that area, you can draw...
I mean, it's such a rural...
It's such a rural place.
I'm pronouncing the word rural.
I'm saying rural like country if you guys can't understand and everyone's like, "Of course,
we can't understand."
Chestnut or Walnut.
And you would be able to identify it.
You just drive down and on the right hand side, you'll see a creek.
When I see a creek, it wasn't just like a little stream of water.
There was a bridge.
There was like a straight up like black top bridge with a metal railing built around it.
It was enough of a creek that you have to build a structure over it.
It wasn't just like some kid in cut off jeans catching crawdads type of creek.
Anyways, so yeah, I don't think it was Maine.
100% don't think it was Maine.
But if you live in that area, go ahead and drive on through.
Knock on every door and go, "Do you know about a kid who died here and get arrested?"
Trying to find my ghost.
It's creepy.
So let's get back to this ghost story though.
When I read about that, I go with the blue boy drowned in the bathtub.
I was like, "Dude, that reminds me of my blue boy."
And when you are a paranormal researcher, you want to find patterns.
Because then it does start to build.
You can start to kind of really investigate it as a phenomenon rather than a one off event.
If only one cow was ever found mutilated, you would just be like, "Well, this is weird."
The reason why cattle mutilations is a topic in the UFO community or the conspiracy theory
community is because we can look at these patterns and we can go, "Okay, it's not just
one cow.
It's been thousands of cows over the course of around 120 years.
Cattle mutilations have been going on since almost the turn of the century.
What could be causing this?"
Now we have a phenomenon.
We have a bunch of them.
But anyways, the blue boy phenomenon, I was like, "Okay."
And it would make sense when you drown.
They say you turn blue.
I had to actually look at a couple photos of drowning victims or drowned victims.
As I was getting ready for this segment, it wasn't the best part of my research.
When you have any sort of oxygen deprivation, you can turn blue.
Your lips can turn blue.
It's part of what's happening when you're dying.
They don't necessarily look blue.
They look more purple when you see a dead body that's drowned.
It can take a blueish appearance.
We have two basic...
Now we have a phenomenon, right?
We have two blue boys.
But let's take a look at this one.
This is what's so interesting about this story.
We have this little paragraph in the Shadowlands.net and I'll tell you right now, most of the stuff
I find on the Shadowlands.net that I want to cover, a lot of it's just basic ghost stuff.
Weird stuff that I want to cover.
A lot of times I will then try to dig in more.
I just don't want to read a paragraph to you and move on.
I've had to do that because I haven't been able to find anything else sometimes.
I'll find a really cool ghost story and I'll say this is the only thing I can find.
Let's talk about it.
That happens all the time.
This was one that I expected the same thing.
I was just like, "Let's talk about this blue boy.
It's a phenomenon now because I've had this similar experience."
I was able to find so much information about this ghost and what's even weirder is the
information comes from the university.
The information, most of the information we get is from Dominican University, which is
a Catholic college in San Rafael, California.
So apparently part of the college is a place called Meadowlands Hall.
It's this 30,000 square foot mansion that used to be owned by the De Young family, which
was a wealthy family back in the 1800s.
This mansion was built in 1888.
The college was founded in 1901 and pretty much next door and then eventually they purchased
the Meadowlands mansion in 1918 and became part of the college.
They didn't just get the mansion, they also got a ghost attached to it.
Most of this information I found on Dominican University's walking tour site on their alumni
site.
They really, really like telling this ghost story.
It's so funny because so many other colleges, so many other private and public institutions
are like, "Yeah, we don't really believe in ghosts."
These people, they're like, "Dude, you wanna hear something spooky?
Let's put this on our main website."
The story goes like this.
Back in the 1800s, the De Young family had a son with some mental health issues.
And it's the 1880s, what are you gonna do, right?
Feed him some mercury and hope he gets better.
They didn't have a lot of treatments for people with mental illnesses back then.
So according to the Dominican University's website, what the De Young family did was
keep him in the house all the time, because he would be an embarrassment if it got out
to this kid how crazy he was.
Now they don't say what he had.
We don't know if he was just a little rambunctious like a Dennis the Menace type character.
Or if he was like a wrong turn hillbilly crawling on all fours and barking.
We don't know.
Even between Dennis the Menace and inbred mutated freak, this child existed.
So this little boy, we don't have a name for him.
This little boy locked in his house all the time.
It's a mansion though, if you're gonna be trapped anywhere, which will be trapped in
a 30,000 square foot mansion.
It's not really a prison at that point.
Well one day, the family was out doing something that would be a prison, right?
Your family's like, "Let's go have a picnic in the crazy kids."
Like, "Me too, me too."
And they're like, "Wrong turn, why don't you stay in the house?
We will go outside.
You stay here, 'cause it's dangerous outside."
What?
Yeah, it's dangerous outside.
We're brave, we're brave enough to handle the danger, but not you.
Not you, WT.
So then he's scuttling around the mansion.
Well apparently, you can't leave like a crazy kid running around the mansion all by himself
when the family goes to come back in.
It's a home alone situation.
He's throwing anvils at them.
So there's a nanny who takes care of this little kid.
So on this particular occasion, while the entire family had left to go have fun without
this little boy, the nanny was giving him a bath and she just snapped.
Like whatever this kid was up to, it was just too much.
This particular day, the nanny's like, "I can't take it, I can't take it."
So she drowned this boy.
She held him under the water until he stopped breathing.
I don't know what drowned means.
Anyway, she kills this kid.
She immediately feels bad about it, which I imagine you would.
Like especially if it's in a situation like that where you just snapped.
You'd been down too many wrong turns too many times and you snap and you drown this kid
and she immediately felt bad about it so then she hung herself.
Which I imagine for the family coming back home, they're like, "What a delightful picnic.
God, we should have brought that mutated freak along."
Well, maybe next time honey, and then they walk in the door and they find a drowned boy
and a hanging nanny.
Now I don't know, Jason you were laughing a lot.
This kid being drowned.
I don't know if this story is true, it is posted on the Dominican University's website.
They do use a lot of times where it's like, "Legend say" or "The old stories" would
have it, but it's possible that this kid actually was murdered and in that case I shouldn't have
laughed and laughed so much.
Anyways, this boy's dead, the nanny's dead and to this day people still see the blue
boy because the mansion was turned into a dormitory.
I mean, that's awesome, right?
Even if you're living in a mansion, you're like, "I feel like a wrong turn mutant."
Oh man, this is so awesome in here.
They're like, "What are you talking about?"
And they're like, "Legend say."
Let me start telling you the story.
No, they have it as a dormitory.
I guess at one point it was also like an assembly area.
I'm sure it's kind of gone back and forth.
I don't know what it is used as today.
Either way, dormitory or assembly area, people have seen sightings of the blue boy ghost.
Some of these are pretty benign.
I mean, this is terrifying.
Don't get me wrong, you'd have a heart attack if you saw this.
But people say when they're walking down the hallway or they're in their room and there's
like a corner, it's kind of darkened, lights are off.
You walk into your room and they sit around the corner, you would see a bluish glow.
So you wouldn't directly see the boy but you would see him standing behind the corner.
You would know he's there because in the darkness you would see this bluish glow right behind
the corner.
So, I mean, that's terrifying.
This ghost definitely knows what to do to make it scary.
If you walked into a room, well, actually both of these are quite terrifying.
If you walked into a room and you saw a blue boy standing there, I guess that's actually
more scary than not seeing it.
But he's standing around the corner.
Yeah, I mean, imagine if you walked in and you go, "I think there's a skeleton behind
that corner."
Where he's just walking in and there's a skeleton dancing on your bed.
You'd be like, "Okay, I'm not sleeping in my bed tonight."
He stands behind the corner.
Also people have remarked that their bathrooms will get locked while they're not in them.
And that sucks, right?
You really gotta go to the bathroom.
Super inconvenient, right?
Because you only think about going into the bathroom when you need to be in the bathroom.
You gotta pee or poop or put on makeup, I guess, maybe, or two or three at the same time.
But bathrooms are generally not a place you go just out of a whim.
So getting locked out of it would suck.
But again, that's not like...there's worse things that could happen to skeletons dancing
on your bed.
Also though, like the main story is they'll say you'll see wet footprints around the area.
That's creepy.
We're talking about a manifestation.
We're talking about leaving physical evidence, which is rare for ghosts, to be able to do
that.
But wet footprints around the area.
But all of that stuff is terrifying, but it doesn't even compare to the power level
that a ghost would need to have to do this next one.
And this next one, I believe I found on the alumni website, the alumni Facebook page, the
bathtub that he was drowned in.
They kept it.
I don't think anyone else took a bath in it.
They're like, "Oh, it's your bathtub, little Billy."
They're like, "No, no, no, my brother was just drowned in that."
I'm sure they got a new bathtub.
I'm sure they got a new bathtub at some point, but they kept the old bathtub because this
was old-timies.
I'm sure that bathtub was super expensive.
It probably cost like $20 in old money.
So they kept the bathtub, but they took it up to the attic, which I'm sure was probably
wasn't easy carrying this big old 18th century bathtub up the stairs.
I would have made money to watch that.
They take the bathtub upstairs and they turn it over.
So the bathtub is still stored in the attic and it's flipped over.
But even with that, sometimes you'll go up into the attic and you will see water pouring
out of the bathtub.
So it's like some had, it's not hooked up to anything.
The water is still pouring out from somewhere and because the bathtub's flipped over, it's
just spilling all over the floor.
Or ceiling, really, because it's in your attic.
It's your ceiling if you're walking around downstairs.
You know, like above your head, you'd get a ton of water damage, which would be the
least of your worries because there's a dead boy.
There's a dead boy floating around.
I mean, that takes, we have ghosts that turn on water faucets.
That's super common.
And a long time ago, I found that website that said, "The reason why ghosts are always turning
on water faucets is because being dead makes you thirsty."
Which is a creepy idea.
Super creepy.
I would hope that being dead is like the most comfortable thing in the world.
Not that you're like, "I'm parched and I'll be parched for a million years."
The other idea is the reason why ghosts turn on the water fountains is because they can
transmit their energy easier through water.
We do see a lot of cultures combine water and running water with the paranormal.
And that the bigger body of water or the more flow that water has, the more violent the
spirit can become.
The paranormal ghosts in particular and water have very, very close connection.
So the idea is they're turning on the water, it's basically allowing, it's giving them
more energy to pull off of.
The other thing, the skeptical answer is just the water's faulty and that's something that
can easily turn on.
That's water and like, cause a lot of times water and lights are being affected by ghosts
and they go, "Those are two things that can, are pretty easy to just over time not work
correctly.
Your lights turning on and off is just bad wiring and your water turning on and off is
just pipes.
It's an issue with pipes.
The handle isn't turning itself.
It's just the mechanisms are starting to get bad and the same thing we would call a leaky
faucet over time it will just leak and leak more.
So those are the three options.
But when you have a bathtub that's not hooked up to anything and it's interesting that it's
turned over.
You can understand the logical reason why you would turn a bathtub over so a bunch of
raccoons don't make a house in there.
But I'm wondering if originally the bathtub was upright in the attic and it kept filling
full of water.
So to prevent that they go, "Well let's just tip it over.
I mean this thing's obviously haunted.
Let's tip it over and the problem is it's still filling up with water.
The water now is just instantly spilling all over the floor."
Now it's possible that Dominican University, they love these ghost stories because they're
fun and whimsical.
I mean they're not super whimsical.
It involves a child being murdered and then suicide.
It's possible that they don't...
Well I was going to say it's possible that they're playing these stories up for spookiness
sake but it's interesting because most of these places downplay the stories.
Sometimes during Halloween they'll have a ghost tour at this university or this hotel
or something like that.
But we've come across a ton of institutions, whether they're cities, like what's that one
in Connecticut.
It's a weird, it's like dark forest.
It's a place called like dark forest or something like that.
I'll put the episode on the show notes but...
Or Stoll Cemetery in Kansas.
They will actually have police arrest you if you're out ghost hunting in these areas.
They have signs of saying there are no ghosts, stay away or you'll get arrested.
Some of these places have really, really strict trespassing laws.
Some of these institutions, they go there are no ghosts and Dominican University seems
to be playing it up which makes me think they're having a laugh or they do believe in it.
Maybe they've seen, maybe the deans like, "You know what?
I've seen the blue boy a hundred times.
We're putting it on the website.
I'm tired of people saying that it's not real.
It's real.
And maybe if we put it on the website people will believe me.
A fascinating and terrifying story indeed.
That went a little bit longer than I thought but I think we have time for this.
Vaccine, let's go ahead and toss you the keys to the world famous Carpenter Coptter we're
leaving behind.
Santa Rafael, wave goodbye to that blue boy.
He's not following us under any circumstances.
Fly us all the way out to Algeria.
And I want to give a shout out to Bad June.
Bad June, Patreon supporter, very active in the Patreon Discord.
Sent me over this story.
It's absolutely fascinating.
And this story was posted on Twitter by someone going by the name STW and then some sort of
pink bird at Madrid guy or no that's not his name.
At Magery guy.
We're going to Bled Algeria and we're going to attend a wedding.
You wore your formal wear right?
I always wear my formal wear when I'm hunting ghosts.
We're walking around a little blue boy.
He's the ring bearer.
We're like get out of here.
We told you you can't follow us.
We're in Bled Algeria and we're about to meet this young woman.
She's in her 20s.
We don't have anyone's name.
Apparently the person who posted this, this was his cousin I believe.
Yeah, cousin.
So he is directly related to the participants in the story but he didn't give any names.
Let's go ahead and call her Sarah.
So Sarah is this young woman she's in her 20s and she's about to get married to a wonderful
man.
She loves this guy.
She can't wait to start her new life with him but it's the day of the wedding and Sarah
is crying.
You know her dad's watching this and he's like oh my poor little girl.
My poor little girl's crying but you know wedding day jitters is what he figures.
She's just crying because she's about to start a new life.
I'm just going to say goodbye to her family.
This is natural.
After the ceremony it's time for Sarah to join her new husband at his house but she
becomes incredibly ill.
She says I don't want to see anybody.
I want to be left alone.
Oh Sarah you've got to go to this house.
You've married this guy.
It's time to go home with him.
No, I don't want to be around anybody.
I don't want to go to that house.
I just want to be left alone.
That would be odd enough.
It's quite the personality change but she also begins to talk to herself and not just
talk to herself which again is alarming but she's saying crazy things.
Now the pink bird guy doesn't tell us exactly what the crazy things are.
Like is it two teapots are standing on my head?
That type of stuff like lyrics from They Might Be Giants or she's like saying I'm going
to cut myself open.
I'm going to bleed dogs.
I'm going to turn to town, bled Algeria into what its name is.
They're like no Jason you're clearly mispronouncing the name of that town.
There's not a place in the world called bled.
Anyways, we don't know what crazy things she's saying but some time is passing and she's
still just muttering to herself.
She hasn't gone to the dude's house.
She's still staying at her old home apparently with her parents.
They start to realize that something's really wrong with Sarah.
They start to believe that she might be possessed.
Or maybe not if outright possessed under the influence of darker forces.
So they consult an amam.
They bring them in and they go hey something's up with their daughter she's acting super
weird.
And he talks to her he's doing this investigation and he does come to the conclusion that yes
there is a dark spirit attached to her so what they do is what's called a rakia or
it's a counterspell is one way to put it.
It's also would be the equivalent would be an islamic version of an exorcism.
They do a rakia and this is so fascinating.
The story is so weird.
I love stories like this.
Ba June thank you so much for sending this over.
I love stuff like this.
What she has attached to her so in the English language we have the demon which is a fallen
angel someone who's cast down by God during the war the rebellious war of Satan and one
third of the angels against God.
Those angels and Satan were sent to earth and that is what we call a demon.
In the islamic tradition there's a thing called the jinn and it's not a direct correlation
between the two.
The jinn have some differences that Christian demons do not and this is a big one.
This is a big one apparently in the islamic tradition the jinn can choose to follow a
particular religious faith.
That's fascinating.
We covered something that a long time ago we covered a story where I think it was the
prophet Muhammad was confronted by these jinn and he converted them by speaking the
words from Allah he converted them to Islam and these jinn then became islamic and they
were saved.
In the Christian tradition that's impossible the demons have committed the unforgivable
act of rebelling against God and while they do have free will in a sense because they
chose to fight in that way they're pretty much the bad guys they're the henchmen background
characters in this whole saga between God and Lucifer and Jesus and all that stuff.
I've never come across any stories in the Christian faith of demons and I've wondered
about that I think we did an episode on that.
Could a demon accept Jesus Christ as his Lord and Savior and then go to heaven?
And I've asked ministers that I ask the weirdest questions to people all the time.
Is that possible?
When the islamic tradition it's not a theory that we actually have versions of that so
the jinn now in Algeria there no one as a noun or j'noun one of the two it's spelled
J-N-O-U-N it's the same thing as a jinn I don't know if the J is silent but anyways
I probably can check that out but June said hey do you need any help translating this
I'm like nope I probably did I probably did I was like I'll just use the translator
there Google translate it'll be good anyways there's a different version the same different
name for them in Algeria in typically they're known as jinn's in Algeria they're known
as j'nouns or nouns anyways what's fascinating about this is that this spirit I'll just use
the word jinn because I know how to pronounce it this jinn that is attached to Sarah is
he's Jewish it's a Jewish jinn it's a Jewish jinn it's a Jewish demon it's not a demon
from Jewish theology it's a jinn who follows the religion of Judaism and it is attached
itself to this young girl Sarah fascinating we're not even done we're not even done we're
not even done anyways this a mom says okay listen this Jewish jinn is attached itself
to Sarah we're gonna do this Rockia he probably pronounced it correctly we're gonna get rid
of it and they do and she actually starts to feel better but he goes listen he goes
the way that this works is that somewhere there is a bewitched item someone is like someone
set out to put this on her and we have to find the bewitched the cursed item and destroy
it to completely get rid of this the jinn could come back to get her through investigation
the imam says the item is a cake he saw he saw I will eat all the cakes I'll find out
where the curse is they're like oh we shouldn't have gotten the hungry imam to show up he says
the curse is hidden in a cake and apparently there are these little again probably translation
errors the cupcake type things the bridal party we're gonna have these cakes called Mac
Rodos Mac Rods anyways it's these time there's 300 there's 300 of them at a point it's not
like there's just one wedding cake and you're like okay guys everyone grab a fork let's
find this curse there's 300 cakes and one of them is cursed one of them has to be destroyed
the reason why you know it's cursed because inside it's wet it's moist and wet on the
inside and these cakes shouldn't be like that so the people the people the family of the
bridal party begins to crush these cakes they're trying to find the wet one and they don't
they go through all of them and none of them are wet so the girls doing a little bit better
I mean I'm sure that is a relief when there's a demon no longer attached to you but again
it might come back well you also got to do all your regular stuff you can't be like oh
I'm not coming into work today boss my daughter got possessed by a Jewish demon so you know
and they're like Johnny Johnny you've used that excuse three times this week when is
the demon leaving your daughter you got to get back to work you have to go and do the
normal stuff well the mom the mom of the bride she had borrowed stuff from people for the
wedding right you're not going to go on by a plate that you're only going to use once
she actually had borrowed a plate from a neighbor and she had to go return it to the neighbor
and she goes so weird she goes I need to give this plate back to my neighbor but I don't
want to bring it back empty because she let me borrow it I want to give her something
how about how about these cakes how about these undisturbed cakes that for some reason
we didn't find earlier I'm going to stack a couple of these cakes up on this plate and
go give it to my neighbor so the mom puts the cakes on the plate and she begins walking
down the stairs and she falls she she hella pales down the stairs and she gets to the
bottom and she's sitting there and she goes that shouldn't have happened like 100% like
something tripped me and she immediately begins to go through the cakes on the plate now again
it could be a translation error when they said they destroyed them all earlier maybe
they were just checking the middle this time she's actually breaking the cakes open and
she breaks one of the cakes open and it's wet and moist in the middle so that was the
cursed cake and she knew it when she fell down those stairs she knew that what she didn't
just trip not like she didn't know where she was going something tripped her and she broke
that cake open right there and then the daughter started feeling much much better like before
she was on a slow road to recovery but now she was getting better what's interesting is
that Matt madry guy says she's not 100% she still talks to herself but she's getting
better which is interesting because you imagine getting possessed by just having something
in your body that's not supposed to be there would leave some lingering effects like even
though the demon got exercised from her she's still suffering neurological damage like she's
not communicating with whatever it was but you would have to imagine it would cause if
not permanent damage long term damage and it's a good thing right that they found that
cake if they had they just thrown the cakes away and not destroyed it I mean eventually
I'm sure a crow crow would fly by and eat it at a garbage dump or something like that
but this would have gone on longer and the gin most likely would have repossessed her
so it's fascinating story cursed I mean obviously a skeptic can go issues have suffered from
some sort of mental illness all that stuff right it's possible but in the world of paranormal
we're gonna wear our conspiracy caps and look at this as what it's being said to be it's
a demonic possession of a young woman now why it chose her what's interesting is it
seems like she was targeted some of the stuff some of the things we have to fill in who be
which during the first place I don't think it was the gym was just floating around like
someone maybe a jealous rival or whatever targeted her but she was the one that it was
coming after that's fascinating but what I love about the story about June when he
sent it over he posted it on the discord he added this and we're gonna wrap it up like
this and what a crazy possibility bad June says quote the poster meaning madriguy on
Twitter the poster explains that while a lot of people were surprised the gin was Jewish
they're using the word down but just because they still don't know if I know how to pronounce
that the poster explains that while a lot of people were surprised the gin was Jewish
gins are like people and have religious affiliation so that that's an interesting point we've talked
about that before in the podcast but check this part out this part is nuts this next
part is nuts I love doing this show I'm so glad you guys enjoy listening to it the poster
explains that while a lot of people were surprised the gin was Jewish gin are like people and
have religious affiliations which can be problematic for example if the gin is Muslim you can't
use the Quran to fight it because it would just make him stronger dude that's crazy that
is nuts and we've talked about this and even people who are just passing like have a passing
interest in the paranormal or just their out and out skeptics they'll say like well what
if the ghost was Jewish and then you're using the Bible but he doesn't believe in the Bible
then it wouldn't work or vampire like why does a crucifix affect a vampire what if the
vampire was Jewish it's kind of like a joke it's kind of like a meme but this is the answer
like if you have a Jewish spirit a Jewish demon who's decided to go down the path of
Judaism and it possesses someone in Israel for example and you bring a rabbi out to exercise
that spirit by reading those verses that that demon believes in they're like oh yeah no
I love that verse that verse is what helped me convert to Judaism what are you talking
about that's awesome it makes me stronger or if you had a Muslim demon and you were reading
from the Quran he's like oh no yeah thanks dude that just made me stronger super fascinating
and that does jive with what we know of it's so interesting because gin and demon is it
just a translation thing is it are they the same being like some times it seems like they
are sometimes it does seem like they are the fallen ones that are meant to deceive us but
gin seem to have way more self-awareness and way more freedom to do what they want to do
demons are basically stock characters now we have demons in the Christian theology what's
interesting so when a lot of times people talk about like the Grand Ark Bishop of Hell we
have all those creatures like ball Barith and zippy do or whatever there's all sorts
of weird ones out there game G game G I think was a donkey if I remember correctly that
we wrote them around in an episode we have all that all came very very late in Christianity
like 1514 1516 century when Catholic monks and Catholic priests were supposedly communicating
with demons to write these grand lists of demons in Protestant religion none of that stuff
is real none of it like you will never you may because in a couple times in the Old Testament
I'm not going to go on and on about this because I don't want to talk about the Bible I watched
the listenership just plummet but when you look at the Old Testament there are very few
names of demons mentioned Molok is mentioned by name and Bales above I believe is mentioned
by name Lucifer there's even questions if Lucifer and Satan are the same person Satan
technically means adversary so it's a catch all term but Lucifer was an actual being but
there's no sense we know that like when Jesus showed up demons were afraid of Jesus but
there's no sense where they're actually have any sort of free will or they can make decisions
for themselves they're just lackeys so that we don't know if the gin and the demons are
one for one comparison a demon in Christian theology may have zero free will I've heard
a lot of people say that and that's why they were jealous of humans because humans had
free will because that was really the war between Lucifer and God God loved humans more than
the angels and Lucifer goes we're your greatest creation he's like no you're not they are
that's what really started this whole thing but to have free will to rebel against God
you would need to have free will it's all it's all messy right it's all messy you have to
go through all this fascinating stuff but could a demon decide to follow the works of
Jesus Christ like truly say you know what I think he was a pretty good guy and actually
believe he was a son of God and if that's the case if he possessed someone and a priest
came out to exercise that demon from that body would the Catholic rites of exorcism
only make the demon stronger you go Jason well if he's following the path of Jesus
Christ why would he be possessing people in first place I would say there's a lot of
Christians that do horrible stuff right just because you're a Christian doesn't mean you
never sin or you don't thirst for power you don't do evil things tons of people of religions
still do evil things against their religion so I don't I mean it's fascinating story it
really does make you wonder about the nature of these creatures gin demons like what are
they can they do they have the free will to start following religion see I've always
thought that made me hopeful that if even they could go wow I was wrong this was the
wrong thing for me to do I'm gonna start worshiping God again there's hope for them then there
truly is hope for anybody that's how I always looked at it I never thought that I would
give them superpowers I never thought that if you had a demon go you know what I kind
of like this whole Judaism thing I'm gonna roll with these dudes for a while I think
it would make them immune to exorcism from rabbis it's absolutely fascinating stuff and
bad June thank you so much for sending over like I love this type of because it's a theory
and a spooky story wrapped in a one it's something we've never heard of before we've heard inklings
of it we had that story we covered about the gin who converted to Islam we're like oh that's
cool there's hope for even the ones who have been thrown down from heaven from the dark
forces there's hope for them but again I didn't think that then super but you're like yeah
and if that's the case we didn't have a sort on that too I said what if you had a demon
from another religion go to a continent where that religion isn't practiced I thought it
would be harder to exorcism but it turns out it's the inverse if you had a demon who believed
in the religion of that culture like truly believed in it they weren't an Easter and
Christmas only demon they went to church all the time well could that's an interesting
question too could a demon who followed Christianity go to church like would it be able to walk
above consecrated ground it's fascinating stuff and what an awesome story to lead into
episode 1000 because it's stuff like this that makes me love doing this show and it's
stuff like this that honestly the fact that you guys love listening to it and we are dead
rabbit radio just fills me with so much joy and passion for this stuff I spent a lot of
time researching this stuff but I don't mind it because it's so awesome to share it with
you guys and we are dead rabbit radio it doesn't exist with just me like what a journey we've
been on and we're just getting started 100% just getting started dead rabbit radio at
gmail.com is going to be your email address you can also put us up at facebook.com/DeadRabberRadio
Tiktok is at dead rabbit radio dead rabbit radio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and
true crime podcast you don't have to listen to it every day glad you listened to it today
have a great one guys.
[Music]