A new drug has hit the streets of America, with side effects that are so horrifying.
It's like something out of Robocop.
But without the Robocop it'd be fine if there was a cyborg walking around, but it's not.
It's just people suffering.
It's so crazy.
And then we look at one of the hottest true crime stories taking place this month, but
this one may have a paranormal twist.
When four college students are brutally murdered, police quickly apprehend a suspect.
But is it possible they have the wrong man?
Is it possible the real killer was Bigfoot?
Today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Carpenter, I'm having a good day.
I hope you guys are having a good day too.
I'm having a good day because this is the first episode I'm recording since my COVID
diagnosis.
The last two episodes are actually pre-recorded, but man that COVID really knocked me for
a loop.
But I'm feeling really good now.
I'm feeling a lot better.
I'd say I'm 90%.
I'm still a little sleepy.
I just woke up from a nap right now to record this episode.
It's due in like two hours.
I gotta have this episode out for you guys.
And I just want to thank you guys for your warm wishes and the get well soon and everything
that I got over the course of my sickness.
But someone who always has warm wishes for me, whether I'm sick or not, walking into
Dead Rabbit Command right now, everyone give it up for one of our newest Patreon supporters,
Steve.
Woohoo!
Yeah Steve!
Come on in buddy!
I don't want to be here on the COVID episode.
I got one more day of being contagious.
Come here and give me a big old hug.
Steve you're going to be our captain, our pilot this episode.
If you guys can't support the show financially, I totally get it.
I really do.
Just help spread the word about Dead Rabbit Radio.
That really helps out so much.
And very quick, I have some awesome news.
This is so cool.
This is another thing I've been so excited to tell you guys about.
In March, in the city of Seaside, Oregon, there is the Oregon Ghost Conference.
It's an annual convention they've had going on now for 10 years.
This will be the 11th annual Oregon Ghost Conference.
I'm going to be a speaker there.
I will be giving a presentation live at the Oregon Ghost Conference in Seaside, Oregon
this year.
I will give you guys more details as it comes closer.
The Oregon Ghost Conference runs from March 24th to March 26th.
I don't know what day I'm speaking on or what time I'm speaking on or anything like
that.
I probably could have waited until I had that information but I couldn't wait to tell you.
I will be a speaker at the Oregon Ghost Conference.
It's a 50 minute long presentation.
I can't wait.
That's going to be awesome.
I'm so excited about it.
And this excitement, I hope you guys can feel it.
And thank you guys.
Thank you for putting me at this point where I can be a speaker at the Ghost Conference.
When I was doing the UFO Festival, I remember my friend Sabine came out.
She helped me there.
She helped set everything up.
She hung out with me while I had this haunted museum at the UFO Festival.
I remember I turned to her and I go, "Next time I want to be a speaker at one of these."
The rain is falling down on my head.
And the line for the bathroom was half hour long.
I said, "I'm going to push people out of the way and be like, "Get out of the way, guys.
I'm a speaker."
I'm so excited about this.
I think you guys can tell.
It's going to be really cool.
If you guys can come out to see it, it would be really, really cool.
Steve, let's go ahead and start off by tossing you the hair hang glider.
Let's jump off the highest point of Dead Ravica Man and glide all the way out to Philadelphia.
We're not headed to Philly, though, to run up the famous stairs, the Rocky Stairs.
I don't know what they're actually called.
It's probably like, actually, historical landmark that was made before Rocky.
I don't think they built them for Rocky to run up.
We're not there for that.
We're not there to check out Patty's pub.
No.
We should stop by those places anyways, right?
Let's go for a run up the Rocky Stairs and let's grab a drink at a fictional pub.
I don't even think it exists, but someone I'm sure is using that name in that city, Patty's
pub.
But after we've hung out at those two places, I go, "Hey, let's go here.
I've got another tourist attraction for you.
Come on.
Let's go over this way."
You're like, "Oh, what could it be?
Could it be the Liberty Bell?"
You ask yourself as we are walking deeper into the city.
And eventually I go, "Here is the number one tourist destination of Philadelphia."
And you look out on this open street and you're like, "Jason, I don't think this is part of
the tour.
Not only that, but someone just took my wallet and you see a guy running past us and he's
like, "I got it.
I got all the money, guys.
Give me drugs."
You're like, "What?"
We're currently standing.
Now we have no clothes on.
We're just standing there in our underwear.
Everything else has been stolen.
We're currently standing in one of the biggest open-air drug markets in America.
It's not like a farmer's market.
It's not like some guys are like, "Get your heroin here.
Come on."
He has big bushels of heroin.
People are walking up there like, "Is it organic?"
And he's like, "Oh."
It's just where people sell drugs.
It's where people, the crime situation is so bad that people openly sell drugs and the
police are like, "We got other stuff to do, plus we don't want our clothes stolen."
This giant open-air drug market in Philadelphia, and there's currently, this has been the past
couple of months, this has been growing, but I recently read an article that was published
in The New York Times about how, not how bad the drug problem has become in Philadelphia
because again, they're just selling this stuff openly in the middle of the street.
It's been bad for a while.
But how bad the drugs have become.
Heroin is now one of the hardest drugs to find in America.
Not only are the drug addicts kind of shocked by this, the people who steady drugs, the
people who look at the science of addiction and all of this stuff, they're like, "This
is so weird.
Heroin is now one of the hardest drugs to find in the United States."
Now you can walk into an open-air drug market and you can buy heroin, and you can get heroin,
but it's not heroin anymore.
What happened is basically you had such a crackdown on the opioid market.
So it's even hard to get prescription painkillers nowadays.
If you get them from your doctor, you're lucky, you can turn around and sell them for like
$5 a pill.
I'm not endorsing you doing that.
But prescription opioids, there's been such a crackdown on prescribing them, they're very
hard to get.
Now you can go and buy a bottle of hydrocodone or a bottle of OxyContin, but it's not that
anymore and the heroin is not that anymore either.
It's fentanyl.
It used to be that you would get a little bit of heroin when you went to go buy heroin
from your dealer, you'd get a little bit of heroin.
You get a little bit of heroin mixed with a little bit of fentanyl, which is a synthetic
opioid.
So you would still feel the effects of a painkiller.
And it got to the point where dealers started going, "Okay, well, we can get this heroin,
put a little bit of fentanyl in it, and it'll still be super potent and people will get
addicted to the fentanyl in the heroin that we're selling."
So if you went and just did normal heroin, it's not going to give you a full fix anymore
because now you've become addicted to the fentanyl.
What's happened to the heroin market is a one-two punch.
First off, heroin was becoming more rare anyways.
When the US withdrew their forces from Afghanistan, the Taliban, who then took the country back
over, they had owned it previously, the Taliban has never been a fan of opioids.
And Afghanistan would have fields, just as fields as far as I can see of poppies, just
where you get opium from.
Well, the Taliban, after the US pulled out, the Taliban told the poppy farmers, "You
get one more season.
We'll let you harvest the poppies you have right now.
But after that, you're going to have to start growing wheat or pickles or something else
because we're not going to allow you to grow more poppies.
We're not going to allow you to produce opium.
It's against what we stand for."
It is pretty weird when the Taliban, I think, has a better state of mind than the US government
who came in and was like, "Oh, just grow whatever you want.
People have CIA funded planes to fly it out on the regular.
Just grow the opium."
The Taliban came in.
I don't agree with the Taliban on much.
Probably just this one thing, honestly.
It shouldn't be growing mass amounts of poppies.
So all of a sudden, you have a huge...
It goes from having just a little bit of heroin to no heroin.
This was one of the most popular street drugs for decades.
And now it's going back to no heroin.
You just can't get it in the United States.
So now we're just getting fentanyl and people are selling it as heroin.
A lot of drug addicts go, "Kids nowadays have never done heroin."
And they never will.
They're addicted to fentanyl.
It's called heroin on the street.
It looks like it.
But it's not the heroin high that we grew up with.
And they also said that was another thing.
Before you would have an old heroin user.
You could have people who did heroin like Philip Seymour Hoffman.
They go, "That doesn't exist anymore."
Neither does he, unfortunately.
He passed away from heroin overdose.
They go, "You could used to have people who could be on heroin for a long time.
Maybe they get clean and get back on it.
Maybe they never try to get clean and they just stay on it for a long time."
They go, "Fentanyl's not like that.
People die young when they're addicted to fentanyl."
But that's not what we're talking about.
Because now an even worse drug...
I mean, this...
What I'm about to talk about is so dystopian.
I was shocked.
I read this article and then I started watching documentaries and things on this.
It's been around for a couple months in the United States, probably a little bit longer.
But now it's becoming a public health emergency.
This is so insane.
There's a brand new drug on the market.
Because fentanyl has now become hard to source.
The number one importer of fentanyl to the United States, it's synthetic.
You can just make it in the laboratory.
It was China.
And President Trump said, "You can't ship this stuff over to America anymore.
It's killing people.
It's wiping out an entire generation.
A hundred thousand people died last year of drug overdoses.
That's the biggest amount.
And I think that was primarily opioids.
A hundred thousand Americans died last year due to drug overdoses.
And that's wartime numbers.
So China, to their credit, it took a while.
It took a while.
They're kind of himminin' on.
But China eventually said, "Okay, we're going to declare in China that fentanyl is a controlled substance."
So now you just can't produce it in the laboratory and put it on a plane and ship it over.
We're not going to allow that anymore.
Now, is there some seepage?
Yeah, is this stuff still being produced over there?
Yeah, but at a much smaller amount than it was before, this slack's kind of been picked up in Mexico.
They'll have some fentanyl labs down there, but it's nowhere near the amount of fentanyl that was previously just coming over.
So what do the drug addicts do?
What do the drug dealers do, right?
You need to create a drug that people are going to have.
And that is where we now have Trank.
Trank, T-R-A-N-Q, is the stuff of nightmares.
We've heard stories before about Crocodile.
That was a drug that we would see pop up in Russia and Eastern Europe.
It was for people who were so desperate to get high that they would take basically Coding Cough syrup.
Because a lot of opioids you can openly buy in other countries.
You can buy Coding Cough syrup over the counter in most of Europe.
America has a serious drug problem.
I can't figure out why it's us.
We cannot have Coding Cough syrup sold over the counter.
But they do, and in Russia, people were desperate to get high, and they were looking for a cheap high.
And they began to take Coding Cough syrup and run all these chemicals through it to make it more potent.
And when you injected it into your body, over time, the wound that you were injecting into would start to necrotize.
And your skin would start to look like a crocodile.
It would become black and leathery right at the ejection site.
And if you didn't stop, you would start to show the effects as if you had a flesh eating virus.
You would start to lose skin and muscle tissue around the ejection site.
Trank is far worse than that.
This stuff is brutal.
What it is, it is fentanyl.
There's no heroin left, right?
It is just fentanyl mixed with a drug called xylazine.
It is a legal, uncontrolled substance that is used to tranquilize cows and horses.
Vets use xylazine as a tranquilizing drug.
Super, super sedative effects.
Trank is fentanyl, which is already so dangerous, mixed with xylazine.
You can't snort it.
It's way too painful.
You have to inject it into your body.
And what happens is, give yourself an injection and you immediately pass out.
Because the xylazine is that strong.
You're just like, I need to get high.
You inject yourself, you immediately pass out.
You wake up eight hours later.
And you're already sick from fentanyl withdrawal.
You've gone through withdrawal while you were high on Trank.
So when you come to, you immediately need more drugs.
You don't even get the people go, I inject myself with this,
like I was a heroin addict and then I just started using fentanyl.
But now when I use Trank, which is all I can find,
now when I use Trank, I immediately pass out.
And then when I wake up hours later, I'm already sweating and pooping my pants
because I'm going through fentanyl withdrawal.
And you're lucky if that's all that happens, people.
They call it the robbery drug because people, you're hanging out.
A lot of people, drug use is a social activity.
You inject yourself with Trank.
You wake up eight hours later, all your stuff's gone.
This isn't even the worst part, by the way.
This right here would just be a bad drug.
Trank, super addictive, because what happens is you get addicted
to the tranquilizing effects as well.
So then ordinary fentanyl doesn't do it anymore.
You need more Trank.
That's not the worst part.
The worst part is this chemical is so toxic to the human body.
People's limbs, limbs, not just their skin.
People are losing arms and legs because they are addicted to Trank.
It's something that you would see in some sci-fi horror movie like Robocop
or Repo, the genetic opera.
Something that if you saw in a book or in a cyberpunk novel,
you'd be like, wow, that's a little extreme.
No one would be addicted to a drug that makes their legs fall off.
This is what the drug does.
You inject it into your arm and you'll lose a leg.
That doesn't happen immediately.
It's not like you're like, oh man, I can't wait to get high
and then you wake up, you're like, ah, my leg.
But it does happen.
It has this weird reaction to the human body that it appears that their skin has a huge
chemical burn on it.
Like there's a lot of footage and a lot of photos of these people.
And it looks like their arms have been dipped in acid.
Like even crocodile was localized to where you injected it.
You inject it into your arm and you start to have this reaction over time.
It's not a long period of time either.
Where you start to develop this massive chemical burn on your leg.
It's totally random.
You don't know where it's going to appear.
And you keep doing the trink.
People keep losing skin and then muscle tissue and then tendons and it becomes infected.
And eventually the doctors are like, we're going to have to amputate your leg.
And people are so addicted to trink that even after they've had limbs chopped off,
they're continuing to use.
Here's a quote from the New York Times article.
They interviewed this woman named Brooke Peter.
She's 38 years old and here's this quote from her experience quote.
She unrolled a bandage from elbow to palm.
Beneath patches of blackened tissue, exposed white tendons and pus, the sheared flesh was hot and
red.
To stave off xylosanes excruciating withdrawal, she said.
She injects a trank dope several times a day.
Fearful that injecting in a fresh site could create a new wound,
she reluctantly shoots into her festering forearm.
The trank dope literally eats your flesh, she said.
It's self-destruction at its finest.
But it doesn't matter where you shoot it up.
It really doesn't.
They don't know why.
This is so new.
These effects are so new.
They don't know why if you shoot up in the arm you'll lose a leg.
But you can watch video after video.
I'll put some in the show notes and you can look up the photos.
People are losing legs.
People are losing arms.
People are dying obviously.
That's the end result of having such a horrid drug addiction.
It's insane.
It really does feel so dystopian.
I mean there is a little bit of ethnocentrism here because when I read about what was going on
in Eastern Europe with the crocodile,
you go "Wow, that's insane.
That's so awful."
But it was also so far away.
And I know that crocodile had hit America,
but it was such a garbage drug.
And there were so many other drugs available, heroin for one.
The people weren't really using crocodile like we were seeing over in Russia and Eastern Europe.
But this is an American phenomenon.
This is an American drug.
It's absolutely hellish.
And people are using these drugs.
The New York Times, they were saying that when they were doing these interviews with people,
at one point there was a guy sitting on the street who was injecting
Trank into his leg stump.
He was just sitting there in a wheelchair in Philadelphia,
lost his leg at some point due to Trank use,
and now he's injecting his stump with more Trank.
They've said 90% of the "Heroine"
in Philly is now Trank.
And it will spread to the rest of the United States.
This will become a main drug of choice,
because you can't get the opioids like we used to.
It's terrifying, right?
It really, really is scary.
We can't tell China to stop shipping it in.
We can't put troops along the border to keep it from coming in from Mexico.
Xylazine is legal to have today.
You could drive around with a truckload full of it.
There's not against the law.
Again, that is not a recommendation, okay?
I'm not saying, you know, get into this business.
But they'll make it illegal at some point, but
Trank.
I mean, again, like if somebody told you there was a drug on the streets today that
thousands of people are using today, probably tens of thousands,
that makes their limbs fall off, and they know that.
You'd be like, that's not true.
Nobody is that desperate.
Heroin can make you addicted and you need to lose in your house and your job,
and you're sleeping in a gut or somewhere, but that's so far off.
That's so abstract.
You go, no, I only use on the weekends.
You can't really tell someone who's using heroin that, you know,
this could happen to you.
You could lose all this stuff.
But I mean, Trank, this is the new drug.
This is the new fentanyl heroin.
You can't get it now.
Well, you can in some parts of the country.
You can still get it without Trank, but it's so strong.
That how long will you be able to even buy fentanyl?
Will fentanyl eventually also become a distant memory?
And before we would go good.
There's no heroin in America.
That's awesome.
There's no heroin addiction anymore.
That's great.
There's no fentanyl.
That's even better.
That was even worse than heroin.
But this is what is coming to replace it.
Something that is straight out of Robocop with their nuke.
That's what it was reminding me of the whole time in Robocop too.
They had, this is nuke.
This is the most powerful street drug.
And then that didn't make you fall apart.
It was just a super powerful addictive drug
that only a cyborg could stop distribution of it.
I spent a lot of time talking about that.
So I'm going to do a switch up.
We are going to save the Moscow, Idaho story for tomorrow.
But I got a short but crazy one.
This is another super crazy conspiracy theory.
Steve, I'm going to touch you the keys of the carbonicopter.
We are leaving behind Philadelphia, Pennsylvania.
I really hope that the addicts there are able to get the help they need
because definitely they don't need more drink.
I think I've ruined your guys' day enough.
You guys are eating spaghetti.
You're like, oh man.
Steve, get that spaghetti out of your mouth.
Steve, I'm touching the keys of the carbonicopter.
We are leaving behind Philadelphia.
Fly us all the way out to a pitch black room.
Actually, this is kind of a gross segue.
We're walking into this pitch black room.
But it's not completely pitch black.
You do see in the middle of the room, there is a table that's lit up.
And on the table is 10 sauces.
10 sauces.
I don't know why I'm building up the suspense.
I changed what the story is.
So I'm obviously changing the title of the episode.
I can do that much.
I'm not willing to go back to rerecord the intro.
But we're on the set of Hot Ones.
You guys know what Hot Ones is?
You're like, Jason, what possible conspiracy theory could there be about
one of YouTube's most beloved shows?
I don't know if that's true.
I don't know if what it's ranked.
I used to watch Hot Ones when I was in that phase
or I was playing a lot of Minecraft.
And I was looking for stuff to watch.
This was before I got on my police interrogation binge.
I just like to have something going on in the background.
I know a lot of you guys like listening to this podcast
while you guys game or do your homework or cook up a meal,
cook up a delicious meal.
That happens to look like an open wound on a drug user.
Lasagna, for example.
Hot Ones, if you don't know, it is a interview show
where you sit down with this dude and he asks questions while you eat spicy hot wings.
I watched it a bit.
I watched, you know, you go through and you look for the celebrities you like.
It's not just ordinary people, it's not just a garbage man.
It's some drug addict.
They're like, so tell me how did you get that festering wound?
They're like, oh, I don't know if I put hot sauce on this wing
or just juice shot out of my wound, but I'm going to eat it no matter what.
The way it's set up is that Sean Evans is the host and he'll sit there
and he'll interview these celebrities while they eat progressively hotter
sauces.
So you have the 10 wings and the 10 hot sauces
and they're like, so what was your reason for becoming a celebrity?
And like Bobby Brown will be there and he'll be like, well, I just want to make music.
I want to make music for the world.
Is there a crack?
Is there any crack here?
They're like, no, Bobby Brown.
First off, how did you get in the studio?
Will Ferrell was supposed to be on this episode.
I don't even know.
You were still a celebrity.
I don't even know if he's still alive actually, but Bobby Brown, no, no, no, no, no.
There's no crack here, but they'll ask celebrities,
living celebrities questions and then you eat the wings.
You eat them and then you're all sweating and they get progressively hotter.
It's an okay show.
It is actually super popular.
I went through and I looked at the celebrities I wanted to.
Like I think I watched like Shia LaBeouf's one
and I don't even remember who the other people were that I watched.
And then I was like, okay, that's done.
I mean, I get the appeal to it.
You get to see celebrities kind of in an uncomfortable state and it's very off the cuff.
It's actually pretty scripted.
The questions are scripted, not the answers, but you know what I mean?
Like it does, it's different than say like Jay Leno.
You're chasing how old are you?
These people don't even exist anymore.
Jay Leno burned his face the other day.
I wonder how he's doing.
But anyways, really what I'm getting at it, it is a completely innocuous, harmless YouTube show.
I guess there's a game show version of it now.
Bobby Brown, Bobby Brown keeps running out there like, what did I win?
Did I win crack?
They're like, dude, leave, please.
Totally harmless internet interview show.
People eating little chicken wings, like the stuff you get at Hooters with a little bit of hot sauce.
And the hot sauces do get progressively hotter until eventually like the top one is like 2 million Scoville units.
But then we take a look at a conspiracy theory that's recently popped up online.
This person online, they post under the name lighter than a feather.
They believe, and it's interesting the way they use a lot of Wiggles.
Wiggles words.
They never specifically say, I believe this, but they go, quote, is it too much to assume the show may not be serving chicken?
Now he's not saying maybe they're serving veggie bites, because they do.
They actually, if you're a vegetarian, they'll have you eat some soy compressed into the shape of a chicken.
But he's not worried about that.
He's arguing that is it possible, well, you know, again, he doesn't specifically say this.
But he's implying, I think if someone goes, what if they're not eating chicken?
You're not thinking, well, what is it then?
Is it roast beef?
Is it possible that what they're eating is human meat?
Human meat in the shape of a chicken, with a little chicken bone in it?
I don't know how they do it, but the elite share is powerful.
What if it's possible that they're eating humans?
They're eating human meat on the set of hot ones?
Because he goes, what if this is a way for the elite to prove to each other what they are doing?
Let me actually, I'm trying to make sense of this.
Let me read you this.
Let me read you this quote.
I can't put it any better than he does.
Quote, "Can we guess what the elite might have each other do in order to prove their loyalty
and reserve a hot seat?"
This is what I'm pausing all wrong here, like Jason who's reading this William Shanner.
"And reserve a hot seat for them in hell. After all, the elite are satanic."
So I know I paused this.
I know I paused in some really weird places there, but basically this is them.
If I go on hot ones, if I go on this YouTube show that most people don't even know exist,
I guess now it is a game show, so it's slightly more popular.
But if I am Shia LaBeouf and I want to prove to Will Ferrell that I am also equally satanic,
I will go on hot ones and eat what may be human flesh to prove how satanic I am.
This is so bizarre to me.
It's fascinating to think that I can watch hot ones while I'm playing Minecraft and
they just get bored of it after I've watched maybe six or seven episodes over the course of a week or two.
Watched in the most generous terms while I was playing video games.
And I could be like, "Oh, that's kind of an interesting insight. It's so funny. I don't
remember a single story any of those celebrities talked about." But I watch it as like, "Okay,
it's disposable YouTube content." Just like this podcast, right? It's just something to have.
I love it, and I'm sure the people who make hot ones loves their show, but you kind of understand
that for a lot of people it's just background noise, and that's totally fine.
But it's so weird, right? It's just such a basic show. It's people eating chicken on camera
and answering questions. And because, but this guy, you know, who's free to have his opinion,
right? This is fairly harmless. It's not hurting anyone. It's not hurting anyone to say Shia LaBeouf
is uncannable. It's so fascinating to me. You can have someone who can view the same thing millions
of other people do and see something so different. And the reason why is because they're really what
they're seeing is they're seeing famous people eat meat. That's it. They're seeing the same thing
everyone else is seeing, but because they look at the elite, they look at these people, and there's
something that you always got to remember. They are not special people. They are not extraordinary
people. They simply have extraordinary jobs. I've always found it so interesting when people
look at celebrities as something else, as gods among men, even as demons or devils among men.
There are people who are like, "No, I hate celebrities. They're the worst. They're just
satanic worshiping people. You're giving them power that they don't have over you."
I'm sure there are Saint worshiping celebrities. I'm sure there are powerful people. I've said
this before. I'm sure there are powerful people in the world over who do engage in horrific stuff,
pizza gate type stuff, cannibalism. I do believe that happens when you reach a certain level of
power. I think it's more out of boredom and more out of seeing what you can get away with.
I do believe that happens. I don't think it's all of them, but I definitely don't think it's none of
them. But I don't think it's Shaquille O'Neal or Will Ferrell or Shia LaBeouf or most of the people
who have ever been on Hot Ones. I think that when we look at celebrities and we see them as the
elite. I'll tell you right now, dude, in the amount of time you've been listening to this podcast,
Bill Gates has pooped in the toilet. He is a totally ordinary person who has all the same fears
and wants and hidden secrets and weird thoughts in his head that every other person does.
He's simply famous because he's rich and he helped develop a technology that changed the world.
And there are a lot of people who are rich and develop technology that changed the world,
that we have no idea who they are. He made himself the face of the company and then the media went
along with it. He's a totally biologically normal human person who does everything else everyone
else does. He simply has an extraordinary job. He created an extraordinary or is part of creating
an extraordinary company. That's it. It's such an interesting thing. But when you see a celebrity,
when you see someone that you feel is so different from you on a show eating chicken wings, your
brain goes to, I think they're eating babies. And really the only proof he has of this is
it shouldn't be a shocker. It's none. People said, "Hey, do you have anything to back this up? Do you
have anything to back this up?" And he goes, "If you watch the Will Ferrell episode around the 16
minute mark, you'll see something." Well, this is what he said. He goes, "If you watch it on the
16 minute marks, you'll notice that they quote, 'Poke fun at it,' the idea of like the rich hiding
something or the elite hiding something before our eyes. They will quote, 'Poke fun at it around the
16 minute mark if you have eyes to see.'" Will Ferrell's appeared on two episodes of Hot Ones. I watched
them both around that 16 minute mark. One episode I watched the whole thing and then the other one
was like some Christmas special or some donation thing, whatever it was. I watched for the Will
Ferrell around a 16 minute mark. I saw him at a different time in the episode. There's nothing
there. There's nothing there. He's not even joking. Like I expected him to be like, "Yeah, you know,
who knows what we eat, right? Or are you making some sort of veiled reference?" Nothing. Nothing.
He's watching the same stuff we're watching and coming up with this conspiracy theory about it,
because he's seeing someone that is so divorced from who he is, from what his reality is, that if
he sees a rich and famous person eating meat, he thinks he's eating babies. And not only is he
eating babies, it's a worldwide conspiracy. So eventually Justin Bieber can be watching Hot Ones
and be like, "No! How come I don't have my seat in hell? Agent, get the phone, get Lucifer on the
phone. I want to have that seat in hell." And then he goes on Hot Ones, "I'll eat all the babies right
now." And the host is like, "Dude, what are you talking about? I just had a newborn baby."
Justin Bieber is attacking the crib. That's the other thing. We'll wrap it up like this. Like I said,
I don't think the number is zero of people who engage, of powerful people who engage in sick and
perverted things. I don't think it's all of them by any means. And really what would come down to
this? To pull off, when you're watching a YouTube show and you're watching this guy, this host,
Seth Evans. Ooh, Seth, like Seth, like this demon from Egypt. I think I've cracked the code, good
sir. You have Seth Evans. And then you have a world famous celebrity on there as well. You have
Gordon Ramsay. You have Gordon Ramsay on the show as well. That's all you see. So you could say they're
eating human babies. Gordon Ramsay is all criticizing. It was like, "I've cooked a lot of babies in my
life and this sir is too dry." You have celebrity and then you have the host. And then you have these
10 pieces of cooked baby in front of you that you're putting the hot sauce on. To have that set up,
you need to have a dozen people behind the scenes. You have to have not the elite. You would have
people that you only know the name of them because you know them personally in real life or you read
the credits at the end of each episode. You have to have transportation people and set designers
and the lighting crew, person working the mic, all of that stuff plus your marketing agent,
your person talking to YouTube, everyone on the back end. It's more than 12.
And they would all have to be in on it. They would all have to be on it because if the lighting guy
is the only person who's not in on it but the microphone guy sitting there, the makeup team,
everyone knows that Gordon Ramsay is about to chow down on 10 different baby arms.
And you're the lighting guy and you don't know. You may start to dawn on you after a while. You
know, it's super weird. I've never seen a box of chicken wings come in to the studio. We're located
right next to a nursery. We're located right next to this daycare center in Utah, this green building.
And then three, there's missing person flyers everywhere. There's missing person flyers everywhere
when it's like, "Hey guys, I'm going to go take my break and I go down to local Starbucks." There's
flyers everywhere for missing children. Now you could go Jason. Jason, maybe the children are
being killed in another country and being shipped over here. Okay, you suck out. We'll accept that
argument because yeah, you could say that it's just a bunch of orphan children. Jason, wow, this
got dark really quick. After the losing the limbs, I thought that was bad enough. You're just shipping
over orphan arms from somewhere else to America. So you're not going to see missing person flying
fires everywhere. My key point of evidence would be they're clearly not baby arms that they're eating.
They're clearly chicken wings. And you would have, now you have to have a whole distribution
network of people moving baby parts across the border and all sorts of things. All for the purpose
of doing some YouTube show where people are eating hot wings. It's such a bizarre take. It's,
I would have to wonder like what type of enjoyment you would find in any media at a certain point
if you thought all media was created by infernal forces. Like how could you enjoy music? How could
you enjoy movies or television if you thought they were all bad guys? I wonder what goes through
his head when any television show comes on or he listens to any music. It's just such a fascinating
view of the world. It really is. I don't have a, my battery's about to die actually. I didn't
plug in my laptop. I don't have another way to wrap this episode up, but it is my first post COVID
episode. So I hope you guys have been patient with me. DeadRabbitRadio@gmail.com is going to be
your email address. You can also put us up at facebook.com/DeadRabbitRadio. TikTok is at DeadRabbitRadio.
DeadRabbitRadio is the daily paranormal conspiracy true crime podcast. You don't have to listen to
it every day, but I'm glad you listened to it today. Have a great day.
Bye.
[MUSIC]