World famous actor and wrestler, The Rock, has not been seen in public recently.
Is it because he's taken a little bit of time off, or is it because he has no more
legs? His legs fell off. This is an actual conspiracy theory. Does The Rock
still have his legs? It's so bizarre. And then, and then we travel to Utah to take
a look at one of the most bizarre press conferences in recent memory where the
Utah County Attorney took the stage and proclaimed he does not eat babies. Today
on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host
Jason Carpenter. I'm having a great day. I hope you guys are having a great day too.
I hope you guys are having tons of fun out there in the world. We've got a ton of
stuff to cover so we're gonna get started right away. First off, walking into
Dead Rabbit Command right now is a longtime Patreon supporter. Everyone get
on your feet and give it up for Kaz Montague. Woohoo! Yeah, come on in! Come on in Kaz
Montague walking into Dead Rabbit Command. Long-time Patreon supporter, always
active on the Patreon Discord. Kaz, it is always good to have you into Dead Rabbit
Command and you're gonna be our captain or pilot for this episode. You guys can't
support the Patreon. I totally get it. Just help spread the word about Dead
Rabbit Radio. That helps out so much. Kaz, let's go ahead and touch the keys to the
Dead Rabbit Durgible. We're gonna leave behind Dead Rabbit Command. Well, I just
saw the way out to Hollywood.
Taking that beautiful blimp out. Hopefully they don't get shot down. Hopefully
no one thinks it's from China. I'm gonna say this for this first story. I came
across this conspiracy theory and it was so ridiculous that I did not say I
didn't actually like archive it, which is what I normally do. Like I'll archive it
or I'll release bookmark it so I can go back to it. I saw this and I was so
perplexed by it, but I go this also so ridiculous. I'm not gonna talk about this
on my podcast and little did I know that then for the next two three weeks I've
been thinking about this. Almost non-stop. Almost non-stop. To the point that I
originally wasn't even gonna cover this segment for this episode. I had something
else ready to go and I said I have to cover this. I have to cover this now
because then it will be funnier when it turns out not to be true, but who knows?
Who knows in the world of conspiracy theory? Let's take a look at this and
please to all of the internet sensors out there. They keep a pretty good hands-
off thing to the podcast. Now that we're not not on YouTube, I can talk a lot
about different stuff, but I'm not saying that this conspiracy theory is true. I'm
just saying I find it highly amusing. Let's take a look at it. It involves human
grief and suffering. This conspiracy theory starts off like this. There is...
This is super interesting because I do have to kind of lay this out. Blood
clots. Blood clots are a thing. Originally people just thought they were
words shouted out by Jamaican rappers, but it turns out that blood clots can
actually happen to you or me. I thought I might have had blood clots last week
because I was showing symptoms of having blood clots. Now you can get blood clots
from all sorts of different things, but two things that can give you blood clots.
I will say that to varying degrees, okay, to varying degrees, you can get blood
clots. You can have blood clotting problems from COVID-19 itself. And I
actually went and I found a medical journal that stated that before the
first vaccines are ever rolled out. The earliest thing we have about COVID
causing blood clots, and it's very rare, but there was a paper published in June
of 2020. So this was way before the vaccine rollout. COVID-19 causes blood
clots. There have also, despite the fact that people were told no, no, no, everything
safe, there have also been in a very small amount of cases blood clots caused by
vaccines, COVID-19 vaccines. So both of those things can be true. They're both very
rare, but we have had documented cases of people getting blood clots from
vaccines, COVID-19 vaccines, and we've had people getting blood clots who were
not vaccinated from COVID-19 itself. So both of those things can be true at the
same time. I'll put all those links in the show notes. What we're looking at here
is this conspiracy theory is coming from the COVID-19's cause blood clots and
it's going to wipe out humanity. The COVID-19's are actually a plot to
depopulate the planet Earth. That's where we're at in this conspiracy theory. So
you figure everyone who's got the COVID-19 vaccine at one point is going to die
according to this conspiracy theory. See, this is what I get to talk about when I'm
not on YouTube. Spotify might have a problem with this as well. I'm not saying
this conspiracy theory is true. I don't think the vaccines were a depopulation
agent at all. I don't think that's what they were designed for. But this
conspiracy theory comes out of that and this, this is a fantastic conspiracy
theory. It's someone who loves to study conspiracy theories because you can
never be wrong. People who believe this conspiracy theory, what we're about to
get into right now, they can't be wrong. Let's go back to, and again I didn't plan
on doing this, but I can't stop thinking about it. Recently Jeremy Renner, actor,
guy, he was in a bunch of stuff, his Marvel movies and born identity stuff.
Anyways, Jeremy Renner is writing a snow plow at his property and from what we
understand he got out of the snow plow. This wasn't like a Charlie Brown snow
plow pulled by a puppy. This was a man, this was basically like an industrial
snow plow. He had all of the, I guess he loves heavy equipment. He has all these
different vehicles that he used at his own property to plow his own snow because
he liked it. People go he's so rich, he could have hired someone to do it. Why
was he snow plowing that day? Well anyways, he was snow plowing that day. Maybe
he gets off on it. Maybe it's his fetish, I don't know. But he was snow plowing that
day and it basically rolled over on him. It kind of chewed him up. And he's doing
okay. We've just never, and it's none of our business at the end of the day. It's
his own private medical stuff, but it's never been released and the early
reports was like he sustained massive damage to his lower body. And it was a
giant piece of equipment. So that would make sense. That popped up really quickly
in the conspiracy theory community. People go oh that's not what happened.
That's a cover story because Jeremy Renner's legs fell off due to blood
clots. He took the COVID-19 vaccine and he got blood clots in his legs and they
fell off. And the Hollywood elite, the media was like how are we going to explain
how we're going to explain that this Marvel superhero no longer has legs.
I know we're going to crash him with this giant piece of machinery. But I guess the
story is he never got crushed in the first place. Forget all the medical
you know people seeing the helicopter come down in the area. No those are the
blood clots. The blood clots were flying the helicopter. He had blood clots in his
legs. They had to remove one or both legs and people go people are going to
wonder where his legs went. So the snow cloud was a cover story. And I remember
reading that back when it happened. Then I go okay I mean there would be quite the
cover story. It would make sense. You would wonder why your favorite actor no
longer had legs. If just one of the day he just didn't have legs. You would
wonder a good cover story. But I don't I wish Jeremy the best. I wish Jeremy's best
recovery. We don't know how bad the injuries are. At the end of the day it's
really none of our business. Like I don't need to know the HIV status of a
celebrity or whether or not Jeremy Renner has legs. That's his business. I mean
obviously we would find out eventually. But I read that. I go that makes sense. I
could see the conspiracy theory community looking at that accident and say
no it was blood clots and they had explained was Lake's fellow. But then
recently I'm going to scour my computer database. My history. My bookmarks. I did
last night but I'm gonna look even harder. Because maybe about two weeks ago I
found a new conspiracy theory that says the rock famous wrestler Dwayne the
rock Johnson star of Fast and Furious and what was that other movie he was
recently in that I saw. Oh Black Adam I enjoyed that. Star of all these movies the
mummy returns or the mummy's back whatever one that was and his legs are
gone. His legs are gone. And you go wait I don't remember. I don't remember
how in any snow how did he lose his legs. Well apparently this conspiracy theory
is blood clots took his legs off like here is a guy who's peak fitness right
he lifts a lot and you out of everyone to not lose their legs due to blood clots
you would assume it was the healthiest. But that's not how blood clots work. But
apparently they don't matter if you're healthy or not. Well here's the thing
let's back up I don't know if the rock still has his legs. This conspiracy
theory started going around that the reason so this all came out of this all
came out of one thing so the rock was supposed to or there was a rumor that
the rock was gonna wrestle at a upcoming WrestleMania like 38 or 39. It's gonna be
a huge return. Black Adam didn't do that well. His vision for the future DC movies
got swept aside. Henry Cavill was fired. All this stuff. And so he's like fine if
I can't make movies I'm gonna spend some time wrestling I'm gonna go back and do
what I love. He was or that's the rumor right we don't know for sure that he was
gonna make this appearance. Well his I think they're cousins his cousin Roman
Reigns who's another wrestler recently went on a talk show and he said he
squashed the rumors and he goes the rock will not be wrestling at a upcoming
WrestleMania and the host is like why. And Roman goes he's not in wrestling shape.
And everyone kind of laughs at that because again he's so fit right he's so
fit. And Roman goes there's a difference between being in shape and being in
wrestling shape because in wrestling shape you know it's it's super acrobatic
you're doing all this cardio you're picking people up throwing them over
your head if you're just muscular and you're kind of flexing your muscles for
movie he's spoiled the rumor he's not actually flying around in Black Adam
he's just walking around and then everything else is special thanks you're
like what I didn't know that I thought that was documentary. He's not in shape
he's not in shape to wrestle and out of that statement a conspiracy theory was
born. The real reason why the rock won't wrestle at WrestleMania 38 or 39
whichever one it is is because he doesn't have legs anymore. Now this
conspiracy theory was put forward by someone said he was a member of the
Rocks Inner Circle he was the stone he was just a stone on the side and he goes
listen I'm a member of Rocks Inner Circle and I got to tell you the rock
doesn't have legs anymore he had been feeling ill for a while and he had the
blood clots in his legs and it was too late to they saved his life they had to
remove his legs so that's why he's not in wrestling shape you do I'm sure there
are wrestlers without legs honestly worldwide throughout the history of
wrestling I'm sure there are wrestlers without legs but again it would be
shocking if the Rock showed up to WrestleMania 38 and he didn't have legs
people would wonder about that people would really be confused and so that's
why he's there I mean they don't have an answer for that right they're not like
the Undertaker took them and if he wins the Rage and the Cage match the
Undertaker will give them back nothing like that you're gonna build them into
the storyline his just legs are gone so instead of confronting Matt until they
can come up with a good story they're just gonna say the Rock's not ready to
wrestle. What I love about this conspiracy first off this is a great
conspiracy theory because it is built on people's fears the idea of getting
blood clots like I said I had to deal with that last week and maybe that's why
the story's been so in my mind but I had to deal with that last week and I don't
know blood clots but there was a concern about it because I was having
symptoms that I had never had before and the only thing they pointed to was
blood clots there was no we still don't know what it is it might be like a
nerve issue but the only thing was I kept getting these warm sensations in my
legs couldn't figure it out so they said let's just test you for blood clots
it's scary right whether or not you've gotten the vaccine you could be afraid
that you're gonna get blood clots from the vaccine you can be afraid you're
gonna get blood clots from COVID or both right it's nothing exists in a vacuum so
it's scary - it's super efficient this is a great conspiracy theory because you
never have to be proven right or wrong on it this conspiracy theory is
constructed in such a way that if now you see the rock with both of his legs
it's Hollywood magic they're fake they're CGI legs someone else is holding him up
and walking behind them in a green suit and then they just you know give them
give him legs give him computer graphic legs there you go people will say have
you ever seen the rock in person have you ever touch his legs to make sure
your hands didn't pass through them are you sure it's not some sort of lawn mower
man-like illusion you never have to be proven wrong if Jeremy Renner has not
lost his legs or at least the use of them it would be a miracle from how this
injury was described this giant vehicle rolling over on his lower half and I
remember when I you know because the news it was in the news for a while I was
thinking about it and I thought on obviously if he lost one or both of his
legs you would just whatever the audience would be like whatever they'd CGI
them in you still want to carry the character of Hawkeye along I know he had
another television show called like the mayor of boomtown or town of the boom
something like that you just haven't sitting in a chair the whole time because
he's like just like a journalist or mayor mayor maybe maybe he's the town itself
maybe the entire movie takes place on his chest I don't know but you would have
you just haven't sitting down and you can have in a show being like yeah he lost
his leg you could easily work that into a drama a superhero show you would kind of
want to explain it I don't know maybe King shot him with a beam nobody would
care we'd obviously feel bad that he went through it but he's fine right he's
fine and they would just CGI stuff in because they would have an explanation
for it I do believe that this piece of machinery rolled over on not Ron Jeremy
it's a whole different story but Jeremy Renner the rock thing if he just all
of a sudden didn't have legs it would be weird because they would have to explain
it and what would you how would you explain the rock not having legs I
think you probably don't have to he probably has both of his legs but he has
been AWOL for a while now it's been a couple weeks after the whole DCU getting
shut down and the black Adam movie I enjoyed it but it didn't do as well as
it could have and then the wrestling he hasn't been seen publicly apparently
for like three weeks so that's why these rumors are getting born and it kind of
sucks right like you want a vacation you're the rock you want a vacation
but you decide just stay inside right lift weights maybe maybe just keep doing
that thing that you always do and no one sees you so then the rumor goes around
that your legs are gone that's a pretty bizarre rumor to start but again if he's
seen in public it can easily be hand-waved away with Hollywood magic and
then from going forward when anyone famous isn't seen for a while their legs
fell off that will be the conspiracy that's the reason why you don't see them
anymore because they don't have legs they're working on a cover story for it
and it's here's the thing I wanted to cover the first off I wish I had sick
because when I first read it I just was like this is insane this is almost too
insane to talk about but then I thought what if what if what if he did that we
never see him again and then that would just be weird right just you never saw
the rock again but then I thought if rock shows up tomorrow and he has both of his
legs no one would care right everyone be like yeah that's kind of what I assumed
seen him a couple weeks he had legs and now he has legs but I wanted to record
this before he shows back up in public because I'm telling you whether or not
he wouldn't that be insane I know his mom got in a car accident the other night
I was reading that headline but they didn't mention it mention I read the
article and at no point did they mention whether or not the rocks still had his
legs it's very lazy journalism TMZ if he doesn't show up it'll be intriguing
that would be a mystery right if the rock just disappeared that's a totally
different story but then the idea that what if you know you listen to this
episode and you chuckle along as well if you want subscribe you're like dude
this is going way too nuts I'll finish listening to this segment and then like
two or three days after this podcast comes out the rock gets an horrible
accident right loses his legs such a bizarre story I mean I'm not making fun
of like Jeremy Renner in his vehicle that's horrible I just think it's so
weird that people can go oh no that's a cover story really it was a blood clots
it's blood clots all the way down when anything bad happens to a celebrity and
you don't see him for a while his blood clots their legs have fallen off
fascinating look at the world of conspiracy theory Kaz Montague and he
keep an eye on the rock keep an eye on the rocks career maybe that was the rock
post that's where people would go see his next movie just make sure he still has
legs all the trailers are just him from the waist up and people are like hmm
I got a ticket I got my tickets find out for sure Kaz Montague let's go ahead and
touch you the keys to the carbon or copper we are leaving behind Holly weird
which is what I call it let's leave behind Holly weird fly us all the way out
to Utah and we're standing outside this building just like you know like a
governmental building there's a press conference getting ready to be held
grab your camera and a little press pass we're like pushing past the other
pushing past the other real reporters you're like get out of the way conspiracy
theorists we have priority and pushing them aside or getting right up to the
front it's June 1st 2022 and we're here for this just absolutely insane press
conference but at the time none of the reporters here thought what was about to
possibly come out of this guy's mouth this guy is the Utah County Attorney
David Levitt he's like the lead attorney for the county and he gets up to the
podium and he's the one who called the press conference in the first place and
he begins to speak now for context let's go back to just about a month earlier
it's May 2022 and the Utah County Sheriff Mike Smith he says my office we're
gonna reopen this case we've had some new developments about a cold case that
we've never really stopped working but we just didn't go anywhere we're gonna
reopen it we are going to look into allegations of ritualistic sex abuse
between 1990 and 2010 he says this sex abuse of children ritualistic sex
abuse of children was spread across several counties including Utah County
Jawab County and San Pete County these stories are just like the stories
coming out of the satanic panic as the media has dubbed it back in the 80s but
we believe that we actually have new proof that these weren't just stories
this wasn't just a moral panic that the children in these communities were
molested on a wide and ritualistic scale wasn't just some creepy teacher or a
neighbor luring kids in with candy this was an organized effort and it was
super creepy it was like creepier than the normal stuff right Utah County Sheriff
Mike Smith reopens this case in 2022 almost 30 years since the first
allegations came out so on June 1st 2022 Utah County Attorney David Levitt
calls this press conference and I need to see if I find an audio clip of it I
really I'm really trying to find an audio clip but from what the basically
from what the articles have stated David Levitt gets up on the stand then
after a few pleasantries like hey everyone thanks for coming out to this
press conference if you don't know my name is David Levitt I'm the Utah County
Attorney and I do not eat babies my wife does not eat babies we have never eaten
babies we are not currently eating babies and we never will eat babies any
questions and then the reporters had no idea this was gonna happen the
report really yeah we have nothing but questions what are you talking about
why would you call the press conference to say you don't eat babies like this
I never thought you ate baby until you called 30 people in my room to
proclaim you don't eat babies and your wife doesn't eat babies David Levitt
says here's why I'm bringing this up now here's why I feel like I have to defend
myself against all these baby eat now like no one's no one's alleging that
not a single person in this room has ever heard what you're talking about
reporters are like what in the world he goes David Levitt goes it's an election
year and my seed is one of the things people are gonna be voting on and Mike
Smith the Utah County Sheriff is taking sides because you see he's dredging up
all of these old charges you know I reopened that case last month about
ritualistic sex abuse he's trying to let you and the voters know that me and my
wife used to eat babies but we never ate babies so this is an election year
ploy honestly I think Mike Smith should step down for such a dirty trick I
think that this is wrong and I do want to record one more time that I David Levitt
and my wife have never eaten babies
so immediately there's basically a stampede of reporters from the press
conference just like you see in those old movies where they'd run to like the
pay phones real quick they all just ran into the other room and pulled out their
cell phones and called the police department the Sheriff's Office and
said are you investigating are you investigating attorney David Levitt
for eating babies and the Sheriff's Office said no we're not we are looking
into cases of ritualistic child sex abuse but we are not looking into the
allegations of David Levitt eating babies the reason why this is such an
overreaction because what happened was David said David Levitt says when I
found out there he knew from back because this was investigated for a long
time these these allegations were investigated the police didn't really
have much to go on but the complaint was out there and there was a hundred and
fifty one page report from a single witness and it had been sitting in the
police department for a while this was in like I don't think it was like in the
evidence locker but this high and you know Utah County attorney he's the
highest attorney in the county he would have access to the evidence locker but
he was able to get a copy of the hundred and fifty one page report that had been
submitted years and years and years ago that names him and his wife and 15 other
people who were part of this ritual sex abuse cult where it talked about them
eating babies now the sheriff said we are not going to comment on who and who is
not under investigation but we are not basing this new investigation off the
hundred and fifty one page report because that is old I mean it's definitely
creepy don't take it don't read it before you go to bed it's creepy and it's
horrifying but that's not why we reopened the case we've had that for
years and years and years that's not why we're reopening the case we have gotten
new information a new victim has come forward and gave us stuff we didn't know
previously and that is why we're reopening the investigation if David
Levitt wants to walk around saying he's not eating babies which again not a lot
of people even knew that was an allegation there was that report that
hundred and fifty one page report but I don't think they gave copies to the press
back when the investigation was going on he goes that is not our main focus now
however that hundred and fifty one page report does name because it named those
15 people including the wife and the attorney it does name a guy named David
Hamlin and this new focus when the police get this new victim and they start
looking into this investigation that is who they are investigating is this guy
named David Hamlin he was arrested in 1999 this this type of stuff really
pisses me off this type of stuff really pisses me off and I think it pisses off
most people David Hamlin I get it innocent until proven guilty all that
stuff but David Hamlin he was a therapist he were he was arrested in
1999 for child sex abuse so that was right remember this this ritualistic
sex cult was doing stuff between 1990 and 2010 he was arrested in 1999 for child
sex abuse 18 counts 18 counts doesn't necessarily mean 18 kids because each
kid could be like three or four counts but still that's a lot that's a lot
whether it's 18 victims or four victims and anyways the point is 18 counts is a
lot he was arrested in 1999 charges were not officially filed until 2012 so he
was arrested you hold him overnight for a couple days he paid pays bail and then
he goes about his business as a therapist having these one-on-one
conversations with people in a closed room from 1999 to 2012 the charges were
not officially filed where now we're actually gonna have a trial and then in
2014 all the charges were dropped
now here's the thing he was on the list and David Levitt was on the list as
being a member of this cult and I know your first question this was my question
too was Levitt the Utah County attorney when these charges were dropped and he
was not that actually happened five years before Levitt was the attorney so
he started he became the Utah County attorney in 2019 so that does absolve
him from him putting his thumb on the scale and saying hey I know this guy we
kind of ritually abuse kids together we're gonna let him go so he had no
point in that so you could look at David Levitt yeah anyone can be named on a
list of all of these people maybe he knows maybe he doesn't even know David
Hamlin right maybe someone was just picking prominent members of the
community and they all just happened to be on the same list that's possible right
it also you got to throw that one out the window because David Hamlin and David
Hamlin both them named David I don't think there's anything there don't make
people named David have to worry about it but David Levitt the attorney and
David Hamlin the therapist were next door neighbors so now you have I mean
again listen you might live next door to a pervert I hope not I hope not right I
hope I don't either I know I don't but you might live next to a pervert and that
pervert gets arrested that mean you had anything to do with it no not
necessarily if your name appears in a an undated document that names you and 14
other people including your wife of ritualistic sex abuse does that 100%
mean you did that no I mean people can say all sorts of crazy things and that's
kind of what the sheriff was saying he goes listen we have new evidence what
happened we have new evidence against David Hamlin we're not gonna say whether
or not we're investigating other people we never do but we think we have something
to go on that we can actually make the charges stick this time David Levitt you
know so remember he's being recharged in 2022 this story is happening in 2022
where David Levitt's like no no I don't need babies I don't need babies so now we
have a trial for what might be a co-conspirator right Hamlin and Levitt
may be part of this child sex cult so people ask I mean nobody even thought
that David Levitt had any connection to any of this until he started running his
mouth about how he doesn't eat babies nobody would have put two and two
together that old report the police weren't even using that as a piece of
evidence they had their eyes on David Hamlin and then he put himself right in
the middle of it David Levitt's like I don't need babies he says my office will
prosecute David Hamlin to the fullest extent of the law in fact I actually
prosecuted him not too long ago for killing a deer and eating its heart and
drinking its blood that's the type of guy I am when my next door neighbor
talking about you're saying this therapist ritualistically killed a deer
and David Levitt goes yeah yeah I actually it was poaching that was the
crime but he was eating deer hearts and drinking their blood in the middle of
nowhere so you know that's kind of that's why you should read that's why you
should reelect me I will prosecute my neighbors if they do disgusting stuff
well again he wasn't being prosecuted for drinking blood he's being prosecuted
for poaching a deer from it's all you right now if people suspect you of being
a satanic child molester you might want to tamp down on the blood drinking just
a little piece of advice maybe not drink so much blood
so why is Levitt even getting caught up in any of this stuff I mean again sure he
had a press conference where he declared once and for all he doesn't eat babies
which you should just never do I mean obviously don't eat the babies but he
thought he was getting in front of it and all of a sudden he made himself the
story is that it is the fact that there's this undated report that names him
along with a bunch of other people and someone who has been re-arrested for
child molestation I mean that's a bad list to be on to begin with but is that
all they have he had this weird press conference and he's an extra neighbors
with a guy who drinks blood and molested kids we have these weird quotes and these
weird decisions and this is where you kind of any of these in a vacuum you may
be able to explain away but let's take a look at this stuff this first one there's
a way to explain away honestly we don't have the context for it I found this
quote and an article or two this is something David Levitt did say on the
record like this is an actual quote from him I don't know what the context is but
this is what he wrote there is no context I mean there might be a context but
there are certain things when your brain goes I should say that that's a good
example and then your brain goes don't just don't here's a quote he goes quote
I mean how do you train a dog to roll over when it's time to roll over you do
it by giving a reward and repetition that that's that's fair right stop there
that's your brain's telling you to stop but David Levitt continues I mean how
do you train a dog to roll over when it's time to roll over you do it by giving
a reward and repetition he continues if a man wants to program some little girl
to give him oral sex anytime he wants start young and give rewards it's the
same way you help a child learn to make their bed what is the context for that
what is the context for that I figured maybe he was talking about how groomers
operate but the way he says it he goes this is how you teach a dog and then he
goes off in this perverted and super specific example and then he goes yeah
or make their bed one of the two that's creepy that's creepy and then when he
came into again think about it he knows that he is part of this alleged
child sex network he knows that that 151 page document names him so you kind of
want to do stuff that that doesn't make that seem real when he got elected this
is so boneheaded when he got elected as Utah County attorney he eliminated the
special victims unit which was a dedicated team of detectives to
investigate sex crimes that's all they did he closed it down he goes it wasn't
working they found me in my co-conspirators I mean they made up that
list he goes it wasn't working these I think it was eight detectives it was
like four to eight detectives he goes they were overworked there's so much sex
abuse going on they were overworked and I was afraid they were going to burn out
so I canceled it and then just made every every police officer do a little bit of
sex crime stuff I kind of you know spread it spread the madness out and the
police and therapists and all these other people said listen before police
especially if a beat officer saw something that was weird a patrolman
stops the car and sees something that was weird he would then go to the SVU and
say hey I don't know if this is real or what but XYZ and the special victims
unit would go that actually sounds like a a that actually sounds like there
could be possible real child abuse going on there or it could be something where
they go yeah that's kind of we've seen that before that's actually not child
sex abuse that's something different I mean you know what I mean like you would
have these experts and people said the experts were gone now everyone just did
a little bit of it you spread it across and David Levitt said all replaced was
something better and he never did imagine you've been accused of sexually
abusing kids for 20 years as part of some weird cult and then you shut down
the second you're like I'm totally innocent and to prove it I'm gonna shut
down experts investigating sex crimes I'm gonna let everyone do a little bit of
it so nobody's perfect at it so remember this was an election year and
obviously none of this stuff looked good for David Levitt he ended up losing the
election the other guy got 73% of the vote so it he basically destroyed his
own career he thought he was getting out in front of this by proclaiming it as an
eight babies and then all of a sudden everyone needed to know what that was
the sheriff said I was never investigating that in the first place we
are investigating this Hamlin character he has been recharged just in
September 2022 David Hamlin so that process is playing out now and the
sheriff has said Sheriff Mike Smith has said our focus after this new allegation
was against David Hamlin we do believe we have enough now to charge him
successfully and there are more arrests coming we're not gonna say who we're
looking at we're not gonna say who we're not looking at but expect us to arrest
more people involved in this activity very shortly
super bizarre story right I mean it's that that collision of true crime
conspiracy and the paranormal right that they say it was this ritualistic sex
quote they don't use a lot of words like satanic because it gets kind of brought
into that satanic panic thing but a group of 15 powerful people even before
David Levitt became the Utah County attorney you have to wield some power
just to be able to get up to that level anyways and let me say to allegedly
right he may not have done we definitely know he didn't eat babies he proclaimed
it but fascinating story of local politics local power and lust to such a
degree that you pray on children you pray on the helpless to get off and what I
be really interested in seeing this 151 page report because I what were the
actual allegations back then but I'm telling you this is something I do not
and I use it I use the term to just because it's a catch-all thing but the
idea of the satanic panic you see article after article and they're almost
joking about it they're like oh yeah I remember when all of those weirdo
conservative Christians thought there was a saint worship or hiding around
every tree and their children weren't safe and that it you'll see articles like
that like remember when yeah I remember it and you know what some of it was real
some of it was real I don't think all of it was real but I don't think none of it
was real either and we have cases like this that 151 page report there may be a
lot of exaggeration in it I'm not saying that reports a hundred percent
authentic but just across the United States you had a time period from the
1970s into the 1990s where you have these allegations of and this is what I
find we got to wrap it up because otherwise I'll go forever about this but
we have allegations of medium-sized groups of people right 10 to 15 to 20
people in a local community abusing children in a ritualistic way even if
you got rid of the ritualistic part even if someone goes well you know the
satanic the satanic elements they were a little overblown those children were
abused though you were right there sir that's just as bad even if you removed
the window dressing even if you had an investigation to go well they weren't
saying worshipers but they did run a child human trafficking scheme that's not
satanic panic that's a crime and those people should be prosecuted and I think
there was this big hand-waving motion about oh look at how the fundamentalists
wore back then because that's really the narrative right they thought there was a
saint worshiper behind every tree not every tree yeah there were some people
who over blew the accusations they made it into this whole thing but again to
say that none of it happened and the weirdest thing is it's like we know
this type of stuff happens today so why do they just hand wave away everything
that happened in the 70s the 80s and the 90s we know that there are organized
groups of people who trade photos and video and bodies of young children they
have these networks we know these exist so why is it so some ABC reporter some
high-level award-winning ABC journalists just got arrested for possession and
trading of child porn so I mean like it exists that happens and to hand wave it
all the way and say it's all made up I just don't buy that I don't buy that
and then we get a little example like this you know this is that entire
movement distilled into a moment remove all of the trappings remove the
pentagrams and the inverted crosses if you take all of that out of those reports
the allegations themselves are disgusting and damning 100% and I've always
been of the belief this has always been my view of the satanic panic if you were
a part of this just you were a bunch of sickos right you wanted to do sick stuff
you would make it fantastical not because you're bored and not because you
want to add a little pizzazz to your dungeon but you would do crazy things
you would have like these weird imagery that you have the upside down crosses and
the pentagrams and you would come in and you would be like look at these pigs
look at these pigs we've killed throwing guts on people and then just do what you
normally do to your victims do that normal awful sex stuff because you know
if they ever do tell the story about what happened they're gonna be like yeah
and then like there are all these dead pigs and he threw guts at me the whole
room was painted red and it had all this stuff and people are gonna go that's not
true you're exaggerating that's not true you make the
outlaw gate you make the scenario so ridiculous that boil it down to the crime
just like the guy drinking deer blood I don't care about that the fact that he
was poaching deer that's the crime forget all the other wackadoodle stuff
that's going on look at the crime was that crime committed yes or no that's
something that people who dismiss the satanic panic always do they dismiss the
crime it's so bizarre to me army hammer can get cancelled over Instagram post
about him wanting to eat human ribs which he posted which he said sure is
that a crime no not pro army hammer on this show but I do think he wants to
eat people honestly but what I'm saying is somebody says something like that they
can lose their career but you can have allegation after allegation after
allegation against powerful members in your community people just dismiss it
all because there is a pentagram in the background while they were abusing you
it's absolutely nuts absolutely nuts the way they look at it but here we got a
look at a case that may actually be one of the verifiable real cases coming out
of the satanic panic and will we know more
well I guess we'll find out if they arrest more people but I'll say this if I
was ex Utah County Attorney David Levitt I'd be a very very nervous man right
now because he must know that the sheriff has their eyes on him
DeadRabbitRadio@gmail.com is gonna be your email address you can also do this
up at facebook.com/DeadRabbitRadio. Tiktok is @DeadRabbitRadio. DeadRabbitRadio is
the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast you don't have to listen
to it every day glad you listen to it today
have a great day guys
you
(upbeat music)
[MUSIC]