Is it possible that ghosts, ghouls, goblins, elves, leprechauns, and the assorted list
of goodies and baddies in the paranormal world are actually friends with each other?
Interesting story.
And then we'll take a look at the final story of Season 20, when a man hosts a little girl's
birthday party.
At his house he's just expecting a bunch of kids running around screaming at their top
of their lungs.
Little did he know he would be the one doing the screaming.
Today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host, Jason Carpenter, I'm having a great day.
I hope you guys are having a great day too.
I hope you guys are having an absolutely fantastic day.
We got a ton of stuff to cover today.
So first off, walking into Dead Rabbit Command right now everyone turn to the front entrance
and give a salute and a round of applause at the same time.
For our newest Patreon supporter, Matthias Gamara.
Woohoo!
Yeah!
I was actually trying to do the salute and the applause and I hit myself in the nose.
Don't do that.
Please don't sue me if everyone else hit themselves in the nose as well.
I thought it was just a joke.
Matthias you're going to be our captain, our pilot this episode.
Thank you so much for supporting the show via the Patreon.
You guys can't support the show via the Patreon.
If you guys can't support the show financially we also have a merch store as well.
But if you can't afford any of that stuff or maybe you can't afford it and just don't
want to that's totally fine.
That really really is.
Just help spread the word about Dead Rabbit Radio.
That helps out so much.
You have no idea how telling your friends and your family whether they're people online
or people you know in real life or maybe both.
Maybe you have a gaming crew and you're also friends in real life.
The point is, is that get the word out, that always helps so much.
That's something you can do to help the show grow.
Matthias you're going to stand there on standby.
Go ahead and help yourself to the fridge.
I got some, I don't know there's actually nothing in there.
I got a bunch of Diapepsy but I don't know maybe like Diapepsy.
There's some Sprite Zero in there as well.
This is the end of season 20.
This is the end of season 20 and I feel like this season went on for a really long time.
I'm pretty sure that it did.
This was a season I got COVID.
So that put us back a week and all that stuff.
But pretty eventful.
It is the season I got COVID so pretty eventful.
As far as that goes but it's been a really good season.
I think this has been a really good season and I'll tell you guys that's a little behind
the scenes tip.
This is the first season in probably 20 seasons where I haven't ended the season going.
I don't know if I want to continue the show anymore.
Because not because of you guys, not because I think the show is running thin on material.
It's just I'd be so exhausted by the end of that 20 weeks.
Luckily I got COVID and I got a break in the middle of it.
No I don't know.
This was the first season that I've been like okay I'm going to take my break and then we're
just going to come back to doing more Dead or Abra Radial.
Pretty much every season before this I was so burned out by the end of those 50 someod
episodes.
Some seasons would go longer.
I don't know if I'm coming back.
I always came back because I love the show and I love you guys.
But this is the first season where I haven't even had that thought.
So that's good.
I'm sure that that is good for the future of the show.
I haven't been doing my YouTube shorts, my true crime TikToks, nothing like that.
I was like okay I am done doing these.
I need a break from these.
That's a ton of extra work but we are at the end of season 20 so we will be back April
3rd.
April 2nd, April 3rd around there.
That is when we'll be back season 21 of Dead or Abra Radial.
It's a bit of a longer break than I normally take by only two days because one last pitch
for the Oregon Ghost Conference in Seaside, Oregon March 24th at 6pm.
I will be a present tourer.
A what's a speaker.
You're like I'm going to go just to watch you mispronounce words in real life.
What was that first word?
What was the present for?
I'm going to be a speaker at the Oregon Ghost Conference.
I'm giving a...
Oh it's going to go great right?
I can't even say what I'm going to do.
Imagine me.
It's 50 minutes long.
It's longer than an average episode.
My presentation is on why are there no fat ghosts.
And I know we covered that on an episode a while back but I've been doing even more
research finding all sorts of crazy ghost stories that I've never talked about before
on the show that I'm going to present live.
I will talk about some of them in the future but all sorts of stories about why ghosts appear
physically one way burst the other.
What does that mean for us as we inch closer and closer to death?
You're like I want to leave a ghost that is cool looking.
You're getting scarred up by a bear.
You actually just have really bad stomach ulcers.
Doctors are like these are going to kill you in like 1400 years.
You're actually not going to die stomach ulcers when you run out in the forest.
You're going to have some cool scars in the afternoon.
We're going to talk about that so it would be really cool if you guys could show up.
If you guys don't show up, if you guys can't show up, that's fine too.
I'll probably cover some of those little ghost stories in future episodes that are
ever ready to.
But for those of you who do show up, it's going to be like 99% all new material.
So I think it would be really cool.
And then I'm going to hang out at the ghost conference and be attending.
Geez, I don't know how I.
I almost want to sit in the audience and listen to myself just stumble on stage.
Also, I know this is a lot of intro stuff but last episode of season 20, hopefully you
guys are being patient with me.
One of the speakers at the Oregon Ghost Conference is going to be Dr. Kelly Schutts.
She recently interviewed me for her Paranormal Encounters podcast series.
I'll put links to that in the show notes.
There's an episode where she interviewed me.
I talked about a lot of my personal ghost stories and that was very fun.
Also, if you're looking for another podcast to listen to in the next two and a half weeks,
Paranormal Encounters podcast series has a ton of interviews with people in the field
of paranormal research.
And also, if you're looking for a podcast to listen to, try the Asylum Case Studies.
It's a podcast I've been on twice with fan of the show, Tressa Slater.
She does the podcast, The Asylum Case Files.
Is it Case Files or Case Studies?
I'll put the link in the show notes but I'm pretty sure it's Case Files.
Anyways, I could be wrong.
Great podcast all around.
She reviews Asylum Movies.
The Asylum Movies.
Not Movies.
People trapped in the Asylum so that'd be so depressing.
You're like, "Here's a documentary from 1942.
One of the worst Asylums in America.
We're going to watch this footage of horribly depressed people."
No.
Movies like Megapurana and Transmorphers, they review those movies.
The Avengers, Grimm, all that stuff.
I'm going to see if she wants me back on the show.
I'm going to see if she wants me back on the show because I'm itching to talk about
Shark Side of the Moon, the Asylum's recent Asylum film.
But anyway, so those are podcasts if you're looking for something to listen to in the
meantime.
I'll put my episodes in the show notes and then you can listen to that.
Maybe find a brand new podcast.
Maybe find fun.
But you got to come back to this one.
You just can't go, "Oh, I love these podcasts way better."
Thanks, Jason.
Unsubscribe.
Matthias.
I think that's everything we have to talk about.
I don't think there's anything else big coming up.
So, Matthias, I'm going to go ahead and touch the keys to the Jason Jalopy we're going to
leave behind Dead Rabbit Command.
Drive us all the way out to Ireland.
And don't forget to hit that time travel button because we're going back to the year 1914.
We're actually going to Scotland.
Sorry, I read that wrong.
You're like, "Oh man, it's St. Patrick's Day.
It would be so cool to go to Ireland.
Do you want to go to Ireland?"
We're going to Scotland.
So make a left.
Now we're in Scotland and we're in the year 1914.
Specifically we're in Inverary, Scotland.
And it's a sunny afternoon.
We're sitting there in the car.
We see a little boy riding his tricycle on the outskirts of Iverary.
Now it doesn't say how old this kid is.
I'm assuming he's pretty young.
If he can't ride a bike.
If he's riding a tricycle, I would assume six or under.
He doesn't specifically say, he doesn't give his name either.
We're going to go ahead and call him Jake.
But he's on trike all by himself in the middle of Scotland.
And who would have guessed something bad is going to happen to this tyke?
This little kid, so Jake, is riding this tricycle.
And all of a sudden he bails, which again would be quite hard.
Generally the tricycle is designed so it can't tip over.
But he does.
He's on the trike and he's six.
He's outside.
He's on the outskirts of town on this tricycle by himself.
He has a hard tumble and it's so hard.
He breaks his arm.
Maybe a tricycle means something different in Scotland because I can't imagine.
I guess it means three wheels.
Maybe the three wheels are in the wrong order.
I can't imagine what sort of bicycle accident you would have that you could break your arm.
I remember once when I was a little kid, I was on a tricycle and we were moving into
a new house.
And listen, and I probably was younger than six, so it's probably like four or five.
I was a jerk and I would just do stuff to make people mad all the time.
I thought it was hilarious.
I still do.
I repress it more nowadays.
We were moving and I decided I knew what I was doing.
I was not innocent in this.
I got on my tricycle, which is like the widest of all child vehicles.
I'm on a tricycle and I begin tricycling up and down the hallway of this new house.
I'm like, oh, that's fine.
That's like childhood innocence.
That's a very sweet image.
Well, remember, we're moving in and I'm fully aware that people are trying to go back and
forth down this hallway.
I was blocking them.
I was doing it on purpose because I'm a jerk.
Even at four or five, I was like, oh, you know, it'd be super funny if I ride this tricycle
super slow down this long hallway.
Parents are trying to move stuff in.
Well, I don't know, maybe like three hours later, I'm still doing this.
My mom was carrying a heavy box down the hallway and she said, she goes, Jason, you were on
the tricycle going slow and in a mocking tone was going, la-do-da, la-de-da-da-da-da.
She goes, you were doing it to aggravate us.
You 100% were going as slow as possible and she was carrying this super heavy box and
my mom wanted me to move.
That's all she wanted me to do.
They were telling me, you're going to go down the hallway, go down the hallway quicker.
She's carrying a freezer.
Put on the hallway, go down the hallway, la-de-da-da-da-da-da on my tricycle and my mom got so frustrated.
She put her foot on the back of the tricycle.
You know, you have those like stairs on the back of the tricycle, so an even smaller kid
can ride on the back for whatever reason.
She put her foot on the back of the tricycle and she goes, Jason, move.
And she went to push me forward with her foot.
So I would go, wee, down the hallway.
That would encourage me to do it more.
Now that I'm getting an assist, she put her foot on the back of the tricycle.
She's carrying this heavy box.
I'd been doing this all day long.
She finally had enough.
She put her foot on the back of the tricycle and she goes, Jason, move.
And she pushed it with her foot to propel me forward, but instead it flipped the tricycle
backwards and I landed on my head in the hallway and I'm like, now I'm screaming at the top
of my lungs, the indignation of it.
Oh, here I was.
Just making people physically discomfort.
That's all I was doing.
All I was doing was holding up the process of moving into a new home and how dare, and
also, you know, I hit my head.
I did hit my head.
I was a little kind of hit my head, but oh man, I made such a ruckus and then all of
a sudden everyone had to stop moving stuff and pick me up and little baby Jason had to
be taken care of.
So I got my way.
I was still, I was still irritating people, but now I was crying and probably got like a
bowl of spaghetti with the little hot dogs in them as a reward or to shut me up or both.
But the reason why I tell that story is because I myself am a veteran of tricycle accidents.
My mom kicked me off of one, but I, it would be hard to break your arm.
I think it would be pretty hard to find.
I'm not doubting this dude.
This is the weirdest part of the story.
I'm not like, whoa, isn't that crazy?
Have you been around with tricycle?
Our next story, I'm not doubting his story.
I'm just trying to figure out physically.
Maybe it was like those old tiny tricycles that were taller.
They used to see it like the dude with the mustache writing.
Maybe it was one of those.
Maybe the kid was like 10 or 12 writing a giant tricycle.
I don't know.
But anyways, I probably could have Googled how big a tricycle was in 1914 and saved us
all 10 minutes, but instead he falls off a tricycle and breaks his arm and he goes,
listen, I'm such a little kid.
I couldn't tell you for a fact that I broke my arm.
But looking back on it as an adult, I swear that's what happened.
I actually broke my arm when I fell off his bicycle.
And he falls on the ground and he's crying because he's in a lot of pain.
And Jake realizes, oh, wait a second, nobody knows.
Nobody knows that I'm out here on the outskirts of town, not even like in the middle of the
city where a concerned adult could look out of the window and be like, ah, be gotten.
There's a little kid out there.
No.
He was on the outskirts of town and he's just like a path that he was on and he's crying
and he's crying and no one's coming and he's crying and crying and no one's coming and eventually
he's like, uh-oh.
Like I don't know how I'm going to get home.
I'm in a lot of pain.
Pretty sure my arm's broken.
I don't know because my tricycle is ready to go.
I don't know how much damage the tricycle got.
Even if it didn't have a bent wheel or a busted steering bar, you wouldn't want to get on
it with a broken arm.
You just, this thing just betrayed you.
You'd be afraid.
So anyways, he's like, oh no and he's crying.
He's like, I'm kind of in a pickle here.
I don't know how this is going to resolve itself.
And right when he was thinking that, out of the bushes jumped a little man.
This man, Jake said, was about two and a half feet tall and he just appeared out of nowhere.
Like Jake had been crying for a couple of minutes and all of a sudden this little dude
shows up and he's like, hey, can I help you with something?
And Jake's like, oh dude, my arm, I fell off my tricycle.
Don't, I can't explain how that happened.
But my arm hurts.
I hurt my arm.
And he said this little man walked up to him and began to tend his injury, tend to his
injury.
He doesn't go into a lot of detail, but he says he begins to tend to my injury and almost
immediately all pain went away.
Like, I don't know what he did, but almost immediately the pain went away and I felt
that what had ever been done.
That's why he says as an adult, I don't know for sure that I broke my arm.
I look back on it and swear that must have been what happened, but it was healed in like
a minute.
I'm sitting out here, this two and a half foot tall guy comes out of the bushes and
heals me instantly or almost instantly.
Jake goes, who, who are you good sir?
And this little man goes, I'm a gnome.
And Jake looks at this gnome.
You say you're a gnome, but you actually look a lot like a leprechaun.
And the gnome goes, well, I will assure you that I am a gnome.
I am not a leprechaun.
And around this time, off in the distance you hear Jake's parents go, Jake, Jakey boy,
where are you?
Oh, we miss you so much.
Oh, that boy's probably out.
Boy's probably out breaking arms like he always does on Wednesdays.
I have to tell that kid he needs to stop breaking stuff.
He hears his parents off in the distance coming towards him.
And at that point, the little man jumped back into the bush.
When the parents came up, they see Jake just sitting there on the ground next to his tricycle.
And the parents are like, oh my God, what happened to you?
And he goes, you will not believe what happened.
But I'm going to tell you everything.
I fell off a tricycle.
The dad's like, OK, wait, stop, stop.
That was that first Friday.
He goes, I listened.
I fell off a tricycle.
It did hurt my arm really, really badly.
And the little man showed up, fixed it.
And he wasn't a leprechaun.
He was a gnome.
Did you know that?
He wasn't a leprechaun.
And the dad's like, what are you talking about?
He was possibly tired.
That's it.
No more outskirts of the city for you, young man.
He said his parents didn't believe him that any of this happened.
Now, that story, while simple, raises a super interesting question.
We'll get to that in one second.
First off, I want to give a shout out.
This was-- I found this on ThinkAboutItDucks.com.
They got it from a book called Hidden Neighbors by a guy named W.M. Michael Mott.
W.M. is a big W and a little M. I don't know if that's a signifier for anything, like
sir or madam.
I don't know, but it's weird.
Not the weirdest part of the story.
I was like, man, look at this guy's signature.
Is that paranormal?
W.M. Michael Mott, he writes a lot of books about faithful and fairy lore, which long
time listeners of the show know I'm not a huge fan of either of those things.
But gnomes and leprechauns, what a perfect time to talk about it, is we're leading up
to leprechaun day, also known as St. Patrick's Day.
This story when I read it, I thought this is super interesting because let's dissect it
here.
This guy was magical.
This little gnome was magical.
He was able to heal the wound of this boy.
And when the boy said, "You look like a leprechaun," they didn't say-- like, again, not a lot of
details.
It took place in 1914.
The guy probably didn't tell the story to the author or to anyone until he was like
in his 70s, right?
Because otherwise people would be like, "Hey, look at this leprechaun guy."
He'd be mocked around town.
Is it the man who was saved by a leprechaun?
He's like, "It's actually a gnome."
They're not saying, like, was he dressed like a leprechaun?
Did he have on the black shoes and the striped underwear, the stockings, whatever that is,
and the black shorts and the little green vest?
We don't know.
A little hat.
Little hat, little black hat as well.
We don't know.
Or was he just thinking he looked like a leprechaun because he was a tiny guy?
I imagine that-- well, because leprechaun-- I would imagine that they would probably
have to be some green involved.
I don't know.
Maybe not.
Maybe a little kid would just see a tiny guy and go, "Hey, look, it's leprechaun."
But here's my thing.
So he asked the gnome, "What are you?"
The gnome says, "I'm a gnome," and the boy says, "You look like a leprechaun."
And the gnome corrected him patiently.
That's the term that's used in the story.
Corrected him patiently.
He's like, "No, not-- gnome.
I'm a gnome."
The reason why that's interesting is it makes me think, "Do these beings know each other?"
Not just leprechauns and gnomes.
We can extrapolate this so far.
And yes, we will get to the ghost cake in this episode.
But I'm wondering-- let's take Western Europe, for example.
We have fairies.
We have gnomes.
We have leprechauns.
Do they know of each other?
Probably the term "faithfulk" is in this big, encompassing term.
But a gnome would have knowledge of a leprechaun.
The gnome would be like, "What are you talking about?
What's a leprechaun?
Tell me about your human words.
Who is this very handsome being you speak of?"
I'm sure he's quite dashing.
If you say it, look like him.
Fairies and gnomes and leprechauns.
You go, "Jason, yeah, of course they know each other, but I think some of that's from
our media, right?
We watch cartoons and there's like the leprechaun sitting on the toadstool and David the gnome
walks up and he goes, "Get off.
That's my house.
Get off of that."
Leprechauns like, "Nope, squatters rights.
That was a two-parter on Nickelodeon."
But would they?
And then you extrapolated out from there because they weren't the only paranormal beings in
Western Europe.
And I'm just picking that as an example.
Would a gnome talk to a ghost?
Would they be on good terms?
How far does the world of the paranormal go?
Is it possible that a leprechaun, if you caught a leprechaun, if you're lucky enough to catch
a leprechaun this March 17th, could you take him back to your house and time up to a little
chair and then ask him, "Where's Bigfoot?"
He's like, "What?
Don't you want my gold?
I'll give you all the gold, bro."
I don't know what you're talking about.
Who's Bigfoot?
Bigthings scare me.
I'm a leprechaun.
Where's Bigfoot?
I don't know Bigfoot.
Have you ever heard of the Chupacabra?
He's like, "What?
Would he be like..."
This is where it gets trippy because with the leprechaun, the leprechaun's going to tell
you whatever he thinks you want to know because he just wants to get home to his family.
He wants to get untied.
But while he's still trying to gnaw at the rope so when you're not in the room, he could
say, "Listen, I know of Bigfoot because I obviously live on the planet Earth.
I'm an interdimensional being, but I have knowledge of things."
This gnome didn't come out and go, "Oh my goodness.
What is this three-wheeled metal construct right on this road?"
He's like, "Oh, that's a tricycle."
He wouldn't know what that was.
He wouldn't, every time a gnome popped out, he wouldn't be like, "What year is it?
What year is it?"
And they're like, "2023?"
He's like, "Tell me everything that's happened since between now and 1914."
You're like, "I barely remember most of the details of my life, let alone world history.
I might want to skip the 30s and 40s though.
I think we'll gloss over that part."
Gnomes like, "What?"
Yeah, it gets kind of bad.
We'll probably skip over the Vietnam conflict."
He's like, "Ah."
So they would have modern knowledge.
Not only we've ever come across this story where, obviously we assume aliens know everything,
aliens because they're above us, not just physically, but just technologically wise,
just technology wise.
We don't ever have to keep them abreast of the news.
But yeah, like a fairy or gnome or leprechaun, would they know about the, oh, first thought,
would they know about the Gulf Wars?
Would they be like, "Oh, Saddam Hussein, man, we had to remove them from power.
They're total war hawks that are like, "Oh, you don't know, we're behind all the wars.
We're the true Illuminati."
You're like, "Ah."
But they would probably know current events.
But would they know?
And they may know of Bigfoot.
You might be able, and that's the thing, you could have asked the gnome, "Are you a leprechaun?"
And it's funny because the gnome could have been like, "No, leprechauns aren't real,
dude.
Leprechauns aren't real.
I'm a gnome."
And I know in your books, you talk about leprechauns and cylinder gold and stuff like that.
He actually might have been a leprechaun now that I think about it.
He didn't want to get jacked or all of its gold.
He's like, "Ah, I'm just a gnome, bro.
Let me go."
You wonder, like, he might go, "I know of leprechauns.
I know of the stories of Earth."
Right?
I know of leprechauns.
I know of Bigfoot.
I go, "Squatch in from time to time myself."
But he doesn't exist.
Or as far as I know, like, I've never seen Bigfoot.
There's no proof that I know of Bigfoot.
I am a gnome.
I am a mystical creature.
You can move beyond the veil of what you call reality, but I don't know if Bigfoot exists.
Chubacabra?
What?
I don't know if any of this stuff is real, but I've heard these terms before and I know
what you guys are into.
Or would they know Bigfoot?
Does a gnome know why he looks like a leprechaun and he's tired of being compared to leprechauns?
He corrected him patiently because the boy doesn't know any better, but he's like, "I'm
not a leprechaun."
Every time I jump out of a bush, the rubber boy's arm.
Someone thinks I'm a leprechaun.
I'm not a leprechaun.
But he personally knows leprechauns.
He knows they're really, really skeevy dudes.
He's like, "Oh, come on."
They're comparing me to them.
And then would they know Bigfoot?
Would they know ghosts?
Like, do ghosts know Bigfoot?
We know that there's a connection.
Now, I'll put the episodes in the show notes.
It's really weird.
There's a connection between Bigfoot and UFOs.
Really weird connection between Bigfoot and UFOs.
A lot of encounters with that.
But like, is a Bigfoot aware of ghosts?
Do ghosts know of Bigfoot?
Do ghosts know leprechauns?
This is interesting.
Where is this?
Because I think I'm in the...
And I will wrap it up here.
Not the episode, although we're already at like 30-some-on minutes, but we got a lot to
talk about.
And Ghostcake Story, finally.
You wonder when we're paranormal researchers, we have like UFO researchers, cryptid researchers,
ghost researchers, faithful researchers, things like that.
And there is starting to become more of a crossover between them all, which is good for the research
community.
But is there also a crossover in that world as well?
Like, do ghosts know leprechauns?
Do demons know of Bigfoot?
Super interesting question.
It comes from a very simple story, but it does make you wonder, like, how much of this
stuff is interconnected.
Ghost is kind of a hard one, because a lot of ghosts are just like a psychic imprint.
They don't know anything.
It's just a...
And something repeating over and over again, we're catching a glimpse of the young widow
standing at her window waiting for her lover to come home from the Civil War.
Like, that's not one.
You can't show up and be like, "Would you like some cookies?"
And she turns around.
She's like, "Oh, I love cookies."
And you guys are friends.
No more than you can walk up to a Madonna cassette from 1988 and start listening to
Cherish and go, "I love you too, Madonna."
And Madonna shows up at your door, because it's just the recording of Madonna's voice.
But there are ghosts that you can communicate with.
And would those ghosts that do have intelligence...
I think that's going to be the theme.
If I get invited back to the Oregon Ghost Conference, I think that might be my theme.
New ghosts, no Bigfoot.
I mean, sometimes you just need to have a Kenji title.
It's an interesting question.
This gnome knew what a leprechaun was.
He didn't go, "What's a leprechaun?"
The question is, does he personally know leprechauns?
Or does he know of the story of leprechauns that humans have made up?
It's a very, very interesting question.
And just another reminder that the world of the paranormal is weird.
Jason, that's the last thing.
That anyone needs a reminder of.
It's called paranormal for a reason.
Mephaeus.
Let's go ahead and toss you the keys to the world, a famous carpenter copter for our last
flight during season 20.
We're leaving behind Scotland.
We're waving goodbye to this gnome.
We freed the leprechaun from our basement.
And we're headed out to a house in the suburbs.
The year is 2018.
And we're at this dude's house.
He didn't give his name.
We're going to go ahead and call him Sean.
And his niece will call her Rose.
Just turned six years old.
And Sean's brother goes, "Hey dude, listen, our apartment is super small."
And Rose wants to have a big birthday party.
She's apparently really popular at school.
So can we have her birthday party at your place?
And Sean goes, "Yeah, sure dude, that sounds great."
That's exactly what I wanted to do this week and clean up after a bunch of little kids.
So 15 to 20 kids show up at this place.
I'm sure he expected like three, right?
You'd have to be pretty popular to pull 15 to 20 kids to your sixth, not sixth grade
birthday party, six year old birthday party.
You're like, "Of course, Jason."
No one has a sixth grade birthday party.
You're like, "I want everyone.
I've graduated.
I guess that's just called a graduation party anyways."
Mom was done.
Mom was done with the season.
Keep it together.
Six year old birthday party.
She's turning six.
And 15 to 20 kids shows up to Sean's house plus parents.
It must have just been a madhouse.
It must have just been absolutely insane.
Maybe Sean had a good time.
All the friends are there, all the presents, all the presents stacked up in the corner
and cake.
Of course, delicious cake for a six year old girl that's sitting in the kitchen every
so often Sean's looking in going, "He's like the big bad wolf in a red riding novel, but
he just wants to eat cake.
I can't wait to give me some of that delicious cake."
Oh, guys, your bulging out of his head.
The big birthday party is going on.
Huge birthday party.
I imagine it was bigger than he thought.
And it goes on for a couple hours.
That's crazy.
That's a long party for kids, right?
You get bored.
You're all taking a nap in the middle of the party.
Taking 30 minute nap.
Wake back up.
Be energized again.
Clown shows up.
Eventually though, party comes to an end.
People are cleaning everything up.
Rose had a great time.
That's what matters, right?
You only turned six once.
She had a great time.
Sean feels really good that he was able to help out his brother, help out his family.
Everyone's cleaning up and it's time for everyone to go.
So bye, bye, everyone.
See you guys later.
Then Rose and her parents leave.
They walk out.
Sean is left alone with the cake.
Now when I was looking over this post, apparently Sean, I don't know where this story takes place.
Sean, because someone goes, "Why did they leave the cake behind?"
People were really intrigued about this cake and Sean goes, "Well, in my culture it's normal."
This should be normal for every culture.
This actually sounds pretty dope.
He goes, "In my culture it's normal that when you bring food over, let's say that you're
going to host a party at your house and you're having all these people come over and they
bring over food.
When they leave, they leave the food with you as basically a thanks for letting me use your
place."
That's super reasonable, right?
I mean, assuming you like the food.
It's like a bunch of veggie platters you can take with you.
I don't want that stuff.
But who doesn't like cake?
Who doesn't like cake?
And so there's some cake left.
I don't know how big this cake was too.
15 to 20 kids plus parents.
Apparently, there's some cake left and not a small amount.
And the whole time Sean and Vinay balling that cake.
He's all kicking kids off.
They're all riding tricycles.
He's kicking them out the door.
See you guys later.
Cake's all mine.
He has that cake in the kitchen and he's thinking about it.
Everyone leaves and about five minutes pass.
All of a sudden, ding dong.
Turned door bell rings.
Sean's like, "Huh?
What?"
Someone must have forgot a present.
Someone must have forgot a purse.
I don't know.
So he opens the door and standing there on his front porch is Rose.
His six-year-old niece.
And he kind of looks side to side and doesn't see her parents anywhere.
And he goes, "Rose, what are you doing here?
Where are your parents at?"
And Rose goes, "Uh, they forgot me.
They forgot about me."
You just drove away.
They're like, "You're six now.
You can fin for yourself.
Test the one.
Find your way home."
She goes, "My parents forgot about me.
They actually drove off and left me here."
And Sean goes, "Well, let me call your parents and I'll have them come pick you up."
And Rose said, "I'm actually really hungry.
Can I come inside and eat some cake?
Can I come inside and get some of that delicious cake that's left behind?"
And Sean's like, "Yeah, sure.
You can come in and get some cake."
Little tear dropy turns away to hide his tear dropy.
He's like, "Oh, less cake for me."
He goes, "Rose, yeah, sure.
Come on in.
Have some cake.
I'm going to call your brother."
I'm a little disappointed that he forgot about you.
Forgot you existed and on all of all days your birthday.
This is definitely going to be some therapy in the future.
Come on in, get some cake.
And he cut her a slice of cake and put it on a plate, set it down, and then he went
to call her brother and goes, "Hey, dude, why in the world is Rose still at my house?
It's not that I don't like her.
I have spent the last couple hours with her screaming at the top of her lungs.
But she should be with you.
You drove off and you left your daughter here.
You're going to come pick her up or what?"
She's eating my cake.
Hurry up.
Get back before she eats it all.
And his brother goes, "What are you talking about, dude?
Rose is with me right now.
She's sitting right next to me."
And at that point, Sean said, like his heart physically skipped a beat.
Like there was no like, "Dude, quit messing with me, bro.
Quit messing with me.
Always pull these pranks."
He always pulled these pranks, dude.
It was, he immediately realized something was wrong.
There was no debate.
He realized his brother was right.
That Rose was not in the kitchen eating cake.
She was with her parents.
So Sean walked into the kitchen and when he gets into the kitchen, no one's there.
The kitchen is completely empty.
Sean is the only person in the entire house.
All that's in there now is him.
The kitchen is completely empty, but sitting on the kitchen table is a plate with a slice
of cake sitting on it and it's been half eaten.
Now he said, I looked a little bit further in my notes, he does say what culture he's
from.
It's Hmong.
It's Hmong culture.
I don't know where the story takes place, if it takes place in America or in other region
of the world, but he's Hmong.
So he said it's typical in his culture that they do leave the food behind, which again
is a great tradition.
We should all share that.
He goes, I never told the story outside of my immediate family.
Never told anyone about it.
He's posting about it now like five years later.
He goes, I never told the story outside of my family and neither myself nor anyone else
in my immediate family has ever had any paranormal activity, ever.
This was the very first time we have anything that was even close to this.
He goes, but in the Hmong community we do believe in shamans or your parts of the Hmong
community.
We talked about that in an earlier episode.
We did an episode about Hmong shamans, but he goes, we did contact to Shaman and he came
out and he cleansed the house after this encounter.
I'll put the episode about the Hmong shamans in the show notes.
It's a really interesting one.
It's actually one of my favorite episodes.
It's one of the episodes we've done a classics on and I'm going to start doing the classics
again, not this season break for the next one, but it was the story about the movie
A Nightmare on Elm Street is based on a true story.
As clickbaity and as insane as that title sounds, the film A Nightmare on Elm Street
is for a fact based on a true story.
Wes Craven was reading a series of articles in the LA Times about Hmong refugees leaving
Laos and Cambodia during the Purge, during the huge genocide going on over there in the
wake and during the Vietnam War.
They were spread across the country and their shamans would randomly be placed in different
cities because the US government is like, "Yeah, you can come over here, but we're going
to put you here.
We're going to put you here."
It really disrupted the spiritual needs of that community and a dream demon showed up.
It sounds so insane, it sounds so insane, but it actually is based on a true story.
I'll put that episode in the show notes because it has nothing to do with this story.
I just love that episode.
It's creepy and the shot, it's so creepy.
I'll put that in the show notes.
But anyways, let's get to this story, which also it's not necessarily creepy.
I think it's a good way to end season 20 for two reasons.
One, it's one of those stories that I talk about where I love the mundane paranormal
stories because something like this could happen to anyone.
You go, "Chase, I don't have a six-year-old niece."
Well, okay, maybe the same details won't happen.
But the visitation, it doesn't have to be like a super evil demonic spirit throwing books
at you.
It could be something that simple.
What I find interesting is a little girl asks for permission to come in, which is what
we see in the stories of vampires and to another extent demons having to be invited into your
body.
But the little girl asks to come in and you wonder, was that a rule she had to follow or
was she simply being polite?
Did she really just want to slice a cake?
Did she have more nefarious motives in mind?
I don't know.
I honestly think she just wanted to eat some cake.
We've covered stories about kids eating candy.
There is a bridge.
I don't remember exactly what state it took place in.
Tennessee or Mississippi or something like that, where if you leave a candy bar on a
bridge, ghost children will crawl out from underneath it and take a bite.
Then you have half of a whatchamacallit bar sitting out there.
Now of course, where I skipped a goal is maybe it was a raccoon.
Maybe it was me.
Maybe I got hungry.
I'll make ghost hunt.
But I'll put that episode in the show notes.
We do have stories of ghost eating things.
That might be a raccoon.
That's Robbie.
I'm like, look at this.
It's evidence.
It's really Jason.
But maybe this ghost just wanted a bite of some cake.
Maybe it was a little hungry for it.
It's also possible that this ghost assumed the shape of Rose or the spirit, whatever it
was.
I keep saying ghost because that's kind of how I feel.
But it could be obviously a spirit.
It could be a darker entity like a demon or something like that.
It might have assumed the form of Rose, but it's also possible it was at the party as
well as a different child.
Like it was invited in by the joy of 15, 20 children just having a blast and it invoked
this spirit.
And it was also there having fun.
In the corner you're all playing in the town of Donkey.
There's this dripping wet girl facing the corner just standing there.
I'll twitch and they're like, aren't you going to give her a try?
And they're like, what?
They turn.
There's no one there.
It's just a puddle of water.
You're like, someone put something in this cake.
It's a spooky Samara ghost.
It could have been a ghost.
It could have been a spirit that was brought there by the party.
And then when all the kids left, it left as well.
But then it goes, you know what?
I'm going to shape shift into this little girl.
Okay.
Maybe I'm going to give it.
And maybe it left when all the kids left, but then thought, you know what?
I want a little more cake.
So she changed her appearance back to someone who could gain access to the house.
Do I have any proof for that theory?
No.
I just think it's fun.
I just like the idea that there was a ghost attending the whole party and they just wanted
a little more cake.
But you know, it could have not been that.
It could have just been just a regular spirit, not a spirit that's breaking into parties.
It's a party crashing ghost.
But it's a fascinating story because it's so mundane.
I mean, it would terrify you, right?
Like that probably is the right course of action to bless the house because at the end
of the day, he invited it in.
That's the tricky part.
I mean, there are some people that any ghostly activity, they're going to call their spiritual
advisor to have it taken care of.
And that's fine.
That's, you know, the decision that they're making.
I don't think all ghosts need to be kicked out of the house, but some I'm sure do, right?
Ghosts that are definitely interfering with your ability to concentrate or keep your health
going.
We did that episode.
This almost feels like a best of wrap up.
We did that episode by that woman who was losing her mind and she couldn't get her act
together.
She couldn't even get her act together enough to sell her house.
She was trapped in that house.
And it was a very interesting look at like that mental and physical decline of a traumatic
haunting.
He did invite it into his house.
So you would be a ghost just seem to show up.
They don't necessarily need an invitation.
The invitation waiting to be invited in does give it a sense of menacing.
But again, it could have just have been polite.
It's possible that Rose herself wouldn't just walk into somebody's house.
So she was just mimicking what a little girl, especially a little girl in that community
may do in the Hmong community.
So who knows?
It could have been a dark spirit.
It could have just been a run of the mill ghost, which is kind of funny term because
they're so wacky and so bizarre to begin with.
But a run of the mill ghost or spirit just wanted a little bit of cake.
But it would be a story.
It's one of those stories that you would have a hard time telling.
You tell your immediate family because you might be concerned for the real Rose.
But outside of this, it's not something you're really going to talk about at work because
people may make fun of you for it.
I don't think it's cool to make fun of people, even though I do spend every 10th episode
highlighting the absurdity.
I know yesterday we spent 55 minutes talking about a woman who believes reptilians were
invading Santa Fe.
So I do make fun of people, OK?
But what I'm saying is that I also want people, even though I make fun of some people, I want
other people to share their experiences.
The second reason why I wanted to cover this for the ending of season 20.
Well so, say funny, I say I wanted to use the story.
It was an accident the story ended up as the last story of season 20.
It really is.
I was supposed to do it last week.
It got bumped back.
I was supposed to do it yesterday.
It got bumped back because I was having so fun with that crazy lady in Santa Fe.
The story is about a celebration.
The story is all about this party with this delicious cake sitting there.
Not to be schmaltzy, but this podcast, you guys, we're going on five years in June.
I mean that's crazy.
That's really cool.
Like after I hit episode thousand, I go, "What's the next milestone?
What's next?"
Like we hit a thousand episodes.
Like that's a huge achievement.
And little did I realize that we were just a couple months shy of five years, a daily
podcast.
It's crazy.
And guys, it's all because of you.
It's 100% because of you guys.
It's really awesome.
This might be your first episode and you may feel like, "This doesn't really apply to me."
This is your first episode.
You probably shut it off 15, 10 minutes ago.
You're like, "Why is he still talking about this conference?
Get to the ghost, bro."
But if your first episode, if this episode is not your last episode, but this is your
one thousandth and fiftieth episode, maybe this is even the second or third time you've
listened to the whole catalog through and I get a lot of emails from people saying,
"I've listened to your podcast all the way through two or three times."
It's fantastic.
It's so awesome to be part of your lives.
It really is.
And I'm glad you're part of mine.
I thought, "I didn't plan on this to be in the last story of season 20, but I think
it's a fitting one because this is all about celebration.
Even when we talk about the spooky stuff, even when we talk about the dark stuff, celebration.
It's us sharing these stories with each other.
And I'm just so...
It's so dope.
It's so dope to be doing this.
And I feel like I'm in a real good mental place.
Like I said before at the start of the episode, almost every season before this, when I stopped
recording the last episode of that season, I would go, I would say to myself, "I don't
know if I'm ever going to put out another episode.
I'm going to see how I feel at the end of my break."
That was how it was almost every season.
But now that I don't feel that way anymore, now that I'm looking forward, as this break
starts, I'm already thinking about what I'm going to be doing for season 21.
That's a big game changer for the show.
It's a time of celebration.
It's a time...
Apparently, there's a dog outside my window.
Hopefully, it's not a paranormal dog, written by a leprechaun/nome.
The dog's barking outside my window.
That's probably a sign.
It's time to wrap up season 20.
But again, I want you guys to celebrate.
Oh my goodness.
How big is that dog?
It's like getting closer.
It's like I'm on the ladder.
It's coming up to my window.
That's like the biggest dog I've ever heard outside my window.
This is the way season 20 is.
With a big old dog outside my window.
Oh my God.
Every time I lean forward to the mic.
I think this season 21 will be the start of the gangstauging season.
I'll be like, they're after me.
They're after me.
They keep rubbing their bellies and driving yellow super-roos.
And have German shepherds.
Anyways, guys, I got to wrap it up because the dog is driving me nuts.
I appreciate you guys.
I hope you guys really do have an awesome break.
I hope you guys have lots of fun.
I hope to see some of you at the Oregon Ghost Conference.
But even if you're not able to make it.
Even if you're listening to this episode way in the future and the Oregon Ghost Conference
is coming on.
I hope you guys know that I will be thinking of you on my break.
And I can't wait to get back to the microphone for the first time in 20 seasons to share
more stories of paranormal conspiracy and true crime with my friends.
I love you guys.
Stay safe.
Have fun.
DeadRabberRadioGmail.com is going to be your email address.
You can also put us up at facebook.com/DeadRabberRadio.
Tiktok is at DeadRabberRadio.
DeadRabberRadio is the daily dog stock, of course.
DeadRabberRadio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast.
You don't have to listen to it every day.
I'm glad you listened to it today.
Have a great break.
I'll see you guys soon.
I'll definitely see you all on April 3rd.
It's going to sound crazy if the mic didn't break up that dog.
If you can't hear on the mic that dog is working and I just found it.
I love you guys.
Have a good one.
Bye.
[MUSIC PLAYING]