A creepy apparition makes itself known, but what does it want?
And then we travel to Hawaii to take a look at a family that has recently rented a house.
At first they begin to experience minor disturbances, but as mysterious events after mysterious
event continues to manifest in this house, the family has to wonder if there's a poltergeist
haunting them.
However the truth is far more terrifying.
Today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Carpenter, I'm having a great day.
I hope you guys are having a great day too.
I hope you guys have some awesome plans for this upcoming weekend.
I might go see the new Ant-Man movie.
I hated the first one, I thought it was awful, and I didn't watch the second one, but something
tells me that surely maybe this third movie will be entertaining.
Probably not.
But at the very least I'll be able to eat some popcorn and drink soda.
You're like, "Jason, you can do that.
You don't have to go see Ant-Man to drink stuff.
I'm all dehydrated.
I was like, "Oh, I'm only an Ant-Man movie would come out.
I haven't had a drink in 10 years."
But that's probably what I'll do this week.
I hope you guys have more entertaining plans than watching Ant-Man.
But someone who's always entertaining no matter the circumstance, he needs a horrible car
accident and he's doing a dance.
He's doing a dance.
Dancing is waiting to Dead Rabbit Command right now.
Everyone give it up for one of our legacy Patreon supporters, Bougas.
Woohoo!
Yeah, come on in, Bougas.
Yay!
Welcome into Dead Rabbit Command.
Bougas, you're going to be our captain or pilot this episode.
If you guys can't support the Patreon, it's totally fine.
It really is.
Just help support the show by getting the word out.
That is another way you can really help Dead Rabbit Radio grow.
Bougas, let's go ahead and toss you the oars to the Dead Rabbit Robot.
We are leaving behind Dead Rabbit Command.
Captain this boat all the way down to San Francisco, California.
Splash!
We're all rowing this rowboat while Bougas is looking all admirably standing on the bow
of it.
We finally get to San Francisco and this is a story that has very, very specific coordinates.
I love stuff like this because you can kind of go there and double check it.
Although this story, this story may be like, "No, I'm good.
I don't need to go to that haunted house."
Apparently, we don't have the exact house address, but this takes place in San Francisco
on 23rd Avenue near Lincoln, which is right across the street from Golden Gate Park, which
if you're not from California, it sounds beautiful, right?
Golden Gate Park, you imagine in San Francisco and like it's just, you know, San Francisco
stuff, hilly and grass.
I lived in the Bay Area for a good period of time and you couldn't catch me in Golden
Gate Park for nothing.
You cannot pay me to go there.
Maybe it's better now.
It's probably far worse than it was in the '80s, but Golden Gate Park, locally, I don't
know if it's as internationally known as, say, what's the big park?
Central Park in New York.
Central Park in New York, again, things could be different now, but when I was growing up,
it was the same thing with Golden Gate Park.
You can be there during the day, but if you're out after the sun sets, you're dead.
You're basically dead.
The police won't even go there to help you.
They, once the sun, once the sun no longer gives its life-giving light on the world,
these giant parks just become murder factories.
It's basically the purge every night.
At least that was my, how it was brought to me as a child.
I was basically told, don't ever go into Golden Gate Park at night.
And really not during the day either because there's a bunch of drug users and stuff like,
I don't know, maybe it's better.
Probably not.
But anyways, the reason why I bring all of that stuff up is if you want to talk about
a place with an aferi as haunting, which is what we're going to get into right now, it
totally makes sense that it's across the street from this park.
Because a lot of bad stuff happened there.
A lot of bad stuff happened there.
23rd Avenue, near Lincoln, across the street from Golden Gate Park.
Someone posted this story online.
It's very, very short, but the visual is just terrifying.
This person said, they go online, they go by the name Spooky Inky, 987.
So if you can't trust a guy named Spooky Inky when it comes to ghosts, who can you trust?
He said, I used to live in this house next to Golden Gate Park in San Francisco.
And one day I was there and I saw something come out of the wall.
It bubbled out of the wall and it was a dark cloud made of human skulls.
And he's watching it bubble out of the wall.
But this dark cloud of human skulls was bubbling out of the walls.
And he says, the bubbling was he would watch these human skulls get bigger and bigger and
bigger, about the size of a human skull.
And then it would begin to shrink into a tiny skull.
And then another skull would appear.
But it was like, all this was happening at once.
It was basically like this roiling mass of human skulls growing and shrinking, enveloped
in this black cloud that's phasing through this wall.
And he says, it came out of the wall and for around 10 seconds it sat there, hovering in
midair, continuing to boil and bubble out human skulls.
And then after 10 seconds it slowly began to ooze backwards into the wall.
That's it.
That's the whole ghost story, right?
That's the whole ghost story.
But when it's that insane, do you need more?
Like if you saw that, if you saw that, you go in there with your EMF detector and you
got your little tape recorder to record EVPs and you're like, yes, we're going to go ghost
hunting, maybe we'll pick up a voice of an old lady who got murdered in Golden Gate Park.
And you got all your equipment set up, right?
You're ready to spend the night.
And then all of a sudden a undulating mass of human skulls float through the walls.
You'd be like, okay, that's all the proof that I needed.
We're leaving now.
You probably want to stick around a little bit longer.
But you know what I mean?
Even a hardened paranormal researcher would be like, that's the most insane thing I've
ever seen.
I've seen a lot of ghosts floating down hallways.
I've heard some spooky noises and abandoned asylums.
But a floating mass of human skulls growing and shrinking.
Yeah, that is going to go on my resume.
That is quite the feat.
Very, very interesting ghost story.
He actually posted it.
Someone was asking online.
What are some physically unusual ghosts that you've come across that you've seen?
People who've seen paranormal stuff.
What some physically unusual ones.
And that was the one, there was a lot of them, but that was the one that really stuck out
the most to me.
There was another one where a guy said he saw a Civil War ghost.
But this might have been on a different forum, actually.
This might not have been in the same question.
But he said he saw a Civil War ghost, but half of its jaw was torn away like the cheek.
The sinus cavities were torn away and he could see the teeth.
He could see like the open jaw and the teeth and everything like that.
It was a very mangled up ghost.
Which is interesting because we're going to talk about this at the Oregon Ghost Conference
on March 24th.
I'm giving a presentation there at 6pm March 24th in Seaside, Oregon.
We're going to talk about stuff like that.
Why some ghosts appear incredibly grisly while others just seem, I mean, everyone dies one
way or the other.
Not all deaths, but a lot of deaths are gory.
Getting ripped apart by lions or getting ripped apart by dogs or falling to a thresher, a
wheat thresher and then spitting your guts out all over the wheat.
You know, are you just now going to float around for the next hundred years?
Are you going to hunt the farm as a, it's like floating entrails?
Just floating around the farm?
They're like, "Oh, Billy, Billy and his entrails floating around."
No.
Traditionally, what we see in Ghost Lord is people who die, like you fall into a machine,
you get shredded up.
You're not now a floating pile of guts.
You're Billy.
You're just like the ghost of a guy walking through the field.
And they're like, "He's never left the wheat thing done."
I don't know anything about wheat.
We hired Billy because the government paid half of the salary.
We just kind of let him hang out.
But now he just walks around the wheat.
We see old Bill, old Billy boy walking around the wheat.
It's not this horrific vision of guts everywhere, but sometimes it is.
Sometimes it is headless ghosts, like we talked about earlier this week.
Sometimes it's a civil war ghost with half of his face missing.
But then other civil war people get just blown to bits and they show up back at the house
of their sweetheart.
They finally made it home, even in death.
And they're walking around with their ghost girlfriend.
She jumped off the building when he died during the battle, jumped off the top of their house
and now their ghosts are sitting in the tea room.
Every so often you look in there and you see this young couple.
So how come that happens?
But this other dude has half of his face for eternity.
But even this boiling mass of human skulls, this goes beyond ghosts.
This is such a demonic image.
But what is it?
What could it possibly be?
What is this trying to tell us?
What does this manifestation say about the world of the paranormal?
We don't know.
This is one of those things that's so far outside the norm.
What's interesting, and I'll wrap it up like this because I can talk about this forever,
what's interesting is that this is the type of imagery you see in horror movies.
So people who don't follow paranormal, people who aren't like paranormal researchers like
us or people who are at least interested enough in the paranormal to listen to podcasts and
read articles about it, they assume this type of stuff is far more common.
They assume poltergeist activity is more common and these type of monstrous entities coming
out and ghost killing people, all of those things are extremely rare.
Extremely rare.
Visually seen a full body apparition is rare.
Being killed by a ghost is, I mean it happens, but it's such a small percentage of actual
ghost sightings.
You could almost statistically say it doesn't happen.
And then like this.
A ghost appearing in monstrous forms, inhuman monstrous forms.
Again, it's happened so rarely.
They might as well not exist as well.
So fascinating story coming out of San Francisco, quite short but quite terrifying.
Boogus, go ahead and call in the carbonar copter.
We are leaving behind San Francisco.
Make sure you got your wallet on you because we were near Golden Gate Park.
We're leaving behind San Francisco.
Take us all the way out to Hawaii.
I wanted to do a real quick Dead Rabbit Recommendance.
I swear that I had talked about this but I couldn't find in any of my notes any mention
of it so I definitely want to recommend this and it's very topical.
We've been talking about this for the past couple weeks, not only on the show but in
society in general.
There's an anthology film called Doomsday Book.
It's a South Korean anthology film.
There's three different stories but the second story, I mean I saw this over 10 years ago
and I think about that second story all the time.
It is one of the coolest pieces of sci-fi.
Very thought provoking, right?
You're stuck in my head.
It's called the second, you mean you watched the whole thing.
You can watch the first story is okay and the third story is kind of funny but the second
one is some of the coolest sci-fi that I've come across.
Really, I'd rank it up there with some of the best.
It's called The Heavenly Creature.
The movie itself is called Doomsday Book but the second story on that is what I want to
highlight, The Heavenly Creature and what it is the story of.
It's basically the story of a robot repairman.
It takes place in modern times but technology is a little more advanced.
There's a robot repairman who gets called out to a Buddhist temple to repair a robot.
This robot was originally purchased and they are all over the country as a tour guide.
It has this memory and it will walk around and go like this fountain was built and so
and so and then it would walk a little bit through the Buddhist temple and look it over
there.
There is a bench.
That bench is brand new.
They just installed that last week.
This robot would give tours and the Buddhist temple calls up the company and says, "Hey,
our tour robot is malfunctioning."
So they send a repairman out and he gets there and he's like, "Where's your robot?
I'm here to fix it."
And they go, "Come with us."
And they lead him into the temple and the robot is praying.
And they go, "This robot malfunctions."
It thinks it's Buddhist.
It believes in all of the tenets of the Buddhism religion.
And the repairman is like, "What in the world?"
And it's super interesting.
It's quite long too.
It's not like a 10 minute short.
I think it's like 40 minutes long.
The thrust of the story is some of the monks are saying, "This is totally legit."
He actually believes.
It's not just that he has this memory and can cite everything about our religion.
He believes in it.
And not only does he believe in it, he might be the Buddha because he has been able to
release himself from all attachments.
He can truly, when he meditates, he thinks of nothing.
He has truly learned to cleanse his mind.
He is devoid of all sin.
He might be the Buddha.
And the other group of monks are saying, "Yeah, his mind is clean because he can literally
shut himself off.
It's a machine.
He can't actually believe this stuff.
He's just a machine.
A tour guide, really.
So he knows everything about it, but he can't believe it.
And the technique, it's super interesting because you see that kind of argument going
on and then we get to see the robot following the tenets of Buddhism and how that's affecting
everyone of the temple.
And the repairman is trying to figure out what to do.
So you have all these different stories going on.
Do you shut him off?
Because that's what the officials of the temple want.
They just want him to shut off.
Or do you let him continue to work?
It's super interesting.
I really, really love that short film.
I've watched it a couple of times over the years.
And we've been talking so much about AI recently that I was like, "I got to mention this.
I really got to mention this."
It's called, the full movie is called Doomsday Book, but the second feature, I barely remember
the first.
I think it had somebody do a zombie's the first movie maybe.
But the second part, the heavenly creature is fascinating.
It's just great sci-fi.
Really, it's just really, really good sci-fi.
So Dead Rabbit Radio recommends checking out Doomsday Book.
That is the movie you will look for if you want to check this out.
Doomsday Book.
And the second feature is the one about the robot, the Buddhist monk robot.
It's just absolutely fascinating even to say that.
And yeah, it's great.
I really, really enjoy it.
So we just go ahead and land this carpenter copter in Hawaii.
Specifically we're in Honolulu and when we land, we're all stretching our legs out.
We're like, "Yeah, dude, this is awesome.
We're running into the sand."
Weee!
In the waters, we're swimming like sea turtles.
We're just totally relaxing.
It's been a long time, if ever, that we've had a vacation spot and a Dead Rabbit Radio
episode.
So we're just chilling on the beach, catching some rays and enjoying the beautiful Hawaiian
islands.
And while we're doing that, a family is headed out to a new house.
This is a house they've just rented as they are going to live in Hawaii for a while.
We have the Campbell family.
This story starts in May 2019.
You have the Campbell family, James and Brittany Campbell.
And he brought two boys with him from a previous relationship, but together they're one happy
family.
There's a couple dogs as well.
James was just loving life.
Now James is in the military and he was now going to be stationed out of Hawaii, so that's
why they're renting this house.
And I mean, what could be better, right?
Young family, young love, beautiful location.
It's all going to work out.
They move in in May and there's a slow unboxing process.
So it's not like they're in a hurry to get all the, every box unpacked.
You know, you're just going to let the process play out.
But by the time they go for a vacation in September, it's been quite a few months, they
still have a lot of boxes in their garage.
They go for a week-long vacation in September 2019.
When they come back, Brittany goes into the garage to grab something and the boxes in
there are all opened up.
And things, the way Brittany described it was she said things were thrown out of the
boxes, but then they were thrown into piles.
So there was an order to it, but it still appeared like things were just pulled out and thrown
in every direction.
And yet you had these different piles of items that were related.
She calls in her husband James.
James, James, come in the garage.
I think someone's broken into the house.
That would be your first thing.
Someone was rummaging through your boxes looking for valuables.
So James comes into the garage, he looks at it.
He also assumes they've been robbed while they were gone for a week.
But after checking through everything, it appears that nothing has been stolen.
At least nothing of value, nothing they could notice was missing from the boxes or the piles.
Everything seemed to be there.
These figures, maybe one of the dogs did it.
Maybe one of the dogs opened up all these boxes and threw the things into very specific
piles.
You're going to quickly learn that James, while probably a good father and husband,
makes a lot of really boneheaded decisions this whole story.
And this is 100% a true story.
There's been a bunch of news coverage of this, all sorts of stuff.
It's absolutely insane.
James, probably a good guy, makes a lot of weird moves in the story.
Anyways, a week later, Brittany is at home alone and she hears the front door slam.
And it's loud.
It's like an angry slam.
She's in the house and she's home alone, but she assumes that it's James and the kids coming
back.
"James?"
House is dead quiet.
"James, did you just come in?
What was...
Did you just slam the door?"
No answer.
Later when James and the boys do come back home, she asks him, "Hey, did you come back
earlier?"
And he heard the front door just like slam shut.
He's like, "No, no, actually we're just coming back right now."
I wasn't here earlier.
She goes, "That's so weird because I swear that I heard the door slam shut."
And he goes, "Well, you know, maybe it was the wind.
Did you leave the door open?"
She's like, "No!
Someone would have had to open it to slam it shut.
Maybe it was the wind."
Later that same night, Brittany wakes up in the middle of the night because she hears
the sound of a door opening.
"Wake up, James.
James, wake up.
James, I think someone's in the house.
I'm hearing a door open up."
Remember, just a week ago, somebody was in the dogs.
Somebody or something got into their boxes and was throwing stuff everywhere.
Earlier that day, a front door was slam shut.
Now she's hearing a door handle being jiggled.
He says, "You're just being paranoid.
I'm not even going to get out of bed.
I am not even going to get out of bed, Brittany.
I think you're just being paranoid.
Don't worry about it.
Don't worry about the sound of people trying to get into our house."
Well, he goes back to sleep.
She goes down and she checks.
I don't know if it's exactly the front door.
It might have been the back door, but it was one of the doors leading outside.
She goes down and she checks the door.
It's unlocked.
She then locks it, goes upstairs to tell James, "Hey, listen.
I think someone's in the house.
I just found the door unlocked.
I know that I locked it when we went to bed."
She wakes him up and James is so mad that she keeps waking him up.
Over her being paranoid, they start fighting.
They get into a full argument in the middle of the night about whether or not Brittany
is being paranoid because she thinks somebody is coming into their house.
And while they are having this argument, they hear the back door slam shut.
Both of them clearly hear that back door slam shut and James goes, "It's just the wind,
baby.
It's all the wind.
I'm not even going to check.
I'm a service man.
I've been tasked with protecting America's freedoms, but walking to go check that back
door, I didn't sign up for that.
I didn't sign up for that.
You're just being paranoid.
That was just the wind.
We're going back to bed."
Several days later, James is alone in the house.
Here's the point time where James gets a taste of it.
James is alone in the house and he's playing the piano.
Now he's not a supervillain.
He's not the fan of the opera.
I don't know if that's a thing.
I guess people do sit in their house all alone and play the piano.
That sounds menacing in and of itself.
Just sitting in a house alone playing the piano.
I don't know.
Is that a thing?
But he did it.
I'm sure Lex Luthor's done it a couple of times.
He's sitting in his house, playing the piano.
When all of a sudden he gets the feeling that somebody's watching him, that unmistakable
feeling that somebody has their eyes locked on you, and he turns and he looks and the
drapes were shut.
So he couldn't see outside the window, but the way that the sunlight was hitting the window
so perfectly, he clearly saw the silhouette of a man standing outside.
He sees the silhouette of a man standing outside as a window.
He can't really see who it is.
He just sees the outline of an adult male perfectly framed by the sun, beaming down.
This dude's staring at James.
James sees the silhouette watching him play the piano.
The silhouette then runs away and James goes, "Hmm, that must be one of my neighbors I haven't
met yet."
They were just curious.
They walked right up to my window in the middle of the day to hear me play piano.
They didn't knock on the door.
They didn't introduce themselves.
They just stood menacingly right outside my house, staring at me while my back was to
them.
It must just be a neighbor.
Now I'm not saying he had a run out there with a crowbar or anything, but at this point
he should be putting stuff together that whatever is going on, it is connected and it is unusual
and it is something you should be afraid of.
A couple days after that, the family decides to go to the movies.
And there's this thing where Brittany likes to bring her favorite blanket to wrap herself
up in the movie theater.
But she can't find it.
And they look all over the house.
I'll be honest, this family, at least the parents, seem a little high maintenance, but they can't
go to the movies so they find Brittany's favorite blanket.
The kids are looking for it.
James is probably pretending to look for it.
He's like, "Ah, not this again."
Brittany's tearing the house up and down looking for this blanket.
They can't find it anywhere.
Whatever, we'll just go to the movies.
Let's just go.
Brittany's finally given up finding this blanket.
When they come back from the movies, right when they walk into the living room, sitting
on the couch, neatly folded up, is Brittany's blanket.
So at this point, there is no more, "This is the wind.
This is the neighbors.
You're just being paranoid."
Something is going on in this house.
And really, the smartest move anyone's ever made in any of these type of stories, they
leave for three months.
They're like, "We're not even going back to this house.
Get what you have on you.
We're out of this house for three months."
And you would have to think.
I read a bunch of articles on this.
At no point did they say we thought it was a ghost.
But you would have to think.
At a certain point, you would go, "It has to be a ghost."
Because what other phenomenon could possibly do this?
It's in the house.
It's rummaging through your stuff.
It's opening and closing doors.
Now, you would assume it was like a burglar, but what type of burglar is going to fold
your blanket?
Like burgle your blanket and then bring it back.
It's all nice and washed with a little note from the burglar.
Doesn't make sense.
You have the person standing outside.
And honestly, I would be shocked if James told Brittany that happened.
He might have told her about that way after the fact, but I doubt Brittany came home from
work and he's like, "Honey, you won't believe what happened today."
A neighbor stopped by and she's like, "Oh, really?
Which one?"
And he goes, "I don't know."
He was a silhouette.
He was a stationary silhouette.
He's standing right outside the window staring at me while I played the piano.
She's like, "What?
That's not a neighbor.
That's probably the same weirdo who keeps opening and closing doors."
I doubt he told her about that at the time.
They leave the house for three weeks.
They figure whatever is there, I don't know actually what they were thinking.
I mean, you have to come back, right?
You rent the house.
You've already signed a lease.
You'd have to come back at a certain point.
But anyways, after three weeks, they come back to the house and right when they're pulling
up, I mean, they don't even get in the house.
This already goes insane.
As they're pulling up to the house, James sees that his bike that he left in the garage
because that's what you do when you're going to be gone for a period of time so people
don't steal stuff.
As he's pulling up, he sees his bike sitting in the driveway.
At that point, they open the garage and it is a complete mess.
It's just completely tore apart.
Stuff's everywhere.
I'm assuming they left the kids in the car because at this point, they're like somebody's
in the house.
It could be a pulled or guys, right?
But they open the garage, they see all these junk strewn everywhere in the garage and then
there's a bunch of prescription bottles.
They're not James and Brittany's prescriptions.
There's a bunch of medicine there and they're like, "What in the world is this?"
So Brittany calls 911.
James, this is probably what I would do but I would also think I was being boneheaded in
this.
Brittany's on the phone at 911.
James grabs a hammer out of the garage and decides to go into the house.
Somebody is getting their brains beaten out tonight.
James goes to open the front door and he can't.
Well, I mean, technically he could.
He did just a little bit but then he felt a force pushing on the door from the other
side.
And James hears a very calm voice say, "This is not your house."
James put that phrase to the test when he proceeded to kick his way through the door,
kick the door open, knocking the guy to the ground and then dragged him outside of the
house.
This was not a ghost.
It was not a fan.
It wasn't a neighbor.
It was a dude named Ezekiel Zayez.
He's a 23-year-old man and he'd been living in the house with them.
The police show up, right?
They arrest this guy for breaking and entering but the truth was going to be far more insane.
Like we're just getting started with this story.
I know we don't have a lot of time left but his story is insane.
This guy was living in the house with him undetected.
I mean, he wasn't doing the great job on the undetected part.
He kept making a lot of noise when he was coming and going.
And the police don't know how long he was there.
The police don't know if he was there for a long time.
They don't know if he showed up during the week they were gone on their first vacation
but he was living in the house while they were there.
But he wasn't some homeless bum.
He might have been a homeless bum but his goal wasn't just to find a place to live and
he'd have access to delicious food as long as he snuck around at night.
No.
He was using a laptop computer.
One of James and Brittany's laptop computers.
So funny because Brittany goes, there was some webcam footage.
He was doing like this.
He was doing this video blog apparently and there was webcam footage of him completely
naked sitting in Brittany's office chair and she's like, "That's so gross.
He was naked.
He was in my chair."
I was like, "Listen lady, he did way grosser stuff.
That's really the thing you're complaining about than you are very, very isolated.
You've lived a very comfortable existence because that wasn't the worst thing he did
that he sat with his balls touching your leather chair."
No.
On a computer he began writing the Omnivore Trials.
That's not a spin off of Hunger Games.
The Omnivore Trials was his research paper.
The full title of it was The Omnivore Trials, A Rehabilitation for Rat-Like People.
And this was a diary of sorts.
It talked about him breaking into the house.
It talked about how he observed the Campbells, aka the Rat-Like People.
He considered they were simply test subjects and he was a researcher compiling notes.
His goal, he was going to turn these Omnivores into Ezekiels.
That's what the prescription medication was for.
I would love to get my hands on this document.
They haven't released it to the public.
Probably completely terrifying.
They don't want to inspire any copycats.
His goal was to drug the family, all of them.
The husband, the wife, and the two kids.
And give them "corrective surgeries."
He went into detail how he wanted to give them sex changes.
He wanted to drug this family and then...
What do I have to go into detail?
You're like, "Oh, I wonder what that means, Jason."
Go into detail about that.
What did he plan on doing to the kids?
I don't think I have to go into detail.
He wanted to give them all sex changes.
He wanted to do that.
He also wanted to do hand transplants, which I mean, at that point.
If I'm tied to a chair and someone goes, "I'm going to cut off your genitals."
I'm like, "No!"
And then he goes, "And then I'm going to cut off your hand."
I would be like, "You might want to start with that one.
That one's not as threatening."
I mean, I want both my hands, but if you're trying to psychologically torture someone,
start by saying you're going to cut off my hand.
And then my genitals.
I'm all giving him advice.
I'm like, "If you really want a good cut, hold the salt like this."
No, he talked about doing limb transplants.
He wanted to cut hands off some of the family members and give me hilarious.
This mom woke up and she had her little son's hands.
He's like, "Oh no, these hands haven't even gone through puberty yet.
There's no hair on the knuckles."
I don't know why she would complain about that.
She's like, "Come on, man.
Give me my husband's hands.
Give me them hairy knuckles."
But yeah, he wanted to do hand transplants and sex changes.
And this would turn them into Ezekials.
I'm sure there was other stuff he wanted to do.
Again, that's why I kind of want to get my hands on this talking book, my transplanted
hands on it.
Right now I have the hands of an elderly grandmother.
I want to get my hands on this document.
I want to see what else he was up to.
That can't be it.
He can't be like...
I imagine there's more.
I imagine he's sicker than that.
But I mean, that's pretty bad, right?
Four?
You're like, "Jason, you wanted to give this a family of four forced sex changes."
And you're like, "Oh, come on, Ezekiel.
You can do better than this."
Maybe I do give advice to weirdos.
The police don't know how long he was there.
They do realize that this guy is a menace.
He'd broken into this house.
He was threatening to mutilate this family.
And in typical police fashion, they let him go.
I'm not joking.
The police didn't let him go right there, but he got basically a charge for burglary.
That was it.
You got a charge for burglary.
And I don't know.
I don't know if it's even the police officers themselves, but a judge was like, "Well, you
know what?
We'll let you go free until your trial."
Maybe it was a low bail or whatever.
So this lunatic who had been hiding in his family's home was allowed to walk free shortly
after his arrest.
Then what happened was he went to a Buddhist temple.
He went to a Buddhist temple in Hawaii and vandalized it.
And that was when the court system was like, "What?
You painted on that building?
You sir or a menace to society?"
They threw him in jail long term for that.
Breaking into someone's house, talking about cutting a bunch of dicks off, that's totally
fine.
That's what we do here.
But vandalizing a building, they've gone too far.
And it is a religious structure, I get that.
But I'm assuming even most Buddhist monks would be like, "Wait, that guy wasn't already
arrested?
Wait, what?
How was that guy even free?"
It's nuts because he gets to that vandalism charge and the burglary charge.
He ends up in prison in 2020.
And that's when, if you don't remember, we had all those COVID lockdowns.
And I remember when I, because I have friends that are in prison, I remember thinking about
my cousin Billy.
I was like, "Dude, it's crummy out of prison during all this COVID stuff.
I'm locked down.
This is like the initial two weeks, right?"
And I was thinking about my cousin Billy.
I was like, "Dude, that must suck.
You're locked up and you're in prison and all of a sudden you have this disease flowing
around that nobody knows about.
How much it must have sucked?"
Well, that's what Ezekiel was going through.
I get careless if he had a sucky experience in jail.
But in 2020, he got COVID.
And he was put in this cell with three other prisoners who had COVID at the time.
They were just trying to isolate them.
This is super early days.
I don't think they do this anymore.
This was the super early days of the outbreak.
So you had Ezekiel, this lunatic, and then you had another guy.
We don't know who that guy was.
But then we had a career thief.
Listen, this guy wasn't an angel.
This other guy, his name was Vance Grace.
He was 62 years old.
He dealt drugs and he was a career criminal.
He'd been in and out of incarceration throughout his life.
He was one month away from being released.
He's 62 years old.
He gets COVID and they throw him in this cell with Ezekiel who proceeds.
We don't know why he did this.
Because again, the guy's a lunatic and the third inmate was just watching this going,
"Oh my God, apparently there's a safety button you can hit in this isolation cell that helps
the guards get in.
Helps the guards get in faster.
I don't know if they call it the snitch button or what.
But I assume you're going to have to use it from time to time."
Who knows why he did this?
They've never really figured it out.
But Ezekiel knocked Vance to the ground and began attacking him.
The 62 year old man who was a month away from getting out, he begins attacking him.
And when the guards are alerted, the third prisoner's like, "Help!
This guy's getting murdered in here."
The guards are trying to get into the cell and they're like, "They can't get in."
And now Ezekiel has this man, has Vance on the ground and he begins stomping on this
old man's head.
And the guards are trying to get in and that's when the third inmate has to activate a button
from inside the cell that'll help the guards get in quicker.
This is so bizarre.
But anyways, maybe they just made this story up because people were wondering, "Hey guards,
what took you so long?
This old man was getting assaulted in the cell and they're like, "Well, you know, the
button on the inside that opens the door."
They're like, "Wait, there's a button on the inside of cells that opens doors?
I don't get it."
But anyways, the guards finally get into the cell and Vance is already dead.
Like he just got stomped out by Ezekiel.
And Vance's son is suing the prisoner.
They go, "You dropped the ball a hundred different times there.
One, you didn't get it on the cell quick enough.
Two, he goes, "My dad shouldn't have been in there in the first place."
Like you put him in with dangerous people.
You put him in with psychopaths.
And he was just a thief and you just go, "Oh, he has COVID.
Let's just put him in a cell with other people who have COVID."
And he goes, "You're responsible for my dad dying."
I definitely think there's a lawsuit there, right?
Because the prison made that situation happen.
But after that, Ezekiel is now getting charged with murder.
He's now getting charged with murder.
And he is determined to be too crazy for trial.
The court psychiatrists say, "This guy is certifiably insane.
We can't hold the trial right now."
And what they do when they do that is they put you in a mental hospital until you become
fit for trial when you can actually comprehend the charges against you.
And then they will put you on trial.
That's how this system works out.
And I imagine he was showing psychotic behaviors in prison.
And that's why the guards should have known better than to put these people in the cell
together.
But they were just like, "Everyone has COVID.
You're all going in here."
Because if you're so insane, usually like people can be be, Jeffrey Dahmer was found
fit for trial.
Like you can be an insane person eating other people.
And the court goes, "Yeah, you know, you're sane.
You have to be pretty bad off to get one of these too insane to be held fit for trial."
So I doubt, I'm sure that he was showing symptoms of this for a while in prison.
He was definitely showing them outside of prison.
He was breaking into people's house trying to cut their hands off.
So they put him in a mental hospital where he will be held until trial.
But here's the creepy boy.
If that really takes it, it was all creepy.
It was all terrifying.
As you're listening to this episode, you're walking around the broom.
You're checking your attics and everything.
You're like, "I don't know.
Man, this episode is kind of creepy.
I was hoping it was just a ghost.
I was hoping it was just as much as skulls floating around.
Now this is real life."
He was put in the mental hospital and there is no word of what has happened next.
Nothing.
Nobody knows where this guy is.
They don't even know what hospital he's in.
I couldn't find any articles that talked about that.
This was actually, there's a bunch of stories about the Campbell family.
It was an episode of a show, like there's some lifetime I think, or a TLC show called
Living in My House, or some weirdo in My House, you know how all their shows are.
It's real life stories about people who live in other people's houses.
You're like, "Yeah, Jason, that's Airbnb."
No, I think they call it frogging or fragging or something like that.
That's where someone lives in your house and you don't know it.
There's enough of these that they have an entire television show about it.
This story was highlighted on there.
This is a high profile case.
There's a ton of articles about it.
You have an open lawsuit as well.
Whenever you have an open lawsuit, there's constantly information coming in because Vance's
son is suing the Hawaii Department of Corrections.
Where is this guy now?
Because I'll tell you this.
I do not trust the system to keep us safe.
I read more than enough true crime stories where people, I don't know just for example,
break into a house and want to chop off people's genitals and then they're allowed to walk
free.
I read stories all the time about killers who get paroled.
I actually covered a story recently on my TikTok.
A guy was acquitted of double homicide, a gangland slain at a recording studio.
This guy shot two people at a recording studio execution style.
He was found not guilty and then nine days later kills his girlfriend who was carrying
his baby.
She was five months pregnant, nine days after being acquitted of a double homicide.
The system is not set up to protect us.
So when they say we're going to put him in a mental hospital and we're going to keep
him here until he's fit for trial and then we're going to move.
I don't believe you.
I don't believe you because I have eyes and I read the paper and they're not saying where
this guy is.
Nobody knows where he's at.
Court documents, reality television shows, journalist writing articles, they don't know
where he's at.
And because the system sucks, because it does not protect us, it is possible that he is
in your house right now.
Right?
It's possible.
If you live in Hawaii, it's probable, right?
It's most likely going to happen at some point that Ezekiel will be in your, is basically
classified as some sort of spider.
Now they're like, well, if you live in Hawaii, you might run into an Ezekiel hiding in your
cupboards.
It is possible.
It is not outside the realms of possibility that right now Ezekiel is hiding in your house.
So sleep tight, dear friends.
Have a pleasant dream as you drift off to sleep.
You didn't notice that you're milk, you drink warm milk every night, don't you?
You didn't notice the taste at a little odd this time.
It tasted like crushed up prescription medication.
You're like, hmm, just like grandma used to make.
My grandma, who was a drug dealer, had to hide evidence all the time in my milk.
Oh, this taste reminds me of good.
And your eyelids grow heavy and you're fighting the sleep.
All of a sudden you see your bedroom door open and Ezekiel walks in.
You know what's Ezekiel?
Because he's wearing like a super village shirt with a big E on it.
He's like, ah, yes, sleep, my pretty sleep.
Soon you will wake up with new hands.
You're like, what?
You dude, you know how terrifying that would be?
You're falling asleep.
You've been drugged.
And the guy's like giving a speech about what he's going to do to you.
He's like, oh yeah, these are particularly nice genitals.
But I have some much, much better for you.
I found the perfect match.
And you're like, ah, you're all snoring.
You're snoring like it's a bobbycut.
As he begins to saw your hands off, it could happen.
It could happen tonight.
You don't know.
We don't know where this lunatic is.
Right now he could be waiting for you to take a drink of that milk.
He's going to turn you into an Ezekiel.
Welcome to the new world.
Hope you enjoy.
You enjoy baby hands.
Hope you enjoy having tiny, tiny hands.
DeadRabberRadio@gmail.com is going to be your email address.
You can also go to stepfacephys.com/deadrabberradio.
DeadRabberRadio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast.
You don't have to listen to it every day.
I'm so glad you listened to it today.
Have a great weekend, guys.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
(upbeat music)
[BLANK_AUDIO]