When a young woman is found dead in the middle of the woods, everyone's a suspect.
And then we travel to Mexico to take a look at the story of an alien invader that landed
on the outskirts of a village and began killing the men one by one.
If you think that's the plot for the movie Predator, you're not alone.
What was that hit movie based on a true story?
Today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
[Music]
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Carpenter.
I'm having a great day.
I hope you guys are having a great day too.
I hope you guys are having tons of fun out there in the world.
We got a lot of stuff to cover so we're going to get started right away.
First off, walking into Dead Rabbit Command.
Everyone give it up for our newest Patreon supporter, Matt.
Woohoo!
Yeah, walk on in.
Come on in, bud.
Come on in to Dead Rabbit Command, Matt.
You're going to be our captain, our pilot this episode.
You guys can't support the Patreon.
I totally understand.
Just help spread the word about Dead Rabbit Radio.
That helps out so much.
Now, Matt, I hope that you are ready to fight.
Like, no dude, I just joined the Patreon.
I just like the show.
I hope you brought all the weapons you need because we're going to hunt a beast in the
second story.
You can kind of relax.
The first story only involves a horrific murder.
Hopefully, don't bring your gun to that one.
You might be a suspect.
Matt, let's go ahead and toss you the keys to the Jason Jalopy we are leaving behind Dead
Rabbit Command.
Drive us all the way out to the Netherlands.
Nice leisurely journey across the bottom of the Atlantic Ocean until we finally arrive
in the Netherlands.
Specifically, we're headed to the town of Eindhoven.
It's October 6th, 1995.
I've recently learned I can't say 6th.
You know, like the number 6.
October 6th, 1995, two days after my birthday.
We're going to meet this girl named Nicole Vanderherg.
She's 15 years old and she's had quite a troubled life up to this point.
Her mother had committed suicide in April of 1995.
So it's just been a couple months dealing with that trauma.
The custody of her was given to her stepfather, a man named Joss D.G. and she now had a step
brother as well due to this marriage.
His name was Andy.
So he had Joss D.G. and Andy.
The father was 46, Andy was 19, and then he had this 15 year old girl.
Her mother's gone.
At this point, she actually seems to be staying with her grandmother because on October 6th,
1995, or at least she was this night.
She left her grandmother's house on her bike.
Not the grandma's bike.
Nicole's bike.
And she rides away.
She's headed to go to work, but she never shows up.
And that's out of character for Nicole.
The work is concerned.
Why isn't Nicole here?
She also never shows back up at the stepfather's house.
She never shows back up at the grandmother's house.
She's completely missing.
So the police begin to search for this 15 year old girl.
Later that day by the River Dommel, they find her bicycle.
Thirteen days later, October 19th, her backpack is found.
It's in another area.
It's not near the bicycle.
At this point, they 100% not only believe she's missing, but she's at risk.
So when they find her backpack in another location, the police are like, "Okay, something
really, really bad has happened here."
And their suspicions are confirmed a month later, a little over a month later, on November
22, 1995, they find her body.
Nicole Vanderherg, 15 years old, she had been raped and murdered, was brutally beaten, and
finally stabbed with a fishing or a pocket knife.
She was stabbed until she bled out and she passed away.
The police really zeroed in on two suspects.
Her stepfather, Jos DeGee, and her stepbrother, Handy.
The police were looking at other leads.
You're trying to figure out where she'd been in the town.
Did she have any enemies?
Did she have any stalkers?
But they really zeroed in on her family members.
This is 1995 and the fact that she was raped gives the authorities a little bit of DNA
evidence.
But in 1995, the technology is not there to really zero in on who it could be.
The interesting thing about DNA evidence is to analyze it, you must destroy it.
So you pretty much have one shot with a lot of this stuff.
And if you're looking at this and you go, "The technology is not here to 100% or even
90%," point us in the direction.
We have at least these two main suspects.
There were other people that they thought, "Well, it could be this person."
But their two main suspects was the stepbrother and the stepfather.
Both of them are arrested.
Both of them are interrogated.
Both of them have full investigations done on them.
The police are looking for evidence.
Both of them end up being released.
The police cannot prove it's the stepbrother or the stepfather.
But those are really at this point in the investigation, they've kind of ruled out everyone
else.
They've talked to the people in the town, all of that.
They know it's one of these two people.
The question is, who is it?
A few months after the murder, a family friend is arrested for drug trafficking.
And she says, while she's being investigated for that, she goes, "I know who killed Nicole."
And she pointed out this guy, saying, it was a guy that wasn't even on the police radar,
that he was the one who killed Nicole.
He knew a lot about the murder.
He seemed to know a little too much about the murder and that he had done it.
But when the police investigated him, they could find absolutely no evidence that leads
him in any way, shape, or form to the murder of Nicole.
But now that that allegation had been out there, people in town started to think, well,
maybe it's not one of these two people.
And Josti G, at this point, he wants justice for his stepdaughter.
He really wants justice.
So he says, I really think it's this guy.
I think it's this guy that this woman, he's obviously a criminal.
He's working for this drug trafficking network.
She says that he did it.
He probably did it.
And he tries to get the police to double down their efforts to look into that guy because
you want justice for your stepdaughter.
You understand that she's not of your blood, but she's still of your family.
But the police just kind of, they don't have any evidence to go off of.
Just have this statement.
They've done this full investigation.
And this stepfather understands that you need evidence.
So unless somebody confesses, or there's some sort of huge breakthrough, her murder will
most likely go unsolved.
Fast forward to the year 2004.
At this point, the case is completely gone cold.
The police have no leads.
They do not know who killed Nicole.
When she had died, there was a thousand people who attended her funeral.
The entire community mourned for the murder of this young girl.
And yet she still has not found justice.
Fast forward again to the year 2011.
Her stepbrother Andy is now 36 years old and he's living in England.
And he posts a very curious statement on his Facebook page.
He wrote, quote, "I will be arrested today for the murder of my sister.
I confessed.
We'll get in contact soon."
Imagine if you saw any of your Facebook friends post that.
Plus he was living in England.
How many people even knew about his sister?
He'd completely left.
Andy wasn't connected to this anymore.
He's got a fresh start.
And here he is in 2011.
He confesses he is the one who raped and murdered his sister.
That's not something you want to wake up to on your Facebook feed.
March 8, 2011, he is arrested.
He actually is arrested.
He's sent back to the Netherlands.
And the police began to interrogate him.
Absolutely bizarre.
He confessed to the crime.
But the police do not have enough to hold him.
There is a judge who ordered him let go.
You don't have enough information.
They're like, "He confessed.
What other information do we need?"
He was one of our main suspects and he's confessed to it.
And the judge ruled, "Listen, if you think he did it, it's the year 2011.
Let's exhume Nicole's body because now we have the DNA technology.
We know that she was raped.
We have the DNA technology to test the DNA.
He doesn't want to get gross about it.
He's like, "I don't really want to say what we're testing."
But we know that she was sexually assaulted.
So we can then test the DNA, but we have to exhume the body to get it.
Then we'll know for sure.
He's confessing, but I'm saying there's not enough evidence to hold him.
Let him go.
He was released five days later.
And the police are like, "Okay, let's exhume the body."
September 2011, they exhume the body of Nicole and there is a single sample of sperm that
they have to test.
It's a very, very small amount.
They're going to destroy it at this point, but they have a confession.
Now they just need proof.
So they test the DNA and there are three different individuals in this DNA sample.
Her boyfriend, who you would expect, right?
She was having sex with her boyfriend.
You would get a sample of that.
An unknown individual.
They could never match who that was.
And her stepfather.
This is absolutely insane.
The other day, the other day, the other day, the other day, the other day, the other day,
the other day, the other day, the other day, the other day, the other day, the other day,
the other day, the other day, the other day
the other day, the other day, the other day, the other day, the other day, the other day, the other day, the other day, the other day, the other day, the other day, the other day, the other day, the other day, the other day, the other day, the other day, the other day, the other day, the other day, the other day, the other day, the other day, the other day, the other day, the other day, the other day, the other day, the other day, the other day, the other day, the other day, the other day, the other day, the other day, the other day, the other day, the other day, the other day, the other day, the other day, the other day, the other day, the other day, the other day, the other day, the other day, the other day, the other day, the other day, the other day, the other day, the other day, the other day, the other day
the other day, the other day, the other day, the other day, the other day, the other day,
(upbeat music)