At what point does good intentions turn you into a super villain?
And then we travel to Ohio to kick off close encounters of a canine kind week.
We're going to look at three stories of what happens when dogs meet aliens.
In today's story, two hunting hounds are on the prowl looking for a skunk or fox, something
like that, something they can kill with their teeth, probably not a skunk.
Another thing about it that would be the worst thing to hunt.
Honey, look at what I brought home dinner.
With these two hunting hounds are on the prowl looking for its prey.
Instead these two dogs end up in the presence of a grey alien.
Today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host, Jason Carpenter, I'm having a great day.
I hope you guys are having a great day too.
I hope you guys are ready for close encounters of a canine kind week.
I only have three stories, I'm not going to force five, but there are three really cool
stories of what happens when man's best friend meets invaders from another world.
We'll go ahead and get that started in just a second.
First off, walking into Dead Rabbit Command is one of our legacy Patreon supporters.
Everyone get on your feet and give it up for BurntToastGhost.
Woohoo, yeah, walk on in, yeah, he's walking on in with a bunch of hound dogs, he's ready
to fight aliens.
BurntToastGhost, you're going to be our captain, our pilot this episode.
If you guys can't support this show, totally fine, I get it, just helps spread the word
about Dead Rabbit Radio.
That really does help out a lot.
And if you guys do support this show, if you guys are Patreon supporters, don't forget
we have a Patreon Discord.
And we do live episodes every Sunday and BurntToastGhost is one of those guys who tries to make sure
that he swings by all the time.
So, it's really, really a lot of fun.
It's a lot of fun.
BurntToastGhost, we're going to go ahead and start off by tossing you the keys to the
Dead Rabbit Dune Buggy.
We're going to leave behind Dead Rabbit Command and drive us all the way out to a volcano.
We're walking around the edge of this volcano, lava spewing everywhere.
It's all erupted and stuff.
And we got on our heat resistance suit, you're not just wearing regular clothes as you listen
to this podcast, you're not geared up, sorry bro.
Lot lava spewing everywhere and those of us who wore heat resistance suits were like jumping
around in it.
I think it's just that they're heat resistant.
I don't think they're lava proof.
But anyways, we're hanging out at the edge of this volcano or feet are dangling over
the rim.
And the reason why we're here is volcanoes are sometimes good.
That was the name of my thesis in college.
Volcanoes are sometimes good.
Because yes, while they suck because they're like shooting lava everywhere and people have
to run from them like boulders are falling on top of people.
Sometimes if the world is, okay I can strap in because this is a science based story.
This is a good old Jason.
Jason read a single article.
That's not fair.
I did read multiple articles but Jason's going to try to explain something that world class
scientists struggle to put into words.
Anyways, lava sometimes bad because it melts people.
If it's like chasing after you and you have a cramp in your leg you're like, "I'm dead."
But while we mourn your sacrifice to the lava gods, sometimes lava is good or volcanoes
are good because it can reduce the temperature of the planet.
Because as it's like spilling lava everywhere, there's also a bunch of dust coming.
How does the dust shoot out of it now?
Oh, clouds.
So the clouds billow out.
It's not actual dust I don't think.
Google search can easily answer this for me.
But anyway, clouds are shooting out of the volcano.
Hot lava is terrorizing the people below.
But then because the clouds will cover the sky, the sunbeams can't get in.
So it makes things get cooler.
So as you're slowly boiling to death as you're like, "Oh man, why did I pick today to eat
this watermelon on the edge of a volcano?"
And you're boiling, you're blowing up, melting from the inside, pick your poison.
You can enjoy.
You're like, "Oh, this sure is a nice breeze.
This sure is a nice cool breeze on the last remaining two inches of my skin."
Because it can actually cool the planet.
But sometimes volcanoes are still bad because as the planet cools, crops, like you're growing,
you got a bunch of wheat, and you're like, "Good old sunlight.
Thanks for doing your part.
Thanks for doing your part on this farm, giving these plants all the nutrients they need."
And then all of a sudden, a giant volcanic cloud starts floating around and it's like,
"Ha ha ha ha ha."
And it's like standing, it's standing just over your crops.
It's like all your neighbors, their wheat continues to grow and the volcano is like,
"I hate you."
And then if it's too cold, crops can't grow and people have to buy jackets because they're
getting a little chilly too.
But sometimes volcanoes can still be good because despite the fact that everything's
getting cooler and you're only your crops are dying, it can reduce the temperature overall.
And people are concerned about global warming.
They don't really use that term anymore.
But global warming, they're concerned about climate change.
So volcanoes can be good and bad.
It's all well and good.
Or bad.
It's all well and good or bad.
But what happens?
This is actually a real story that's going on and people are incredibly concerned about
this because listen, we can't tell when a volcano is going to go off and it can cause
massive disruptions to the environment.
We know that.
But what if somebody decided to start setting off volcanoes on purpose but to solve global
warming?
What if there was a group of people, a dedicated organization that exists today that decides
we are going to set off multiple volcanoes all around the world and it will actually,
in the long run, it will help the world because the temperature will drop and we will end
the climate crisis.
Generally, we would call that group, we call that group Cobra, right?
That sounds like a terrorist act from a 1980s cartoon.
But there is actually a group called Make Sunsets.
And this is a real group.
Now while they aren't as cool as actually like I would have been like I have 10 nuclear
bombs built underneath all of these volcanoes.
I lost thousands of men planting them.
They all melted.
But the bombs didn't melt and now world leaders bow to me and climate change.
That's what I'm really doing it for.
It's not to make people bow to me.
It's climate change.
I'm fighting it.
They're not that cool.
They're not actually blowing up a volcano.
What would happen if you blew up a volcano actually?
That's kind of interesting.
Jamie, find that out.
Find that out and get back to me.
They are creating artificial volcanoes.
It's not much of an air baking powder or baking soda, whatever it is.
It's not that.
They have these weather balloons.
It's the real reason why Biden's been shooting all that stuff down.
What they're doing is they're using weather balloons that will release.
This is totally true.
They have these weather balloons.
I don't know why I keep saying that.
I talk about ghosts all the time and I just assume that stuff's true.
They have these weather balloons that are going to release sulfur into the air.
This mimics the good part of the volcano.
It's the less cool part of the volcano to be honest.
It's kind of lame.
But the sulfur in the air, they're releasing it.
So it mimics the effect, the cooling effect of the volcano.
You know what all the smoke and dust is of there.
It creates a cloud of particles that reflects the sun rays away from the planet.
And here's the thing.
They've already done this once.
This is a new article.
I just read this article written by Emma Gatton.
This article came out about two weeks ago where they were talking about it and they're
like, "We're doing this because we need to save the world.
We need to stop the climate problem.
We need to cool the earth down because it's steadily getting hotter."
Think about all those chunks of ice that are breaking off and stuff like that.
That's what we're trying to stop is what this...
You know what's so funny?
Their group is called Make Sunsets.
And that's not as cool as Cobra or Skeletor or the Decepticons, right?
But it's actually worse because I think in real life the creepies, the creepos out there,
allegedly, allegedly, I don't know how creepy these people are.
I don't know if they have a bunch of mutant henchmen or stuff like that, but you would
name your group like Rise or you would call it like the Helping Hand Project.
And you would basically be like creating mind-controlled monkeys to take over countries.
You wouldn't name a group Cobra.
As cool as that is, you wouldn't because everyone would go, "Well, I don't want you operating
in my country.
I'm not going to donate money to your 501(c)(3) non-profit.
You're called Cobra."
So they're called Make Sunsets, which is spooky.
Spooky.
So anyways, and you go, "Jason, you're just being an alarmist.
All these people are doing it.
All of a sudden you remember of the group, all my Patreon donators, they just leave.
So like he's discovered our plan."
This has gotten so bad that you can go back, because this is not a new plan.
People have been talking about this for years, but you can also see articles going back years
where other scientists, most scientists are saying, "This is a terribly bad idea."
Like yes, the world's getting hotter.
And yes, if you release sulfur into the air, it will do what you're saying it to do.
But the scientific community is totally against this.
And it was interesting, Sir David Attenborough, you know, the narrator guy.
He was talking about this, I think, back in like 2012, and he said, "He called this fascist.
He called this practice fascist."
He had this interesting quote.
He said, "Geoengineering is a very difficult thing, because what that means is that you
allow one nation or one small group within that nation to determine what's going to happen
to the whole globe."
And he says, you know, that's really, it's fascist to do that.
You have other scientists, other leading scientists saying, "Everyone agrees that this
would work as far as like a scientific experiment, a scientific principle."
But they go, "Listen, you'd have to do it all over the globe at the same time.
If you just change, if you just release this sulfur into the northern hemisphere, it's
going to destroy the southern hemisphere."
They go, "Monsun seasons would become completely unpredictable.
We wouldn't be able to," not like they're doing a good job of predicting the weather
now, but we want to be able to predict it even less, and we want to know when to prepare.
It would throw everything off.
So if you're going to do this, you have to do this everywhere.
The problem is, is make sunsets has done this, well, as the time of this recording, they've
done it once.
They originally planned to do it from Mexico, and they released this balloon in December,
December 2022.
This is the first time people are announcing that they're doing this.
It'll be interesting.
I wonder if anyone's tried it before.
They're releasing two kilograms of sulfur into the air.
They launched it from Mexico, the first one.
The Mexican government goes, "You can't do that here.
You can't do that here."
So this is so insane.
They can't do it in Mexico.
The government said, "Get out of here.
We don't know what."
I mean, we know what you're trying to do, and that's nice, I guess, but this is rogue
science.
So the government in Mexico kicked them out, so now they're in California.
In California governments, like, "Sure, go ahead, throw up that sulfur, guys," and they're
planning on launching another balloon full of this.
And they're like, "We have..."
The thing is, when you look at these articles, when you...
They're all being in the show notes, but when you look at these articles, you have this
divide.
Basically, you have everyone in the scientific community.
Well, not everyone.
A biologist probably doesn't know anything about this, or a social scientist is like,
"What sulfur?"
But in the climate scientists, they're like, "Don't do this.
This is a terrible idea.
If you're going to do it, you have to do it everywhere at once, and you can't have one
person deciding to do it."
But on the other hand, you have...
Make sunsets say, "We can't wait for global consensus.
We can't wait.
Eventually, it's going to be irreversible.
The damage to the climate is going to be irreversible.
If we wait, it'll be too late.
So we are going to take action because of the rest of the world sitting around twiddling
their thumbs."
So they're launching these balloons.
They're being funded.
People are donating money to this.
And they're changing, or at this point attempting to change the environment.
One balloon at a time.
That would be so hilarious.
That's the reason why all these balloons are getting shot down.
It's not UFOs.
It's make sunsets.
And they're like, "Drats!
My balloons!
They keep getting destroyed!"
And then there's like a sexy scientist in a black leather medical coat, and she's like,
"Oh, yes, but maybe.
Just maybe.
Well, the plan is just to release more balloons, right?
Yes, we'll release balloons until they run out of missiles!"
And that's what they're going to do.
I actually didn't actually say that.
It wasn't a direct quote.
We're going to release balloons until they run out of missiles.
But bear their interesting story.
And it comes to, I get, listen, I get the idea of saying, if we sit around and wait for the
entire world to decide to do this, it may be too late.
I understand the logic.
But on the other hand, if every other scientist in this field is telling you to stop, you
probably should stop.
But you can't make them.
Again, this is, it comes down to rogue scientists, where you have people saying, "We're going
to launch these balloons because we can't wait."
And that's the thing.
We'll wrap it up like this.
I find it so interesting.
The most compelling villains have understandable motives.
If not, I think, but here's the thing.
I'm not going to talk about Thanos or anything like that.
When you look at Ted Kaczynski, the unabomber, he, sure, he loved blowing up innocent people.
I mean, that's the first thing that you don't want to sing on a resume.
Someone's going to get a job with you.
But his goal was to de-technologize the world.
He was like the world.
The modern world has become sick.
This is so funny.
This is way before the internet and smartphones, a little bit of internet, but not like it
is today.
Social media, smartphones, all that stuff, self-driving cars.
He's like, "Society's sick.
It has too much technology to it.
We're losing connection to nature."
He built his bombs out of natural parts.
Wooden bombs.
He's like, "Oh, I shaved the gunpowder myself.
I mined it out of a mind and used the woodpeckers beak as the firing pin."
He made these bombs 100% natural, 100% organic killing machines.
So you could say his means was terrible, blowing people up, but his motive wasn't.
I mean, again, I'm not saying, I don't want to live in that world.
I like social media and I obviously have a podcast and stuff like that.
That doesn't exist in his world.
I'm writing stuff down and giving it to carrier pigeons and I'm like, "Fly, fly away."
I don't want to live in that world, but I can understand someone who would.
And again, he's like, "Well, no one's making a change, so I guess I got to blow up all
these people."
It's interesting that I used him as an example because there is a theory, a conspiracy theory,
that he really just like blowing people up.
And then he retconned a theory.
He retconned a, because he wrote that big manifesto afterwards.
And it's so funny to note, I remember when the Unabomber wrote his manifesto, you could
buy it at a bookstore.
They published it.
It was like 20,000 words or something like that, maybe even more.
You could read his manifesto.
Could you imagine them doing that today?
Isn't that really interesting?
And that would have been like the late 90s was when he got caught.
His brother had recognized phrases and beliefs.
Actually, that shoots that conspiracy theory out of the water because he had the brother
read the manifesto.
We didn't know who the Unabomber was.
He didn't say buy Ted Kazinsky on the manifesto.
People were like, "Oh, my favorite author.
I hope he publishes more books soon."
He recognized phrases that his brother used.
"I'm going to kill you all."
He was like, "Yeah, my brother did often mention about killing us all with a wooden bomb."
We thought it was weird growing up, but now it all makes sense.
Phrases that his brother used and beliefs that his brother had.
So, Ted Kazinsky's brother was reading the manifesto and he's like, "Oh, Ted.
Ted.
Teddy, teddy, teddy."
And turned his brother in.
Now he sleeps on a pile of reward money every night.
That'd be hard.
I shouldn't make fun of that.
That'd be hard to turn your brother in.
But anyways, you understand the motive.
When you look at somebody like...
Who's that guy?
This one's probably more controversial to bring up.
Then we'll move on because I could keep doing this.
It's on the tip of my tongue.
I'm pretty good at remembering my mass killers.
Timothy McVeigh.
Timothy McVeigh, Terry Nichols, and the third...
There was a third guy involved in that.
I 100% believe...
My conspiracy theory...
I know I'm going to go on a little off script here, which I'm not known to do.
My conspiracy theory is that Timothy McVeigh...
There's evidence to back this up.
Timothy McVeigh was funded and assisted by Al Qaeda.
I think the Oklahoma City bombing was funded by Al Qaeda.
I don't believe he acted alone.
Well, you know, Terry Nichols got arrested as well.
Because Timothy McVeigh never talked.
Like, I mean, he was in Super Max, he was in Super Max, he was in Super Max, he was in
Super Max, he was in Super Max, he was in Super Max, he was in Super Max, he was in
Super Max, he was in Super Max, he was
Super Max, I'm not, you know what, get the documentary dude, get Sir David Attenborough
up here, talk to him, he called him fascist, he started it, he said they were much
fascist, actually he gave that interview before this company even existed, but he's like,
"You can't do this, you guys can't do this, this is going to cause havoc." That should
be the name of them, when they take off all of the make sunsets banners, they rip them
down, all of a sudden it says "Havoc", actually I think that was the bad guy group from that
cartoon mask, but still, I think it would be, if you're going to try to destroy the
world's weather systems, embrace it, start having all your employees wearing menacing
costumes and maybe you know that your CEO can be like horribly burned in a sulfur
accident and then he has to wear like a metal mask in the shape of a sun and he just like
interrupts the Super Bowl one day, you're just sitting there watching a bunch of people
throwing the old pig skin around and then all of a sudden you're, and then it's like
just a picture of some dude in a, is this a new commercial for Sunny D or something like
that, why is he wearing that big sun mask and he gives us a huge speech about how he
now controls the world's weather and then when it goes back to the Super Bowl and
snowing they're like, "Ahh, we didn't expect to play this game in the snow, we're in
Tampa, Florida, but let's keep going and then you're like, "Ahh, you know, better go
check my wheat fields and make sure they're not destroyed."
Burnt Toseco, so I'm going to go ahead and toss you the keys to the world's famous
carbonicopter, we are leaving behind the rim of this volcano, take us all the way out
to Ohio.
We're in, or near, Bethel, Ohio. This takes place back on December 1st, 1996, late one
night. Back in 1996 you had two hunters and they're hunting dogs, "Wha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha
night. Back in 1996 you had two hunters and they're hunting dogs, walking through this
harvested corn field and the hunters are like, "Yeah, there's probably stuff to hunt around
here, right? Probably some crows that are still looking for some corn to eat, maybe
a porcupine or something like that. This is their first day hunting, they don't really
know how to do it. They're going to let the dogs lead the way, so they let their hunting
dogs loose, the dogs are just tearing through the area. "Woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo,
woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo
woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo,
woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo,
woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo,
woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo,
woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo,
woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo,
woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo,
woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo,
woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo,
woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo,
woo, woo, woo, woo, woo,
woo, woo, woo, woo,
woo, woo, woo,