What would you do if you were asleep in one night, catching some z's?
When all of a sudden you realized something was watching you.
And then we take a look at the story of the puppy named Eddie, a curious little guy who's
found stranded on the side of the road.
But when a family adopts Eddie and brings him home they have no idea he's going to
become a gateway to the world of the dead.
Today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Garvin, and I'm having a great day.
I hope you guys are having a great day too.
I hope you guys are having tons of fun out there in the world doing whatever you're doing.
And don't forget it's coming up to the end of season 20 and we are about to take a break.
I don't think there's going to be any classic episodes this time.
I know that I always say that we're going to do them.
There's so much more work.
I need to do them at the beginning of the season and I say that every time too.
But we will have more classic episodes for you at some point in the future of Dead Rabbit
Radio because I do love doing them.
I'm just done.
You know by the end of the season I'm so overworked.
And also a quick reminder, March 24th, 6pm in Seaside, Oregon at the Oregon Ghost Conference.
I will be giving a presentation.
Why are there no fat ghosts?
And I would love to see you guys there.
It's $15, but that's not just for my speech.
$15 gives you three days at the Oregon Ghost Convention.
Or Oregon Ghost Conference.
I guess I should say the name right.
You're walking around.
Here's a big sign that says Oregon Ghost Conference.
You're like, "Oh, Jason said it was the Oregon Ghost Convention."
So I'm not walking in there.
Oregon Ghost Conference in Seaside, Oregon.
It's three days and lots of fun of people talking about the world of the paranormal.
So I can't wait.
I'm going to be stopping by a lot of other speeches.
I want to hear that.
I might attend a workshop or two.
And I hope to see you guys there.
That'll be really cool.
Someone who's always cool whether or not he goes to the Ghost Conference or the Ghost
Convention, walking into Dead Rabbit Command right now is one of our newest Patreon supporters.
And give it up for Lazy A Farms.
Woohoo!
Yeah!
Come on in.
An entire plot of land, an entire farm is coming into Dead Rabbit Radio Command.
Lazy A Farms.
You're going to be our captain, our pilot this episode.
If you guys can't support the show financially, I totally understand.
I really do.
Just help spread the word about Dead Rabbit Radio.
That helps out so, so much.
Lazy A Farms.
Everyone let's walk around on his plot of land.
And you're like, Jason, clearly that's a business.
You understand that a farm itself is not supporting the Patreon.
I don't know.
Weird things have happened.
We're walking around with hoes and pickaxes and we're like tilling the soil.
A bunch of cows are giving us orders, telling us what to do.
It's a pretty cool place, Lazy A Farms.
But while we're doing that, I'm going to go ahead and bury the keys for the Dead Rabbit
Dune Buggy in the soil.
Lazy A Farms uses those keys somehow.
I don't know.
Grow some vines.
Drive us all the way out of Dead Rabbit Command.
We're headed out to a little boys house.
Ding, ding, ding.
It's a nice little speedy drive across the world.
We don't know where the story took place.
We don't really even have a timeline.
But it took place in the past.
It took place sometime between Earth cooling and evolving life on it.
And today, this was written, posted online anonymously.
We're going to go ahead and call the guy Fred.
And Fred said this story happened when he was eight or nine.
So we'll figure it minimum 10 years ago.
I'd probably say it's in that time period, 10 to 15 years ago.
Fred said that he was spending the weekend with his cousins and having a lot of fun.
He actually didn't have that having a lot of fun part.
But you know, I can do a little bit of editorializing.
I'm sure it wasn't terrible.
Well actually, not that I think about this story.
He's kind of terrifying.
He was spending the weekend with his cousins and he was sleeping on the couch.
And this was the house of his aunt and uncle and their kids.
And we'll go ahead and call him Uncle Jack.
He's the other named character in the story.
He goes to the house, Uncle Jack's house.
The way it was laid out was you had a front door.
Obviously, he's like, no, he had a climb up sheet rope where you could only enter on
the second floor.
Had a front door.
And the way that the front door was set up was there was a window at the top of the door
frame.
So you have the door.
You have a nice big window to let the sun in.
And that would not be notable in any house.
Right, obviously he's pointing that out for a reason in this story.
You're like, what?
That's weird.
I've been in a dozen houses like that.
No one's ever been, hey, when you visit, make sure to check out the window above the
front door.
He's like, what?
Is that the best thing in the house?
They're like, yeah.
There's a window above the front door.
So anyways, Fred is spending the weekend here.
He's sleeping on the couch.
His eyes are closed.
His little eight or nine year old eyelids are tightly shut.
But he sees, well, it's like that weird thing.
You know when your eyes are closed and someone's shining a light?
Probably me.
You're trying to get a nice sleep on top of you with a flashlight.
I was like, wake up, wake up.
You know how when you have your eyes closed, but someone turns on the light, even though
your eyes are closed, you can kind of see the light through your eyelids?
And like, before you even wake up, you're kind of annoyed that the light's on.
It's that.
That's the sensation he's having.
His eyes are shut, but he kind of wakes up in the middle of the night because he senses
a light is on a very bright light, a very bright green light, which would be more alarming.
There should be far more alarming.
You may think, no, it's not.
You may be a leprechaun and you're like, oh, my lights are green.
Imagine if you woke up in the middle of the night and there was, you shut off all the
lights and all of these scenarios are terrifying.
I always make up the scariest.
Imagine all the lights in your house are off.
You wake up in the middle of the night and you can see underneath the crack of your bedroom
door that your hall light's on.
That'd be spooky.
But imagine, if I chase the door, I don't care what color the light is.
If I shut them all off, I woke up in the middle of the night and it was a strobe light.
Well, see, that's the thing.
It'd be scarier because then you'd think aliens are in my hallway.
If it was a green light coming from underneath your doorway, you would go paranormal.
If there's a red light, you'd go demons.
You would associate different light with different phenomenon.
All of them would be equally terrifying.
But if you were over at your uncle's house, an unfamiliar house, and there was a green
glowing light, you'd think, oh, maybe someone has a really bright alarm clock.
Maybe someone's experimenting with radiated rods nearby.
But whatever it is, whatever's going on, it's annoying.
And Fred's trying to sleep and he opens his eyes up and he sees, of course, like he thought
with his eyes closed.
The entire living room is bathed in a green glow.
And then he almost immediately realizes the source of the glow.
It's not a alarm clock.
It's not radiation.
Well, it might be radiation.
I can't really think about it.
But he realizes, like, he looks around and his eyes settle on that window above the front
door.
And what he sees is so impossible.
He goes, I must just be dreaming.
That's not possible.
I'm going to go back to sleep.
So he closes his eyes.
He holds them tight.
And the green glow is continuing to permeate his eyelids.
And then he begins to get this sensation that he is being watched.
That tried and true sensation we've all been through where we feel like someone's watching
him.
And now he's like, OK, this isn't fake.
It's impossible.
But it's real.
He kind of takes his eyes.
He's kind of squinting.
He's kind of, like, barely looking.
He doesn't want it to know he's awake.
Fred does not want this thing to know that he is terrified.
What Fred saw when he first opened his eyes was a massive green eyeball floating outside
the front door window.
So the front door itself is what?
We're talking about six, seven feet tall.
It's six feet tall.
We bump our heads all the time.
It's about seven, eight feet tall, right?
So this giant eyeball is floating about nine or 10 feet off the ground.
It's giant.
If it was a normal sized eyeball floating 10 feet off the ground, you're like, ah, whatever.
You're all trying to attack it with a place water.
But it's giant.
It's a giant green floating eyeball.
It's taking up almost the entire window.
So you imagine it's floating about nine feet off the ground.
And you could say it's maybe four feet in diameter, maybe a little bit bigger than a
basketball.
You're like, what basketball do you play with?
That's actually huge.
Four feet in diameter would be a massive basketball.
The globe trotters are like, ah, yeah, it's funny looking, but we'll hurt our backs if
we try dribbling that thing.
Big, big eyeball floating.
And when he first saw, if you saw a giant eyeball, if you woke him in the middle of
the night, there's a giant eyeball floating outside your house, you would go, I must be
dreaming, that's impossible.
If you saw what looked like an intruder, if he had just seen the green glow, he probably
would have been more curious of what was out there.
Giant eyeballs don't exist, but when he tried going back to sleep, when he shut his eyes,
that's when he felt the eyeball was watching him intently.
And so Fred is laying on this couch and he has his eyes closed like he's pretending to
sleep, but he's kind of squinting through them because he wants to like double check.
Is that what I saw?
Is there really a giant eyeball out there?
And he said when I was squinting and I'm looking at the eyeball, the eyeball twitched.
It had a physical reaction as if it knew for a fact that Fred was looking at it.
He said it made a physical movement and I felt now that it knew that not only was I
awake, but I was steady in it.
I was trying to figure out what it was.
And Fred just begins screaming at the top of his lungs.
He's being screaming at the top of his lungs.
That's the middle of the night.
And his uncle comes storming down the stairs.
Not like oh no, I gotta protect this blood of mine.
I gotta protect this nephew.
He's one of the pack.
No.
He hears a little boy screaming and he's pissed off, which is fair, right?
You're not gonna assume oh, the burglar must have gotten into my house and is killing my
nephew.
You would be running down the stairs being like great, I have a little kid over here.
He's in a new house and something scared him.
The burglar, the burglar, yes, he can be scary kids, but as long as he just steals the stuff
we don't use anymore, everything's okay.
Uncle Jack comes downstairs and he's actually really upset because he just woke up.
He was deep asleep.
All of a sudden he heard this little kid scream and it's not even yours.
And Uncle Jack enters the room and grumpily says what is it?
And Jack just points at the window and goes look.
And Uncle Jack follows the finger and looks at the front door and looks at the window
and takes a step backwards.
He's startled by what he sees.
He has a physical reaction to it.
This wasn't just the nightmare.
This wasn't just the hallucination or the trick of the light.
Uncle Jack sees it too and he steps back.
And Uncle Jack's like what is that?
And Fred goes it looks like an eye.
And it's still just floating there.
Now there's two witnesses who are watching this phenomenon.
And Uncle Jack to his credit walks towards the eye.
I don't know if I would have done that.
I might have scooped the kid up and ran upstairs and fucked all the torus.
I don't know.
Maybe I would have walked towards the eye.
Maybe I'm braver than I think.
But Uncle Jack walks towards the eye and he puts his hand on the door handle and he opens
the door up.
And right when he does that the eyeball vanishes.
Uncle Jack shuts the door and then we have probably the most realistic conversation that
could happen in one of these situations.
We run into it all the time.
If you're an experienced of the paranormal this is something you run into all the time.
If you're a fan of the paranormal I'm sure you've read accounts like this as well.
Or wondered why did they do that?
Giant green eye floating nine feet off the ground bathing the entire room in green light.
Two witnesses and adult and a child in two different parts of the room.
You know one's much taller, one's laying down.
It's not a trick of the lights, not a hallucination, not a dream.
Giant green eyeball door opens up and disappears.
Fred goes what was that?
And Uncle Jack's exact quote what Fred told us he said was quote I don't know it's gone
now.
It's gone now go to sleep.
And then Uncle Jack just left.
Uncle Jack just left the living room walked up the stairs and went back to his bedroom.
And Fred was like dude I can't do that what are you talking about there's a giant green
eyeball out there.
And he goes I spent the rest of the night just looking at the window.
I couldn't go back to sleep.
He goes it never showed back up.
And the next morning when we were sitting around the breakfast table I asked my uncle
what was that?
Like what was up with that giant eyeball that was floating in and Uncle Jack goes I must
have just been a trick of the light.
It must have been something 100% explainable.
It's interesting because when you do look at accounts of the paranormal people will
do things where they'll have these extraordinary events and they'll go back to sleep they'll
have these extraordinary events and then they continue about their day.
They'll go shopping and then they'll come home and then they will hit them.
The terror the excitement whatever they actually went through.
People act in interesting ways and most of the time it's avoidance.
It's like that can't be true and that's what Fred did at first too remember he saw it.
He was deep asleep saw the green light then saw the eyeball and goes I must be dreaming
that's not real.
And then the event intensified from there.
It was the same thing with Uncle Jack he's like it was nothing like even though he clearly
saw it and he had a physical reaction to it like he it scared him he stepped backwards
he was scared and then he walked to it opened the door and it went away and his first thing
was I don't know what that was but it's gone go back to sleep.
It's super interesting isn't it it would have been one thing if Fred was the only witness
Uncle Jack would be like just go sleep it was a nightmare and Fred could be like it
but to this day I know it was a nightmare.
No there were two witnesses and even though the adult saw it he goes whatever whatever
there is probably some eyeball from another dimension just ignore it and then the next
day he completely dismissed it he's definitely the the uncle's not posting online being like
you won't believe what happened.
I was 30 years old and a giant eyeball no you just went on with his life maybe he thought
about it later maybe he didn't.
And what's interesting too is I found when I was looking more into this there were a
couple different people who also described giant floating eyeballs you'd see other people
comment on the story and one girl said she opened up her closet once and there was a
giant floating eyeball in her closet another girl said that she would wake up this one
was particularly creepy.
I mean I don't have a giant eyeball in her closet is anything to sneeze at or outside
your house but she goes this one seems more malicious she goes I would always sleep with
my bedroom door kind of cracked open and one night I woke up and there was a giant eyeball
floating in the hallway of the house that also gave off a green glow but she said this
one floated in such a way that it looked like it was trying to peek over the top of the
open bedroom door like it was making a attempt to spy on her like it was kind of like looking
around like a pervert in a Walmart dressing room and the reason why I pointed out you
could go well Jason the first eyeball was looking at a sleeping eight year old boy I
mean that's pretty perverted too.
When you have paranormal phenomenon sometimes it is like my experience with the shadow people
the shadow men I'll put it up so the show notes they were completely aloof they didn't
care my experiences with them was they did not care that you were there they didn't care
that you observed them it was basically the same thing as a squirrel sitting on a rock
watching the river the river doesn't care it's simply a phenomenon that it neither hates
nor loves the squirrels it's simply happening in this place and time and it's being observed
by this squirrel so an eyeball floating outside of a house could be a neutral phenomenon it
didn't like being looked at for sure and it disappeared when the door opened but that's
fairly neutral the eyeball kind of angling for a better view of a little girl sleeping
in her bedroom that seems creepy to be fair they're both creepy but you know what I mean
like one of them the one floating in the closet that seems fairly neutral a neutral phenomenon
then you can have helpful paranormal phenomenon which I think happens so often we don't even
recognize it sometimes it's super dramatic and we'll talk about guardian angels but I
think sometimes it's just you see something you're walking down the road and you see something
that makes you smile you see giant green eyeball being dribbled by the Harlem Globetrotters
and you're like ah I think sometimes good paranormal events are so minor they just kind
of like lighten our mood you get home and your favorite television show like you didn't
miss a minute of it right when you got home Jason no one does that anymore you boomer
we all watch stuff on streaming you know what I mean I'm sure there are a little paranormal
things that happen quite often that we just account to luck or being like wow everything
just kind of worked out I think you could qualify that stuff as good paranormal evil
paranormal stuff obviously you know murders people getting chopped up by demons people
falling it deeper and deeper into addictions or depression and completely destroying their
lives and the lives of their family all that stuff that would be more of the negative even
I think a spooky ghost floating around your house they don't he's like I'm sorry to make
you a hero in attic I'm just a spooky ghost he has such high standards Jason I just wanted
to float around and be spooky and now I gotta take you down to the casino make you sit in
front of a slot machine for 10 hours dude you can have just spooky ghosts spooky noises
things to scare you and then things that actually ruin your life yeah but I again like I think
it's interesting because the glowing green eye how malicious is it and how widespread
is it to it's really interesting when someone comes out and says hey here's the story I
have and then you see other people talk about it some of them could be made up because they're
kind of hanging on to the story but some of them a story like this like again we talk
about this all the time to show where do you classify it it's not a ghost it's not a UFO
it's not a cryptic there's dedicated organizations for those so if you see an alien kill your
dog like we talked about on Friday and Monday's episode you contact Mufon if you see Bigfoot
you contact the Bigfoot research group if you see you know a ghost you contact ghost
researchers but who do you call for a giant green eyeball so who knows how common this
is probably not super common but it may have happened more than just a few times it was
posted here and Fred went online by the name Fitzy the artist that was the name they posted
this on I wanted to give them credit for that but interesting story what is the phenomenon
and is it going to be watching you tonight like I hope so you buy some new underwear you're
like getting all sexy before a badge you're like oh I have that green eye spies on me
lazy A farms we'll do it and leave all these pervert leave all these eyeball perverts behind
the rest of you get on board the world a famous carbonar copter lazy A farms I'm going to
attach the keys catch them in your corn stock we are leaving behind Uncle Jack's house take
us all the way out to a road the whole time is like this road is like no none of that
road we're going to a specific road we're going to a specific road again another story
we don't have a location for or a time and this story might pull on your heartstrings
a little bit so if you're currently going through a bout of depression be warned also
if you love talks like Jason what is it just got done with close encounters of a canine
kind of week let's take a look at this story I find this story beautiful but let's take
a look at it doesn't start off beautiful it starts off quite grim we're going to take
a look at Joey's family all these names except for the dogs name the dogs name is real but
all these names we've had to create are supposed to be honestly Joey tells this story he said
one day my stepdad Philip was driving down the road and he sees a little lump on the
side of the road little he's like oh that's my favorite that's my favorite furgy song
he's all humming it as he's walking up to the lump he's like my home be home be homes
my lumps my lovely lady and then he looks and the lump it's not a lovely lady lump although
that would be disgusting too there's just a boob sitting on the side of the road he's
like ah it's not what I expected either what he sees is a puppy but this puppy is not in
good shape this puppy because you're my friend I'm not going to go into detail but apparently
what it seemed like okay I'm not going to tell you that just admit the puppy is not
in good shape and Philip goes Phil is all set in imagining in great detail what could
have happened and he's like I'm not going to tell anyone that Philip takes the dog to
the vet and he goes hey this isn't my dog I found him by the side of the road and the
vets like dear God you know what happened to this dog and he starts talking about it
and Philip's like I don't want to know just fix the dog just fix this dog please and the
vet goes we will rebuild this dog and so they did they spent a lot of money but Eddie was
ready to go they're like back to the road buddy's like and they named this puppy Eddie
and Philip goes you know what we did a lot of money on this dog let's take him home
let's consider him an investment alright I'm off from my taxes let's bring good old Eddie
home so they take Eddie home and at this time Joey is a little boy and Joey and Eddie kind
of start growing up alongside each other going on little adventures he's like he's like you
want to go for a walk down the road and he's like whatever in the liquid I know you can
talk Joey and Eddie are growing up together but Eddie although he loves hanging out with
everyone he is Philip's dog he loves Philip so much and and Joey goes we all had our
time to sit and pet Eddie chase him around Eddie is constantly hanging out with Philip
and wherever you found Philip you found Eddie right next to him it was like a true bond
but he but everyone it wasn't like he growled at everybody else but you know Philip comes
home from work and a little puppies walking next to him he was to have to pull my two
yes a little hat a little hard hat on his face is all dirty and when Philip comes home
from work Eddie runs up to him sits in his lap and they sit there and they watch the
news together prices right whatever and that's just life that's life for Eddie he's found
his home he's found his family he's found his dad Philip little Eddie loves this family
and Joey eventually it's time for him to go to college and when Joey is at college he
gets a phone call from his mom saying Eddie passed away last night and obviously Joey's
heart broken right like he this was like a member of the family he grew up with Joey
and in the back of his mind he's thinking oh my god what about my stepdad like it's
hurts me it hurts my heart that Eddie is past but I can't imagine what my stepdad's
gone through like it was like he rescued this puppy this puppy was going to die and my
dad just happened to pull over and pick him up and not only save his life but then bring
him home and make him part of our life and Joey says this happened so suddenly him dying
and then being buried in the pet cemetery he goes I felt like I didn't have a chance
to say goodbye I definitely didn't get a chance to be with him in his final moments and he
doesn't say how Eddie died but you know probably natural causes I think he would have included
if he involved the road but anyways he just says that Eddie passes away and it all happened
so quickly he didn't get to say goodbye to Eddie either while he was getting sicker or
even after you know like at the funeral ceremony for the dog and all that stuff so he felt that
he had lost something when a piece of the grieving process he Joey felt like he wasn't
he wasn't part of that you know he said a few months later though Joey's still in college
and he has a dream he has a dream that he's standing outside in a fairly unfamiliar place
he just knows that it's this outside location and there's this trail and trotting down the
trail is Eddie and he sees Eddie come towards him and he's so relieved he's like Eddie oh
my god oh I've missed you so much and he looks down and Eddie is a little worse for where
but he's happy his tail is wagging he's doing little puppy dance his hair is matted and
dirty and as Joey is petting Eddie he realizes that Eddie's flesh is also a little rotten
probably probably stop petting him at that point dream or no dream but he realizes like
what he's looking at is Eddie is dead even in the dream but Eddie is so happy and so
excited it doesn't matter Joey's gonna take this moment to be with Eddie just a little
bit longer and they begin walking down this trail and the whole time Eddie is just wagging
his little tail so happy he's back with his buddy Joey his brother Joey and Joey said
the farther we got down the trail the more excited Eddie got started prancing a little
bit more tail wagging even more so excited to be on this journey with Joey until eventually
they come to this giant wall of mist and Joey said that it covered the entire horizon you
could look both ways it would go on forever and when he looked up he saw it reached far
past the sky the wall of mist was silent peaceful there was a beauty to this barrier
but Joey knew that this was the end of the trip Eddie walks up to the wall of mist and
then turns around and walks back to Joey Joey reaches down to pet Eddie again and Eddie
just licks Joey's hand Joey picks up Eddie they do a couple little nose kisses and he
sets Eddie back on the ground and Eddie begins to whine just a little bit just for a moment
and he looks back up at Joey walks back towards the wall of mist and as he gets to the mist
he begins doing his little happy dog dance again his little prance that Joey had seen
so many times before in the moments when Eddie was the happiest he would do this little dance
Eddie walks through the wall of mist to the point that now it's just a silhouette of a
dog all detail has been lost to the fog this little dog is dancing around in the mist and
begins jumping up and down as a humanoid silhouette shows up Joey sees Eddie jump up and down
as this shadowy apparition appears next to him Joey takes a step forward himself he wants
to see what's beyond the mist what's on the other side of this unending wall he reaches
down he puts his hand against the mist and his cell phone goes off he wakes up his cell
phones ringing he reaches over looks at the number answers the call it's his mother she's
sobbing Philip just died of a heart attack it's a fascinating on so many levels it has
what we expect from a traditional ghost story it has all of these elements in it the idea
of dreaming of a dead loved one coming back to visit you one last time very traditional
ghost experience we've had a couple stories this week I didn't plan it this way definitely
didn't plan all the dead dogs in the past two weeks but of people we covered yesterday
about the boss at the work site who died and nobody knew he died but they saw his ghost
the story has that type of element as well the implication is that the humanoid figure
on the other side of the mist was Philip it's never explicitly said but I think that's the
implication and that was this dream and Eddie was going and he was excited for multiple
reasons to see Joey again but Eddie also was there to walk with Philip in the afterlife
they were inseparable and now they would be together in paradise this is one of those
stories I mean when you look at it when you look at this person's posting history they
haven't posted in a long time but it's not a ton of spooky stories it's not a ton of
actually it's zero this is the only one there otherwise they're just constantly kind of
walking around reddit and every so often they're in a subreddit called retconned which is actually
a new version of the Mandela effect it's kind of an itch I've been spending a lot of time
on that subreddit there's some interesting stuff coming out of there but you know what
I mean he's not like on the creepypasta subreddit he's not like in then the next day Eddie returned
to the Indiana watch a magical watch that allowed him to control a UFO he's not constantly adding
to the narrative story could be made up but it's also possibly true in the world of the
paranormal nothing in the story is out of place for the most part it just seems like
a traditional ghost story and it's one that I think depending on your point of view is
either sweet or sad because I think you can hear the story and go well that's just so
sad that you know like Eddie and Philip are dead or any story involving a dead dog is
sad I don't know why you can't I don't know why you can't get into your head Jason listen
I love dogs I don't eat dogs I think the story is sweet I think the story is sweet I think
the story is a reminder that death is not the end I think that's the reason why the appeal
of a lot of ghost stories I think even when they come back as monsters is like death is
not the end that I'm gonna watch until your death and then I'm gonna keep on you because
that's not the end I'm gonna bully you in the afterlife as well you're like ah you know
what I mean like to know that there's something after this I think it's a sweet I think it's
an endearing thought I think it's it's calming in a way and I know there's not everyone's
like that some people go I think it's more intriguing to think that this is all that
there is and when you die it's over I mean to each their own right but and they may hear
this story they may go well it's really the story about a kid whose dog died and then
his stepdad died and everything else was a hallucination everything else was just a
dream Jason this whole thing took place in the dream like what's the paranormal aspect
it's funny now that I say that the only paranormal aspect of the dream is the fact that he knew
well actually okay this is super interesting because this is part of this this show has
no script if you guys haven't guessed that thinking about it this way and I could go
on forever so we're gonna have to wrap this up because I just thought of this there is
no element in this story that is paranormal zero not saying that it has to be someone's
like oh no my kid died as like well but did they get killed by a ghost they're like no
I was like I don't tell me about it you I was reporting on it as a paranormal story and
I made all of these the way I read it was it was the ghost of Eddie coming back to say
goodbye to Joey one more time and then led Joey to the wall that separates the world
of the living in the world of the dead and on the other side of that wall was now Eddie
and then a humanoid figure appeared who Joey at no point I'm gonna double check because
I don't even know if he specifically says I think that was my stepdad let me double
check that here it says then he turns around again and starts to do that happy dog prance
toward the wall until he finally passes through it I can sort of see his outline jumping up
and down excitedly next to a human shaped figure I jog after Eddie and reach my hand
out to touch the wall hoping I'll be able to pass through it too that's when my cell
phone rings in real life waking me up when I answer it my mom is on the other end crying
my stepdad has just died of a heart attack so he never even makes that claim and that
interesting the way I read the story was that the dog had come back from the afterlife to
greet say say goodbye to Joey and then Phillip showed up and was on the other side of this
wall and that's why Eddie was doing such a little happy dance and then Joey wakes up
and finds out that his stepdad is just out of a heart attack but there is zero it's so
that this is interesting because as a paranormal guy right as a paranormal researcher I defaulted
to that because it had so many hallmarks of a paranormal story but it wasn't a paranormal
story was it just a dream was the human could you argue the humanoid figure wasn't him knowing
in advance even just by a few seconds that his stepdad was going to die like I'm assuming
the stepdad died the mom wasn't calling him as he was having the heart attack I'm assuming
the stepdad had died and the ambulance just picked him up and all that stuff and then they
get the phone call but who knows it's an interesting story now to think about it like there may
it may be a paranormal story of ghosts and premonitions of death even if it's just by
a couple seconds a couple minutes before that phone call right it's still a premonition
it could be story that or could just be the story of a dream and the humanoid figure on
the other side of the wall was not Phillip it was just another guardian spirit there
with Eddie that's super interesting that's just an I think looking on that that's an
insight into how I read things my psyche right it was posted someone asked the question what
is the most paranormal or unexplainable event you have ever witnessed and people were responding
to that question so it wasn't unexplainable you could say it was unexplained you could
say it was paranormal my view on a life after death which I believe in if you asked me what
exactly is that I got like I don't know I don't know how it works I don't know if it's
reincarnation I don't know if it's heaven like a literal place called heaven if it's
some sort of paradise world who knows I don't know but so this story I read it and I go
oh these are the things that I already think about the after there's gonna be a lot of
dancing dogs better there better be fascinating story the ghost story unexplained event or
just simply a dream that I've read not only did I read too much into but I told it in
such a way that led it to maybe you also going oh this is about ghosts I think I even said
in the beginning this ghost brings home open support all to the other world or whatever
it said in the beginning so that's interesting I almost feel like this is a medic commentary
how did you experience that story was the whole time you think oh it's just a dream
or oh Jason's making a joke about dogs on roads again Nick come on dude just tell the
story but fascinating and shows kind of my view of the world and how I can lead like
again if you weren't predisposed I don't want to get too meta but if you weren't going to
be predisposed to hearing that story and thinking it the way I did did I tell it in such a way
that you didn't have an option that's all real fascinating stuff but not as to me not
as fascinating as the story I really love the story of Eddie and Philip and it's a story
that love lives on even after death love does not die with death I truly do believe that
and so does Eddie dead rabbit radio at gmail.com is going to be our email address you can also
visit facebook.com/dead rabbit radio. Tiktok is @dead rabbit radio. Dead rabbit radio
is the daily paranormal conspiracy true prime podcast you don't have to listen to it everyday
but I'm glad you listened to it today. Have a great day.
[Music]