Just when you thought babies weren't the creepiest thing ever, another story to remind us that
they are.
They're so weird, kids are creepy.
And then we traveled to Arizona to take a look at a man who enjoys spending his days
and nights hiking through the desert.
But on one of these hiking expeditions he discovers something that he was never meant
to see and now they're after him.
Today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Garvenor, I'm having a great day.
I hope you guys are having a great day too.
Hope you guys have some cool plans for the weekend.
I don't know what I'm doing honestly.
No idea what I'm doing this weekend but I hope it is cool whatever I decide to do.
Probably be a 72 hour nap.
But someone who always has something awesome to do walking into Dead Rabbit Command is
one of our legacy Patreon supporters, longtime supporter of the show, active member of the
Patreon Discord and always on the live streams as well.
Everyone give it up for Rudy Jazz.
Woohoo, yeah, walk on in.
Yay!
Hey guys, jumping on into Dead Rabbit Command.
Rudy, you're going to be our captain or pilot this episode if you guys can't support the
Patreon, I totally get it, I do.
Just helps spread the word about Dead Rabbit Radio.
That helps out so so much.
Rudy, I'm going to go ahead and toss you the keys to the Jason Jalopy.
We're going to leave behind Dead Rabbit Command.
Drive us all the way out to a daycare center.
Place leisurely drive to this daycare center.
We don't have a specific location for this because if they ever give out the location
to this place no one would ever let their kids go there ever again.
Well, you know, it's interesting that I say that because I guess it would depend whether
or not you believe in this phenomenon.
I'm sure like, there's so many bad daycares out there.
You're constantly reading about the news.
I think at a certain point you're just like, I'm going to have my baby strapped to my back
until they're 18 because there's just too many horrible things that can happen and then
you're mountain climbing, you're like, oh, this is okay.
And then you fall directly on your offspring.
I guess basically the moral of the story is kids are always going to get injured or have
creepy occurrences happen to them.
Let's take a look at this story because this is a weird one.
And think about it.
Would you think about it from two points of view?
Then if you heard that this was happening at your kid's daycare center, would you let
your kid go back there?
You're like, I at least want to discount.
At least want, I don't know, 40% off.
You got to give me a discount here, guys.
Would you let your kid go there?
And then also, because it's Friday, imagine that you yourself are the baby or the kid
or whatever.
I don't know.
All of a sudden, look who's talking three.
Let's go ahead and get into this.
There's this little baby guy walking around the cigar.
Just imagine yourself as a baby and a, never mind.
Just listen to the story.
You're all watching the dishes.
You're like, what?
This is way too much.
This is way too much right now.
I'm actually doing real life chores.
We're in this daycare center.
We're going to go ahead and call the person who posted it didn't use the real name.
We're going to go ahead and call her Elizabeth.
She works at the daycare center with toddlers.
I had to look this up.
A toddler is not a baby per se.
It's like one to three years old.
All of the characters in this saga are one to three years old, except the daycare workers,
of course.
They're adults, but toddlers.
That's the time span.
Not like tiny little baby people, but tiny people who still need their diapers changed.
At this daycare center, a little baby walking around and they pooped in his diaper.
And then the daycare workers, I'm sure, do a very, very intense game of rock, paper,
scissors to decide who has to clean out that baby's diaper.
And you go, you put the baby on the changing table, change the diaper.
The baby's just kind of, it's not baby.
It's a toddler.
So toddlers sitting there thinking about Scooby-Doo and stuff while their diapers getting changed.
Standard toddler stuff.
But Elizabeth said at this daycare center, there was one particular girl.
We'll call her Patty.
There's one particular little baby, baby Patty.
She goes, one day we picked Patty up.
She pooped her pants or peed.
She wasn't specific on the bodily function, but she takes the baby, takes baby Patty to
the changing table.
They have this changing station set up and they put baby Patty down.
And all of a sudden Patty starts going, no, no, no, no.
And she's like, swatting away using her little legs and like crotty chop and doon baby crotty
chops on Elizabeth.
And Elizabeth is like, we need to change your diaper, honey.
Let's just change your diaper.
No, no, the man is watching.
The man is watching.
I don't know why she sounds like Edith Bunker from all in the family.
But she's the man.
The man is watching.
No, no.
And Patty would point up at the ceiling.
Now you understand that there's no man in the ceiling as adults.
We understand that there's not a man in the ceiling.
But you would look.
If you were walking on the street and someone goes, dude, there's a T-Rex right behind you.
And they ran away.
You wouldn't be like, I'm not going to matter what happens.
I'm not going to turn around.
Even though you know that there's not a T-Rex behind you, you would look.
You would turn around and double check.
And now if the guy goes, there's T-Rex behind you.
Look, look, look.
And he's not running.
Now he's just going to steal my wallet or something like that.
But if he's like, if I'm the brown shaking, I hear the roar behind me and I'm like, sorry,
you're not going to get my wallet as he's already like a block away from me.
If someone goes, look, look.
Okay, maybe T-Rex was a bad example because that would cause like seismic disturbance.
You'd hear police sirens and military helicopters all around.
If someone came out of your bathroom was like, dude, I don't know how to say this, but there's
a man in your shower and you live all alone.
And you're like, what?
Oh my God.
You're like, can't we dance over right now?
And he likes to take showers when people go to the bathroom.
If someone said, you came out of the back and you made up these hypotheticals and then
I wonder why my episodes are so long.
Basically you would look.
And that's what Elizabeth did.
And little toddler's going, there's a man watching a man.
And Elizabeth would look up and it's just a tile, like a ceiling, just a ceiling with
those tiles.
And she goes, here's the thing.
There would be times because it doesn't sound like the most well constructed daycare center.
I mean, the one thing you want to, well, two things you want at a daycare center is competent
workers and a building that won't collapse at any given moment.
But apparently she says, if you open the back door, if you open and close the back door,
it causes a gust of wind to move through the building, which is fine, right?
You, if you slam a door, you can feel the wind, but it moves the ceiling tiles.
There's so much force of air coming in that sometimes the ceiling tiles move, right?
So sometimes there would be gaps up there.
You know, they'd fix them.
They'd get the broom and kind of knock them around your back.
Sometimes there would be gaps up there, but something that's never up there is a man.
It's not a man watching, but of course you would, I just out of, I don't even know if
it's curiosity, just someone points at something for the most part you're going to look and
a little kid going, there's a man watching and you'd look up and there'd be no man up
there.
But Patty refused to let her diaper get taken off on the changing station.
She refused.
She put up such a huge fight, she'd be kicking and screaming the whole time.
And then once they got her changed, cause they would still do it, you know, you, you
little baby's kicking you, you can still go on a diaper.
They'd let Patty go after the diaper changed and she'd just go about her business walking
around the daycare center.
But then when Patty pooped her feet again, it's, oh man, are you kidding me?
What are you doing with this screaming infant?
I think it took them a while to realize.
I think the first time she did it, that was weird.
But by time 10, she's done this so many times, they're like, dude, if we pick her up and
put her on the changing station, she's going to scream and cry and fuss.
So eventually, every time, every single time they put her on that changing station, there's
a man, there's a man up there, he's watching us.
So eventually they just say, you know what, let's just change Patty on the floor.
Don't tell her parents.
Don't tell her parents that we're going to be, the kids are building forts around her,
they're all trying to change the diaper.
The kids are like, wee, jumping on her and stuff like that.
They're like, she's not trampolating, she's laying on the ground.
It doesn't make her a toy.
But they change her on the floor.
The parents, when Patty gets home, the parents are like, that's, why is there a penny in
my daughter's diaper?
She's just picking up all that debris.
She's like straight up dirty because that back door keeps throwing dirt around whenever
you open and close it.
Anyways, Patty was totally fine with being changed on the floor.
She thought it was great.
She no longer screamed about a man watching her.
Kids are weird, right?
Kids are super weird.
Kids are going to say all sorts of goofy things.
You just deal with it.
A year later, that daycare has moved on like those kids have gone to preschool at this point.
So she was probably like a three-year-old because then now they're going to preschool.
A new group of kids come into this daycare center and one day Elizabeth takes this little
boy, we'll call him Joey, and she's like, Joey, did you go poop poop in your pants?
And he's like, maybe.
And she takes Joey over to the changing station and lays him down and starts to take off the
diaper.
And all of a sudden Joey's little body starts to tremble and he points up at the ceiling
tiles and goes, no, he's watching.
He's watching.
No.
And she goes, these two kids didn't know each other.
These two kids did not know each other at all.
And it was the same thing with him.
We could not change him on that changing station.
He fought us every single time.
We're like, we're just doing it on the floor.
Let's just change little Joey on the floor.
And it's interesting to apparently other people have witnessed this phenomenon.
Elizabeth wasn't the only worker who was having to change these kids and they would be saying
there's a man in the ceiling watching us.
There's a man up there.
The first time you would think it was a kid's overactive imagination, but when you have
two kids that are saying the exact same thing in the exact same location under the exact
same set of circumstances, you have to think that there is, well, here's the thing.
She knew.
Elizabeth knew for a fact there was nobody in the ceiling.
She's like, I don't know how she knows that.
I don't know if they ever spent the night in the daycare center telling spooky stories
and then walked up into the area.
You could also just look up and go that would not support the weight of an adult.
Looking at this cheap ceiling in this rundown daycare center, an adult would fall through
that ceiling.
And that's normally how it is with those.
Kind of like, listen, if opening and closing a door makes your tiles shift around, leave
gaps big enough that you can just see into the darkness, it's not going to hold the
weight of a 180 pound man.
I would argue it wouldn't hold the weight of a couple toddlers.
I think we can put that to a test.
We got a bunch of them down here.
Let's put them up and we'll have a little safety mat form on the ground.
We'll see how many we can put up in the ceiling before they all come below.
At that point, you would have to go.
It doesn't hold the weight of a man.
When the first kid was seeing it, you would think it was just overactive imagination.
When the second kid seen it, you would then start to think paranormal.
This was posted online by someone with the screen name of Moonschild86.
And you have to wonder, thanks for posting it.
It was pretty interesting story.
You have to wonder, what would you do?
Not, I mean, as a daycare worker, your options are pretty limited.
This is what I was talking about in the beginning, like, as a reasonable adult, if your kid came
home and said, hey, they're like, hey, how was this daycare?
And they're like, hey, it was okay.
But there's a creepy guy in the ceiling.
I mean, definitely if your kid told you that, you're headed down there with a shotgun that
night and you're getting in the front door just shooting under the tiles.
But then after you get bailed out of jail, your toddler goes, no, no, no, no, I mean,
I think he's a ghost, maybe?
I just learned that word.
If you thought that the daycare that your toddler was going to was haunted by the ghost
of a pervert.
Because I think that's what's implied here, right?
Would you let your kid go to that daycare?
And it's not an easy question because on the one hand, the answer is no, right?
The answer is no.
I don't want a creepy ghost staring at my kid, taking their clothes off.
I mean, I don't even think I, I don't think any reasonable person does.
But this is the thing.
I would not allow it.
But what if one, they're the only daycare in town?
The other one's like miles away and you're like, well, listen, we could spend, we could
spend an extra $10 a day on gas to the non-perverted daycare center.
Well, see, here's the thing.
If it was a real pervert, you wouldn't deal with you to go down there with a shotgun.
The situation would be over with.
But if it's a ghost pervert and like, how would you explain that to your significant
other?
They're like, dude, seriously, we can't be driving all the way across town to go to this
different daycare.
You would say, but honey, there's a pervert ghost in the ceiling of this one.
And I don't want my kid being stared up by some perverted spirit.
Most adults would say, what in the world are you talking about?
These kids have overactive imagination.
The other day they said that there was a monster under their bed.
Like, do you believe that?
And you're like, oh no.
You're all running around the house.
You're all boarding up the bottom of each bed.
You have to be very careful what they say to certain adults.
They'll believe everything.
But you know what I mean?
At what point would you say, I'm not going to have my kid at this ghost pervert daycare
center?
And the answer is not as easy as you think it is.
I would say, because I don't have a kid, I would say no dice, never, ever, ever.
But if that daycare center was the closest to me and I'd still would drive out of my
way or just put them on a backpack like my original idea, take them to work.
What if your significant other or the people you live with go, dude, don't be an idiot.
There's no such thing as ghosts for one.
And then two, there was what can the pervert ghost do?
That's when you realize all your roommates are pervert ghosts.
You're like, ah, you're part of the problem.
I wondered why you were always leaving to go to work at the same time I was dropping my
kid off.
Shouldn't be roommates with a bunch of pervert ghosts.
They always take that side.
But you know what I mean?
Would you be able to logically explain to someone, hey, why are you late to work today?
You're like, boss, I told you my daycare.
It takes me an extra 20 minutes a day to drive my daughter to the daycare.
And your boss is like, but there's a perfectly good daycare right in your neighborhood.
And you go, yeah, but there's a ghost.
There's a ghost out there.
I mean, like, I love talking about paranormal.
We all love talking about paranormal, looking at it.
So to us, it's not a huge issue.
But the thing is, is like, to most people, even people who believe in ghosts and supernatural
stuff like that, they still don't talk about it out loud.
So to most people, if you try telling your boss, I'm going to be late to work for a while
because I don't want to take my daughter to a haunted daycare.
I'm trying to find a non-perverted, non-haunted daycare for her to go.
Your boss will think you're insane.
Most people would.
It would be better off lying and say, oh, asbestos.
They found asbestos in the ceiling and lead in the water.
They're like, oh, yeah, no, totally.
Take your time.
Find another daycare center.
And you'd be like, oh, God, sweet.
When you then have two kids both saying that there's a creepy pervert watching them change,
I think you have the duty as a parent to move your kid.
That I will, I think that's probably a good idea.
I think people are like, yes, Jason, we all agreed with you.
We don't know why you talked about that for the past seven minutes.
There's not a single person who would go, you know what?
That drive, that can meet too long.
Sorry, kid.
You gotta stay at the haunted pervert place.
Nobody would say that, Jason.
Why were you doing this big hypothetical thing?
Everyone just kind of shook their head at the same time and go, I'd be making work.
Rudy Jass, go ahead and catch the keys of the world famous carboner copter we are leaving
behind this daycare center.
Play us all the way out to Arizona.
The year is 2015.
We're in northern Arizona in the middle of nowhere.
We're out in the desert and we see a truck pull up.
And out steps a man who enjoys being out in the middle of nowhere.
He did not give his real name when he was writing this account.
We're gonna go ahead and call him Charles.
But this is what he loves to do.
He loves to just get out and spend time in the desolate wasteland of northern Arizona.
I mean, I say that, but there's like shrubs and probably like birds and stuff like that.
Maybe coyotes, lizards, lots of lizards.
And he just likes walking through the area.
I mean, he'd actually park his pickup truck and just kind of explore the landscape.
And he's done this multiple times before.
This isn't the very first experience he's had out there, but he's enjoying it so much
that he goes, you know, it's actually getting kind of late.
I'm just gonna sleep in my truck tonight.
Maybe do some more hiking tomorrow.
But for now, sleep.
So he hops in his pickup truck.
Oh yeah, stretching out.
Rolls down his windows for some fresh desert air.
Charles is just sitting out there in the middle of nowhere with the windows rolled down, full
moon lighting up the desolate wasteland that surrounds him.
When all of a sudden he sees movement outside of his car.
He goes, I'm sitting there and I see my driver side rear view mirror, like that external rear
view mirror.
I see something moving behind the car.
It's interesting.
He's very calm while he's looking at this thing.
But that changes.
That changes fairly rapidly.
He sees something.
He goes, I would estimate it was about four to six feet behind my truck and it was walking,
just walking behind my truck without a care in the world.
And he described it as an eight foot tall humanoid.
Didn't get a good look at its face.
Didn't get a good look at a lot of the features of it.
He goes, the way that the moon was is I could perfectly see it silhouette.
Couldn't tell you how big the eyes were.
Couldn't tell you what a lot of that stuff was, how big the nose was if it had a nose.
He goes, I saw this eight foot tall humanoid walk by.
Incredibly skinny.
Very very skinny, very very tall.
Long arms dangling down.
He said the elbows were kind of in an odd spot.
They weren't where, even if you gave a human long arms, the elbows seemed to be in the
wrong spot.
Tall skinny long arms.
He goes, the neck alone was a foot long or a foot tall would probably be a better way
to put it.
So this is not just like an emaciated human.
I mean like, oh, I've been less in the desert.
I need water.
And he's like, ah, it wasn't like that.
Like this was definitely some sort of creature.
But you couldn't say it was a great alien.
You couldn't say it was really alien at all.
It's just something, he's trying to make sense of this thing.
One interesting, I mean the whole thing.
There's an eight foot tall monster walking around in the desert, right?
But what I think is interesting is a lot of times we see similarities and sometimes it's
interesting to see these stark differences.
It had, because when I was seeing this I go, maybe it's one of the crawlers.
I had experiences with these things.
I saw two of them and I didn't even know there was a term for them.
I didn't even know what I was looking at.
I'll put that episode in the show notes.
This thing, this wasn't that.
This wasn't that.
Because those are just these long or tall, long, because they walk on all fours.
These weird looking human, that's creepy.
Just to even remember seeing, being close to one.
I only saw the hind quarters of one, but it's this long tall.
It's like if you took a human and made him walk on all fours and never fed him anything
and he super maciated and his skin is gaunt.
And that is kind of what he's describing, but this one's walking on two legs.
And it had a four foot long tube, or what he believed was a tube.
Again, he's just looking at this in the silhouette.
A four foot long tube-like object protruding from its jaw.
And he said it actually dangled all the way down and then came to a point at the bottom
as if it was a beard.
But he didn't say it was a beard.
It didn't move like a beard.
He described it as being a tube.
Looking off of this thing's jaw.
This humanoid walked very slowly, very deliberately, not like a predator stalking prey.
Charles said it almost looked like it was having difficulty moving.
It was very painful for this creature to even have any sort of locomotion.
He goes the way that a walk seemed like walking was a struggle for it.
Now he's taking all of this in.
He sees the silhouette, he's taking in how it's moving and all that stuff.
And Charles was like, "Okay, this is creepy.
I've never seen anything like this before.
I'm just going to roll up the window.
That'll clearly protect me from the eight foot tall monster in the desert."
Well he goes to roll up the window and he has one of those new-fangled cars with the
automatic windows and the car shut off because he was just enjoying the solitude.
He goes to do that and it's just like click, click, and the window's not rolling up.
And he's like, "Oh yeah, I forgot.
I forgot.
I live in the year 2015."
Most cars now have automatic windows.
Well when he's clicking this button, the creature turns and looks his way.
And he said even the way it turned its head was just kind of this very slow, deliberate
turn staring right at Charles.
And Charles is sitting in the car.
He's watching all this out of the rear view mirror.
He still can't see what this thing's face looks like, but I mean you can understand
movement and motion and you go, "Oh, okay, now it's looking at me."
Like just the way the silhouette has turned, it's looking at me and he starts to think,
"Okay, I'm going to die."
This is the end of me.
He goes, "This thing is clearly going to kill me and it's going to kill me for one reason.
It's starving to death.
I don't know what it is, but it is starving.
I can see how emaciated it is.
It's going to kill me and eat me."
He goes, "My only option I could think of at the time was if this thing takes one more
step towards me, I'm going to turn on my car, roll up the window, and just drive away as
fast as I can."
Which is not a bad plan.
I probably would not roll up the window first.
I probably would start driving first, but anyways.
And you figure he'll just speed out of there anyways, but it's nighttime in the desert.
Sure, he has headlights, but he's going to be driving through.
It took him a while to get here in the first place.
He's driving his truck over this terrain and then he gets out and walks around in the middle
of nowhere.
So it's not like he's on a city street.
He's like, "See you later, sucker!"
And there's like, he can make all these quick turns and lose it.
So he goes, "I'm going to roll my window up and drive out of here and safely get back
home."
He puts his hands on the keys.
They're in the ignition.
And this figure is still just staring at Charles.
And then it just slowly turned its head and walked away.
Continuing on its journey, it was moving, just walking by the back of the car, right?
He totally was ignoring it.
This creature, whatever it was, was totally ignoring it.
Stopped, looked at Charles, and now just his continuing on his journey.
He made no movement, no threats, nothing.
Towards Charles, he just mows his own by.
Charles said that he waited for about a minute and then he drove away.
It's a minute longer than I would have been there, but anyways, he said he waited a minute
and he drove away and that was that until you got to go back, right?
You would have to go back in this type of situation.
Your curiosity would be piqued.
Again, if you saw a UFO, if you saw a ghost, if you saw a Bigfoot, you know what those
things are.
And most of those, you may go back as well.
Check them out.
But you know what those are, but when you see something totally unexplainable, it's not
like you can even really talk to anyone about it.
How do you categorize this?
So curiosity would get the best of you and he realized this thing may know threatening
actions towards him, right?
Maybe he'd go out there and find out it was some weird trick of the light.
On these particular nights, there's always a cactus in the exact same position, and
a bunch of squirrels hanging out on it and it makes the shape.
You would go, you would be curious to go back.
And also remember, this is his turf.
He goes out into the desert all the time and hiking and you wouldn't want to be afraid
to go back out to the place where you find peace.
I think both of those, I think curiosity and then also, you know, kind of reclaiming what
you own, what you love.
About a month later, he goes back out there during the day.
He's not an idiot.
He is going back out there when he's not an idiot.
He goes back out there during the day and he finds the exact same spot he was at.
And he parks his car and he gets out.
And here's the thing, he was like, what was that?
And where did it come from?
Not just from a metaphysical sense, like what plane of existence, but like, no, literally,
where did this thing come from?
It just appeared out of the middle of nowhere.
Sure, it was night.
But like, where would it have come from?
There's nothing around here.
I don't understand.
I've never seen anything like that before.
And then all of a sudden I see it.
It's right next to me.
Well, he begins to just hike around this area, this area in particular.
And he's just going, exploring, looking at all this stuff.
And he comes across something that he had never seen before out here.
But it's a vast desert.
It's not like he's been everywhere.
Of course, there are going to be things you haven't seen.
And what he's looking at, he can tell this has been here for a long time.
This has been here longer than I've been hiking.
So it's not that it's happened recently.
I've just discovered it.
But maybe this is a clue.
He describes this place looking like an old crash site.
Now, he doesn't say that he sees debris.
He doesn't say that he sees pieces of metal or anything like that.
He goes, the reason why he's using that terminology, he goes, because clearly there is a, a, a
depression in the ground.
It looks like something impacted here.
It's not a deep hole, but in the crater, I guess would be another good word for it.
Not a giant crater, but in this crater, there are rocks with scorched marks.
But there were also bushes growing in and around this crash site.
So he goes, whatever happened, happened a while ago.
I mean, definitely nature has reclaimed the land, but there's still evidence that something
crashed here.
Whether it was a plane, a meteorite, or something else, this is a unnatural deformation of the
ground.
He's kind of standing around.
He's looking at this thing.
Beep, beep, beep, beep, beep, beep, beep.
He's looking around.
He's like, what?
Beep, beep.
He's standing in the middle of the desert.
He's standing in a place that he's never been before, and he enjoys the middle of the desert.
And he can clearly hear, because it's so quiet out there, the sound of a truck backing up.
Beep, beep, beep, beep, beep.
And as well as hearing the beep, beep, beeping of a truck backing up, he hears heavy machinery.
And he goes, it wasn't like a guy was just driving a dump truck somewhere.
I mean, that's what I'm thinking.
Someone was driving a dump truck somewhere, but he goes, the amount of different noises
that I'm hearing, I'm not even just hearing one truck going beep, beep.
I'm hearing five, six, a dozen.
He goes, it sounds like somewhere, somewhere there is a huge construction project going
on.
He goes, not the volume level, but the amount of different noises.
He goes, you can hear all of this heavy machinery going on.
You hear all these trucks moving.
Not the volume, but the amount of different noises would be akin to you walking by a construction
site.
So he's like, someone's building something out here.
That has to be what's going on.
So he actually, he has to get to the bottom of this mystery, right?
You have to figure out what's going on.
And really at this point, just to realize that you're not insane, but also curious.
You're right.
Maybe you don't mind about being insane, but you're also super curious about it.
He hiked back to his pickup truck and began driving all around the area, looking for this
construction site.
They're building something in the middle of the desert.
He wants to know what it is.
Can't find anything.
Finds nothing.
He's driving around for miles.
He's looking.
He has a perfect view of everything around him.
And if he can't, if there happen to be like a plateau in front of him, he just drives
around it.
So on his pickup truck, he's driving around for miles and miles and miles.
He cannot figure out where they even would build anything.
I mean, technically you could build it anywhere, but where in the world are, where in the world
are these noises coming from?
But here's the thing.
He's realizing too, the more he drives out, he can't really hear the noise.
He doesn't, it's not like he can hear the construction sounds as he's driving around.
When he jumps out of his pickup truck, he's walking around.
He can't hear the construction noises.
It's not like they're echoing through the desert.
And he, again, has to realize, okay, this is insane, but he hops back in the pickup truck,
drives back to the crash site, gets out of his pickup truck, and just stands there motionless.
Beep, beep, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh,
shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh,
shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh,
shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, sh
shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh,
Shhh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh,
shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh,
shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh,