In 2020, a man detonated a bomb at an AT&T building in Nashville.
Remember that?
Geez, that sounds like forever ago in the world of conspiracy theory.
The official story is because his father died of dementia, he blamed 5G technology that at
that time was rolling out across the world.
But is the truth behind the bombing even more bizarre?
And then we travel to a house in the suburbs to take a look at the story of a young girl
whose best babysitter is the television set.
When her mother turns on the television set and leaves the room she has no idea she's
opening her daughter up to.
Supernatural attacks today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Carpenter, I'm having a great day, hope you guys are having a great
day too, hope you guys had an awesome weekend doing whatever you were doing, I hope it was
a lot of fun.
First off, crawling into Dead Rabbit Command on all fours, wearing nothing but tattered
clothing.
Everyone give it up for Jim Morfis Gas.
Jim Morfis Gas sent me a book off my Amazon wish list.
It was the book of werewolves.
It was an old tome published back in 1863.
So this is back when werewolves were a thing.
This was basically a guide to keep you from getting your guts mauled out of your body.
So thank you Jim, it's a totally awesome book.
I love reading books of the time period, right?
That's really really cool, the book of werewolves.
And you're going to be our captain or pilot.
And as Jim is preparing the Jason Jollibee, I'm going to be the captain of the show.
I'm going to be the captain of the show.
And as Jim is preparing the Jason Jollibee for our first story,
I'm going to give you guys some details, dude.
This is so dope.
So March 24th, I will be giving a live presentation at the Oregon Ghost Conference in Seaside, Oregon.
I invite all of you guys to come out.
This is going to be awesome.
This is going to be fantastic.
Let's go ahead and touch the keys to the Jason Jalopy.
We are leaving behind Dead Rabbit Command.
Drive us all the way out to
Nashville.
Bop Bop
Nashville, Tennessee.
Home of Country Music
Probably other stuff.
Actually, I don't know if it's the Home of Country Music.
I think that's probably Virginia or something like that.
I think Country Music has been around since the Civil War.
But
Nashville, Tennessee.
We covered this story
a long time ago, back when it happened.
And it's really weird.
It's one of those stories that was so huge
in the conspiracy theory community.
It was mainstream news.
People were talking about the solar news
and then it completely disappeared.
Everyone just kind of shrugged
after a certain point and left.
And I didn't predict it with this one.
I didn't think this one would go away
so quickly, but I did predict it
with the Georgia Guidestones.
When's the last time you've heard about that?
A massive bomb
was detonated
in the middle of Georgia.
Destroyed
the structure that had been around
since the 70's, right?
So almost 50 years.
Never caught them.
They had video footage of the car
leaving the area.
You think at least the ATF would be interested
in who built a bomb.
It's gone.
I totally predicted that.
I go, "We're never going to find out who did this."
Somebody blew up the Georgia Guidestones.
Later that day,
a construction crew came out and just knocked it down.
And then the entire time we were told
there was a time capsule underneath it,
an article was released
saying, "Oh, we opened up the time capsule
and it was full of like, quailudes
and it's like some other knick-knack."
That wasn't true.
That was 100% fake.
That was not the time capsule
in there. And then a couple of days later,
they go, "Oh, no, there's no time capsule under there."
We like knocked it down and we looked,
there was nothing in there.
So I mean, in that story is pretty much,
every show often you'll see someone in the paranormal community
kind of go, "Hey, what's up with the Georgia Guidestones?"
Like, "We haven't heard anything about that."
But the mainstream media is not investigating it.
It's forced me to tell law enforcement isn't investigating it.
It was a pretty powerful bomb.
And they kind of ran with the,
"Hey, look at what they buried in the 1970 time capsule."
That wasn't true. That wasn't the time capsule.
They never found the time capsule.
The official report is there was
no time capsule.
Someone who went through the trouble of building
the Georgia Guidestones to survive
a nuclear war, to basically be
in a dietary setting humanity
goes, "Yeah, but I don't believe any artifacts
from the 1970s or from before.
We don't need a time capsule.
We'll tell people those are time capsules and not really have."
Super weird.
This Nashville bombing thing,
I remember it obviously was weird at the time
we did an episode on it. We talked about it for a bit.
And I forgot about it too.
So when I saw this conspiracy theory
pop up recently,
I was like, "Okay,
this is super interesting
because
in a vacuum, right,
we've had an absence of conspiracy theories,
really even mention of it.
People don't even really...
Now, this was another massive bomb
in the city of Nashville.
Let's go over a few quick facts
if you don't remember.
What are you talking about? Should I be concerned?
It was Christmas morning. I mean, so iconic.
Right up to the top 10 most iconic bombings.
Christmas morning, it was 2020.
There was a man named Anthony Warner,
63-year-old man.
He detonated
a RV
full of explosives
outside of an AT&T facility.
And
it basically completely destroyed
the building it was in front of
and shattered windows
up and down the street.
One building collapsed, the 41 other
buildings were damaged.
There was a countdown, basically,
so I'm kind of getting scattered here,
but Anthony Warner pulls up outside of this
AT&T building
in this RV and basically
a...
The first report is someone is firing
shots in downtown Nashville
and as police respond to the area
and people are leaving
and it probably wasn't a lot of people down there
anyways, it's Christmas morning.
A recorded announcement begins playing
from the RV saying a bomb will detonate soon.
And then it starts
a 15-minute countdown.
So the police are like, "Okay, no one's
down here anyways, it's Christmas morning."
The police still have on there a little sleepy
stocking cap and their new
Christmas pajamas. They basically
clear the streets of squirrels
and it does the complete
15-minute countdown and then
it begins to play the song
"Downtown"
(singing)
And then...
(explosion)
This is all caught on video.
This is all caught on video because we have
ATM cameras and stoplight cameras and all that stuff.
There was talk of a missile
like you actually...
a missile crashes into the building
and then the RV goes off. There was a big
conspiracy theory about that for a while.
That was one of the conspiracy theories.
I didn't necessarily believe that.
I think the explosives were in the RV
but anyways, the RV explodes.
It does all this damage. Only one death.
And that was Anthony himself.
And the story we got from
the mainstream media was that Anthony's
father worked for AT&T
and he had recently died of dementia.
And Anthony was a 5G conspiracy
theorist. That also sounds quite
quaint now, right? Because 5G is
pretty much everywhere at this point.
You don't hear that. You hear it sometimes
connected to COVID, but
it's not as big
as like your eyeballs are going to melt out of your head.
We don't see that so much
about 5G because it's everywhere.
As you're listening to this, your eyeballs are
melting. You're like, "Ah, it's true, it's true!"
Just took a while. 5G conspiracy
theorist Anthony, that's the
what we were told.
And his father died of dementia. He worked
at the subsidiary at AT&T.
So therefore, AT&T is responsible.
So I'm going to blow up this AT&T
building
and
I'm going to get revenge. I'm going to expose
the truth to the world. Unfortunately, it just
basically one man died.
And you know, the guy was
we built a blockbusting
bomb. I don't wish him death.
You know, it's unfortunate that he died.
There's other ways to get your message out.
But, and again, did it work?
Like again, like this whole entire thing
has been swept under the rug.
People don't really talk about it
anymore. What happened?
We figured out, because see, listen, AT&T
is this is where I'm going to get myself
blown up by the government. AT&T
is in lockstep with the American
government and they always have been.
I don't even think that's a conspiracy
theory, really. I mean,
they
were the original Google
and at any point
the government could say we want to know
what this person's phone calls were. All this
stuff about warrants and needing, oh man,
I really wish it could have gotten that wire
tap. But that judge said no. Oh, dang it.
I guess we're going to just going to have to sit
here until those terrorists strike again. That's all
like local politics.
Like maybe your local cop won't be
able to wire tap your phone. And the
judge is like, you don't have any probable
costs. But the government is just like
we want to listen to all the phone calls in this area.
And the phone companies, despite what you read
in the media, they go, sure.
Every so often you'll see
something pop up where they're like, we won't let
you, we stand for freedom. And the government's
like, errr. No. They know
everything we're saying at all times.
So,
when this happened, we
found out though, because the government is
constantly spying on you, what we found out
is when this AT&T building went up, it also
disrupted 911
dispatch services in the area.
Nearby flights were grounded.
It basically caused this massive
infrastructure
shockwave.
Flights were grounded. You had communication
systems within hospitals
go down. What you figure
would have been like self-contained.
So, starting to see, it's very interesting. We're
starting to see how interconnected all of this stuff is.
Credit card machines, even
people just wanting to stream the movies.
Even if you weren't using an AT&T
network, it
created this huge ripple through the system.
But
everything was pretty much back online.
Oh, and AT&T was disrupted throughout the
country. This one little
area here that blew this building up.
AT&T had disruptions
across the country, but within two days, everything
was back to normal. I mean, obviously like
you know,
flight commands, they didn't ground flights for two days.
Flights were able to get back on.
I'm sure the hospitals got started up
pretty quickly, got their communication systems
back up. But you trying to stream
spy kids for, it could have taken
a while. That was not a priority.
You're like, "Oh no, will they win the spy wars?"
Anyways,
I find this super fascinating, because
recently I came across this conspiracy theory
and it'd be fair. Even the guy
who's writing the conspiracy theory is like
"Maybe." He's not
totally sold on this, but
this led me to a really, really
interesting fact that I didn't know about any of this stuff.
There was a guy online, he goes
by the name
Aphrodite4120
and he posted this and he
is saying, possibly,
right again, he's not totally married to this,
but his idea is this.
What had happened
is that
a rogue artificial intelligence program
had been detected
inside
that AT&T building.
And people were feverishly trying
to keep it contained in this building.
They're severing
all escape routes.
They're basically pulling T1 cables out
of the wall.
Knocking satellite dishes off
the roof.
And when they realized that they couldn't
contain it, they said, "We need to blow
the building up."
So what we're seeing is something
that's working backwards.
And now he says, and I wasn't able to confirm this,
he says the
infrastructure, like all of the
911 calls going down and the airports
going down and the hospitals
going down, he says, "That all happened
two hours before the bombing."
That was
basically
step two. The first step was to try to contain
it in the building at 100%.
If they couldn't do that, then they were going to shut off
all communications throughout the city.
And when they realized that wasn't going to work either,
they were going to have to go to step three,
which was blow up the building
and they needed a cover story.
Now it is interesting
what they happen to have,
what the government happened to have access to
was the body
of a 5G conspiracy theorist,
Anthony Warner.
Now whether he had died of a heart attack
earlier that morning
or the feds took him out,
we don't know.
Again, this is just a conspiracy theory.
This is just a conspiracy theory.
But the idea is they already had
and who knows? I mean, listen, man, again,
and
it's not just the United States government.
Every government does these things.
It's just what governments do.
They have one goal to survive.
It wouldn't surprise me
if governments have
fictional databases on people.
You obviously have all the real stuff
you do.
And then they just make up stuff too.
When I die, I'm going to be like some big Harry Potter fan
and I organized
the live action Quidditch matches.
I'm like, come on, bros, come on, make me a cool corpse.
They may just have dossiers
and they have a body
and they go, this was this guy's grievance
with us.
And the media thumbs through and goes, okay,
makes sense.
But anyway, so they had Anthony Warner,
they had this dead 5G conspiracy theorist
and they basically said
oh, he was there.
He was blown to bits.
Literal bits were left
of Anthony Warner, so you couldn't really.
And again, it's one of those things like
even me, who
I have distrust of the media
in general, and I think
most people do,
I obviously rely on them
for a ton of information, especially stuff
that I'm not particularly either interested in,
or
have any way to fact check myself,
because I don't live in Nashville.
I can't drive out there
and I'm like picking up pieces and picking up like a toenail
and taking it back to my lab, even if I could get out there.
I don't have a lab, I can't run DNA tests.
So you do, I can
kind of scratch my head and go, that's kind of suspicious.
I thought it was weird.
Remember there were gunshots, that's what brought
the people to the area at first.
To hear the countdown,
we never found out who fired the gun.
We assume Anthony Warner
fired gunshots, so police would
show, because the streets were pretty much deserted,
everything was closed, so the police
would show up so they could hear the countdown
and know that this bomb was coming, but why would
you give them the
warning, if you were going to blow up the building
anyways and weren't going to give some big speech,
you weren't going to stand on the top of the RV
and go, 5G is killing us all.
So, who fired the gun?
Who was Anthony Warner, did he exist?
Everdy saying that there was this
AI program locked
in this facility
and they needed, they basically
blew it up and then came up with
the story.
We got the body,
we have videotape of this RV
out front,
it was this guy who had
grievance with the company.
Now, fascinating
conspiracy theory, does he have
any proof? No, he's
really just going, what if?
The reason why I wanted to cover it
was because I learned something
brand new about the whole national bombing
thing.
Let's take into
account, let's take the official
story, that Anthony Warner
blew up this 18T building
because his father
died of dementia while
working with the subsidiary of
18T. It was a retaliatory
strike, it wasn't to
spread the message
of the dangers of 5G, it was to
punish those who
killed his father.
So, let's take that, let's take the official
mainstream story.
I'm reading Aphrodite's post
and Aphrodite keeps mentioning
"How could you have a bomb
that's so big it could destroy
a 33 story building?"
Yet, you'd still have
DNA, you'd still have toenails and bits of flesh
that you could match to Anthony Warner
and he made that comment
once or twice and I go, "33
story building, what's this guy talking about?"
Like, it was like a
historic downtown Nashville
because I'd seen the footage, I was
very familiar with the footage
and then I was re-watching it
as I was reading his post and going, "Oh, this
is kind of interesting."
It's not a 33 story
building, maybe at most like 4
or 5, like this was like historic downtown
Nashville, all the buildings are
just those square buildings.
One next to another.
I'm like, "What's he talking about 33 story
building?" The bomb went
off on 2nd street
and if you go to
Google Earth today
you can
do a little tour down that street,
that street is still completely closed off.
Which is weird.
Which is super weird, right?
You had all the rubble for 9/11
removed
fairly quickly
and some people say
too quickly, some people say
it should have been molten lava, but anyways
anyways
that's my 9/11, that's my X 9/11 truth
are coming out, it's still
in there somewhere. You have
you have this whole
block is just completely shattered
and it's basically
it's turned into a one way street
and even if the footage isn't up to date
as of today, it was
even given them 2 years, none of these stores
have reopened.
They haven't done any
major renovation or demolished
and now if it's a historic thing, you might have
certain rules, but if it's historic you figure they would demolish it.
Anyways
this all happened on 2nd street.
If you go over
1 street
if you know how to do math
if you go to 3rd street
there is
the AT&T building
it's called
and it is the tallest
building in the state of Tennessee
if you wanted to strike a blow
against AT&T
I can understand if they were on the other side of the country
or even on the other side of the state
you didn't want to drive an RV
full of explosives that far
I could totally see you wanting to hit
like a local facility
because the one that would be
the truest symbol
of tyranny
over humans
putting out this new technology
that killed his father
he would just hit the closest target
this was 1 street away
1 street away was the largest building in Tennessee
it was the AT&T facility
and it had he driven his RV
just a block over
this bomb
destroyed one building
and damaged 43 others
that street has still not been reopened
because of the damage
2 years
I double checked
that photo was taken in June of 2022
2 years that street
they have had no businesses there
had he parked that RV close
to that 33
story AT&T building
glistening glass and steel
could have done some serious damage
he could have taken down
a building or at least blown a huge chunk in it
so why did he pick the little building next to it
and not the AT&T tower
itself it's almost as if
something escaped from the AT&T tower
and made it just the block away
before some missile struck out of nowhere
and destroyed the building
this AI was in
it escaped from its prison on 3rd street
only got to 2nd street
before it was erased from reality
it's fascinating
conspiracy theory
don't know if it's true
don't even know if I buy the missile thing
but I find that super weird that he didn't attack the big building
that's super bizarre
and I didn't even know there was that giant building
people in Tennessee were like "yes it's the tallest building"
we can see it
we can see it from where we're at
I'm living down the street and I can see the building
I just find that so weird that he didn't attack the big building
I'm glad he didn't
I'm not for more property damage
from a conspiracy theory spawn
but okay awesome
I really love that story but we have to move on
to something a little creepier
I guess if you're an AT&T stockholder
that entire story made you wet your pants
but Jim Morphagas
let's go ahead and toss you the keys
to the world famous
Carbentercopter we are leaving behind Tennessee
take us all the way out
to a house in the suburbs
*imitates carbentercopter*
Jim landed this Carbentercopter
outside of this little girl's house
and let me set the story up here
this is kind of interesting
the story was posted online
it's a throwaway account
by someone called throwawayliva
and they said
this isn't my story this is my mom's story
but I gotta tell you a little bit about my mom
my mom
she
is one of those parents who doesn't make stuff up
technically the term she used is
she never led us to believe
that there was things like Santa Claus
and the Tooth Fairy
so my mom was not
a fabricator
she wasn't a liar
basically would be the term some people would use
but you know what I mean
she wasn't indulging in our childhood whimsy
so when
throwawayliva's
mom
told her this story
makes you think
this is probably true
at the very least
my mom
saw something she couldn't explain
but it was like
stress or a dream
or hallucination or something like that
most
my mom had an incredibly creepy
paranormal encounter which
affected the way that she raised
her own children
we're gonna go ahead when I'm names or locations
for any of these people we're gonna go ahead and name
the mother Nancy
when Nancy was four years old one day she was hanging out
in her mom's bedroom while her mom
was taking a shower
it was just her and her mom home at the time
and Nancy was just
watching a little television
it was
a Mickey Mouse show
it was a show starring Mickey Mouse
which tend to be the lamest one
I hate Mickey Mouse
so that's one cover in this story
I was like yes, yes, it's true form
finally I can convince the world
and I didn't need to use an RV full of explosives to do it
Nancy is watching television
while her mom's taking a shower
she's watching a Mickey Mouse show
Nancy when she's thinking about it
she goes I think it was that
Mickey Mouse Clubhouse
she was watching Disney Channel
watching a little Mickey Mouse Clubhouse
when she hears a voice go
Nancy
Nancy instinctively
goes
yeah
now she knows her mom's
taking a shower
and she knows her mom doesn't normally
sound all squeaky
Nancy
but she
just instinctively is like oh someone must be calling me yes
and there's no answer
and she can hear her mother
still taking the shower in the bathroom
Nancy turns back to the television
and continues to watch Mickey Mouse Clubhouse
when she hears
Nancy
clearly hears her name again
but this time she realizes
it's coming
from the television
the
TV
itself is calling her name
and Nancy goes
the second I realized this
Mickey Mouse and Donald Duck
float out of the television set
Nancy remembers this
clear as a day
imagine you would if fictional characters
were walking around in your living room
well technically I think they're just kind of floating there
Mickey Mouse and Donald Duck float
out of the television set and she said
they were
transparent like ghosts
you could see right through them
and Mickey Mouse and Donald Duck are floating
out of the television set
they're floating in front of Nancy as her mom's
in the other room completely oblivious
to this absolutely bizarre event
and the two animated characters
start begin to go
come here
come here with us
you liked it Michael Jackson
Michael Jackson float out of the television too
and Donald Duck saw
come here
come here with us
come back
she's like who are these
dollar store versions
where these terrible voices coming from
a yuck yuck
see if Goofy had come out
I could have done a little bit of Goofy
yuck yuck come here with us
that's barely
serviceable
hey Nancy it's Yogi Bear
come get the big
a n***a basket
but unfortunately she wasn't watching anymore
bear cartoons right
Mickey Mouse
laughed again come here come here with us
basically
these two floating characters are trying to get
Nancy to go somewhere
and what's so interesting
so if I was
4 I would have been 1980 but
but with 4 years old in 1980
if Luke Skywalker walked
into my living room
and says hey man we need you
we need you to help fight the empire
jump into this television
before he even finished the sentence
I would be inside the TV
Optimus Prime ever told me to crawl in his
cab
drive him around town
I'd do it
but what's interesting is Nancy realized
something was wrong
it's probably because her voice is soft
she's like I don't know it doesn't sound like Mickey Mouse
doesn't sound like Mickey Mouse I don't know what it sounds like
yuck yuck
she says she immediately gets weirded out
once these characters begin
speaking to her because even at the age
of 4
she knows that
television characters aren't supposed to be floating
out of the screen
and I don't know if I knew that at the age
of 4 but Shay did
and she said that
these two
this one beloved character
and Mickey Mouse are beckoning
her to come into
well they're saying come here
come with us is she going to get teleported
into the television
are they going to grab her and take her to some
hellish dimension
these demons posing as these characters
are the characters actually coming out of the television set
she's trying to figure all this stuff out too
and she's 4
and it's happening right now
and she doesn't know what to do because on the one hand
cartoon characters
on the other hand this shouldn't be happening
and as she's trying to figure this out
as they continue to beckon her
to come towards them
the mom
steps out of the shower
and they immediately disappear
Donald Duck and Mickey Mouse just vanish
they don't float back into the television set
Mickey Mouse is shaking his fist I'll be back later tonight
he he
no they just disappear
and Mickey Mouse Clubhouse is still playing
I don't think she finished the episode
she's like that was quite terrifying
but I wonder if Pegglay Pete
will win the hand
of sweet sweet Daisy
she shut the television off
and in fact from that day on
she stopped watching anything Mickey Mouse related
this is a lesson to us all we all should have done this
she didn't watch anything Mickey Mouse related
and
she didn't let her kids
ever watch anything Mickey Mouse related
and
I mean this is like a generational curse
she stopped watching Mickey Mouse
kids can't watch Mickey Mouse
and her grandkids
when they come over to her house
no Mickey Mouse
which would be
it's not a bad tactic one Mickey Mouse sucks
but secondly kids constantly
want to rebel against their elders
and your parents tell you not to get a tattoo
you get a tattoo parents tell you not to smoke
you start smoking
parents says don't watch Mickey Mouse
you're like I hate you mom and dad I'm totally gonna rebel
you go to the Disney story
you're like I'm gonna get all the Mickey Mouse paraphernalia
watching tons of Mickey Mouse
you know
and you just like you be laughing it was a huge prank
you could care less if they watched Mickey Mouse
but it gave them something harmless
to rebel against
you with right watching all this Mickey Mouse garbage
anyways
no more Mickey Mouse
in this this was no longer a house of
mouse
from that day forth
it's an interesting story
my dislike
of Mickey Mouse is long
and storied
we've actually done previous episodes on it
it's also possible
that Mickey Mouse and Donald Duck
did float out of the television set
and then that's a whole other slew of questions
was it actually
Mickey and Donald
I think would be the first important one
because it could be
demons masquerading
as if I was a demon
I would totally be
a cool guy
I would totally be like appearing at what it would be
like these days I'm walking around
I'm Mr. Beast I'm giving money away
is it a demon
who is disguised as Mickey and Donald
which would be I mean both of these
are terrifying alternatives
and none of them are like well that's a little
that's a little soothing
is it a demon or demons disguised as Mickey and Donald
and had they caught her
then what
I think the go-to thing
is whether it's Mickey and Donald
whether these characters
these beloved characters are some sort of demonic constructs
in and of themselves
like Mickey is an actual
demonic force and Donald
while he is pretty funny
and he is cool
is unfortunately aligned with Mickey
in this conspiracy theory
that is actually
and they are constantly trying to subvert
children into
falling into this hellish landscape
you know that's the
that's one conspiracy theory that is actually
I don't know I feel like they are both so weird
either they are demons
disguised as Mickey and Donald
or they are Mickey and Donald
who are actually demons
and so yeah
she was right to never allow Mickey Mouse
in her house I don't know if she watched DuckTales
again I am a little iffy on that detail
she might actually be much younger than me
she might not have been born during the time of DuckTales
because I was an adult when that Mickey Mouse
Clubhouse was on
so the point is
is that I am wondering if
if we take the story of face value
we will have to wrap this up real quick
but were the demons disguised as Mickey and Donald
or are Mickey and Donald actually demons
and every so often they are able to come out
of the television set
to beckon children to come to them
we have these two possibilities
and then the big question is
what happens when the kid goes with them
because I could obviously be super creepy
and say
she goes yeah sure
and then they bleed her into the television set
and then the mom comes out of the shower
and the bedroom is empty
and she is like Nancy
Nancy Nancy and she is looking all over the house
she can't find her 4 year old daughter
and she calls the police
the police show up they scour the area
they are putting missing person signs
all over the neighborhood
it becomes a local news story
not quite national
and Nancy is never seen again
but
if you watched episode 87
of
Mickey Mouse Clubhouse
in the background
while Pegleg Pete is chasing Daisy
through a hall of mayors
for a split second
you see the distorted face
of a 4 year old girl screaming
out in pain
banging
on one of the mayors
her soul trapped
in this
cartoon forever
right that would be super creepy
that would be super creepy
but
I don't think that's it
call me call me a little more
stable than that I don't think she gets sucked into the television set
because
here's the thing
kids disappearing in their houses
is so incredibly rare
and
Mickey Mouse Clubhouse was aired all over the country
if not the world
so I don't think
that it's that these kids are being
kidnapped and sucked into the television set
you're like Jason I'm actually surprised
that's not what you're thinking
what's more likely
and we'll wrap it up like this
is that yes
if you do go with these entities
they don't
canap you and take you to a hellish dimension
they don't do something like super horror
movie to you
the mother doesn't come out of the bathroom
and found her daughter just completely
eviscerated
single tear drop on a 4 year old's face
as she turns to her mom and goes
Mickey played
oh my god you know what I mean
obviously this stuff is great
in a horror movie
it's great in a horror movie
it's super spooky but I don't think it happens
I think that
let's pretend that Mickey comes out of the television set
but he doesn't do that
Mickey and Donald basically would
just corrupt her
these demonic forces they don't need to do
anything like super spooky
any Dean Coons level horror
they just say come here
come here and she reaches out and she touches them
and then they disappear the mom comes out
but because she did
what they said because they realized that this young girl
is actually malleable
they can
convince her to do something that then through the rest of her life
they're basically convincing her to make bad decisions
she's some guys like hey do you want some crack
she's like oh no I heard in school that
cracks bad for you and then Donald Duck's like
I don't know
crack is delicious
and she's like
well Donald Duck said so
the drug dealer's like what
man you must already be high
not like that
it doesn't have to be like Donald Duck's on one shoulder
and Mickey Mouse's on another
you know what I mean like they would just realize
she's easily persuadable
they never have to show up again
they just know that she is susceptible to
suggestion
so it's an interesting story
it's one of the stories that probably did happen
in one
I don't think the poster's making it up
I don't think the mom's making it up
I think it's interesting that the mom
never talked or didn't lead them to believe
in these childhood
illusions like the tooth fairy
and like Santa Claus right she probably still gave
the kids a dollar when they lost the tooth
just to keep the economy going
but they're like no the tooth fairy's not really a thing
but I will give you a dollar
because that's what all the other kids are getting for their teeth
now Santa Claus isn't really a thing
but you still get presents
because if anyone knew
the power of a child's imagination
mixed with
dark and mysterious forces
taking the form
from a childhood's imagination
if anyone knew how dangerous that combination could actually be
it would be a woman like Nancy
she wasn't willing to indulge in her children's
zest for fantasies
believing in the tooth fairy
Leopard cons
Santa Claus because she knew that these
could be
pathways of temptation
that would only take her children
and her grandchildren
down the darkest of paths
Dead Rabbit Radio at gmail.com
is going to be our email address
you can also hit us up at facebook.com/deadrabberadio
Tiktok is at Dead Rabbit Radio
Dead Rabbit Radio is the
daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast
you don't have to listen to it every day
I'm glad you listened to it today
have a great day
[Music]