Two men driving to work one morning witness a terrifying and impossible creature.
And then we travel to Boston to meet a young man who has repressed memories.
He's blocked out entire portions of his childhood because it was too painful to even comprehend.
But when a wave of terrible memories comes crashing over him, he realizes that he's
only one thing to do. Become a killer. Today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host Jason
Gardner and I'm having a great day. I hope you guys are having a great day too. I hope
you guys are having tons of fun out there in the world. We got a bunch of stuff to cover
so we're gonna get started right away. First off walking into Dead Rabbit Command is one
of our legacy patreons. Everyone get on your feet and give a good round of applause for
TK. Woohoo yeah! Woohoo yeah! TK! Woohoo yeah! Come on in to Dead Rabbit Command. TK is actually
not his real name. His name I don't know what it was. It was probably something inappropriate
because Patreon just has him listed as invalid ID. But TK that's the first two letters of
your email address so I hope that you know that I'm talking to you and not trying to
talk to you. But I want to make sure you get credit because you've been a long time Patreon
supporter. TK you're gonna be the captain, the pilot of this episode. You guys can't
support the Patreon. I totally understand. It really do just helps spread the word about
Dead Rabbit Radio. That helps out so much. It really does. TK let's go ahead and toss
you the keys to the dead rabbit dune buggy. We're leaving behind Dead Rabbit Command.
Drive us all the way out to Mexico. Beep beep beep beep beep. Driving out all the way down
south to Mexico. Specifically we're headed to Chiapas, Mexico. We're in the late 1990s
and as TK is driving us down there we see another car driving through the area. This
car is being driven by a man we're gonna call him Charlie. He didn't give his name online.
Charlie and his co-worker were carpooling to work this day. Early in the morning it's
dawn really. This one's just coming up and they're like "Hey let's get to work." He described
this area. He goes, "The area we were driving through of Chiapas was a suburban area so
it would be like a couple houses, a building and then an undeveloped field and then a couple
more houses, a couple more houses, building, building, undeveloped field." You know just
kind of like a standard suburban area that's still starting to grow. And Charlie says
as we're driving past this grassy field we see in the field this huge black dog and it's
running towards them. And he specifically said it was tall. It's not that it was like
a big bulky load of the ground dog. It was a really, really tall dog. It's running across
the field and when Charlie and the co-worker are looking at the dog, the dog is looking
at them now and it slows down. It's walking towards them now. It's still moving towards
this car that's driving by. And I'm assuming that Charlie, that they're actually slowing
down as well because it's such an odd sight and they actually get a really good look at
this. I don't think they were flying by at 60 miles an hour. Charlie says me and my co-worker
were watching this dog, this really abnormally tall dog walk, first run and then walk towards
us and he said when you get a good look at the dog, it's not just that it was tall. The
dog had two faces and he described it as one half of the face was a dog's face, which is
what you would expect on a dog, but the other half of the face was a man's face. He says
he's looking at this dog across this field, half of its face is that of a man. He said
it was a Hispanic man and the face had really sharp features. He goes both me and my co-worker
saw it. We both saw this. It's impossible, right? You can picture it in your head as
like maybe like a cartoon or a drawing, but once you kind of start to think of, because
the dog head is so much longer than a human's head, there would be a lot of deformity. I
guess having a human face on a dog is a deformity, but you know what I mean? Like the snout
comes out. I don't think then it was like a clean cut and then you have, or did the
human face, did the nose turn into the snout? Was it a big human face? Was the human face
is like, I guess I'm really focusing on the minor details. The point is this dog had a
human face. Maybe it was a normal human-sized face. Maybe the face was all distorted to
look like a dog, but be a human face, you know what I mean? That's not how I picture
it. I picture it like it's like when Prince dressed up as Batman and Joker, like he has
a line down his face and when he, that's what I imagine. Like if you saw the dog from one
angle, you would see the snout. It would look like a normal dog, but then when it turned,
when it turned towards you and went bat dance, you would see that it had a human, like a
totally normal human face. So it's not like his jaw was all morphed out into the, like
the morphine and snoop-tongue dogs video. I don't, I think it was just a normal human
face on the, like the right side is how I imagine it too. I don't know why I have the
detail in my head, but the human face is on the right side and it looks normal and the
snout is all just like protruding, but it's not part of the human mouth. Does that make
sense? You're like Jason, it kind of made sense the first time he said it. Now I'm super
confused. Hey, when did Prince ever sing about Batman? You're like Googling that, you're
like whoa, whoa, whoa. Wait a second. Is Jason having some sort of weird fit or did Prince
actually dress up as Joker in the Batman? Super distracting, I know. I'm so sorry. You're
like what? Anyways, that's what they saw and Charlie goes terrified him, obviously, right?
It's so frightening. You wouldn't be like taking out your notebook, you're like let's do a
little sketch. It's horrifying to see something like this and he goes even thinking about
it today. Like this happened back in the 1990s. He goes even thinking about it nowadays, brings
tears to my eyes. Scared tears. He wasn't like oh those, those dawn memories with my
buddy. No, it was like it terrifies him. It's an interesting story. It was posted online
by a guy going or I call him Charlie, but he goes by the name the Mystic Mind. It's an
interesting story. I think this is one of the stories that honestly could be a werewolf.
That's what a lot of people are saying online that he caught a werewolf mid-transformation.
That would check as far as the time, right, dawn happening and then I read that book breaking
dawn and had a bunch of werewolves in it. You have the possibility it's a werewolf. It's
possible that it's an unknown cryptid. It's some sort of beast. It's possible that it's
a cursed man. I mean it's different than a werewolf. A man like cursed to walk the,
yes, it's definitely a werewolf, but you guys know how much I hate people being forced to
turn into things against their will. It could be a man being like all like freaking out and
stuff like that. This is interesting too because it could actually be one of the more stories
that we could give a plausible answer to. It could have been a dog with mange, right?
It could have been a dog that was suffering some sort of like fur loss, but then again
like he clearly recognized it as a human's face, not just the dog that had lost some
hair. And they both saw it. It's interesting. It's also interesting to note that years ago
it still stands as one of my favorite episodes. We had another encounter in Mexico. I'll
put it in the show notes. I'm not going to give the ending away of the episode, but those
of you know what I'm talking about. We had another encounter in Mexico. I think that's
all I can say without giving it away. I'll put it in the show notes. Very, very fascinating
story though. Like that's the time you don't expect to see anything spooky. You're driving
to work. It's the morning and you see something that was so terrifying, so impossible that
even thinking about it to this day brings tears to your eyes. You're not supposed to
see stuff like that in the middle of a suburbs in the morning on your way to work. That's
supposed to be the very least stories and fairy tales and the very most haunting the
darkness outside of town. But here this creature was walking around as the sun rose. TK, let's
go ahead and toss you the keys to the carbonar copter. We are leaving behind Mexico. Fly
us all the way out to Boston, Massachusetts. I want to give a shout out. I got, I had never
heard of this story before. I got most of the information and I found out about this
story reading an article on morbidology. They do a lot of true crime stuff on there. It
was written by Emily Thompson. Let's go back to May 2011. We're going to be hanging out
on Saratoga Street. We're about to meet a young teenager named Marco Tulio Flores. He's
17 years old and he's over the house of a very close family friend in a very tight knit
community. This friend's name is Jamie Galdamez. He's 31 years old. Now pretty much everyone
in this community, this is in East Boston. They're immigrants from El Salvador. And so
generally that happens. You have people kind of move up together and you're like, hey,
let's go to this area. I know a cousin who's living there and then they move in there and
then more people come up from another country and they're like, hey, let's go here. You
know, my brother lived out here and you see everything's going really good. We got, that's
how we have like Chinatown and Little Russia and all these ethnic groups, which would make
sense, right? You're not going to be like, hello, Ohio and you're just walking around
in the middle of a farm. You're like, yeah, I just got here from Bulgaria. Anyone know
of a good Bulgarian joint to grab a meal at? Well, anyways, Marco is over at Jamie's house.
I think they were having like a gathering or something like that. I don't think he
was over uninvited, but Marco's over at Jamie's house, longtime family friend, upstanding member
of this community. Marco sees a photograph and it's a photograph of Jamie and Marco's
six year old nephew. Now again, this is a very close community. They have a lot of bonds
together. So it's not unusual. It wouldn't be unusual to have a picture of two unrelated
people because they're all brothers. But when Marco sees this photograph of Jamie standing
next to Marco's six year old nephew, it's like a damn burst. Within a second, years
and years of traumatic memories begin to overcome Marco. He had repressed so much for so long.
He had forgotten. He had completely buried what Jamie had done to him, but he remembers
it now. When Marco was a little boy running around Saratoga Street, everyone knew him.
Good little Marco, great kid, gets in trouble every once in a while. But you know, what
boy doesn't? And he had very positive interactions with Jamie. But when Marco turned nine, Jamie's
attitude towards Marco changed. The relationship seemed to change. Marco couldn't really place
it at first. You know, he doesn't know. He just realizes that Jamie's acting differently
around him. This adult who'd previously just been a guy that he, you know, big family gatherings
hang out, he knew him. Now it's different. He's treating me differently. Didn't know
what it was. What it was was grooming. But you know, a child doesn't know that term.
He didn't realize what was going on. He didn't understand the predatory nature that Jamie
now had for this young boy when he turned nine, right? When he turned to what Jamie
was attracted to because Jamie was obviously a big ol' pervert. And that's where this story
is headed. He began molesting Marco after he turned nine. And it lasted until Marco hit
puberty. So three, four, five years, this went on. And once Marco hit puberty, Jamie just
went back to being a friend of the family. Everything went back to normal. And Marco
had to internalize that in some way. Had to figure out he must have done something wrong,
right? Because things were totally normal. And then I had three or four years of pure
hell. And now things are normal again. And he just took all those memories and buried
them as deep as he could. So deep he'd forgotten that it even happened. So deep that he would
even find himself back over at his abuser's house because he's a friend of the family.
I wouldn't even think twice about it. Why would he? Jamie never did anything to me.
He buried it that deep. But when he saw that photograph, when he saw a photograph of Jamie
and Marco's six-year-old nephew, it all came flooding back. And he knows what's going
to happen to this little boy in the picture. He knows the hell that will await this child
if he doesn't do something about it. May 22, 2011, Marco sets up a video camera and records
himself saying, quote, "Today is the day. I'm off now. I'm going to go for a bliss walk.
And then I'm going to head down there." Marco loads up the video camera and a couple
other tools he's decided to bring along with him. And he heads over to Jamie's house.
This 17-year-old boy, powered by rage and adrenaline, is quickly able to take down this
31-year-old man. But this isn't going to be a quick kill, Marco decided. He didn't want
to just take Jamie's life. He wanted to take his legacy. He ties up Jamie and then sets
up the video camera. Hits record and says, "You need to confess to what you did to me."
Jamie's like, "I don't know what you're talking about, dude. You broke into my house. You
tied me up. Let me go." No, you know why I'm tying you up. You know why I have this camera
going. You need to admit what you did to me. You need to tell the camera. You need to tell
everyone what you did to me all those years back when I turned nine. I remember it now.
I don't know what you're talking about. I have no idea what you're talking about, Marco.
Just let me go. He denies it. He's denying it. He's denying it. Marco is pressing harder
and harder and harder. I know you did this. Admit it, admit it, admit it. This goes on
until finally, I mean, Jamie, he's a child predator. These people aren't known for their
strength, for their fortitude. He does crack under the pressure. He does. He looks into
the camera and he admits to it. He goes, "Yes, I did." Well, that's Marco. Did it for years.
You have to wonder how much of his, now that I'm saying this out loud, you have to wonder
how much of his confession he thought, "If I just say what Marco wants me to." He obviously
did it, right? I'm not saying that. I do believe he did it, but I'm wondering if he thought
at this point, he's a bit of a spoiler, I guess, but if he would get out of this alive,
if he thought all that Marco wanted was a confession and then he was going to turn
it into the police and he could go, "Listen, the guy tied me up. He broke into my house.
Like, of course, I was going to admit to whatever he wanted me to." Maybe he thought
he could still walk away from this. But when Marco pulled out a knife and pressed it to
Jamie's throat, Jamie had to know that this was the end. Marco puts the knife to Jamie's
throat and begins to drag it across, but he can't get it deep enough. It's very hard
to slit a human's throat, deep enough to kill them. You're not just cutting the skin. You
have to really get in there. And most people don't know that. And he's slicing Jamie's
throat, but it's very messy and extremely painful and he's not doing it right. And Jamie is
pleading for his life, but again, he realizes at this point there's no way he's going to
get out of this. And I think maybe in a last gasp of some sort of humanity, because he
is a monster, maybe he does realize that this is justice in some sense, right? He's being
killed by one of the children he abused. Maybe he's probably just a big, sicko. I don't
think I should give him any noble motives. But whatever the case is, he pleads with
Marco not "Don't kill me, but don't slit my throat." This is, there's blood everywhere.
This is extremely painful and it's kind of gross. And just kill me another way. He's
begging for death at this point, but not to have his throat slit. And it's too painful,
there's just too much blood. So he asks, this is where another thing about maybe there's
some weird sex thing for him, but he asks, Marco, can you just strangle me instead?
What's interesting when Marco is putting together his kill kit? He had the camera, he had the
knife, he had the rope, he also brought along a dog chain, which is another restraint device,
obviously, right? It's like a doggilish chain, but it's not something I would bring. I don't,
I mean, it's so specific, right? But the dog chain comes in, this is the reason why I'm
not a vigilante killer. I can't pack well. The dog chain comes in useful because he realizes
that's fine, I won't slit your throat, but I will strangle you. He wraps, this is all
on camera, by the way. The video camera has not been shut off. This is the police, we're
able to view all this. It might be online somewhere, he tries to slint the guy's throat,
it's not working out well. Jamie asks to be strangled and Marco then puts the dog chain
around his neck and yanks it tight until Jamie stops moving. Marco then walks over to the
camera, talks directly into the lens and says, "It felt good to do this. It felt good to
do this and I did it to protect other children." He also says, "I can think so much clearer
now." You have to imagine all this, even with the repressed memories, once he realized what
he was repressing, you figure that would have just, that must have been such a psychic strain
on him and then remembering what happened. This all happened in the month of May, like
he saw this photo sometime in May and by May 22nd he's killing his abuser. He can thank
so much clearer now. He drags Jamie onto the bed, douses him in lighter fluid and then
leaves. Marco returns the next morning, steals Marco's computer and his television set and
then sets the apartment on fire. I don't know why he did the spread across two days. There's
really no, I don't think in his kill kid he's like camera check, rope check, knife check,
dog chain, double check and he never thought, "Oh, I should probably bring a lighter. I
have all this lighter fluid." I don't think it was that. I'm not exactly for sure why he
did that. We'll get to why he stole the computer though. He set the apartment on fire, the
body is found obviously. There's a fire in an apartment. That's the most dangerous thing
he did. Like yeah, he killed this child molester, whatever, but don't set apartments on fire.
That's a safety lesson from your good old pal Jason. There are other people. There are
other people living there. Anyways, fire department showed up, put out the fire, the burned body
of Jamie is found. This is one of those things that Marco could have gotten away with, but
he turned himself in. 18 hours after the body is found, because at the end of the day he's
a good person. He murdered this guy, but he's a good person and good people want to get
stuff off their chest, so they will confess. Bad people confess too, but he turns himself
in and he gives them Jamie's computer. He says, "Yeah, I killed him. He's a real disgusting
guy. I have a video of me murdering him." Starts off with him confessing to these horrendous
crimes, but I figured none of that might hold up in court. Well, I mean obviously this video
of me murdering him, that'll hold up, but here's his computer. He's making all these allegations.
The community's completely shocked this good kid murdered this good man, as far as anyone
knew. They took his computer in and the police started doing a forensic analysis of the computer
and they found all of these encrypted chats with other pedophiles. So Marco wasn't making
it up. It wasn't some weird delusion. It wasn't like he had some psychotic break and made
all these stories up. No, the guy was a pedophile. And there were these chats. I don't think
they found any child porn. I don't think they found any child porn on the computer, but
not like that makes him any better. He's still a pervert, but he's talking to these people
online about how he liked boys around the age of 10 years old. He said they were easy
and they often asked for it. It's just disgusting piece of shit type of person. And all these
people he was talking to, they were still out there. They weren't an army of Marcos taking
them out one by one. All those human debris. Hopefully they found justice by now. Again,
the story took place back in 2011, but and so he's writing this and he says that, you
know, I'm not going to repeat it. You guys remember. And then he also said that this
is so creepy. This is so creepy. Whether or not you feel like vigilance. He is I'm should
be endorsed. This is nuts. So remember what started this whole thing was Marco finding
the picture of him and of Jamie and Marco's nephew, six year old nephew. Jamie said to
some of the pedophiles online that quote, there are some good ones coming up. Unquote
So he was looking at these six year old seven year old boys in the neighborhood saying,
you know, because he doesn't like them till they're nine, 10 years old. Discuss like disgusting,
right? There are some good good ones coming up. So Marcos nephew was 100% going to get
molested by this dude. Like he was part of the grooming process isn't just the child,
but you groom yourself with the family as well. He was he was 100. He was 10 toes into
this community. People just trusted him. Everyone loved them. They also this is again, it's
absolutely insane. The police when they were doing this forensic analysis on the computer,
this all came up in the trial. I don't think they went to Marco's cell and been like, Hey,
you did us a favor. This all came up in the trial. But apparently not only was there the
comment that there are some good ones coming up, meaning there are some other kids in his
neighborhood. He can't wait to molest. They also found that very recently, like shortly
before him getting murdered shortly before Jamie getting murdered, Jamie uploaded a photo
of Marco uploaded a photo of Marco himself when he was a young boy. Jamie wrote when he
uploaded the photo, the caption read quote, he was so beautiful then. It's creepy to think
right Marco didn't even remember any of this. And this dude was talking about him online,
like reminiscing like you would over an ex girlfriend. He didn't remember Marco did
not remember a single thing. This guy was posting photographs of him as a boy, absolutely
insane. And you can understand why people did not want this dude prosecuted. People in
the community were like, Listen, we know vigilante ism is wrong. Because here's the thing vigilante
is this is a good example of a vigilante a bad example of vigilante is a lynch mob. Someone
going that guy did something. And then people going and hanging him. That's a problem with
vigilantes. It's we have these cases where there's evidence. But imagine if there was
no computer. Imagine if there was just a video of a guy begging for his life and saying,
please don't kill me. I didn't do anything to you. And then after 1050 minutes of that,
he goes, fine, fine, fine, I'm less than you. Let me go. And then then him getting his throat
slit and then strangled instead. To this day, people would go, we don't believe there would
be people in that community who would not believe Marco. They'd be like he was psychotic
and he killed that guy. But because we have like, he saved the computer. Right. He had
that evidence. But vigilantes, you know, they can go either way, you can have good vigilantes
and horrific vigilantes. But the people didn't want him prosecuted. They go, Listen, this
guy was a six scumbag and he abused Marco for years and Marco grew up and got strong
enough and Marco took action. He took out a pedophile who was going to pray on other
kids. And you know, the DA, the district attorney Ian Paulumam, he basically said, we got to
prosecute this guy. Like you just can't not prosecute people who break into other people's
houses, premeditated murder, breaking other people's houses, set up a video camera and
murder them. You just can't do that. And DAs are constantly, I know people, you know,
DAs constantly are making decisions over who to prosecute. And sometimes they drop the
ball for sure. And sometimes they may overly prosecute other people, but it's on camera.
I mean, you brought in a video camera, the whole thing was recorded. He could have gone
away with it. Remember, too, would they have been able to track it back to just some random
teenager in the neighborhood? But anyways, he goes, you can't just go out and kill people.
We can. We have to prosecute him. And they did. And in 2013, this was the best outcome
possible really with the laws that we have in 2013, Marco pled guilty to voluntary manslaughter.
I mean, this was premeditated murder 100% first degree. The reason why he could get
voluntary manslaughter or plead down to that one is public sentiment, right? If the people
wanted to hang him, if the people wanted him in prison, right? If the public opinion was
against him, the DA could have pushed harder, but you're going to have a hard time finding
a jury. And two, voluntary manslaughter would basically be like, I went crazy because all
of this stuff happened. And then yes, I meant to kill him, but I was under stress because
of everything that happened to me. I think voluntary manslaughter is fair. He got sentenced
to 15 years in prison, which as long as you do not have that L after it, you will get out.
If it's 15 to life, you may never, ever, ever get out. But if they give you just, it's better
to take 20 years than 10 to life because they just, they have the option of keeping you
in there until you die. 20 years, you're going to get out maximum 20 years. You keep your
nose clean. You don't get caught with any drugs, contraband, killing people in prison,
anything like that, right? You'll do, you'll probably do 70% of that, maybe less than the
amount of crime. But 20 years is better than 10 to life because you just may never get
out. Anyways, he got 15 years in prison. So, you know, it's crazy. This is what I love
about doing a true crime podcast, right? This story happened in 2011. He'll, he'll be out
max in five years. If he's kept his nose clean in prison, he'll be out in five years
and he will be welcomed back into that community with open arms because he killed a pedophile.
He killed a monster, a true monster. He was planning on doing this to other kids like
you can't get any worse than that. A predator in a tight knit community doing whatever he
wanted. No one suspected him. It was so awful what he did that not even Marco suspected
anything because he'd blocked it all out. They never say if there were other victims
of his in that community, but I'd be shocked if there weren't. I hope there weren't. But
I'd be shocked if there weren't. But I hope there weren't like obviously I hope. It's
a story, isn't it? A vigilante videotapes himself murdering his abuser and it's true. He did
it to save other kids and in the end he saved other kids. It's an insane story of a kid
who grew up and then remembered everything he forced himself to forget. But then he did
something about it. The memories came flooding back and he did something about it. He saved
people. He saved, who knows how many kids? Who knows how many other kids from going through
this torment. There are some good ones coming up is what Jamie had wrote to his fellow pedophiles
online. He couldn't wait until those boys turned 10 years old. But little did Jamie
know he wouldn't live to see even his next birthday.
[Music]