Is it possible to have a science that is so scary people don't want to even research it?
And then we travel to Iceland to take a look at one of the most bizarre and yet most powerful
magical relics known to man.
What would you do if you found out that the only way to become rich and successful is
to wear the necropanths?
Today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Carpenter and I'm having a great day.
I hope you guys are having a great day too.
I hope you guys are having tons of fun out there in the world.
We got a lot of stuff to cover so first off walking into Dead Rabbit Command is one of
our newest patreon supporters.
Get on your feet and give it up for our very own necropanths wearing Jonah.
Woohoo!
Yeah come on in.
He's like wait I don't know what the necropanths are yet.
Oh you'll learn soon.
Jonah.
And you'll be like I don't want to wear these pants.
Well you can't take them off but we'll get to that.
Now you're prisoner of the necropanths Jonah but thank you for supporting the show.
You're going to be our captain or pilot this episode.
You guys don't want to support the show financially.
That's totally fine.
It really is.
It really helps spread the word about Dead Rabbit Radio.
That helps out so much and I see you guys doing it online all the time so I appreciate
that.
Jonah let's go ahead and toss you the keys to the Jason Jalopy we're going to leave behind
Dead Rabbit Command.
Drive us all the way out to Georgia.
[POP]
Specifically we're headed out to Savannah Georgia.
And hey Jonah you see that house right there.
Yeah the yellow one with the blue trim.
Go ahead and pull the Jason Jalopy over.
Let's get out.
We walk up to the house.
I'm standing there at the front door.
Check my watch.
I go.
One thing that's interesting that I find so fascinating about the I would say the art
of ghost hunting.
Rather than the science of ghost hunting.
So many people want to make.
I mean listen it's a free world you can do whatever you want with your hobbies or with
your profession.
But I find it so interesting that people try so hard to make a science out of the paranormal.
Because science is something I mean you just have just the basic foundation that you have
to be able to repeat and experiment over and over and over again under the same conditions
and if you get the same results then that's the scientific method.
And that's something that we don't see happen with paranormal events.
Every so often we come across the paranormal story and it's things like every labor day
if you go out to this graveyard you'll see a little girl dancing around a grave and she'll
look at you and she'll go shh she'll vanish in the thin air.
If there is actually a story creepy right?
The story is creepy but if there is any way to actually prove that it's a repeatable time
right?
You know when it's going to happen you know the day it's going to happen.
You'll know to bring out your recording equipment and capture proof of it.
I've never been, I guess maybe when I was younger I might have wanted to prove.
Actually no I don't think I was ever in that mindset.
I think I've always been in the vein at least as far as the world of the paranormal goes.
Conspiracies is a bit different you know.
I believe that there's a criminal conspiracy going on or a conspiracy the government is
putting against people.
I want to prove that.
But as far as whether or not people believe in ghosts it doesn't really matter to me
in the end.
I understand why people don't believe in ghosts because it's not repeatable.
There's no way to provoke this response.
You know whenever we do have some sort of tool like a spirit box or a Ouija board or
things like that.
Physical items.
I'm not talking about mediums.
I'm looking at my watch again.
Not talking about mediums or anything like that.
Physical devices.
A microscope.
If you turn the knob it will always get closer on the Amoeba.
But Ouija board under different conditions will work or will not work.
Same thing with the spirit box and all of these things.
And I understand that.
I understand why people don't believe in ghosts because it can't be verified.
I don't necessarily like it when people don't believe in ghosts simply because they think
it's stupid.
And they believe that people who believe in ghosts are stupid.
That's when now it's a personal attack.
And I don't think it's a personal attack on me.
It is.
But I guess so I do think it is that.
But I mean I don't get offended by it.
I think it's a attack against millions.
Really billions of people around the world who do believe in ghosts.
People go oh they're just stupid.
They're just mentally ill.
Yeah I mean then I guess you live on a planet that is ruled by the mentally ill.
But whatever everyone's free to have their own opinion and I'm not here to prove anything
to anybody.
But science is.
I check my watch I go okay we're here at the perfect time.
And I get down and I start picking the lock to this house.
We open the front door.
It's an average house.
We walk into this house and we hear a television playing in the bedroom.
So we make our way to the bedroom and we walk in there and playing on television is a rerun
of Sanford and Sun.
That's not the first thing that catches your eye.
You see a middle aged man dead in a bed.
And I go yeah just in time.
I had this time perfectly and I walk over to this man.
He's laying in bed.
Hmm.
His heart stopped.
His heart stopped the minute we walked into the room.
Now his brain is not being supplied with blood.
And we're watching this man die in this room.
And you go to shut off the television set because you don't think anyone should die
while it's 1976 comes playing.
I go no no no no no no no don't touch the TV.
First off fingerprints.
Secondly this man loves Sanford and Sun.
It's one of his favorite shows.
It's a good show I used to watch it.
And I'm sitting by the side of his bed.
We're watching this man die.
Finally he's already dead.
His heart has stopped.
At this point we're just watching all of the biological functions cease in his body.
We continue to let the episode play out until it's over.
What you just witnessed was science.
You're letting no chance in.
I think we just witnessed a man die and you easily could have done something.
Well we could have done chest compressions but it was this man's time to go.
This was on his terms.
He wanted to die in bed at home watching television.
And the reason why we're here and the reason why we timed it so perfectly is that I wanted
to talk about a very intriguing article I read about how long can the dying here.
Fascinating study that came out of the University of British Columbia Canada.
It was printed in the publication Scientific Reports which is a journal.
Finally they did the study hospice center.
They had this cap with these electrodes on it.
They put it on the heads of a control group.
People who were totally alive.
And then they would put the same cap on people who were in the process of dying.
Because again like our friend here when you're in hospice there's not much that they can
do for you.
If you have a heart attack in hospice care the worst thing they can do is drive you across
town to the hospital bring you back to life.
And take you back to the hospice center where you may just repeat the whole thing next day.
Hospice center is where people go in their final days, weeks, months.
However they have it set up.
So we have one set of electrodes on healthy living people and another set of electrodes
on people who are in the process of dying.
And what they've realized was that when they were doing this study right, the people who
are in the process of dying, they're not dying right now.
They're just you know they got a couple days, couple weeks left.
The scientists would play these different changing melodies, these very simple melodies.
By playing these they called this type of melody an oddball sequence.
By playing these melodies we can measure what's going on in the brain.
It gives us a baseline of what a human brain shows when it's hearing these melodies.
What parts of the brain light up.
Now when these hospice patients are actively dying right they've fallen unconscious.
They are not going to be revived.
At this point whatever disease or ailment has gotten them it will finish them off in
a matter of hours or minutes.
Whatever it is depending you know obviously.
Usually it's hours but it can vary.
They would put the caps back on the now unconscious patients.
I should be very clear they were all aware this was going to happen.
They signed up for this.
They weren't like "ah now I get to sleep.
The sleep of kings."
All of a sudden they're feeling someone put a ill fitting hat on them.
They're like "what no this wasn't part of the deal."
They knew that they were going to do this.
So anyways when these you have a control group and then you have a baseline reading of the
dying hospice people hospice patients and now when they're actively dying when they
fallen unconscious these electrodes are reattached to their head and they begin playing the tones
again.
Even after they fell unconscious they could hear the tones because we could see their
brain reacting to them.
It wasn't as strong as when they were alive like fully alive.
Now that they're unconscious and they're in the final moments of life their brain is still
reacting to the sound.
But you know we've always heard if someone's in a coma you sit next to them you can talk
to them that can help.
So we've always figured that that wouldn't be a barrier if someone was unconscious.
People can talk to you while you're sleeping and maybe affect your dream.
You're like "watch out zombies zombies they're coming the right behind you."
You're like "ahhh" in your dream and they're giving you sleeping pills to keep their entertainment
going.
Even after the heart stopped pumping blood.
So at this point they are generally people are considered dead.
It depends really there's actually become an active debate in the medical community.
When is somebody dead?
Is it when the heart stops pumping blood and there is no way to revive them?
Or is it when the brain sees as activity?
The problem is we don't know when the brain sees as activity.
The brain seems to be active for quite a while after when a doctor would say you're dead
and that's where a study like this gets creepy.
If that intro wasn't creepy enough for us.
Even after the heart stops pumping blood the brain is still reacting to the tones.
What they believe and this has been a theory in the medical community for a long time that
hearing is the last sense you lose as you're dying.
Vision goes fairly quickly especially if you're unconscious right?
You're going to lose your vision.
But I imagine as your body is shutting down it does like obviously we don't need taste
buds no more.
We don't need to pump energy to our taste buds so you lose a sense of taste would probably
be the first one to go.
But touch, hearing, sight.
What's the other one?
What is the other one?
Touch, hearing, taste, sight and a sense of rhythm.
I don't remember what the five senses are but anyways I imagine taste is the first thing
to go but there's been a theory that the last one to go is hearing.
So even after you've become unconscious even after your heart stopped beating what we can
tell again it's not as strong as it was when these patients were still alive.
It wasn't even as strong as when these patients were just unconscious but the brain is still
picking up signals after the person's heart has stopped beating.
It's still reacting to the tones.
Now the scientist said listen here's the thing, according to this study people can still hear
after they've been declared dead.
The question is can they comprehend it?
It's still terrifying right?
It's still absolutely terrifying to think about but they go just because the brain is reacting
to it.
It is picking up on it.
The sense of hearing is still there but do they understand what you're saying or what
anyone's saying or what Sanford is saying when he's having another heart attack?
We don't know.
That would be the worst show to watch after you've died of a heart attack and you're
just laying there in bed and the last thing you hear is Sanford going oh Martha I'm coming
home Martha.
You guys are like I've never watched Sanford and San what is this?
Does every episode he have a heart attack?
Yeah every episode he had a heart attack.
It's crazy.
It's really chilling if you think about it but at the same time I think it also is, it's
reassuring.
I think it's kind of sweet on one hand because then when you are dying your loved ones around
you as they're saying their goodbyes to you you're hearing all of that even after you've
become unconscious you're still hearing them even after your heart stopped beating you're
still hearing them.
I think that is sweet and nice.
However the chilling part comes from is when does this sense of hearing leave you?
Like as your body is being zipped up you hear the gurney wheels you hear a door open up
you're stuffed into a freezing cold morgue.
I mean the good thing is you've lost your sense of touch.
Actually we don't know that that's the next thing they're testing.
These Canadian neurosciences are going to test whether or not the dying can feel touch.
How long they can feel something touching their skin.
But I mean like imagine if you could hear your coffin being shut.
Dirt being shut.
You're like okay Jason that's you took it too far.
You're taking it to ruin.
I imagine they don't hear all of that.
I don't imagine they're like I can hear the worms.
I can hear the worms digging through the wood.
I don't think they can.
I bet they couldn't but until we get scientists down there who knows.
Probably not though.
Probably not.
Creepy creepy story.
And I want to talk about that for two reasons.
One because I found it infinitely disturbing yet kind of cool.
Two I wanted to contrast it with this story.
We walk out of this guy's house and now we're standing in Savannah Georgia and I said you
know there's one thing that gets the old thirst going.
It's my sense of taste.
Kicking up.
He's watching a man die.
Let's go to a local tavern and wet our whistle.
Jonah go ahead and call in that bunny bicycle.
We're going to jump on the handlebars.
Bike us all the way out to Pirate's House Tavern.
Weak and weak and weak.
He's pedaling down the streets of Savannah Georgia.
We get to Pirate's House Tavern and we walk in.
We're like Saspirilla is all around.
The guy's like what is this is a bar.
What year do you think this is?
We don't serve Saspirilla.
We're like oh man.
Root beer is all around.
He's like there you go.
We all got a nice Henry Weinhardt's root beer in our hand.
Ice cold.
We're drinking it.
I wanted to talk about this in contrast to how that is a scientific study that was done
by scientists and it was probably creepy for them too.
I don't think they're working on it late at night.
They're like look at these readings.
The dead can hear and they're like hunched over their laptop and there's like an old
man ghost standing behind him and he's like we heard it all.
What was that?
Scientists is all sweating.
I don't think it's creepy but you know it's science.
You got to do it.
You got to hang out with these dying people.
Let's contrast it to the Pirate's House Tavern.
I came across to this ghost story the other day when I was going through the shadowlands
dot net.
And Pirate's House Tavern it was built in the 1700s.
We don't have an exact date.
It's a real place.
It's a real tavern.
Originally it was a place for pirates.
I don't think it was called the Pirate's House Tavern back then because piracy was a crime
that you would get hung for at best.
They often would torture pirates.
I don't think that they actually called it the Pirate's House Tavern.
That'd be like having a bar in downtown Chicago today called the Drug Runners.
Not a smart idea.
Very very notorious though.
This is where you had Robert Louis Stevenson when he was getting ready to write Treasure
Island.
He spent time at Pirate's House Tavern to get a feel of the energy from the area.
He wanted to go to this pretty, I mean I'm sure it's a nice place now but it wasn't for
a long time.
It basically it's where sailors would go whether or not they were pirates to where sailors
would go to get drunk and to beat each other up.
There'd been a lot of stabbings, a lot of murders, a lot of kidnappings.
Apparently there's a series of tunnels from underneath the Pirate's House Tavern to the
local port.
We do know a lot of men got kidnapped out of Pirate's House Tavern and dragged through
the tunnels and what happened is they'd get drugged and then they'd wake up on a pirate
ship a hundred miles out to sea and they'd like swap the deck or get off.
Not sexually.
Although we'll probably do that later.
You can jump overboard.
And so you're like well I guess I'm a slave now.
That happened.
We did have stories historically of men being shanghied, being kidnapped and forced to
work on boats.
Because what choice would you have at that point?
So this place was considered very lawless.
It had a reputation for being lawless.
So nowadays it has all these ghost stories.
It's very standard ghost stories we see in places like this.
Poltergeist activities such as glasses getting knocked off the shelves.
Full body apparitions appearing as well.
A lot of times these ghosts will appear right in front of people staring eye to eye with
them and then they just disappear.
It's not like you catch something out of the corner of your eye and you turn and you think
you saw a peg leg walk by.
No, he's standing right in front of you.
You're getting ready to use the urinal and he appears right in front of you and there's
no mistake.
You're looking at a ghost because he appears and then disappears right in front of you.
Screams coming from the tunnels.
I'm so blase about that I'm like oh not the screams.
Boring.
And so you know that would be horrifying.
Screams coming from the tunnel but we have those stories.
A very very interesting ghost lore.
Is it Dead Rabbit Radio interesting though?
The reason why I wanted to highlight it was because of this.
This is where I get upset.
And I hope I have time.
I don't go off on too much of a rant and I have time for the Necro Paint story since
Joan is wearing them and all.
Listen I get it.
The world, the paranormal is not taken seriously in the scientific community.
And your mileage may vary on that.
Some of you guys may deeply care about that and you want it to be considered up there
with chemistry and astronomy and biology.
And that's why you have terms like parapsychology in the study of the paranormal.
You have all this stuff.
We keep inventing equipment.
A spirit box.
Temperature meters.
EVPs.
These are not just for ghost hunting.
These are to prove to people who don't believe in ghosts.
That's why these devices keep getting invented.
People who just go ghost hunting for the love of it.
And that might be the wrong way to say it because I know people who do go ghost hunting
for the love of it and bring these devices.
But you know what I mean?
When I go to a ghost location, when I've done a lot of on the ground hunts, we never ever
worried about recording anything.
I don't think we ever did that.
I think maybe once I did set up a camera to do EVPs at a house that was pretty haunted.
But even then, I didn't pick up anything.
Actually, to be honest, I didn't finish listening to the tape.
I got bored.
It was like eight hours.
I was like, "I'm done."
So who knows maybe after I shut it off, they're like, "We have your soul."
But anyways, I don't care whether or not people believe in it.
I believe in it.
And if you don't believe in it, that's totally fine.
When you mock people, you don't believe in it.
That's when it's kind of like, "Okay, now you're just kind of..."
Now you're just being a jerk, right?
There's a lot of stuff that I don't believe in that other people do and I don't go out
of my way to tell them I don't believe in it.
And I'm just like, "Whatever.
It doesn't matter.
It's not affecting me in any way, shape, or form."
But if you are going to try to be taken seriously, like a lot of ghost hunters are, you cannot
scream and run away.
I'm going to read you this little story that happened at the tavern and tell me what other
scientific pursuit would this happen at.
According to theshadowlands.net, and I saw this reported in other places as well, there
is a group, first off, this name, right?
We can have the University of Cambridge Center for Astronomical Studies, right?
We can have something like that.
This group is the national...
They don't exist anymore.
But the National Ghost Chasing Association.
The good old NGCA, the National Ghost Chasing Association.
Probably looks funny.
Probably looks kind of funny on a business card and on a shirt.
But if you want to be taken seriously, probably leave out the part where you're chasing it,
right?
I know there's storm chasers, people who chase tornadoes, but meteorologists don't generally
call themselves weather chasers.
But anyways, I don't want to feel like I'm, you know, nitpicking.
Although that's probably what I'm about to do.
National Ghost Chasing Association.
12 of them, 12 members of the National Ghost Chasing Association.
Now, for all I know, these guys were just a bunch of dudes out having fun.
But when you name yourself the National Ghost Chasing Association, it does make it sound...
Well, it makes it sound national, right?
It makes it sound like it's this big organization.
And there's 12 of you.
So I don't know if people came from all over America.
Maybe it was just a local group and they had a big ambition.
They don't exist anymore.
National Ghost Chasing Association.
12 of them said we are going to investigate Pirate's House Tattern.
Places all these hauntings, these screams from the tunnels that seem not to impress Jason.
We're going to investigate this.
12 members of the National Ghost Chasing Association showed up.
And they were going to be there for three days.
Three days seems like a long time.
Not necessarily for a ghost hunt, because again, you want that...
If you want to prove it, right?
You want verifiable.
You want to see if it can repeat itself.
But it's also a business.
This is a functional bar.
So imagine if you're trying to run a business and you have a bunch of ghost chasers walking
around.
And maybe it was in the middle of January.
Maybe it was a slow month for the bar.
But still.
And how are you going to do any sort of ghost investigations if you're like, "Oh no.
I hear a voice coming from the floor below us."
Yeah, because there's 20 people down there dining.
Anyways, I'm nitpicking.
That's not fair.
They were going to be there for three days.
They decided.
I'm sure they talked to management.
I'm sure they didn't just show up and not leave.
The boss is like, "We're closed."
And they're like, "Look at our business card goods, sir.
We're ghost chasers.
We make the rules."
And they were going to stay there for three days.
But...
Tell me, name any other form of science that this would happen in.
But it was so scary.
It was so terrifying at the Pirate House Tavern that all of the experts, they call themselves
experts, so this isn't a hobby group.
They may have been hobbyists who called themselves experts.
Sure.
But they didn't see themselves as hobbyists.
It was so spooky at the bar.
Nine of them left the premises before the investigation was over.
So three remained for the whole three days.
And according to this report, "All of the experts were scared out."
I just think...
I can't imagine any other scientific discipline ever using this phrase.
"All of the experts were scared out of their minds."
And I read that and I thought, "Listen, you have to choose.
You have to choose one or the other.
To be taken seriously as a scientific organization or a scientific pursuit, or...
Yeah, I can only have one of these two.
Or run out of a house at three in the morning with your arms flailing in the air going, "Ahhh!"
And you're trying to get the car started because you saw something spooky in that house.
It's one or the other.
All these ghost shows on television, ghost hunters, and ghost adventurers, and ghost travel,
and all this stuff, they're walking through an abandoned asylum or abandoned prison, which
are scary places.
Don't get me wrong.
But they're walking in the dark with their cameras and their infrared cameras and their
devices and everything like that.
And then there's a noise down the hallway and they go, "Ahhh!
You have a choice."
Because I don't think there has ever been at an observatory where a scientist was looking
through a telescope and ran away.
Ran away.
They go, "Hey, Johnson, why did you leave the door unlocked last night?
I hope those came in and re-attached the telescope.
It's going to take years to get it back in place."
He goes, "You won't believe it.
I saw a black hole.
It's all black hole.
Now unless they're black hole, it just opened around Jupiter."
I mean, sure.
Okay, listen, if it's a world ending disaster, if some guy's looking through a test tube and
he's like, "Oh my God, this virus is going to kill humanity in the next six months, sure.
You're free to run out.
You're free to run out of the lab with your arms in the air screaming."
But in the ghost hunting world, you have to choose.
You can either be scientists trying to prove that ghosts exist or people running out of
the study.
This is a study you've set up.
You've set up something that you go, "We're going to observe a phenomenon.
We're going to try to contact it.
We're going to document it."
You can't run away screaming.
I remember I read this book about the history of diseases, modern diseases.
It wasn't like the lame ones, like the flu.
They were talking about AIDS.
They had a whole section about AIDS and they were saying they didn't know how it was spread.
This was when it first started popping up in parts of Africa.
This is before it got to America, got to the San Francisco is where it really popped off
over here.
But they can trace AIDS in America to a single person.
It was an airline flight attendant.
That was patient zero.
They know that person's name.
I don't remember it, but they do know the person who brought AIDS to America.
But anyways, when they were first trying to figure it out, it was just this disease that
was killing very, very young people.
There was, I think it was in France or Sweden, there was a laboratory and a guy had samples
of AIDS infected blood.
They don't even think they had named it at that point.
It was just like a series of letters and numbers.
He had this vial and he's in this laboratory and he dropped it.
Shattered.
And they locked the lab down.
It's like something out of a sci-fi movie.
They're like, "Sorry, Charlie.
Everything got locked.
I don't know if it was automated.
I don't know if he was thinking about sliding underneath the door."
But he was locked in because they didn't know if it was airborne.
They didn't know how you contracted it.
They had zero idea.
For all they knew, they just watched the guy die because he butterfingered a vial.
He'd been up all night working on what is this.
And they did.
They isolated him for quite a while and then they got brave enough, because it's what you
have to do, to start testing him and he didn't have it.
So now they know, well, at least it doesn't seem to be airborne.
Now I'm sure that guy was, I'm sure that guy was moving his pants, right?
I don't think that guy slept well for the next couple nights.
But even in that situation, he didn't run out of the room with his arms flailing in
the air.
They wouldn't let him for what.
He was locked in the room.
But two, do you see what I mean?
Science can be scary, but no other scientist.
I mean, listen, if there's a nature, a biologist or whatever out in the jungle and a gorilla
comes after him, yes, you can run.
If I see him running, I'm like, you whip.
Go steady that monkey.
I'm all driving away.
I was like, I'm not picking you up until you get some monkey science done, sir.
You go chase him.
What's the difference between an 800 pound gorilla chasing a scientist through the jungle?
That's kind of funny, actually.
What's the difference between an 800-pound lab coat?
His lab coat keeps getting tattered.
He's like, oh, why did I wear this dude with lab coat?
I'm not even in a lab.
800 pound gorilla chasing a scientist through the jungle.
What's the difference between that and your in the catacombs of a place where you know
untold amounts of people were dragged out of here unconscious to wake up on a ship miles
away and now you're hearing them scream.
You're hearing the disembodied screams coming from the end of these deep tunnels.
What's the difference?
Well, listen.
I'm not.
Listen, it would terrify me.
It would terrify me.
But I am not a scientist and I don't approach this as a science because I understand that
it really does defy science and the sciences as we know it.
It just can't be replicated.
We've learned that.
You cannot replicate this phenomenon.
You can't replicate any of it.
You can't replicate.
And this is actually a good segue, too.
Let me finish what I was going to say.
Yes, it would be scary.
I would be scared to be in those tunnels, but I'm not there to prove anything.
I'm there to go down there and be like, I wonder if this place is actually haunted.
And then I would come back and say, yeah, I was down there and I heard this and I heard
that and it was so scary.
I ran away.
You're like, Jason, you'd run away, too?
Well, yeah.
I'm not thinking about it.
I would totally run away if it was that bad, too.
But again, I'm not a scientist.
I consider myself more like a journalist.
And when I was reading this article the other day about how journalists in Mexico, they're
like, yeah, we've just kind of stopped reporting on stuff because the corruption is so bad
that if we report on the corruption, we get killed.
So we've just stopped reporting on it.
And I go, that's fair.
I mean, it's not fair for the citizens of Mexico, but I understand that.
But I'm just telling ghost stories, ghost experiences I've had.
And if you don't believe my stories, that's fine.
That's fine.
But if you're trying to prove the existence of ghosts, which a lot of these ghost hunting
shows do, that's why they bring in these monitors and they're like, look, we caught this EVP.
They hit play and it's all mashed potatoes.
And they're like, let me rewind that for you.
Mashed potatoes.
And they go, it's sane.
I hate God.
And then they play it again and it goes very clear.
Once they say what it's supposed to say, the end play and it goes, I hate God.
They're like, wow, how did I not hear that the first two times?
It's weird.
Once he told me, he's saying mashed potatoes, but once he told me what it said, I clearly
heard it say, I hate God.
You know, that's I think the difference.
The difference is that if you're a ghost scientist, you're a parapsychologist, you're
trying to prove this stuff, you're trying to use the scientific method to, for something
that at this point defies the scientific method.
I think someday we may understand what it is, but it'll be outside the bounds of what
we know as science.
It won't ever fall underneath that umbrella.
And we won't get to the Necro pants.
Jonah, we're going to have to have you back.
Keep those Necro pants on.
Good sir.
We'll have you back.
What I think is interesting is this is the old, even in paranormal, even in the world
of paranormal, this is the only place we see this happen.
We do not hear stories about UFO hunters leaving the scene, right?
They went up to the mountains.
They went out to Mount Shasta because there were reports of UFOs and hidden tunnels underneath.
You never, as far as I can remember all the UFO research we've done over the years, even
before the show, I don't think I've ever come across a story where UFO hunters, UFO researchers
go out to an area and they see a bright light in the sky and they leave.
They drive away as fast as they can.
I can't recall that because that's what they're there for.
Hell or high water, they are there to prove that this phenomenon exists.
UFOs are all about proof.
They're all about getting the photographs, getting the video footage.
That's why whenever a little, even the smallest sliver of hope from a photograph or a video
goes viral because people want that with that.
They'll go there where they know there's alien activity, where they know there have been
cattle mutilations, where they know things have been ripped open and had nearly all the
blood drained out of them.
They don't run away screaming.
The same thing with cryptids.
People who go out.
Sometimes you might have a little bit of the run factor, but if we narrow it down to stuff
like the Loch Ness Monster or Bigfoot, you very, very rarely, there would probably be
more than the UFO stories but less than the ghost ones, of people going out to hunt Bigfoot
and they hear something in the woods and then they pack their gear up and run away.
I have seen stories of people who have gone out to hunt Bigfoot, not necessarily shoot
him but to photograph of him, and Bigfoot throws rocks.
They throw rocks flying through the forest at them, tree branches moving in again.
Now you're looking at a physical threat.
They may not see it, but they can tell something very big and very strong is moving sight unseen
through the forest towards them.
A physical force that may rip their head off.
Even those stories are rare.
I'm really thinking there's a story I read recently, well covered on the show I think,
about a wolf man, about this giant wolf-like creature moving through the forest.
It was throwing stuff at these guys.
I actually don't think they were cryptid hunters.
I think they were just regular hunters and they took off running.
That's a cool story.
We'll have to cover that one next week.
But I'm just saying, like ghost hunters, they run.
And that's almost like part of it.
It's super weird.
Basically you want to prove that ghosts exist, but also you want to be like, man, that house
is so haunted.
I couldn't get in.
It was so haunted I didn't even try to get any proof.
I ran away.
Just like me, like when I recorded eight hours of a haunted bedroom, it was at Jackie and
Josh's house.
I was over at Jackie and Josh's old house.
They're old friends of mine.
Don't go looking for them now.
Don't go crawling into their bedroom, being like, "Oh, this place is haunted."
This was out in a semi-valley, not the city, a semi-valley road in Antelope, California.
There's a haunted house out there.
And I remember I was like, I set up my camcorder and I go, "I'm going to record this bedroom."
It's the parents' bedroom.
They weren't there at the time.
I wasn't secretly recording your parents, Josh.
Had the camera set up and I hit play.
It was extended play.
I was going to record eight hours of audio and visual evidence in Jackie's parents' bedroom.
And the next day I was like, "Oh, I'm going to watch that."
And maybe a ghost showed up.
Maybe the sound of the dead and the damned talking.
I watched, I watched maybe 20 minutes of it.
But again, I'm not a ghost scientist.
I'm allowed to be lazy.
I'm allowed to be scared is basically what I'm saying.
This is why people don't take ghost hunting seriously because they don't have the gumption
to stick around.
You can choose.
Do you want to be taken seriously?
Do you want proof or do you want to be scared?
And I think that's the interesting thing.
People don't investigate UFOs to get scared.
People do not investigate cryptids to get scared.
Cryptid investigations really come down to two groups of people.
People who are trying to find proof of, three groups of people.
People who are trying to find proof of Bigfoot.
People who are trying to shoot Bigfoot in the brain.
And then the whole other group of cryptid people are people trying to protect their
farm.
And there's some creature out there in the darkness that's killing their sheep.
Where you have a rash of young men disappear along a river somewhere in South America.
And people are trying to figure out what's doing it and it's some sort of crypt.
It's some sort of creature of legend out there.
Those are really the groups of cryptid hunters.
People who are trying to prove something.
People who are trying to kill something or people trying to protect their territory.
Ghost hunters.
I listen.
I love you guys.
I consider myself a ghost investigator.
Maybe that's just split hairs because I'm always going to.
But even then, I mean, yeah, sure.
Listen, it's scary.
I don't can necessarily say I've run from a location in the middle of a ghost hunt.
I don't think that I have.
But again, I have different motives.
I'm not putting up.
I'm not going to be there for three days to prove this place is haunted and then run
away in the middle of the night because it's so scary.
We can't have it both ways, ghost guys.
We can't have it go.
We can't have it ghost way.
You like that?
That's just my take.
Maybe I'm wrong.
I was really, really hoping that segment wouldn't turn into a rant and take up the rest of
the episode.
But it did.
Jonah, we're going to have to have you next episode because we got to have everyone in
the carpenter copter.
So you will be back.
Keep those necro pants on till tomorrow and then you'll find out the horrifying madness
that you've been wearing.
DeadRabbitRadio@gmail.com is going to be our email address.
You can also set us up at facebook.com/DeadRabbitRadio.
TikTok is @DeadRabbitRadio.
DeadRabbitRadio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast.
You don't have to listen to it every day.
I'm glad you listened to it today.
Have a great week guys.
Bye.
(upbeat music)
[MUSIC]