When a young woman is over at a friend's apartment, she already knows that this place
gives off a creepy vibe, but little does she know she's about to witness something that
will make her question reality.
And then we travel to a Kmart to meet a man who's just there to do some quick shopping
before he goes on with the rest of his day.
Instead he meets an old friend from the past and this chance encounter has him questioning
what happens after you die.
Today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host, Jason Carpenterder, and I'm having a great day.
I hope you guys are having a great day too.
I hope you guys are having tons of fun out there in the world doing whatever you're
doing.
We got a ton of stuff to cover, so let's go ahead and get started here.
First off, walking into Dead Rabbit Command is a longtime supporter of the show and pretty
much becoming my own personal librarian.
Everyone give it up for Greg Gorley.
Woohoo!
Yeah, come on in, Greg.
Walk on into Dead Rabbit Command.
Greg's been sending me books recently off of my Amazon wishlist.
They started thinking maybe I should put groceries on there.
Maybe I should get some Gatorade Zero dropped off in my house.
I do love these books though.
This is a book.
I don't even know if I have this on my wishlist.
I think you can buy stuff just for me.
I don't know.
Maybe not.
This is a book called The Darkest Places.
Unsolved Mysteries, True Crimes, and Heroine Disasters in the Wilds.
So yeah, really, really cool book.
It's from the editors of Outside Magazine, so it's out in the middle of nowhere.
Time for horrific stories.
The places I never go.
I never go into the middle of nowhere.
I hate the outdoors because it's too spooky.
And now Greg has gotten me a book that reinforces my view of the natural world.
Thank you so much.
Greg, you're going to be our captain, our pilot this episode.
You guys can't buy me anything.
If you guys can't support the show financially, it truly is totally okay.
Just help spread the word about Dead Rabbit Radio.
You have no idea how much that helps when you let other people know that you enjoy the show.
Greg, let's go ahead and let's dust off the bunny bicycle.
We haven't used this guy in a long time.
We'll hop on the handlebars as he pedals us out of Dead Rabbit Command all the way out
to a creepy apartment.
Wicca, wicca, wicca.
There's a reason why we don't use the bunny bicycle a lot.
I haven't found a good sound effect for it.
We are at our destination.
Everyone hop off the bunny bike.
Let's lock it up to a nearby tree and we're going to enter this apartment complex where
we're about to meet a young woman.
Now she didn't give her name.
She doesn't give her real name.
We're going to go ahead and call her Abby.
Online she goes by the name Euphoric Mycologist 39.
We don't have any real names.
We don't have an exact location.
We do have a time period.
This is a fairly recent story.
She said this happened around three years ago.
She classifies it as the beginning of COVID.
So February, March, April of 2020 is when the story popped off.
Abby was hanging out at her friend's apartment.
She said this was an older apartment.
I don't know if this, I'm sure the whole entire complex was older, but I don't know
if the entire complex gave off a creepy vibe, but Abby's friend's apartment definitely gave
off a creepy vibe.
When she was over there, when her friend who lived there, anyone was hanging out over there,
it did feel a little off.
On this particular day, Abby's over at this apartment complex with her friend and there's
two other friends there as well.
So there's four women and there's also two little girls who are at the apartment complex.
A four-year-old and a seven-year-old, we'll go ahead and call the four-year-old Samantha.
And it's just kind of a get-together.
Everyone's having a lot of fun, just hanging out, watching television, talking, making a
little lunch, and just an all-around get-together.
Little did we know that this would soon become very difficult to do after COVID really struck
and you had all of these isolation guidelines and things like that.
But towards the beginning, you're like, "Hey, did you see the news about that disease coming
out of China?
Let's all hang out together.
Let's get all these different people together in this tiny apartment and hang out."
Because who knows what's going to happen next.
She's over at this apartment hanging out, making lunch.
She does say this is always good to acknowledge.
She goes, "We do smoke weed, but on this particular day we weren't smoking any weed.
We were all totally sober over at my friend's house."
And she says, "I'm sitting there and the two little girls, the four-year-old and the seven-year-old,
Samantha and the other little girl, are just kind of running around having fun in the apartment.
Everyone else is just chilling."
And time passes.
Time marches on and they're just hanging out.
So after an indefinite amount of time, she just said, "Time passes.
Everyone's just kind of relaxing doing their own thing."
Abby goes at a certain point, she realized that Samantha is running around in the kitchen
area of the apartment all by herself.
Just her in there and she's running around in the kitchen by herself.
And Abby gets this strange feeling in her gut that she should go check on Samantha.
Now looking at my notes, I don't know if Samantha is the four-year-old or the seven-year-old,
but that's neither here nor there.
But just for clarification, I'm not entirely for sure which of the girls.
But anyway, so Abby gets up and she goes into the kitchen because she hears Samantha running
around by herself.
That's not enough to get Abby off the couch, but she also just has this really weird feeling.
So she gets up to check and when she walks into the kitchen area, she sees Samantha staring
up at the ceiling.
Samantha then points towards Abby.
She's pointing towards Abby, but she's pointing past her.
She's pointing up towards the ceiling directly behind Abby.
Abby slowly starts to turn around.
What she sees, what Samantha's talking about and what Abby now sees herself is a, what
she can only describe as a floating blob of ink.
This big black puddle floating in the kitchen.
Abby says the thing was fairly large.
It was about the size of a human head.
This glob of darkness hovering in this kitchen.
But it wasn't still.
It wasn't just like an image or a stain pressed against the wall.
It was a 3D object and this blob of ink was moving.
Abby said it reminded her of the way that an octopus would swim.
It had this weird movement to it.
The way that an octopus propels itself underwater and when she looked up, she saw it quickly
move around the kitchen.
And then it completely disappeared.
It's an interesting phenomenon and it's something that you could compare to a ghost.
But what's interesting about this is if you've seen a ghost, there's generally two emotions.
I mean it's a spectrum, but generally there's two emotions.
There's a, okay, three.
There's, you don't know it's a ghost, right?
Technically that's not an emotion, but you look at something, it doesn't dawn on you
that what you saw was a ghost.
Later you find out that it was something, it wasn't really a person on the deck of that
ship.
It wasn't the maid in your room.
You're not clear of it when you see it.
The hitchhiker on the side of the road and things like that.
But if you know it's a ghost, if you're looking at something and it's like hovering in midair,
it has no legs or it's a shadow person, it's something that you can clearly see.
It is not a real human.
It might take the form of a human.
It might be a full body apparition, but you know that that is a ghost.
There's really two emotions people feel.
One is fear and the other one is curiosity.
It could be anywhere in between the two, but generally speaking that is kind of where you're
at.
You're like, wow, I'm actually looking at a ghost.
What I just saw is a spirit or something assuming the form of a human spirit.
Or, ah, and you're running away.
It tends to be somewhere in between those two.
What's interesting about this entity that Abby saw, what's really interesting is she
gives this quote about her feelings.
She goes, quote, "It scared me," which is kind of where it would start to fall into
if it was a ghost.
She does have that initial "It scared me" thing, but she goes, "It scared me," and
left the core of my stomach feeling like it was doing backflips.
I made an excuse and went home shortly after what I saw.
And so it's almost just more than fright.
It's revulsion.
You're seeing something that shouldn't exist.
Even if you don't believe in ghosts, you're aware of what a ghost is.
So if you're walking down a dark hallway in the middle of the night and you saw your
grandpa standing at the end of your hallway, assuming you don't live with your grandpa,
assuming that you're not renting a room from him, he's not supposed to be there.
He's been dead for 10 years.
Even if you didn't believe in ghosts, you could put two and two together and go, wow,
I actually saw a ghost.
Maybe there is something to that.
You could put two and two together that way.
But this is something that just doesn't make sense.
It's a floating black blob the size of a human head.
And the way she described it, again, it's not moving like a ghost.
It's not a screaming ghost head, which would be equally terrifying.
But what she was seeing, her body was reacting to something that shouldn't exist.
This was some sort of entity or a life form that should not exist in this realm.
And so she had an odd reaction to it, a physical discomfort.
And remember, it started off because she had that gut feeling in the first place.
There was an interloper.
There was something in the house.
I mean, she couldn't put it into words, but she's sitting there.
She hears a little girl running around in the kitchen and she realizes, I better check
on her.
I mean, she ends up seeing this thing.
What's interesting as we get, this is pretty standard for any sort of paranormal activity,
whether it be aliens, cryptids, ghosts, or more blobs.
She told her boyfriend about it and he didn't believe her.
He completely dismissed it and dismissed her for even thinking she saw anything like that.
And then she stopped talking about it.
She just really never ever told anyone else about it until she could talk about it anonymously
online.
It's an interesting story.
I really like this one.
We had, yesterday we talked about the little girls who were flying around the basement.
And again, this was like something that a child could see.
She could see this blob and she was running around in the kitchen trying to catch it.
It was too fast.
Some answer said.
But when you put an adult into that situation where something unreal was existing, when
an adult viewed it, who understands the rules of the universe, a child doesn't.
They're still learning all that stuff.
Whether you're four or you're seven, you still are trying to figure out like what is reality.
You understand that cartoons aren't real and things like that, but you still think that
there is magic.
You still think that Santa Claus is real.
You still believe in these things.
Even if you don't specifically believe in those things, children have a sense of wonderment.
They look at the world differently than adults do.
And what happens is, it's one of the great tragedies of life, is those senses are doled
over time.
We actually get worse at being able to perceive things like that as we get older because you
learn magic doesn't exist.
So anything that appears magical, you just completely dismiss.
You may outright not see it.
It's like quantum physics, the double slit experiment.
By simply viewing the phenomenon, you change it.
A child could be in this apartment and see something that shouldn't exist, but they don't
understand what should exist and what shouldn't.
The little girl does realize this is something unique.
This is something weird.
It's nothing she's ever going to see at an aquarium or at a museum or anything like that.
She knows there's something off about it, but she doesn't understand that this is just
impossible.
But when you put Abby in there, when you put an adult in there, she looked at it and it
disappeared.
She's looking at it through adult eyes.
It collapsed the phenomenon.
Now she knew it couldn't exist, yet she saw it existing and that collision of two different
belief systems made her sick to her stomach.
It would ruin your day, but it would start to shatter your reality in a way.
It's one thing again, if you don't believe in ghosts and you see a ghost, you may go,
"Well, I understand maybe it's just a trick of the light.
Maybe I was dreaming when I was walking around."
But at a certain point, if you don't believe in ghosts and you see a ghost and you have
a full-on interaction with it, it delivers a message to you in some sense.
You would have to accept the existence of ghosts.
If you just woke up in the middle of the night and you saw your dead grandpa standing at the
end of your bed, you could come up with a hundred scenarios to say that doesn't exist.
I've met people who are skeptical of ghosts that have had paranormal encounters and then
they simply forget about them.
We will be together, we will see something.
And then years later, this happened on my buddy Josh.
I remember we used to go ghost hunting in these large groups.
We had this really bizarre phenomenon that happened with a shadow man.
And years later, I mentioned it to him and he's like, "I don't know what you're talking
about.
I don't know what you're talking about."
I was like, "You were there.
You were there.
We talked about it immediately afterwards.
I don't know what you're talking about.
It happens.
I've seen that happen to a couple different people."
But I mean, so you do have the ability to just kind of shut down that part of your brain,
right?
You totally didn't believe in ghosts and now you've heard about ghosts all your life and
you don't believe them and now you've interacted with a ghost that you can't deny that what
you saw wasn't a dream.
It wasn't tricking the mind.
You're not losing yourself.
You're not going insane.
It was a ghost.
You have to go, "Well, then I guess this ghost existed.
I don't know if everyone else's ghost stories or anything like that."
But you have that framework, a floating blob of ink in your friend's apartment in the middle
of the day.
It really is going to mess with your head.
If you don't believe in any of this type of stuff and you see something that bizarre,
that out of the norm, it really could, at the very least it wouldn't make you sick to
your stomach.
And as you talk to other people about it and they dismissed it, you would just, it would
just be better to keep your mouth shut rather than be ridiculed.
So it's interesting because you think how many other people experience this totally bizarre
phenomenon and don't tell anyone because they're afraid of being made fun of.
It's a lot of people.
Whether or not they believed in the paranormal before or after the story or whether or not
they saw it and still refused to believe, they actually will try to forget and eventually
will forget they ever saw that.
I think paranormal phenomenon is more common than we think.
Just people don't report it because it sounds insane.
Middle of the day, a black.
She didn't even tell her friends who were there when it happened.
Oh my God, well I just saw this because she knew she'd get ridiculed.
Also I think she also felt sick to her stomach and she saw something that shouldn't exist
in her friend's apartment.
And then the really kind of creepy way to end the story is, remember it started off with
her sitting on the couch and hearing the little girl running around.
She got that gut feeling.
She should go check it out.
What would have happened if Samantha had caught up to the blob?
We'll never know.
They ended up moving out of that apartment a short time later.
The roommate got kicked out and got evicted.
But that apartment's still out there.
Is the blob still there?
Is there still some sort of weird entity, some sort of interdimensional force or creature
or whatever just floating around there?
Who knows?
But I think it is creepy what if the girl had caught it?
I mean it's possible we see so many stories of people just, like imagine if you're sitting
there and you hear a little girl running around in the kitchen and then all of a sudden the
kitchen goes quiet and you're really not putting two and two together.
You're just sitting there having fun with your friends.
You're not really keyed into all the other stuff.
And then after a while someone walks in the kitchen and there's a dead seven year old
laying there.
And of course she called 911.
The medics come out and they go, "Yeah, we don't know what it was.
We don't know why this seven year old just dropped dead.
It looks like she had some sort of heart attack."
She doesn't have any genetic issues.
It's not like she had any flaws with her heart.
But yet here we have a seven year old who had a heart attack.
And what happened was she ended up catching this thing and released some sort of electrical
discharge and stopped her heart.
It would just be a tragedy, a family tragedy.
A seven year old dropped dead, did the autopsy.
We don't know what caused it but it's obviously natural causes she had a heart attack.
Because that stuff does happen.
Science because we don't know what happened.
We can't explain it but what would have happened had she caught that glob.
Fascinating story.
Greg, let's go ahead and tashie the keys to the carbonar copter.
We are leaving behind this apartment.
It's probably still out there.
It's probably, you're like chasing, you got real dark real quick.
You're talking about a girl chasing a blob.
You're like, "What is he at heart attack?"
Greg, let's go ahead and tashie the keys to the carbonar copter.
We're saying goodbye to this apartment.
Take us all the way out to a local Kmart.
Before we get the next story started I want to do a really quick dead rabbit recommends.
Man, I saw this movie.
It was so weird the other day.
It's funny when I tell people the title they're like, "What?
Sounds like a Jason movie."
It was called "The Girl in the Crawl Space."
And based on the title you could probably figure out the plot, right?
It's about a girl in a crawl space.
I watch a lot of horror movies.
So maybe like some sort of slasher chasing a girl through a house.
The movie begins with her escaping from the crawl space.
And it's about her experience back in real life.
But it's not some dumb drama.
It is so weird.
An interesting component of it is that the script is awesome.
There are these monologues and these scenes that you're like someone really crafted these
words.
They have a lot of really cool scenes.
A lot of really good characters.
A lot of really good acting.
The cinematography is not good.
I don't think it's because the person was a bad cinematographer.
I think it's a budget thing.
The movie felt like it was very, very...
It wasn't like straight up like August Mortem Underground or anything like that.
It wasn't like Gateway Meet.
It's not one of these really bad cinematography movies.
But you know what I'm saying?
You could tell they did not have the budget to get the best cameras.
It was one of those movies that looks like they're like, "Hey, it's in the afternoon.
Let's start shooting a scene right now."
It's just weird scene to it.
So you gotta go in knowing that.
That doesn't bug me.
That doesn't bug me at all because I watch stuff like Gateway Meet and there's just
no cinematography at all.
But you have this movie about this girl.
It starts off with her escaping the crawl space and it's not a drama.
I guess it's still a horror movie with dramatic elements.
I don't watch dramas, so I wouldn't recommend one.
But it is so interesting.
It is so interesting from scene to scene that I would argue maybe 30% of the movie has zero
to do with the plot.
I've never seen anything.
It's like this movie was either made by a genius or an amateur who didn't know how good
they are because there's so much of the movie that any editor would be like, "Dude, why do
you have all of this stuff in here?
It's not moving the plot ahead at all, but it informs the characters so much.
You learn to love certain characters just because of their antics that have nothing to do with
the plot."
And the plot itself is just wild.
It's so weird.
And it keeps getting weirder and weirder and weirder.
And it got to the point where I go, "This movie is going to come down to the last five
minutes."
Like depending on how they end this movie, I'm either going to really, really enjoy this
movie or be like, "It was just okay because the ride had been...it was not going to be
bad no matter what the ending was.
I wasn't going to be like, 'This is a bad movie.'"
Because I had so much fun getting there.
The last five minutes, they did it for me.
I was like, "Didn't see it coming.
They totally set that up.
Didn't see it coming.
Bravo."
Very, very, very well-made movie, especially in the constraints of the budget as well.
The girl in the crawl space.
Just a fun...
It's not fun actually.
It's about torment.
It's about torment and what the human soul can go through.
But just great acting, great riding, twists and turns, weird stuff, weird visuals kind
of.
I mean, as much as you can have weird visuals in a low budget movie, it fascinates them.
Dead Rabbit recommends the girl in the crawl space.
So one of those movies that each scene gives you a little bit more information about a
character.
And I love that.
That's really hard to do.
You walk in a room and they'll be like, "Jag it."
Ever since your wife was killed by the Colombians, you've been on a one-man mission to take down
the cartels.
And you're like, "Okay, I mean, that's fair.
We're watching a movie.
We're watching an action film.
We don't need to know much about this guy."
The girl in the crawl space is totally different.
There's a...
My favorite character in it is the husband.
And every scene has nothing to do with the girl in the crawl space.
He has nothing to do with the plot.
And this husband, every scene, you learn something new about him.
And he is...
I mean, he's obviously like a main character in the story, which is odd because he has
nothing to do with anything else.
Each scene, a character will make a comment.
They'll have this scene and the character will make a comment and he'll be like, "Yeah,
I know."
But...
And you're like, "I didn't know that.
I totally didn't know that about him."
Someone makes a comment about him and then we find out more about him and his relationship
with other people and why this happened.
And it's a very, very just well-written movie, "The Girl in the Crawl Space."
Okay, let's move on to this next story.
You know, it's funny the way I put together this show.
It's quite slapdash.
I pick stories pretty much at random.
I try to find different stories, so I try not to do two alien stories in an episode
or two ghost stories in an episode.
Kind of mix it up.
And sometimes we see similarities between the stories.
And this is no exception.
I actually, when I was reading that last story, I go, "Hmm, interesting.
Some of the visuals are the same."
But it's a quite different story.
No children will have heart attacks in this story.
We're walking around this Kmart.
I haven't been to Kmart in years.
I don't know if they still exist.
It's a big giant department store.
Walking around, you can get anything from your Atari 2600 to a brand new LaTigra shirt.
It's fantastic.
It's a good store if you're in the 1980s and there's no Walmart's around.
Kmart.
Just just shopping them all the time, actually.
That's where we're at right now.
We're about to meet longtime supporter of the show, Hot Diggity Dane.
Hot Diggity Dane, longtime supporter of the show.
He's one of the mods on the Patreon Discord, along with Mason.
They do a great job keeping everyone else from slowly losing their mind and posting insane
memes.
They help out a lot with the Patreon Discord, for sure.
Hot Diggity Dane recently posted this on the Patreon Discord.
He said, "Episode 1005, you talked about interacting with ghosts, people interacting
with ghosts."
And he said, "Let me tell you a story about my dad.
That my dad had told me when I was just a child."
So that's the setup for this story.
We're going to meet Hot Diggity Dad, aka, we're going to go ahead and call him Michael.
I don't know if that's his real name.
If that is, it's just a guess.
Hot Diggity Dad, aka Michael, has this story.
He goes, "One day I was walking through Kmart.
When I ran into an old friend from high school, I hadn't seen this guy in years in a long
time.
He was a good guy.
We didn't stop hanging out because of any particular reason, just life.
People just kind of move on.
I was excited to see him, but life.
I got stuff to do.
It was really cool to run into an old high school buddy of mine, but I'm on my way to
do something else.
So we engaged in small talk.
Shit chat.
We didn't talk long.
It was just a couple minutes.
It was nice to see him.
It definitely wasn't nice to see him again, but I had stuff to do.
So hey, Johnny, hey, what's up?
Man, I haven't seen him forever.
Oh my God, dude, what have you been up to?
What that?
Oh yeah, no, I'm doing good.
I'm shopping to Kmart.
I'm not doing that good.
I am shopping to Kmart, but no, it's really cool.
How's so-and-so?
Oh no, casual conversation.
We have these types of conversations all the time.
He goes, "We talked for a couple minutes and then, hey, I got to get going.
Sorry, we're going to have more time to talk.
But Johnny, I hope to see you around.
Are you back in the area?
It's been years since I've seen you.
I got to run."
Oh yeah, no, it's fine.
It's fine, Michael.
It was nice to run into you, too.
And as Michael is saying goodbye to his old high school buddy, Michael goes, "I was walking
away and I looked and..."
We're just calling him Johnny.
That was the name I made up during their fake dialogue.
Johnny goes, "I turn around.
Johnny's staring up at the ceiling."
I thought it was weird.
That was odd.
He wasn't a big ceiling sterrer in high school.
It's not what he was known for.
Here we are in this Kmart and I got my stuff and I'm on my way and I look and he's just
staring up at the ceiling.
And I didn't think a lot of it at the time.
I just thought it was weird.
Like what?
You know, but I'm busy.
I'm busy.
I got stuff to do.
It's just kind of a weird way.
I think that's the conversation again.
That's not what he was known for.
If he was known for that, then I'd be like, "Oh, it's typical Johnny.
Staring up them ceilings."
I walk away and he's staring up at the ceiling as he's standing in the middle of this Kmart.
The next day, Michael gets a phone call.
Hello, this is Michael.
Working at Kmart.
I'm working at Kmart now.
That's what I do.
Can I help you with anything?
He gets a phone call and it's an old friend.
Just a mutual friend that him and Johnny both knew when they went to school together.
We'll go ahead and call this guy Bill.
Hey Bill, what's up?
How's everything going?
I haven't heard from you in a long time.
Bill goes, "You know, things are okay, but you know..."
Michael, I'm calling to deliver some bad news.
Kind of calling everyone that I know of who knew Johnny.
Two days ago, Johnny killed himself.
I'm sure that the friend went on to talk about, like, you know, this is when we're going to
have the service.
This is how the family's doing.
Giving Michael some more information, but Michael's just sitting there on the phone and he's
thinking, "Wait a second.
I saw Johnny yesterday."
Dude, are you sure?
This isn't some sort of horrible prank.
This isn't some sort of joke.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
No, Michael.
Not joking.
Johnny killed himself two days ago.
I know it's a shock.
I know we haven't all kept up, but yeah.
This is, you know, we're going to have these arrangements for him in school.
So what Michael realizes at this point was that he saw Johnny the day after he died.
The day after he had killed himself, Michael ran into him in the middle of a Kmart, had
a conversation with him.
Small talk.
And then Michael left.
And Michael, when he tells his story to Hot Diggity Dane, he says, you know, "I wish
I deeply regret that I didn't take more time to talk to an old high school buddy who, at
the time I was talking to him, committed suicide the day before."
It's an, you know, this is one of those super interesting, like what I like to call like
the day-to-day paranormal type stories.
Where obviously this was a huge event in Michael's life.
It probably did.
Stick with him.
You know, he's telling his son about it.
This is one of those stories that, sure, someone could go like, you know, you talk about a
floating blob in a kitchen, your boyfriend could just be like, "Shut up.
That's stupid.
That doesn't exist."
Someone tells you this story, even if you don't believe in ghosts, there's a certain
reverence to the "I was visited by a loved one after they passed" story.
I've met people personally who say, "I don't believe in ghosts at all."
But when people tell me that they were visited by a dead loved one in their dreams, I believe
that.
Believe in air quotes, basically, saying, "I'm not going to question that.
I'm not going to try to debunk that."
I've run into quite a few people like that, skeptics, who don't believe in the paranormal,
because there is a certain reverence to it, right?
At the end of the day, whether or not it's a dream or it's grief manifesting itself or
it's an actual spirit from beyond, you're not going to be like, "Well, actually, did
you check your carbon monoxide detectors?"
Like it's a deeply personal story.
As opposed to I was in a haunted graveyard and I saw a goblin jump out from behind a
grave.
You know, you could say, "I don't believe you."
And this is why I'm actually three goblins wearing a trench coat right now.
The goblins were with you all along, not just in the graveyard.
These type of stories people tend not to debunk, because they're really, what's the point?
It's the story of a man saying goodbye to a friend.
It's definitely a weird one.
This is one of the stories that I do think happened, not just because of who I'm getting
it from, like Hot Diggity Day.
I mean, his dad could be making it up.
Again, what would be the point?
What would be the point in terrifying your son?
We talk a lot about this.
I think this is what we were talking about on episode 1005.
It's like, how many ghosts do you think we interact with on a daily basis?
The other day I was walking home, probably like one in the afternoon, noon, something
around that.
I had just gone to get coffee at a local coffee shop.
I was walking down the street.
I heard little kids giggling.
I turned and I looked and I didn't see any kids.
My brain goes they're on the other side of that car.
They must have just gotten out of this minivan.
That's the most likely answer.
I didn't see any parents.
I didn't see any kids.
The giggling came right from the other side of this minivan that was parked on a relatively
busy street.
Then I never saw any kids.
I never saw any kids.
I think when you hear noises, when you hear people, when you see people during the day,
you assume you're going to see people and hear people during the day.
So you don't chalk it up as paranormal.
You assume you're going to see other living, breathing humans in a Kmart and maybe even
an old friend.
So it doesn't click with you immediately when you see something that's weird, that it's
a ghost.
If you hear kids giggling in the clothing racks at a department store, you assume there's
a real kid in there and he's hiding from his mom.
You don't understand that that kid's been in there for 30 years and his skeletal hands
are gripping around the center rack hoping someone will reach in so he can suck them
into his own hellish dimension.
You don't assume that.
You never even thought that that was a possibility, but it's possible in the world of paranormal.
So you have that.
You have them interacting with it, but then also just this whole idea of the tragedy of
the suicide.
When I read this story, thanks for sending it over.
When I read this story, I was thinking about it, it reminded me of those times where sometimes
we have friends that we like them infinitely more than they could ever like us.
Not saying that they dislike us, but there are some friendships that are so close, but
they're a little one-sided.
And again, I'm not saying in a bad way.
I'm not saying someone's taking advantage of you, but you can have a friend that you
really really like.
If you could, you would spend all your time with this particular friend and they just
want to hang out with you every month or two.
And I wonder if that was the relationship between Michael and Johnny.
You know, I have friends like if they stopped in to visit me, like I would just kind of drop
everything and you know, tell work, hey, I can't come in for a couple of days.
My buddy from across the country or my buddy that I haven't seen in years since high school
is here, you know, I'm going to take a couple of days off, hang out because I haven't seen
him in years.
I don't know if they would do that for me, but it doesn't matter.
I'm not saying that that's a bad friendship at all.
I'm not saying that at all.
But you know what I mean?
Like, that's just the way life is.
And I'm wondering, I mean, you imagine out of all the people that Johnny wanted to say
goodbye to and it wasn't even like he appeared and goes, goodbye, I'll never see you again.
And then he floated away like he just wanted to talk to Michael one last time.
And you know, Michael had stuff to do.
Just small talk, talked for a couple of minutes and then they passed on.
And it's just so interesting because Johnny defied the laws of death to go talk to his
high school buddy that hadn't seen him in years.
And you wonder if like this whole time Johnny was thinking like, oh, I wonder what my, you
know, my high school buddies are up to.
I wonder what Michael's up to.
And again, it sounds bad.
It's I'm not trying to say that Michael's a bad friend or anything like that.
We just have different.
Does this is you're like, no, Jason, you're clearly making like his souls floating around.
He's like, and now to see my best friend Michael and Michael's holding a bunch of groceries.
He's like, Hey, I got to go.
I'm not saying that at all.
I don't know.
It'd be interesting.
Like if the roles were reversed, if Michael died, sorry, hot diggity dane, if Michael died
and Johnny was still alive, would Johnny be one of the last people Michael would want
to see on earth?
Would that be one of the people that he slips through the bonds of the afterlife to go visit?
I don't know.
It's fascinating.
I can't think about it.
He's super depressing.
If you're a ghost and you're like, and now to see my best friend from high school.
And then you land in the middle of Kmart and he's like, Hey, buddy, yeah, yeah.
You just talk about like the weather and how families do.
And he's like, how are you doing?
And he's like, well, you know, not good.
You'll be getting some bad news in a couple of days.
But and it's just chit chat.
But who knows who knows.
I'm really putting a lot of like human emotions and human desires on this story.
It's possible Johnny just wanted to say goodbye to a bunch of people.
And this was his way of doing it.
And just the imagery, like the final imagery of Johnny looking up at the ceiling, like
it obviously that to me makes it seem like something is calling him home.
Right.
He's headed up to the afterlife.
He's headed up to heaven.
Something's calling him home and he's looking up.
He's hearing something that no mortal man hears until he's no longer mortal.
But Johnny wanted to see his buddy one last time.
I think I've leaned really heavily into the part.
I do not think that Michael is a bad friend.
You're like, wow, dude, I'm not ever recommending a personal ghost story to you.
I'm afraid you're going to read to it anyway.
I'm not saying Michael's a bad friend, but I just find it fascinating that he does come
into visit him.
And one final note before we wrap this up, I think it's interesting.
A lot of times we'll see stories where somebody goes.
I woke up in the middle of the night.
A loved one was by my bedside.
They sat there on my bed and they said, don't worry, everything's going to be okay.
And then they disappeared.
And then I found out later that was the same time they died in the hospital.
You see those stories a lot.
And I'm not discounting those stories at all.
What I find interesting about this one, it was a full day since Johnny had killed himself
that he appears in the Kmart to Michael.
And really as a ghost, he could have appeared in the middle of Michael's house.
He could have appeared in Michael's car as he was driving down the road.
He could have appeared to him anywhere, but it almost like he appeared in the place that
would scare him the least.
So even in death, Johnny was a good friend.
Johnny didn't want to scare his buddy.
He just wanted to say, hey, what's up?
Talk to his buddy for a few minutes one last time.
Then something calls to him from the beyond.
He looks up.
Michael sees him looking at the ceiling, but he's looking past that ceiling.
He's seeing sights that we will never see until we see those sights ourselves.
And then he goes home.
Johnny may not have found peace in this life, but he'll find it in the next.
And he'll be waiting in paradise for his friends to join him.
DeadRabbitRadio@gmail.com is going to be your email address.
You can also hit us up at facebook.com/DeadRabbitRadio.
Big talk is at DeadRabbitRadio.
DeadRabbitRadio is the daily paranormal conspiracy true crime podcast.
You don't have to listen to it every day, but I'm glad you listened to it today.
Have a great day guys.
[Music]