It's a sexy time special as we take a look at two extremely sexual stories.
You're like, "Oh no, Jason, what do you have in store for us today?"
Well, first off, scientists have finally created a male birth control pill that you can take
an hour before sex and you won't have kids. Is this the pill we've all been waiting for or
will it create an army of soulless goons? Probably the first one, probably the first one.
But who knows? Soulless goons may be on the horizon and then we travel to El Salvador
to take a look at a young man who was out walking one night when all of a sudden he was abducted by
aliens. On board their ship, he learned how these aliens reproduce and the answer is horrifying.
Today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host, Jason
Barber and I'm having a great day. Hope you guys are having a great day too. Hope you guys had a
ton of fun over the weekend. We got a bunch of stuff to cover so we're gonna get started right away.
First off, walking into Dead Rabbit Command is one of our legacy Patreon supporters. Everyone
get on your feet and give it up for Dave. Woohoo, yeah! Come on in, buddy. Walk on into Dead Rabbit
Command. Dave, you're gonna be our captain or pilot this episode. If you can't support the
show financially or if your name's not Dave, that's fine too. Just help spread the word about
Dead Rabbit Radio. That helps out so, so much. Dave, I'm gonna go ahead and toss you the keys to
the Jason Jalopy. We're gonna leave behind Dead Rabbit Command. Drive us all the way out to
a scientific laboratory. As we're pulling up to this scientific research center, we see throngs
of men outside going "Yay! Woo! Science! Yeah! Yeah!" and fireworks are going off. People are
overturning science cars. But for fun, they're not doing it because they hate science. Men around
the world have been given a W on this one. A male birth control pill has now been invented.
Ladies and gentlemen, we, gentlemen, gentlemen, particularly, we have now crossed the Rubicon.
We now have a male birth control pill, something we've wanted for ages because condoms are terrible.
Condoms are awful. Now, I understand why we have condoms. I'm fully well aware of that.
But from the age where they used to cut out sheep intestine to use as a condom. I mean,
it's easy nowadays. You go to the grocery store and you buy like a 12-pack. But imagine before
when you went to have sex with someone, first you had to find a sheep and then you'd kill it.
I wonder if they had actually pre-packaged condoms in like Leonardo da Vinci's time because I don't
imagine they're like "Oh, hot!" and bothered. They're like "Hey, hold on, honey. I'm gonna go out to this
nearby farm." Because I don't think it was fresh sheep intestine. I'm pretty sure it was dried out.
They're like "Oh, it's lubricated. This is fresh." I'm pretty sure they probably sold because they
did used to make condoms out of sheep intestines, right? I remember reading that a long time ago.
You're like "No, Jason, that's not right. Where'd you get your facts for a mad magazine?"
No, no, no. I'm pretty sure that they did. And I'm sure they probably sold packs. I'm sure that
you could go down to like an old-timey market. There's like a vendor selling apples and a vendor
selling straw like hay and stuff like that. And then there's there's some good old-fashioned
condom vendor. He's like "Get your cheap intestine here. Dry it out for her pleasure." And you're
like walking. You're like "I'll take 12 of those. Good sir." I don't think they had like a sheep in
the back that they were like "You know how you buy rope from a hardware store? They just keep
wheeling it out and they tell they say tell us when to stop." I'm sure the sheep were already dead,
long dead. And they probably weren't killed just for that. They probably were like making mutton.
And then someone goes "Dude, what are we going to do with all these intestines?" And someone goes
"I don't know." He looks at his sea of 12 children and he goes "Hmm, maybe we can use the sheep
intestine to keep child number 13 from showing up." I understand. And also you know the thing is,
is with condoms they're good to prevent sexually transmitted diseases. But the main reason I think
most guys wear a condom is to not get a girl pregnant. Like nobody wants super gonorrhea.
But most of us will take our chances with that. But the idea of having a kid with someone you just
pick up on a Friday night or whatever, terrifying. Terrifying. But condoms are awful. Condoms are
equally awful to having a kid that you have to take care of for 18 years. So I think the idea
for me at least for a male pill, a male birth control pill has always been like,
it's always been that noblest of all scientific pursuits. Can we invent a male contraceptive?
That is not totally lame. Now I can take a pill. Well the pill's not official yet. Well anyways,
the National Institutes of Health, they've recently discovered that this compound will work. And
the way they tested it was they gave it to mice and then they made some unpaid interns sit there
and just watch mice have sex constantly. He's like, oh man, I wish I became a botanist. This is
disgusting. All these mice. Imagine that was your job. Your parents are so proud of you that you
became a scientist and they're all, what are you studying? You're like, don't ask. Don't ask. Don't
ask at all please. They bring you, your mom brings you a nice big cup of milk. You're all throwing
one up. You don't want to be anywhere near it. They put on a biggie mouse cartoon. You're like,
imagine that your day job is to watch mice bang and then you take notes as how often
they're having babies. So some unpaid intern had to watch these mice have sex all day long and then
it turns out that when they gave these mice this birth control pill, I'm sure they gave them an
injection. I don't think they're actually trying to shove a big old pill down their mouth. The mice
would take this compound and it would slow down their sperm. So when they bang the lady mouse,
the sperm's like too lazy and stuff. They're just like sitting there and they don't make their way
up the uterus of that mouse and the scientists are like, good job, Jerry. Good job. Good job. Sorry
we gave you that lifelong fetish. Sorry we've broken your soul. But good job watching all those
mice have sex because now we know that this particular compound works and they're expecting
to start using it in people. They'll do a human trial obviously, but they said it's actually
more efficient than women's birth control because women's birth control, you have to take like 20,
25 days out of the month and then you get five tasty pieces of sugar as a treat,
but you got to take it all month. This one you can take up to an hour before sex, swallow that pill
and you'll be good to go. Your sperm will just be chilling and they won't want to swim around in
your lady friend. They tested this on the rats out of 52 attempts. There were zero pregnancies and
they said, yeah, they're just statistically, that's 100%. So they said that is even better than women's
birth control and you take the pill up to an hour before you have sex and you have sex and then
three hours after you took the pill, because they steady this all in mice,
the sperm starts moving again, it starts wiggling around underneath the microscope
and they're like, we didn't permanently sterilize these mice, like this actually will work.
Basically it turns you sterile for a couple hours. Some of them start moving after three
hours within a day, all of them or virtually all of them was a term they used, is moving around,
they're ready to run that race. And this is awesome. I mean, they've been trying to figure out a male
birth control for years because everybody knows that the condoms suck better than nothing, but
originally I guess they were targeting testosterone. They're like, maybe if we can stop
testosterone production, that will make the men less fertile and all, well, I should
say all it did. I mean, it kind of worked, but it also made them super depressed and obese and gave
them high cholesterol. So there has to be a better way, ladies and gentlemen, there has to be a
better way. And they found it. Now here's my question. I would, I would take this pill myself,
I would take this, I'm running into the mice laboratory, I'm like swallowing mice just to
get the medicine. I would take a male birth control pill just to be safe. But then I was
wondering what if you take this pill and your sperm's just kind of chilling, right? They're
sleeping. And then the pill wears off. And then you get a girl pregnant, a girl you wanted to
get pregnant. That was the last three hours I didn't love her, honey, but I love you. Let's have a baby.
And your sperm's moving around. What would be the effects of sleepy sperm?
Like sperm, like falling, taking a little nap and then waking up and then inseminating an egg?
Now I'm sure they'll test that at some point. They bring that intern back. They check Jerry out of
the insane asylum, make them come back to work. I'm sure they'll test that, like what is the
long-term ramifications? But here's my question. A mouse, does a mouse have a soul? Does a mouse
have a soul? I mean, you could argue that, you know, there's no really hard and fast answer
to that question. Does a mouse have a soul? So if you gave a mouse birth control and you made
his sperm fall asleep, and then they woke up a couple hours later, and then you impregnated a mouse,
that baby mouse or mice, because if they give birth on letters, I don't think it's just one,
they're like, "Well, name you Nick." I think there's a bunch of them coming out. They'll probably act
just like regular mice, because, you know, a mouse is a mouse, right? It's all a series of,
what's the term when they do the same thing over and over again, and it's not personality trait,
it's not a habit. That's humans. It's called, like instinct. I wonder if, like, you go, "Well,
that, okay, with this mouse, we, it was originally sleepy sperm, and now Nicholas, the mouse, is
running around this cage, and he's doing mouse stuff. He's eating cheese and running through holes,
painting holes on walls and making cat smash into him. Normal mouse stuff. But that mouse could be,
like, totally, like, his brain could be totally messed up. Like, he's still, like, something's wrong
with him. Something's wrong with his brain, but because it's like a mouse, it's just a basic mouse,
you couldn't tell. And then, you know, maybe it dies, and you do an autopsy on its brain,
and it looks like a mouse brain. So you're like, "Well, this stuff is totally fine." But what happens if,
like, humans are different. At the end of the day, I know that mice and pigs, we have all these
similarities as far as our brain structure and organs, how our organs work, and same thing with
gorillas, chimpanzees, stuff like that, primates. But if humans, I believe humans do have a soul,
would your sperm, would you being basically paralyzed as a sperm, and then you are, a couple
hours later, you do successfully conceive, right? You're swimming around and you get up in that little egg.
Would there be something wrong with you is my question. And I don't think that's something we
can answer. It may not even be something biological so much. Like, you could register that if you're
like, "That's weird. These mice that have been subjected to this medication, we gave it to their
daddy, we gave him this medicine, after a couple hours it wore off, and then the sperms running
around again. If you could measure, you could go, "This mouse is dumber than mice that's,
dads didn't take this drug." Then obviously that'd be a safety concern, because nobody wants a bunch
of dumb kids running around. But if you can't tell if it's something that is instinctively human, like a
soul, that'd be something that you may not even know. It's just an interesting question because I
thought about it and I go, "You can run all sorts of trials on all sorts of animals, and unless it
is a biological thing you can measure, you would never know until guys start popping these pills,
and then they, within that three hour time period, they have a bunch of sex, don't get anyone pregnant,
and then tomorrow they go home and they have sex with their wife, and get her pregnant.
What will be up with that baby? Maybe nothing. Maybe nothing, but maybe something. You know how
science works, it's either something or nothing, and that's nothing we can measure until we have
like a generation or two. It's interesting because I think when you're messing with the
fertility process, because it's not like women's birth control makes it so, actually I don't really
know how women's birth control work. I think it makes it so their eggs aren't fertile or something
like that. I don't know, but that's different because I don't know how it works. I can't say
it's different, it might be the exact same thing, but I'm pretty sure. I don't know. I don't know how
it works, what I'm saying is my point is that that's the same sperm. Like if she's taking this
medication, I know it messes with her estrogen levels and it basically does something,
but I don't think that, now I'm talking out of my butt, I don't think that it's the same.
If I went to sleep as a sperm and I'm chilling there for a while, then I woke up a couple hours
later, I'm still that same sperm floating around, and I'd still be subjected to doses of that medicine,
and then I'm like, okay woke up, time to go become a human. But anyways, fascinating story from the
world of science. Somewhere out there right now, a scientist is holding a pill and he's going, ladies
and gentlemen, we have it, the male birth control pill. You know what would be cool, because we always
see these in science fiction movies where like you have a madman scientist and they're like,
we have to go through all the safety regulation. He's like, no I hate safety, I joined science to
blow stuff up. Omp and he swallows the pill, makes himself the test subject, and then people
are like, we were expecting something more exciting. We thought you were going to turn into a goblin
and fly around. He's like, no it's just pill. I'm going to go home and have sex with my wife,
see if I can knock her up. Nothing super dramatic, but you should start human trials. Try these drugs
on yourself scientists. Let us know how it goes. Get these things to market as quick as you can.
Unless they destroy human souls and then you know, don't release those drugs that turn us all
into I am legend monsters. Dave, go ahead and call in the world's famous carbonar copter. We are
leaving behind this scientific laboratory. Fly us all the way out to El Salvador.
Dead Rabbit Radio, the number one science podcast in El Salvador, is once again returning to El
Salvador. We haven't covered a lot of stories on them. We did a story about a mule with a human
face that turned out not to be true. That turned out to be fake. We covered it and it probably
didn't even take place in El Salvador. There was a lot of questions of where that story took place,
but it was just a deformed donkey. I think we did another story in El Salvador, but this one takes
the cake. This one's absolutely horrifying. We're in El Salvador, specifically we're in the town of
Cuscattenesingo. Cuscattenesingo, El Salvador. It's February 29th, 1996.
And we're about to meet a young boy. He's 17 years old and he doesn't give his name in this report.
We're going to go ahead and call him Marcus. Marcus is walking through the town of Cuscattenesingo
during a blackout. Not a supernatural blackout. We've covered those before on the show and I
think that's one of my newest favorite supernatural phenomenons to investigate, but just an ordinary
blackout. The grid's gone down. It's 10 p.m. at night, so it's very, very dark and Marcus is walking
home. When all of a sudden there is a bright blue flash behind him. It's bright enough that it
illuminates the landscape in front of him and his first instinct is it's the police.
Marcus begins to turn around to see what they want.
At this point, Marcus's senses are kind of overwhelmed. It takes him a couple seconds
to put together exactly what's happened. He's in this white room or the more appropriate term might
be a white space or a white void. There's no walls. There's no furniture. There's no light
fixtures. It's just unending white. Then Marcus realizes that he isn't standing in this white
space. He's actually laying down on a bed that he can't see. It's just part of the void and then
he realizes that he can't move. He does seem to kind of have movement control over his eyes.
He can move his eyes from side to side and probably a little bit of his neck because he does start to
look around this room but definitely like he can't get up and run. He's at the very least
paralyzed from the neck down if not more. He sees protruding out of his own chest cables
reaching up into nothingness. He said on his right arm, attached to his right arm, was what he would
call an IV machine. It was unclear on what that would actually be if that was actually like it
because I know of like an IV bag and that's like on a dolly but he said it was attached to his right
arm. It was an IV machine but he's paralyzed on this table. He has this stuff attached to him and he
begins to see other figures moving around this space. He describes him as humanoids,
not necessarily gray aliens. They probably do look more like humans, more like traditional humans.
He sees these humanoids. He says they were all around five foot five
wearing white tunics with a strange emblem or insignia on the right side of the chest.
I said they weren't gray aliens. They definitely weren't humans either because they
have some alien characteristics. He said that they all had very large heads and very large eyes as well
and in the middle of their forehead there was a third eyeball protruding from the skull
even in the world of aliens. This is all particularly weird. The traditional races,
grays, reptilians, insectoids, even those tend to kind of fit certain parameters. This
a humanoid race with these type of bizarre features. A very interesting look and he's
little less interested. He's a little more terrified at this point. These beings are kind
of moving around this void. They also had goat teeth which again facial hair on aliens is super rare.
Super rare. We've come across them but they're it's incredibly rare. They had little goat teeth
but again he's not worried about that. He's not like oh this is fascinating. He's terrified.
He's paralyzed. There's stuff coming out of his chest. Little aliens with goat teeth. That's the
least of his worries. He notices other humans in this void as well and in a other particularly
bizarre observation Marcus said I couldn't tell how many of them were prisoners which makes
you think some of them were there voluntarily. Some of them just seem to be walking around.
Nothing sticking out of their chest. They weren't particularly scared. Just seem to be walking
around milling about. But he knew for a fact that some of them were prisoners
because of what he saw happen. He said he was able to look at somebody on another table similar
to his. And actually it's interesting at this point I'm wondering if now he can start to perceive
the reality. It doesn't specifically say that the white voids disappeared and now he realizes he's in
a artificially constructed UFO or anything like that. But the terminology is becoming more concrete
the more the story goes. Very very fascinating stuff right. He sees this woman sitting on a table
similar to his. And the reason why he believes she's also a prisoner is because these aliens
are slicing her in half. Right at the waist they're cutting her in two.
And he watches them. He watches these aliens pull this woman apart and now they have two halves of her.
And they carry this top half of this woman from the waist up. They carry her to where there is an
alien female. Same thing big head big eyes three of them. The female alien who's laying down on
this other table has like a hunchback has like a big hump on her back. She's just laying there on her
stomach. And Marcus watches the aliens pull the human woman in half from the waist up.
And now they're carrying this half of a woman over to the prone female alien lying on her stomach.
And as Marcus is watching and what could only be described as pure horror,
they attach the human woman's torso to the aliens hunchback.
They are now fused into one living being. They don't say that the woman was alive during this.
Generally when you cut people in half they are not alive anymore. Right? You don't need a scientist
to tell you that. But with alien technology and also because it's way spookier, right? If you cut a
person in half and they died and then you sewed them to the back of an alien, I mean that sucks for
their family. But it's not necessarily scary. I'm all yon board as the aliens are cutting me
half of the laser saw. I was like I'm gonna die anyway so I don't care. But imagine if you were
cut in half and then you were kept alive. And then sewed onto the back of an alien. You're like
Jason they're both awful. Both ways I'm being cut in half by an alien. Yeah but I think it would be
worse if you woke up and you're attached to the back of an alien. I mean there's no way we can win
this argument. It'll never happen either of us. One day I show up on the podcast and I was like
hey guys a bit of an update. I was wrong. It's actually not that bad to be attached to the back
of an alien while you're still alive. But for spookiness sake I'm imagining the woman is like
no don't put me up there. Don't put me up there. Don't put me. And then gets attached to this alien
woman. But he didn't say anything. He didn't say she was begging for her life or anything. I just
think it's scarier. Anyways you have this human woman attached to the back of this alien. Like
this alien woman had this huge hunch on her and the human woman is like fused into the hunch.
Fused into the hump I think is actually the correct term. And another interesting shift.
We do see this stuff happen in UFO encounters where things don't necessarily like make sense
time wise because as you'll learn a lot of this was he had a piece together over a couple days.
The next thing he remembers is being told by the aliens. They start to give him a little bit of
backstory. They said our race is in a state of war right now. We can no longer reproduce in the
quote original normal manner. The aliens also told him we have a bunch of eggs
that we used to reproduce. We have a bunch of eggs stored in Ilo Pango Lake.
The next thing Marcus remembers is falling.
But really he didn't remember any of that. He didn't remember any of it at all. He remembers
walking through town on February 29th trying to make his way home. The next thing he knows
there's a bunch of police officers all around him 20 miles away from where he was just two days
ago. He'd been missing for two days. He was 20 miles away at Ilo Pango Lake.
He was standing on the shores of the lake when he was found by the authorities.
And they were like where have you been? You've been gone for two days. Everyone is freaking out.
And he did not remember where he was at. It was only under interrogation where he remembered
what had happened. Now it's interesting. The story was originally covered by Dr. Luis Ilo Pes
in something called the Y Files. I actually tried looking for what the Y Files was. I'm assuming
it's like a book or a magazine. Maybe even a television show. When I tried looking for this
I almost got kicked out of the coffee shop that I was in because Dr. Luis Lopez is also a plastic
surgeon on Instagram. Whose profile page includes a bunch of naked women. I guess he does like
pubic surgery or something like that. So thanks a lot Instagram. I almost got kicked out of the
wrong customers walking by. I would have been. I wasn't able to find any more information on Dr.
Luis Ilo Pes or the Y Files. I'm assuming it was a book a magazine or a television show.
Around that time he's the guy who reported this story. It's interesting because a lot of the
words he uses he puts in quotation marks and a lot of the words are definitely like when we talk about
he says in some sort of quote unquote bed. He uses terms like that in a completely white quote
unquote space. So I wonder how many like obviously Marcus when he when the police found him he was
very confused and disoriented. It took him a while to remember. When they say interrogation
that's not in quotes. I don't know if it's that the police interrogated him and they were beating
him up and he had to give him a quick story. I don't know if the police were just really trying
to figure out where he was at and he slowly was remembering it. There's no mention here. I got
it from thinkaboutadox.com which is one of my favorite websites. It's all UFO alien encounters.
There's no mention on here of like hypnosis or you know regression therapy or anything like that.
I think he probably was the cops probably were grilling him and it forced him to remember not
physically forced him but it just forced him to remember what had happened that night or multiple
nights. Was he walking along the shore for two days or did they drop him up because they found him
at 6 30 in the morning. He originally disappeared at 10 p.m. February 29th leap year and then he
is found two days later at 6 30 in the morning so it's possible that that is they dropped him off
right before that. It's possible that he was wandering around the lake for that long. We don't
know. We do know though that one thing that he's noticed. Remember these are the only details he
remembered. After the encounter he noticed that he had strange scars on his body. Several strange
scars on his body. So we don't know if that was just from the tubes in his chest. There's no detail
of to where the scars were but this is what's interesting. Well obviously everything's interesting
about this story but it's possible that they performed way more experiments on him than they
would let him remember or that he even really wanted to admit because this alien mission seemed to be
all about reproduction. In the sense that they were telling him where the eggs were which was
weird you probably shouldn't let you probably shouldn't let a native species. You probably
shouldn't let humans know that you're breeding in their lakes. But I figured the reason
why they would is because the way I read it was this. They can't reproduce that way anymore.
Like they used to have a certain reproduction cycle and they can't do that.
So they're using humans to now reproduce.
So I'm wondering let's put our conspiracy caps on to wrap this up.
I'm wondering when you cut this is going to get pretty disgusting here.
Could you cut like he said he saw the woman cut in half.
He would refer to the top half as her upper torso that type of thing. I'm wondering if you could
cut off a woman's legs and then maintain her uterus and all that and then attach that to a back of an
alien and now the human woman's uterus is now part of the female alien's hump
and they're reproducing that way. Like the woman is just laying eggs. The human woman
is now laying and maybe they speed it up. So it's not like once a month this human woman
is putting human eggs right for lack of a better term. I know there is a better term for it but
anyways maybe they took the human woman and they took the top half of her because they needed to
keep her alive and she is now part of the alien's reproduction cycle. That's what I'm talking about.
Now obviously if you cut a woman in half you're getting rid of the reproductive part. Now maybe
they wanted to create a super warrior. Maybe in their war the alien women just are running around
with human women on top of them shooting lasers. I don't know it's probably less disgusting than
my theory but the reproduction thing would make more sense right. If you're going to chop someone
on in half and attach them to an alien you're like no Jason that doesn't make any sense at all.
The reason why I'm going this direction because they specifically mentioned reproduction. I'm
wondering if you could take the legs off of a woman but keep everything. I mean if they alien
technology you could do anything right but I mean you would figure that if you're having
trouble reproducing as an alien just use a human's reproductive cycle and if you keep the woman alive
for a couple years you're having like a baby a month. Like I don't know. I don't know alien biology.
I barely know. I barely know human biology but that's what I'm wondering. And that's also why I
was thinking that the human female was still alive. The woman was still alive when she was
attached to the back of the alien woman. It's creepy story nonetheless. Whether or not the woman
lived or died whether or not to this day she's still laying eggs for the Empress. It's terrifying
either way and you have to wonder what else they did to Marcus. Like that's the thing. We
he only remembers some of it. He was gone for days so they could have done horrific things to him.
They could have chopped him in half and then put him back together for all we know. The amount of
alien technology that's out there is astounding and the fact like even this race seems to be more
advanced than the standard grays which tend to fly around in vehicles that can be picked up on radar.
You can see them with your eyes. They have dimensions to them. You can go inside. There's all these
control panels. These guys operated and avoid. These guys had complete mastery over dimensions
and it's pretty interesting to note that even at that level of technology they're in a state of war.
So you have to wonder who are they fighting against. It would have to be an alien race that
had an equal level of technology and at that point we would just be ants watching two nations go to
war. Like the technology that what he saw you can barely put it into words and this was their
doctor's office. This wasn't even the highest level of tech they have. This is where people
were kind of milling about with goatees wearing little tunics and who are the other humans walking
around? Clones? Government officials in on it? Both? It's a terrifying story that we'll never
have so many answers to but there is one thing that we can check. What is at the bottom of that lake?
Was this just a 17 year old's delusion? Was it a lie he told so he wouldn't get into trouble of what
he was really up to? Or was a young man actually kidnapped by aliens and taken to a place that
defies explanation? Where he was told that a huge war is going on between two immensely powerful
forces. Did he watch a woman get sawed in half so she would become part of the alien
reproductive cycle? All those questions can be answered.
Whether or not Marcus is telling the truth can be answered with a deep dive into that lake.
But in the search for those answers
we better pray that we don't awaken whatever is down there.
Because out of all the alien races humans have encountered we are definitely no match for this one.
[Music]
DeadRabbitRadio at gmail.com is going to be your email address. You can also
hit us up at facebook.com/DeadRabbitRadio. TikTok is at DeadRabbitRadio.
DeadRabbitRadio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast. You don't
have to listen to it every day. I'm glad you listened to it today. Have a great day guys.
[Music]