When a young woman wakes up in the middle of the night to a strange visitor standing
over her bed, she has to ask herself, is it a burglar?
A ghost?
Or something even far more bizarre?
And then we take a look at the future of AI technology we've talked about a lot on this
show and it just keeps getting weirder.
Is it possible by unleashing artificial intelligence across the internet to create everything from
speeches to artwork, we're actually opening a portal to hell today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host, Jason Carpenter, and I'm having a great day.
I hope you guys are having a great day too.
I hope you guys are having tons of fun.
We got a lot of stuff to cover so we're gonna get started right away.
Let's go.
Walking into Dead Rabbit Command is a longtime supporter of the show and probably the first
person who's bought me the most books in my life.
I think you bought me more books than my mom at this point.
Everyone welcome walking into Dead Rabbit Command.
That's kind of me.
My mom actually bought me a lot of books.
She hasn't bought me that many.
That kind of sound like I was snubbing my mom.
Well, he's a Dead Rabbit Command right now.
Everyone give it up for Greg Gorley.
Woohoo!
Yeah, walk on in.
Walk on in.
Pushing that book cart.
Pushing on in, Greg Gorley.
Greg recently sent me a bunch of books and this is one of the most recent ones.
Fantasyland.
How America Went Haywire by Kurt Anderson and basically it's a look at the myths, the
conspiracy theories, the magical thinkers that have made up America's history.
So I'm really looking forward to this one.
Thank you so much Greg for sending it over.
You're gonna be our captain or pilot this episode.
You guys can't send me books.
You guys can't send me more books than my dear old mom who did buy me a bunch of books.
That's fine too.
If you guys can't support the show financially, I don't care.
Just help spread the word about Dead Rabbit Radio.
That helps out so much.
I guess I shouldn't say I don't care because I do care.
The people who do support the show financially, they help pay my rent and help me buy groceries.
But what I'm saying is I appreciate all of it and if you can't do it, that's fine.
That really is.
Greg, let's go ahead and talk to the keys to the Dead Rabbit Dune Buggy we are leaving
behind Dead Rabbit Command.
Drive us all the way out to a suburban neighborhood.
Driving over the sandy dunes between here and there.
I found this story post online.
It's one of the stories we don't have an exact location for.
We don't have real names.
We're gonna go ahead and call this person, this young woman.
We're gonna call her Joan.
Online she goes by the handle illustrator pretend 91.
But she said about five or six years ago, so let's date the story back in 2018.
Joan, she was living with her mother.
Joan was asleep in her bedroom and she is woken with a jolt.
One of those, I don't know, she was actually breathing every time she was having an anxiety
attack.
No, it was one of those like sometimes you slowly wake up, this was, "Ugh, I'm awake."
She was woken with a jolt and then in the darkness of her room she sees someone standing
there.
She said it was a man who had his back to her and he was wearing a flannel shirt.
And she said, "I honestly could perfectly describe to you the flannel pattern.
This shirt, for whatever reason, had basically left a scar across her memory."
She woke up and she saw this.
I guess that would be pretty memorable, right?
Waking up, there's a stranger in your room.
She wakes up, there's a man in a flannel shirt facing away from her.
She goes, "I could describe the flannel shirt perfectly, but I'd never seen it before.
This wasn't anyone that I knew unless they just happened to buy a new flannel shirt that
night and broke into my bedroom.
My friends aren't knowing to do that either."
She goes, "I'd never seen the flannel shirt before, but I could describe it perfectly."
Joan is in shock.
She wakes up, she sees this man standing in her room and she doesn't really understand
why she did this either, probably being in shock.
She actually reached out towards the man.
Now the baseball bat, not with ninja throwing stars.
She reached out to touch him and he instantly vanished.
So let's stop right here.
That's not the end of the story, but I want to discuss this.
There has been recent talk, and when I see recent, I really am talking like since 2018,
2019, of a phenomenon known as the flannel man.
This is the flannel man.
I came across it when I first, I'd never heard of it before.
I came across it on early, early episodes of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I remember the only source I could find was a podcast that had one or two mentions of
the flannel man.
A couple of you guys recommended me covering the flannel man.
Basically the flannel man is the shadow man's hipster cousin.
So he's like, "I'm not like the rest of you guys.
The rest of you nine foot tall interdimensional entities.
I have fashion sense."
So he wears a flannel shirt.
It seemed to kind of fall in that vein.
I've looked a little bit since then and I looked a little bit in preparation to the
story and that's still, there's a big post on Reddit about the flannel man and yeah,
yeah, so the flannel man, the first time I ever heard about it, the first time most people
ever heard about it was on the Strange Familiars podcast.
The flannel man.
I wanted to address that, but this goes beyond that.
This goes beyond just a man in a flannel shirt appearing out of the void.
You're like, "Jayce, why don't you, that sounds absolutely fascinating."
It does, but I mean like that's it.
It's basically just like, it's basically just an interdimensional entity in a flannel
shirt.
I love that I've, it's not the podcast that's made me blase about a bunch of other worldly
stuff, it's just when you research stuff for 30 years, yeah, the flannel, like maybe if
the flannel man like cursed people, now you can wear nothing but flannel, you're like,
"No, I have a wedding tomorrow."
Like, it needs to be a little more juicy for me.
That's my thing.
If I saw the flannel man, it'd be like this story.
This story was just the girl woke up, and this boy was just the girl woke up and there
was a strange phantom wearing flannel in her bedroom.
I honestly wouldn't have covered it.
Not because I don't think she's telling the truth, not because I don't think the flannel
man exists, he might.
Right?
There are probably enough people, enough different people have reported on it, but it's like,
I want something else.
I want that posass factor when it comes to the world of the paranormal.
Flannel man though, I did want to address that there is a phenomenon known as that,
but this is not, I mean it could be related, but that wouldn't be enough for me.
I need something a little more spicy in my paranormal stew.
A week later, Joan is once again woken up with a jolt.
She is brought out of the deepest sleep to BAM reality in a heartbeat.
In the same location where the flannel man was standing just a week ago, she woke up
the first night, flannel man standing there, just being kind of laying, just standing there,
wasn't killing anyone, wasn't possessing anyone.
She wakes up flannel man standing in her bedroom a week later in the same location where the
flannel man was.
Now there was a tripod with a video camera on it recording her while she was sleeping.
And she knows it's recording her because that little red light is shining in the darkness,
that little red light that indicates that it is recording.
So she thinks she's hallucinating.
She thinks this isn't real, which I think would be a fair assumption.
You would hope it wasn't real, right?
If you woke up in the middle of the night and you realized someone was videotaping you,
you'd be like, "Oh man, I hope it was all that old cheese I ate."
She begins rubbing her eyes.
She must just be seeing things wrong.
She rubs her eyes.
She still sees the camera.
She then slaps herself.
Slaps herself, you know, feel that sensation.
To wake her up, slap some sense into herself, the camera is still there.
She then talks out loud.
She's basically testing her senses.
It's very interesting.
You know, if she has like a checklist that she normally does every morning, she wakes
up.
But you think about it, right?
She's testing the sense of sight, hearing, touch when she slaps herself.
The camera is still there, sitting on the tripod, recording her in the middle of the
night.
Joan then reaches over and turns on a lamp and the camcorder disappears.
Joan says sense.
I don't know if she's still doing it today.
It might just be while she was living with her mom.
But she said, "After those nights, she now does not sleep in the dark.
She sleeps with the light on and that has never happened again."
Now the Flannel Man is cool.
Now the Flannel Man is into some dead rabbit radio stuff.
I'm not trash talking strange familiars.
Are there any other vikas that's covered the Flannel Man?
I just want a little bit more.
I'm not trash talking them.
Don't send your strange familiars to come get me or maybe do it and it'll be more content
for both of our podcasts.
What in the world was this?
I cannot think.
And I could be wrong, right?
I've been setting this stuff for 30 years.
We've put out over a thousand episodes.
I cannot think of a time when a ghost has manifested technology.
I'm not even fully convinced this is a ghost.
What's super interesting to me is when I first read this, and this is kind of the direction
I'm still going in, we can say Flannel Man, Interdimensional Entity.
We can say ghost because of the fact that it's appearing or disappearing.
We could probably go alien.
What I thought when I read this story, when she wrote this up, she titled it, "Has anyone
experienced something similar before?"
I titled it in my notes, "Truman Show Ghost."
Because that's what it feels like.
It feels like she somehow saw not the back rooms, but the backstage.
I mean, we could really go eight dimensions with this thing.
That what she saw, the guy in the Flannel shirt was just a guy working on the set of
the newest show, Planet Earth.
Or maybe it's a spin-off Jones' bedroom.
I don't know.
Maybe it's a teenage drama.
Who knows?
I mean, that's what I thought.
The video camera recording and the darkness, I can't think.
And I could be wrong.
Someone could probably send me an email.
Something else we've covered on the show or something I've never heard of.
I love getting stuff I've never heard of.
But I can't think of another time that a ghost has manifested.
Technology sure we can have like ghost motorcycles, ghost cars chasing people down the road.
That is a phenomenon that's reported all over the world.
But a ghost camcorder?
I mean, I guess if you can manifest a stupefaker, you have trouble manifesting it.
You have to manifest a Betamax.
But you know what I mean?
The fact that it was in, that it was recording.
Who was watching it?
Who was recording it?
Why, like to me, it was like a guy was on the set.
She woke up in the middle of the night and the guy had his back to her because he's just
like some stage hand, dude.
You know how it's how Hollywood works?
They're not allowed to look at the actors.
They all have to face against the wall.
What's the director's action?
I mean, I feel like she almost looked through reality and saw that everything was a television
show.
To me, that's actually the most logical reason.
The other option is Flannel Man is a huge pervert.
Dude, wouldn't that be creepy actually?
I just thought of that.
What if ghosts, stay with me for a second guys.
Stay with me.
A lot of ghosts are filming human porn to sell to demons.
Demons can't get enough of it.
The ghosts are like, "Well, you know, I'm damned to walk the earth for a hundred years.
I might as well make some money.
I'm tired of manifesting only pennies.
I want that money I can fold up."
So they are videotaping humans, selling it to those pervert demons down in hell.
I don't know.
I mean, I'm not even going to say that's a legit conspiracy theory.
That just popped in my head.
That's the type of stuff that pops in my head.
And admit it, that's the type of stuff that pops in your head too.
But to me, that's what it feels like.
It could be a ghost.
It could be interdimensional.
Even aliens, I don't think they're normally...
I'm trying to think of...
The aliens, we've come across stories with aliens recording humans.
The devices are not human devices.
It's always like a device that looked like a box that was recording the event.
Or he hit a box, he hit like a circle on a box and it had a holographic display.
I've never seen a great alien carting around a VHS camcorder in a story.
Fascinating though.
What was this?
I mean, obviously, could have all been a dream, right?
She's waking up in the middle of the night.
But you know, it's a paranormal podcast.
So ghost perverts selling porn to even more perverted demons.
A flannel man.
Is a flannel man would actually make sense because he's so hipster he would want to use
a camcorder.
She didn't specify, for all I know it was a red camera that this flannel man stole from
the set of Avatar 2.
She didn't actually say what type of camera was used.
But I just keep imagining that old camcorder I got from my graduation present that my
uncle stole from me and sold for a crank jerk.
Anyways, yeah, that's what I picture.
That's what I picture when my uncle...
That's a true story.
He stole my camcorder and sold it to my crank.
And maybe a ghost got it.
Maybe it's been put to good use filming young women while they're sleeping for some interdimensional
television show.
Who knows?
A fascinating story.
Like, that's a fair title for it.
Not mine.
Hers.
Has anyone experienced something similar before?
And again, this is why I think a lot of paranormal stories don't get reported because what is
this?
Do you report this to a ghost researcher?
Do you report this to a UFO researcher?
Do you report this to...
Who?
Like, it is so bizarre.
That's why I love it.
Greg, I'm going to go ahead and touch the keys to the world famous carbon helicopter we
are leaving behind Joan.
Fly us all the way out to New York.
DADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADAD
And
like
we
go
to
the world.
And
it's
a
moment.
And
it's
a
moment.
It's a
Be
sure
to
be
sure
to be
sure to be