A first-hand account from a stalker's point of view makes us wonder, "Maybe I should never
leave my house.
Maybe I should be hiding here forever."
And then we travel to Florida to take a look at a little girl out playing at the playground
of her school.
She was hoping to just jump on the monkey bars, maybe swing on a swing.
Then she came face-to-face with the race of alien flowers today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host, Chase The Garbenter, and I'm having a great day.
I hope you guys are having a great day too.
There's some reason I decided to eat a cup, like a literal measuring cup of almonds, and
then I go, "I'm gonna record a podcast and now my mouth is all dry.
It's all salty, little bits of almond everywhere."
But someone who's always willing to clean my teeth, walking into Dead Rabbit Command
right now is one of our newest Patreon supporters.
Everyone give it up for Gutter.
Woohoo!
Yeah!
Come on in.
Ooze on it.
I don't think he's an actual Gutter, although that would be really cool.
A Gutter came to life and became sentient.
The first thing it does is join my Patreon.
Gutter, you're gonna be our captain, our pilot this episode.
If you guys can't support the Patreon, that's totally fine.
It's so hard concentrating with all this almond in my mouth.
If you guys can't support the Patreon, that's fine too.
Just help spread the word about Dead Rabbit Radio.
That helps out so much.
Gutter, let's go ahead and toss you a steam shovel and a little engineer cap, a little
wooden whistle.
Everyone hop on board the Carbinder Caboose.
We're gonna chew, chew, chew all the way out of Dead Rabbit Command to a local grocery
store.
Chugga chugga chugga chugga chugga chugga chugga chugga.
Woohoo!
Woooo!
Gutter is leading us down the tracks.
And actually as we're headed there, I wanted to say this.
I talk about this website all the time on the show.
It's called Phantoms and Monsters.
It's a great website.
They put out maybe five or six articles a day.
Well, the mastermind behind Phantoms and Monsters, Lon Strickler.
A lot of you guys are aware of Lon Strickler as well.
He's written a ton of stuff.
He's one of the biggest and I feel most underrated paranormal researcher out there.
He is going into surgery.
He's having lung surgery.
So thoughts and prayers and healing energy to Lon Strickler.
If you're a fan of Dead Rabbit Radio, trust me, you're a fan of Lon Strickler.
Great, great repository of paranormal stuff.
So yeah, just I'm wishing him the best.
He's going to be out of commission for a while.
But hoping for a speedy recovery, Lon, seriously.
What a great resource.
And you know what sucks?
So I'm doing a pretty good job at it, but I'm trying to death-proof the podcast because
here's the way that...
I know that's kind of a sad segue.
Lon's like, "Wait, what?
I'm not going to die, bro."
I personally have seen entire paranormal repositories just disappear.
The Shadowlands apparently was down for a while.
The Shadowlands.net, which is, I mean, at this point, almost 15, 20 years of ghost stories,
user-submitted ghost stories, that was down for a while.
That was brought back to life.
There were podcasts that I listened to that had 100 or so episodes of paranormal content
and then the people just quit and they stopped paying their hosting fee and it's all gone.
So that sucks.
So YouTube, the video, stay up until YouTube deletes the channel or someone else deletes
the channel.
But when a podcast, once the bills stop getting paid, it gets shut down.
Like they remove everything.
So I'm currently in the process of death-proofing the podcast, right?
So getting all of my stuff up onto the Internet Archive, way back machine, all of these things
because that would suck, right?
To have all of this stuff just go away.
I obviously have backups of it, but it's a real phenomenon and it would suck if you
lose somebody like a lawn striker and wish you knew the best, wish you knew the best,
quit saying I'm gonna die.
How long would years and years and years of all those stories stay up online before eventually
the hosting service cancels it or...
It's crazy.
It's crazy to think about because this is real research.
This shows goofy, but the articles that I source are real research, real work done.
There have been times I've gone back to check something out and the website that I cited
is gone.
Not like conformers, aliens, the government is trying to suppress the information.
They just didn't pay their hosting bill.
And so there are websites that I've personally backed up just in case.
Think about it.
Docs.com, I have an entire mirror of that site on my computer just in case because that
is, again, decades of research.
Think about it.
Docs.com, theshadowlands.net, I have a backup of that.
We really want these researchers, we really want these websites to stick around.
So DeadRab radio or Deafproofing it.
So if something happened to me, the show will still be there.
I know this was supposed to be wishing Long the best than we do, but I do want it.
We have to appreciate the paranormal.
And again, I'm talking less about the show.
We're going to be fine, but all these other paranormal resources.
There's a really cool, open in the show notes.
I don't refer to it that much because it's so vast, just like Phantomas and Monsters.
I've visited the website for years, but only recently I've been including a bunch of stories
because they put out so much stuff.
There's a website called The Encyclopedia of Cryptids that's been around for years,
and then the guy said, "Hey, I'm having some problems.
I'm going to take a break," and he's never returned.
And you think, "What happens when this website goes down?"
I'm not sure if this is super depressing.
Okay, okay.
Anyways, I have a backup of that as well, but I'll put the link in the show notes.
We really love these repositories.
We really love the work you do, Lawn, and all the other paranormal researchers out there.
Hope you live a long life.
Gutter, let's go ahead and stop this train right outside of this grocery store.
And we all jump out.
We're all walking around.
Why am I putting, I'm just about to put more almonds in my mouth.
We jump out of the train.
We're walking around.
And in this store, we'll just say it's a Safeway.
I don't know for whatever reason, I picture it as a Safeway.
We are going to meet a guy named Mikey.
Mikey tells this story. This happened back on January 22nd, 2023.
Mikey walks into this grocery store.
He's a 19-year-old young man.
He's just in there to pick up a couple things, almonds probably.
When all of a sudden, he sees someone wearing a white lab coat.
Well, to be specific, at first he just says a white coat.
So I don't know, this could have been like a big white windbreaker.
It could have been a white puffy coat.
I don't know.
But he goes, he goes about this guy walked by.
I think it's implied that he's walking by in a white lab coat.
Because once Mikey sees this guy walk by in the white lab coat, he has this thought,
that's what I want to do.
That's what I've always wanted to do.
So I'm going to start following.
It's so funny when people post online.
It's so funny.
I've said my share of crazy stuff.
I get it.
I sound like a lunatic when I talk about my personal stories.
I sound like a lunatic when I talk about anything.
But definitely the stuff I've been through.
Shadow men and seeing demonic clowns and all that.
I'll put those episodes in the show notes, but it was what people post online.
He said, he started following this guy wearing this lab coat in the middle of this grocery
store.
And you're wondering why.
You're wondering why he would do this.
He said, quote, I casually kept following this person around because my goal in life
is to be either a doctor or a scientist.
And to be fair, I think the only thing that connects those two is the white coat.
I don't think there's anything else that connects a doctor or a scientist.
I guess medicine is science, sure.
But anyways, anyways, that's not the craziest part about this.
He said, quote, I casually kept following this person around because my goal in life
is to be either a doctor or a scientist.
Not specific of biologists.
I don't know.
Social scientists don't wear lab coats.
Okay, I'll stop getting hung up on that.
Okay.
The goal in life is to be either a doctor or a scientist.
So seeing someone in a white coat caught my attention.
And you could go, okay, this guy's 19 years old.
He's probably in college or going to, hopefully, if he wants to be a scientist.
He's like, nah, I'm just going to try to figure it out on my own.
I got a test tube set from the hobby shop.
I'm a scientist.
He starts following this guy around.
So maybe I've walked up to a news reporter one day.
She was having yogurt.
And I was like, hey, I want to do news.
I want to do news.
I'm walking up to her.
I'm like, I want to do news.
Tell me the news.
I want to do news.
I said, hey, I've seen you on television.
You do a lot of good work.
I like to get into-- I was a journalism student at the time.
And I told her that.
And I said, she's like, yeah, swing on down anytime.
You don't hook you up in an internship.
I never went.
I was too busy out punching people in the face and smoking weed to actually do anything
back then.
But I mean, I could see that.
I could see people living that life, like wanting to be a scientist or a doctor, and
then seeing a doctor and be like, hey, how did you become a doctor?
They sit you down.
They go through five or six years of everything they've learned.
You're like, oh, I just came in here to buy some almonds.
But now my brain is overwhelmed at everything about doctoring.
You can figure that.
Maybe he's going to walk and be like, hey, what laboratory do you work at?
What laboratory and/or hospital do you work at?
He's like, what?
He sees this guy walk by in a white lab coat.
He's always wanted to be a doctor or a scientist.
So then he starts following him.
And you think maybe to ask him, how did you get into that?
But this goes on for a while.
And here's the thing.
He's following.
And Mikey's following this guy through the store.
And at one point, the guy turns and Mikey realizes that it's his doppelganger.
Mikey now sees an exact copy of himself in a white lab coat shopping in front of him.
Well, technically, he's been stalking him.
So he'll always be in front of him.
But he catches a glimpse of his face and he goes, listen, we have the same skin tone,
the same height, same glasses, same face as well.
I probably would have started with that one if I was describing it.
I go, yeah, I saw my exact double.
We had the same skin tone.
They're like, what?
A lot of people have your skin tone on.
Don't let me.
Don't interrupt me.
We also have the same glasses.
They're like, what?
Those glasses look terrible on you, Mikey.
There's the worst fashion choice you've ever made.
You would say, I saw a doppelganger out of the store.
He had my exact same face.
That's how you would start it off.
You wouldn't start being like, we had the same watch.
It was a swatch watch.
And you didn't look alike.
You have the same face.
And he goes, we were exact duplicates except weights.
He was a little bit chubbier than I was.
Apparently, Mikey's kind of a thinner guy.
So when he got a look at this guy's face and realized it was exactly him, he decided,
Mikey goes, I got to follow this guy around even more.
Now remember this kind of lab coat just walked into buy some stuff.
You buy some science stuff.
He went to the test tube section.
He's buying baking soda and vinegar.
He's like, oh, all my science shopping done for this week.
He now realizes that not only is this a guy in one of two of his dream jobs, right?
He's employed as either a doctor or a scientist, but also it looks just like him.
So now Mikey goes, I want to follow him around even more, which is kind of hard because there's
already stalking the guy.
I didn't know I could want to stalk someone even more.
If you think that the mystery has been solved, if you think that this story has already had
too many twists and turns for you, and you're like, Jason, seriously, if there's one more,
I'm going to have to shut off the podcast.
Mikey realizes that this doctor slash scientist shopping looks exactly like him, same skin
tone and everything.
Then this would be a little trippy.
I guess I'm kind of, this would be weird because Mikey goes as I'm watching him put
stuff into his, at this point, Mikey's not even shopping anymore.
He's just like walking around, stalking this guy.
He goes, as I see my doppelganger putting stuff into his shopping cart, he is buying,
he's buying some Coke Zero.
And Mikey goes, that's my drink.
He says it right in his ear.
He pops up from behind a display.
He's like, that's my drink.
Mikey goes, I drink Coke Zero too.
He thinks that he doesn't say it.
I wish he had.
That would be so funny.
If you're a guy in a lab coat, you're walking around, you don't realize you're being stalked.
You go to grab some Coke Zero and all of a sudden a guy jumps up and goes, that's my drink.
And imagine the shock as a doctor scientist to turn and see your doppelganger.
You see a skinnier version of you with no white lab coat, jumps out from behind a display
and goes, that's my drink.
I wish that's how the story ended.
Unfortunately it doesn't.
You would think, oh my god, my cloning experiments worked.
Mikey goes, that's my drink.
And he realizes this has to be my doppelganger.
I would say that's pretty good evidence too because nobody drinks Coke Zero.
That stuff's disgusting.
I'll drink a warm Diet Coke before I'll drink a Coke Zero.
And I've tried drinking a lot of Coke Zero.
It's gross.
I know this episode's sponsored by Pepsi, but anyways Coke Zero's disgusting.
No, I'll die on that hill.
It's gross.
Anyways, Mikey's like, this has to be me.
Who else would possibly drink this sludge?
So now the white lab coat dude is getting into line to buy his groceries and Mikey is
getting in line too.
The tension.
You can feel the tension building.
And what happened was by the time they started ringing up Mikey's items, the lab coat man
had already got all of his stuff rang up.
And Mikey's like, totally sweaty.
He's like, oh come on man, hurry up.
Hurry up, cashier, hurry up.
Don't you see that guy looks just like me.
Cashier's like, what are you talking about?
He's being extra slow.
He's part of the conspiracy.
He's like, oh, you can't know that that cloning facility exists.
Price check on this 98 cent peanut butter please.
He's like, he's like, he's like, he's like, he's like, he's like, he's like, he's like,
he's like, he's like, he's like, he's like, he's like, he's like, he's like, he's like,
he was spitting game or what, but I mean, technically there are two girls, there's one
for each of us, you don't have to be selfish, we look alike. And yeah, so anyway, I've done
that, I that, but see, that wasn't creepy, that was just me sitting down next to a total
stranger. Keep saying, look at us, look at us, like it's a Rick and Morty sketch, but
this took place back in like 2002. So yeah, you could say something, don't, don't be
creepy about it. You could say, Hey, isn't that weird? We look alike. Also, nice jacket,
what do you do for a living? You don't have to be creepy about it. You don't have to rub
your body up on them. But the other people were saying, just don't be creepy, just don't
follow people around at a grocery store. But this raises an interesting question. Because
what if this was, I mean, the most likely explanation was this just guy that looked like him, right?
Not a doppelganger, not a clone or a time slip or something. But what if it was, what if
this guy, the reason why he was wearing his lab coat, because he was a time travel scientist
that he finally, I've always wanted to go back in time and see what Safeway was like in the
year 2023. So he goes back in time and he's walking around or maybe not even that dramatic.
Maybe he just maybe he doesn't know he's in an alternate reality. Maybe he leaves the
laboratories like turns on the device and he's like, I need to go buy some go zero. It's all
warping realities like, ah, and then he doesn't realize anything's different. And then he comes
to our reality. And everything's exactly the same as his reality, except there's two of
him here, or one of him already here. And it's interesting that the one in the lab coat was
heavier, because that would show like different lifestyle choices. Like one in an alternate
reality, our reality, the guy just consumed nothing but Coke zero. He's like, literally,
that's my drink. That's all I drink. But then you have a guy coming from an alternate reality
is a little heavier set. And maybe he came here and he goes, wow, what's this Coke zero?
In my world, everything's exactly the same, but we don't have Coke zero. I'll try this out.
I'm going to take this back to universe 1197. And he does. That's why he disappeared.
Technically, he didn't say he disappeared at the end. He might be just going to find him.
I'm sure he just got his car and drove away. I don't think it was paranormal. But it is
interesting. You could look at it. Here's the thing. This was a crazy guy stalking a doctor
slash scientist through a story. That's the most likely explanation. But in the world of
the paranormal, you do have to open it up. And in that situation, had he said, hey, dude,
we look like that could have cued in that lab coat guy to turn and go, we do. We do.
And also, I've been experimenting with alternate dimensions, which at that point, you would
think that's the crazy guy. The stalker's like, oh, okay, see you later, buddy.
There's a interesting story in the lab for one of two reasons. One, proof of alternate realities
or time travel or to prove that you're not safe anywhere. Wherever you go, there's a chance
that someone's stalking you. Even in a restaurant, even at a Chili's restaurant, you might be
enjoying a delicious meal with two beautiful women all of a sudden a dude rubbing his face
against yours going, don't we look alike? Don't we look alike? I wasn't drunk either.
I was totally sober. I was just sitting in a Chili's with my friends. Don't we look like?
Gutter, let's go and attach you to the keys to the carbonar copter. We're leaving behind
this Safeway. I wonder if he'll run back into them because if it's like a neighborhood grocery
store, that's definitely possible. Maybe we'll get a part two. All the stories we cover on
this show, that's the one we get follow up to. Gutter, I'm going to attach you to the keys
to the carbonar copter. We're leaving behind Safeway or whatever grocery store this was.
Flias all the way out to good old Florida. [imitates car engine]
Specifically, this takes place in Dade City, Florida. The year is 1924. We're about to meet
this little girl named Evelyn Wint. She's seven and she's a student at the Holy Name Convent
School. I'm assuming that's like a private religious school. I don't think in any way shape
or form that's a public institution. But what's interesting about this school is apparently
there is a science building on the campus. So think about that for a second. I went to a
private Catholic school for a couple years and there's like a science classroom. Sure,
this place had a science building. That's not the main point of the story. It's not,
isn't that weird? Have a nice day. But there's a science building on campus. So they must
have been doing some pretty advanced stuff. Like, I don't know if it's K through master's
degree. I don't know if they just had the middle school students or the elementary school students
or whatever doing some advanced science. But there is a science building on campus.
But Evelyn's not worried about that. Evelyn's playing in the playground. She doesn't care
about all those beakers and stuff hanging out in there. She wants to have some fun. So she's
out on the playground and all of a sudden she gets blinded by a bright light and as her
vision slowly returning she sees a strange egg shaped object sitting on the grass in
front of her. I wonder if this was a Saturday because there's no other witnesses to this.
I don't know if she was just playing in this playground all to herself. But she does see
this egg, this egg shaped object and it opens up and emerging out of this egg is a bunch
of...this story's weird. Like, I'm just kidding. Trying to put it in a word so I can tell it to you.
It's so weird. Little girl all alone blinding white light, egg, it opens up and outpour dozens
upon dozens of aliens. She says there's so many she can't even keep count. They keep moving
around as well. They're walking around, they're bumbling around. And if that wasn't weird enough,
which I think that definitely would classify as weird enough. Hey, today I was at school
on a Saturday of all things and an egg showed up and these aliens popped out. The way these
aliens looked, this was in 1924 too. So people, I mean you are aware of science fiction, Jules
Verne and H.G. Wells, stuff like that. But it definitely wasn't a mainstay of pop culture.
Out of this egg hop, not just regular old aliens, but robotic flowers. She said, and this is the
only way that a kid could really put this in words, they look like cartoons. She goes,
they look like cartoons. She goes, their bodies were mechanical the way that their joints fit,
the way that they were kind of walking around. They weren't like 10 soldiers, but she could
look at them and tell that their bodies were artificial, artificially constructed. Their
heads were like a flower, like a sunflower, right? Daffodil or something like that. Where
the center, the bud of the flower is where there were two eyes and a mouth. And then you
had the big yellow petals of the flower all around its head like a lion's mane. Like something
like that. She's seen a cartoon. She sees these robotic flowers jump out of this egg. There's
so many of them and they're moving around so rapidly she can't keep track of them. And
she says, to put things in perspective, probably should have explained this earlier, it's not
the size of an egg. The ship is in size of an egg and all these little guys popped out.
But the robots, she is taller than these robots. She's taller than the flower robotic aliens.
But not by much. She's not towering over them, but she's definitely taller than them. So
we'll say maybe a foot taller. So if she's probably seven years old, I don't know, three
feet, these things are maybe about two feet tall. And there's a bunch of them. Your picture
like, "Wait, I was picturing an egg this whole time. He kept saying an egg showed up. I was
picturing it all small. They're two feet tall, bro. You've got to describe this stuff." So
I can picture it. You're like, "Vanity, you have to pause the podcast." You're like, "Wait,
what? What's going on?" He's just casually talking about, "The robots and ghosts, oh yeah,
they hop out of an egg, but they're two feet tall." You're like, "Ah, anyways, two feet
tall. Big egg." It was an egg-shaped object. I only called it an egg once or twice. I only
explicitly said it was an egg. It was an egg-shaped object. It was big. I hope you pictured a big
one because otherwise you're super confused right now and you have an egg. Anyways, these
two feet tall, I don't know if they're exactly two feet tall, but they're a little bit shorter
than a human girl, a seven-year-old girl. They're walking around. You're all paused and you're
all looking it up. You're like, "Just read the article at this point, bro. I'll see you
tomorrow." These robots get out and they're walking around and they're carrying something
that Evelyn, she used two words to describe it. She would say the word "device," but she
also felt that it was a weapon. She felt like it was some sort of cannon. Now, a child in
1924 would be aware of that. Obviously, at seven, she probably would have been alive at
the tail in the World War I. I think she probably would know what a cannon was. If she was seven
in 1924, she would have been two when the armistice was signed. She's like, "I'm getting breastfed
and I'm watching the news." I actually know it would have been like a newsreel. But anyways,
she knows what a cannon is. She's seen some Betty Boop cartoons, at the very least. It doesn't
explicitly look like an old-timey cannon, but she just gets the feeling that this is a
weapon. One, because it kind of looks like a cannon. And two, because the aliens, these
robot alien flowers, tell her that they're on a mission. They are here to destroy the
science building. It's interesting to note that before they telepathically told her this,
probably should have mentioned this earlier. Probably should have mentioned, I don't know
why. All those almonds go into my brain, all those carbs. Before they told her that, she
saw them moving this cannon around. And she realized, "Hey, they're smaller than me and
that thing's pretty big. I'll help them. I'm going to help them move that." And she
walked over to pick it up, and it was super heavy. It was too heavy for her to lift. Even
though these robots were smaller than her, they were able to carry this cannon around.
And then she gets a telepathic message, and they tell her, "We're going to destroy the
science building." She's like, "What?" They said that there was work going on in that building
that they were specifically sent here to prevent or just destroy. The aliens go, "Yes, we are
going to destroy that building. We're going to stop the work that's being done in there.
It cannot be allowed to continue. We need to put it into it, so we're going to destroy
the building." Now, we don't want to destroy the building. If the work stops in there, we'll
let it stand, but we have this cannon just in case. They didn't use the word cannon, but
if you point a device at a building and say, "We're going to stop what's going on in there,"
even if we have to destroy the building, it's a cannon. And then they ask Evelyn, "Hey,
will you help us? If you'll help us stop it, that'd be grand." And she, you know,
earth first, right? She says, "No, I'm not going to do it." And it's such a weird story.
This is such a bizarre story. It started off weird. It ends weird. They go, "Will you help
us destroy the building?" And she said, "No." They've just unloaded this laser cannon or
whatever it is from their egg-shaped ship. There's a bunch of women there. They're all
two feet tall. They just unloaded this cannon. They say, "Hey, will you help us to stop the
work or destroy the building?" She says, "No." They then go, "Ah, just screw it." The
aliens are like, "Ah, whatever. We were sent here on this mission to stop the work going
on in that building, but whatever." They pack the cannon back up into the egg-shaped ship.
They all climb back on board, and one of them says, "Evelin, we're going to come back in
35 years, and we're coming back for you." Now, I don't know if it was like sinister
like that. I would take that as a threat. Or the flower robot, like the last one everyone
was on the ship, goes, "In 35 years, we're going to come back for you, Evelyn." You're
still kind of creepy, right? But I don't know if it was a threat or if they wanted to visit
her again. I don't know. But all the aliens, she doesn't know. Now, the reason why, like
we don't know what the tenor of that conversation was at the end, or really any of it, right,
is that the story took place in 1924, but Evelyn did not start telling this story until 1974.
So, 50 years had passed. Now, definitely enough time had passed that the aliens said we'd
be back in 35 years for Evelyn. She never encountered these things again. Ever.
Which is an interesting note. We'll put a little pin in that for right now, but the aliens say
we'll be back in 35 years. She never saw him again. Now, it's 1974, and she begins telling
the story. I think it gets originally reported like a local newspaper or a UFO author picks
it up. And you'll find this story, it's not super well known. It's not a super well known
story. It's known as the Dade City Flowers. And you'll see it on obscure UFO websites.
And when I'm reading it, I go, "It's an interesting story. It doesn't make a lot of sense." Because
the aliens didn't do what they came here to do. They lied. They said, "We'll come back
in 35 years. They didn't show back up." There's not a lot of primary sources on this story.
Like, I'm reading just random websites. I'm reading obscureinlegend.fandom.com and ufology.patrickgross.org.
I'm not saying those are bad websites, but they're definitely not mainstays in the paranormal
community. I mean, those sites are good enough that I found this story on there, but I go,
"Is this story real?" Yes, generally, when you find a story on fandom.com, I don't know if it's
some D&D character, which has happened before. I was redoing an episode on demons once, and
I was like, "Oh, dude, this is totally awesome. And what? This guy can get killed in the level
18 sword? I can't wait to talk about this." And I did all this research and I realized it
wasn't dudes homebrew campaign. This is a true story. I didn't end up doing the episode,
but I found all these really cool demons, and I was like, "Oh, this is going to be awesome."
And it was just like, made up. Totally made up. What's interesting about this story? Again,
we never know how much of this stuff is true. I wasn't able to find the original news article.
I just find people talking about an interview that Evelyn Went gave. So I tried doing a little
more digging. And interestingly enough, this isn't proof that this story happened, but it's
more proof than we get for a lot of these things. I found Evelyn Went's, or A. Evelyn Went's,
obituary in Florida, born July 14th, 1918, so that would put her around six years old,
depending on when the story took place. We just have the year 1924. That's around the
right age, right? She died. She lived to be 100 years old. She died June 25th, 2019. I
think she probably did give an interview at some time telling this story. So I think that
she existed, and I think she really had this encounter. I don't think this is something
completely made possible. We've been fooled before on this show, but I do believe that
she had this encounter. I do believe she gave an interview with the local newspaper, and
I do believe that it's out there. It's one of those stories that's so weird it doesn't
gain traction in the UFO community. It's so bizarre. It's an interesting thing. They said
they'd be back in 35 years. She never saw them again. And it's interesting too, because
she said the science building never blew up. The science building stayed there. I'm
wondering too, like again, there's so many details we're missing. I couldn't find the
initial news report, but they could have been aiming it off campus. But, like, "Jayson,
are you making me picture this school differently? Come on, just wrap it up." The science building
may have been a couple of blocks away, for all I know, but she goes, "The science building
never blew up." She goes, "It did eventually fall into disrepair and then just kind of
crumble away." You guys know, like, a house or a property that's not being kept up. She
goes, "Eventually, I guess they just stopped doing science. It was the science of keeping
a building in one piece." And they shut down. She goes, "It just fell into disuse over the
years and just kind of, you know, it wasn't anything dramatic." Which again is an interesting
thing. These aliens traveled from somewhere, whether it's as simple as crossing dimensions
or crossing the stars to stop the science going on in that building, and then they're just
like, "No, never mind." I mean, the story is just so interesting. They just leave.
Fascinating story. And again, it's too weird. That's why I love to highlight this stuff,
because we always talk about the grays and these huge conspiracies with reptilians and
these galactic federations and all this stuff. And while that stuff is fun and it's part
of UFOology, we can't forget the weird ones either. You just can't. I mean, if you're going
to look at this as a phenomenon, you've got to look at the weird stuff too. You've got
to look at stories about robotic flowers walking around on an intergalactic quest to destroy
a building, and then they just forget it. "No, never mind. We're just going to leave."
Because that's part of the phenomenon as well. It's a fascinating story and we can't ignore
it. As weird as it is, it is part of the phenomenon. It's just a reminder of how weird the world
can actually be and its stories like this that just remind me of all the unknown stuff
still out there. All the obscure stories out there so we can continue to discover the world
of the weird. And let's do it together. Lawn, wishing you the best. Everyone out there.
I wish you the best health as well. DeadRabberRadio.com is going to be your email address. You can also
put us up at facebook.com/DeadRabberRadio. Tiktok is @DeadRabberRadio. DeadRabberRadio is the
daily paranormal conspiracy true crime podcast. You don't have to listen to it every day. I'm
glad you listened to it today. Have a great week guys.
[Music]