Is it possible that the real reason we've never found Bigfoot is because we're looking
in all the wrong places?
And then close encounters of a canine kind week continues as we take a look at another
story of what happens when dogs encounter aliens.
When three kids are out in the middle of nowhere with their two loyal dogs, they figure they
are just going to have a nice time in the outdoors.
Little do they know that their dogs are about to encounter an alien life form and the climax
is drenched in blood today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Carpenter and I'm having a great day.
Hope you guys are having a great day too.
Hope you guys are staying warm.
I have to shut my heater off to record these episodes and the temperature immediately dropped
to 15 degrees.
It's miserable in here.
I could probably put on more clothes but nah, it's too much work.
Someone who always loves putting clothes on me though, someone who always loves dressing
me every single day is one of our newest Patreon supporters.
Everyone give it up for Snail Eyes.
Woohoo!
Yeah, come on in Snail!
Snailies!
He's not an actual Snail.
His name is Snail Eyes.
It's far more disgusting.
Snail Eyes, you're going to be our captain, our pilot this episode if you guys can't
support the Patreon.
I totally understand.
Just help support Dead Rabbit Radio by getting the word out.
That's another way you can help the show grow.
Snail Eyes actually met Snail Eyes in person.
They came out to meet me at the UFO Festival last year and good old Snailie is going to
be at the Oregon Ghost Conference.
I will be giving a speech on March 24th at 6pm.
You guys want to meet me and listen to me, which you already kind of do both right by
listening to the podcast, but March 24th, 6pm at Seaside, Oregon, the Oregon Ghost Conference
I'm giving a presentation, Why Are There No Fat Ghosts?
So hopefully I'll learn how to pronounce the word ghost correctly before then and it'll
be a lot of fun.
I should come out.
There's a bunch of other speakers, vendors and all of that stuff, but I can't wait to
do it.
Snail Eyes will be in attendance.
So no salt, no salt allowed.
Snail Eyes, I'm going to go and entach you the keys to the hair hydrofoil.
If you guys want to see what hydrofoil looks like, I'll point to a picture of a 1980s G.I.
Joe toy.
I'm not entirely for sure, but we're in a hydrofoil now.
Snail Eyes, let's go ahead and leave that rabbit command and foil us all the way out
to Florida.
I don't even know what they sound like.
Is this a new vehicle?
I know we have the hair hovercraft, the hair hydrofoil I guess is new.
We're going all the way out to Florida.
The Joes are quick on our heels trying to destroy us, but we get out to Florida specifically.
We're headed to Placida, Florida and we're off the coast.
We're not in the town of Placida.
We're actually in the Gulf of Mexico.
The year is 1970 and it's late.
It's late evening.
And in the Gulf of Mexico, you had two fishermen fishing from their boat, throwing their rods.
You know that noise that fishing poles make?
Little hook floating in the water.
Fish are looking at it.
You like that theater of the mind?
You're like, "Wow, Jason, I felt like I was right there."
And I know what hydrofoil looks like.
And you don't.
They don't make that noise.
Anyways, fish looking at bait, looking at worms stuck on hooks and stuff like that.
That's not the weirdest part of the story.
That's normal.
That's what we just call fishing.
These two fishermen are on this boat and all of a sudden, they see Bigfoot.
They're like, "Whoa, kid, this is weird, right?"
They're off the coast of Florida.
Florida had, they call it the skunk ape down there because it's super smelly because it's
living in swamps.
Bigfoot's in general are fairly smelly creatures.
A lot of times you smell them before you see them or even hear them.
They smell like rotting flesh or dried dung.
That's just Bigfoot.
So you can imagine if there's a variation called a skunk ape.
Smells worse than just the normal old Bigfoot.
But whether or not we're Bigfoot hunting or skunk ape hunting, you don't expect it
to be in the middle of the Gulf of Mexico.
It's not on its own boat.
It's not stuck on a rock going, "Help me."
No.
Which would be quite the quandary, right?
Would you help Bigfoot or in a fishing boat and you came across them sitting on a rock?
I think the humanity in us would say, "Of course I would help Bigfoot get off that
rock and onto my boat."
But again, this isn't 8 foot tall Harry Monster.
I don't want an 8 foot tall human on my boat.
I hate boats.
I'm always afraid they're going to tip over.
So if I saw an NBA player on a rock in the middle of nowhere, I'm like, "Sorry, bro.
I'm already scared enough I'm on this boat."
He's like, "I haven't eaten in days."
I was like, "I don't know.
Catch some more clams.
Here's a fishing pole.
I'll radio in for help."
But he's not on a rock.
They're in the middle of the Gulf of Mexico and these two fishermen see Bigfoot swimming.
He's just swimming in the Gulf of Mexico.
And obviously these two guys are braver than I am.
They're in a boat for one.
When they see Bigfoot swim by them, they look at each other and they're like, "We've got
to follow this guy."
Now he's not swimming towards the coastline either.
He's swimming away.
These witnesses said that they followed Bigfoot for 29 miles.
For 29 miles and they're like, "Okay, that's enough."
We for the once in a lifetime saw this cryptid that people have been searching for for over
100 years.
But we have obviously just been swimming for too long.
They're like, "We better return home."
They actually don't say in the report if he kept swimming and they just pulled away or
if he drowned.
I don't know.
He might have.
They don't say.
They followed him for 29 miles and then they stopped.
Did they lose sight of him?
Who knows?
These two guys do, but they didn't tell us.
And what's interesting is as they're watching Bigfoot swim away from the coastline, he's
29 miles away when they finally just lost sight of him or just gave up.
One of the fishermen turned to his buddy and said, "Yeah, this isn't the first time I've
seen this."
And the buddy's like, "Wait, what?
This is old hat to you?"
Following a swimming Bigfoot and the other dude goes, "Yeah.
One time I saw a Bigfoot swimming underwater."
So what is with this?
What is going on?
Why is Bigfoot swimming through the Gulf of Mexico?
You would go, "Jason, this obviously, obviously, maybe it's not actual, maybe it's not actual
Bigfoot.
This can't, this doesn't fit anything in with Bigfoot lore that we know of.
Bigfoot is the giant guy in the woods walking around using squirrels as toothbrushes and
porcupines as toothpicks and just walking around.
Those are the only two things he does.
That's why we've never found him because we're like, "No, that's gross.
We're not going to do that."
He walks around the woods.
He sometimes throws rocks at people.
Stuff like that.
Why would he be swimming?
Actually, I wonder because I know Gorillas can't swim.
I learned that fact watching Tim Burton's Planet of the Apes.
I actually fact-checked that.
I was like, "Wow, that's true.
Gorillas can't swim.
They couldn't get to marking marks, spaceship that crashed in a lake."
I was like, "Wow, that's fascinating.
Thanks, Tim."
But I wonder if Bigfoot can.
I wonder if having big feet would help you swim.
He would probably be a trade-off, the 30 pounds of back hair, probably make it difficult
to swim well, but with the big feet.
Like Michael Phelps, he has some big old feet.
It looks like a dolphin evolved and then put on a speedo and started swimming around.
He's not a freak.
You're like, "Oh, really?
That's what it looks like."
You're only going to picture.
You're all disappointed.
You're like, "Oh, man, yeah, he does have big feet, but his skin's not great.
He doesn't have a blowhole."
A bit of an exaggeration there, Jason.
Bigfoot might be a powerful swimmer.
And it would make sense.
This could be one of the reasons why we can't find Bigfoot, because we're looking in the
wrong places.
You're looking in the forest.
If you're in Florida, you're looking in the swamp.
We never thought to check the lakes.
We never thought to check that he might be taking a dip.
But if you think that story is weird, there's another story of maybe this is why we can't
find Bigfoot.
I do have to say too, let me give credit.
I found that story of the swimming Bigfoot on, think about it, docs.com.
They got it from a website or a book magazine.
I don't know what this is, but it's called Sliksters.
If you can't trust the source that has Slikster in it, who can he trust?
Sliksters skunk apes sightings.
So this would be like a local Florida repository of Bigfoot/skunk apes stuff.
If you think that's weird, there is another even weirder one of Bigfoot sighting.
This is one that's kind of gone a little viral, and we don't have any information on it.
It's an un-dated, unsourced image.
There was someone going by the initials of AR.
They said at one point they were in an undisclosed location.
I know this is super vague and it's so bizarre.
You're like, Jason, someone just made this up.
But someone was in a place and they looked up, they looked up into the sky and 75 yards
off the ground, they see Bigfoot.
Not because he's that tall, they're like, wow.
Inflation's got really bad.
Bigfoot needs to be 75 yards tall just to get our attention.
No, Bigfoot is sitting on three red balloons.
You're like, Jason, come on, man.
It's clearly made up.
Hold on.
Let me finish before he decides that this is made up.
Bigfoot is sitting on three red balloons.
So they're giant balloons floating there and they are described as either glowing red or
a metallic candy apple red.
But he's sitting on these three balloons.
I just looked over at my notes again.
The person who saw this goes, okay, maybe it wasn't Bigfoot.
I probably should have checked my notes closer.
He goes, well, it was a tall, hairy man.
It looked like Bigfoot.
It's possible he was just wearing a suit, a hairy suit or hat on a hairy cape.
It should be hilarious.
So I was like, hey, let's fake one of those Bigfoot sightings that everyone's talking
about.
We'll do that.
We'll go on the woods, put footprints, fake footprints, walk across the freeway in a furry
suit.
And his buddy goes, that sounds like a great idea.
But what if we did it on balloons?
He's like, what?
Yeah, he got a Bigfoot suit.
It's super authentic.
If you see it, you'll think it's actually Bigfoot.
But instead of, I don't know, walking through the forest, we'll just fly around in the suit.
It'll be the best fake Bigfoot sighting ever.
So this is fake.
They're doing it wrong.
But anyways, Bigfoot or a man in a Bigfoot costume is floating through the sky.
He's sitting on these red balloons and the balloons traditionally have strings hanging
down.
So this guy's watching these balloons float by.
Bigfoot is not hanging from them.
Like he's floating away.
Like he was a clown who put too much helium in his balloons.
He's sitting on top of them.
And then the rope of the balloons are hanging down.
And the rope is tied to the-- the rope is where Bigfoot's floating on the balloons.
The rope, the string from the balloons are tied to the corpse of a dog.
There's a dead dog floating through the sky held aloft by balloons.
Bigfoot's sitting on top of it.
It's one of the weirdest Bigfoot sightings I think we-- I've ever heard of.
We've covered Bigfoot's getting in and out of UFOs.
I almost feel like I've covered this one before as well.
It's hard to tell if I've covered this one because we've covered some crazy ones.
I wasn't able to find any proof of it.
But if I did, then this is one of the few times I don't mind covering it again because
it's so weird.
And if I didn't, it's just absolutely bizarre.
And AR, what's interesting is he-- the witness, like again, there's this kind of viral meme,
this image that's going around.
And it says, listen, I was driving and I saw this guy floating by Bigfoot, dead dog, red
balloons.
And it started-- I was headed towards Smith Road.
It specifies the road they're on.
So I think there's a longer account somewhere that I could not find unless I already covered
it.
Unless I already covered this story.
But he's driving down a very particular street and he saw this guy floating-- this Bigfoot.
I don't know why you say this guy.
It's actually a cryptid floating around on these balloons with a dead dog.
It was a black and white shellty.
He just went out into my dog.
He's having a black and white shellty.
I came out one day and he wasn't there.
There was just like a balloon string on my yard.
I was like, what?
Jack, Jack, where are you?
He should have just looked up.
If your dog ever goes missing, you look up in the sky.
People are like, hey, dude, aren't you going to put up some missing dog flyers?
You're like, nah, who he'll float by eventually.
This guy's following him in his car AR.
He's following Bigfoot on the balloons in his car.
And once Bigfoot realizes he's being followed, apparently he changed the directions of the
balloons.
The Bigfoot tries to lose the witness so he actually flies back the way he came and the
driver wasn't able to make a U-turn quick enough.
I don't know how fast these balloons were flying around.
But you would have to say that any speed is too fast for Bigfoot to fly at.
Now, like I said, we've covered stories where Bigfoot has gotten out of UFOs and Bigfoot.
I've covered stories of people turning into Bigfoot.
There's a lot of weirdness involved in the phenomenon that gets left out, honestly, because
we're so-- there's the two camps.
Most people believe, if you believe in Bigfoot, that it's a biological creature out there
that we can eventually capture and steady and maybe communicate with.
Another group of people believe it's an interdimensional thing.
That's what I believe.
I don't believe that.
I believe that it can-- obviously it's a biological form.
You could shoot it.
You could kill it.
But I don't think it evolved alongside humans.
I don't think it's a-- I think it's more of a-- I think it's more-- there's something
more paranormal to the phenomenon that it's not just like, "Oh, we just haven't found
this guy in-- we could.
We could document its breeding habits and all this-- some perverts out there in the
woods with this logbook."
He's like, "Oh, he was particularly randy tonight."
I don't think that.
I don't think that it's a biological entity.
But I do believe that there's something to it.
Anyways, maybe that's one of the reasons why we can never find it.
That's the interdimensional belief, because it's able to slip in and out of realities.
But even-- I'll put all those episodes in the show notes.
We've covered all sorts of crazy, cool stuff about Bigfoot.
But again, I would have never thought to look up, right?
You hear tromping through the woods and you smell that rotten egg smell and you're like,
"Oh, I think-- I think either Bigfoot's here or somebody ate it."
It's how it goes bell right before this camping trip started.
And then you hear a roar.
And then like a rock comes flying at you.
And you're like, "It's Bigfoot, everybody.
It's Bigfoot."
And then you're looking for him in the forest.
That's where you would look for him.
You're having all these telltale signs.
He's flown above you.
I'll tell you this.
There's not a Bigfoot researcher worth their salt.
The Bigfoot researchers that you see on like animal planets-- the fact that they're on
animal planet.
But they would not acknowledge this to even be possible.
Maybe the swimming story.
But if you're like, "Hey, you go out squatching lately.
You're talking to one of the hosts of the show.
You broke into his house.
You have him tied up to a chair."
You're like, "Hey, did you go squatching lately?"
He's like, "Yeah, yeah.
Let me and my family go."
I'll answer whatever questions you want, you weirdo.
And then you go, "Did you ever look up?
Did you ever look up?"
And he's like, "What are you talking about?
Please."
I'm so scared.
I'm so scared, man.
Cheryl, look up.
Is that what you want?
I don't know why this turned into all of a sudden.
I don't know why.
I just didn't say you were asking him something at a convention.
I don't know why it became you breaking into his mansion and tying up his family.
But anyways, I think they'd be like, "No, that's absolutely ridiculous.
Bigfoot does not float on balloons with a dead dog unless you've kidnapped my family.
And if that's what you want to hear, if that's what will get you to leave my family alone,
sir.
Bigfoot's on balloons.
Bigfoot's on it.
How many balloons do you want him to be on?
He's on that many balloons.
Please, please let us go."
Fascinating Bigfoot escape stories, swimming away, floating away.
Who knows what other things he can do?
Maybe he's really good at digging tunnels.
Have you ever looked underground?
Have you ever looked underground, Mr. Bigfoot Researcher?
Fascinating stuff.
And I'll put all those other Bigfoot episodes in the show notes because what a blast we've
had researching that furry man.
Snail eyes, let's go ahead and toss you the keys to the carbonicopter.
We're leaving behind this animal planet host house.
We've let all of his family members go because he answered the questions correctly.
Take us all the way out to Texas.
We're headed back to the year 1914.
There's like a guy playing a banjo outside of a store.
We're walking in.
We're here to get some supplies, some cornmeal, some grubs.
We're going to have a picnic.
That's all we're going to eat.
Cornmeal and grubs and maybe a head of lettuce.
And we're walking out and we're like, man, it sure is cool living in 1914.
We're in Farmersville, Texas.
We're watching the sun rise over this beautiful landscape.
We're like, part of the animal and grubs.
This sure is country living.
And we're about to meet three country boys.
That's how they describe themselves.
We're two and a half miles outside of Farmersville.
It's about two and a half miles west of Farmersville.
It's 10 in the morning.
There's a trio of children.
They are headed out to this field to chop cotton.
I had to look that up.
I didn't know what that was.
It's where you thin it out.
It's the first process.
When cotton's growing, you kind of get rid of all of the gunk.
They're like, who threw all these grubs?
Who buried our crops in cornmeal?
What type of ecological terrorist was there?
You go and you cut down all the weeds and the weaker cotton
plants, the ones that aren't going to produce.
Because back then, your chores were part of your economic life.
Nowadays, it's like make your kids wash the dishes.
Back then, if your kids didn't do their chores,
your family didn't make money.
So they get these three kids to go out there.
We're going to meet Silby, Silby J. Latham.
And that's the main person who's telling the story.
Silby J. Latham.
And he goes, I was about between 13 or 14 years old.
That's where he's placing this.
And then he had his two older brothers, Sid and Clyde.
And they're walking around with their hose.
They're going to go out.
They're going to chop down this cotton.
And they bring with them their two loyal dogs, Bob and Fox.
[BARKING]
The dogs are barking as the boys are walking two and a half miles
out to do their chores.
And he said, we're sitting there.
We're chopping this cotton, probably whistling.
And the dogs are just kind of wandering around.
The dogs are no use in the cotton chopping thing.
They just brought them out there to keep company.
Probably wrestle the dogs on their break.
They let their dogs wander around otherwise.
And all of a sudden, they hear--
it's an interesting term.
Silby said that he heard a deathly howl erupt from the distance.
[SCREAMING]
And it's funny because these are country boys.
It's the year 1914.
Imagine in your reality, you're sitting in your house.
And all of a sudden, your dog emits a noise
that you've never heard of make before.
And you can only describe as a deathly howl.
You're going to pause the Netflix movie
and get up and be like, you OK Ralph?
Ralph, what's going on out there?
These kids are kind of like, what?
What's that?
Dogs are making some weird noise.
So they just saunter on over.
They don't even see the dogs at this point.
They're just kind of walking on over.
And honestly, Silby and Sid are taking their sweet time.
They're walking super slow because whatever.
It's the country.
We hear weird noises out here.
Clyde gets to the dogs first.
And so Silby's walking and he sees his brother Clyde kind of
stopped and he's looking at something.
And this is a good--
like they've now walked about 75 yards.
There's the same distance of a Bigfoot balloon.
They've walked 75 yards from where
they were chopping the cotton.
There's this fence row there, which
is a fence that divides two uncultivated plots of land.
I had to look that up too.
There's a fence row.
They're in the middle of nowhere,
but they're still separating their land over who owns what.
They get to this fence row.
Well, they don't actually.
Silby and Sid are taking their sweet time.
Clyde is at the fence row now with these two dogs.
And they hear Clyde yell out, "Boys, there's something in there.
It must be something kind of bad."
Silby and Sid are just still strolling over there.
Their brother's freaking out because he realizes
that these dogs are losing their mind.
These dogs are barking so loud at something
and Clyde can't figure it out.
His two brothers are just staring at each other.
His two brothers are just kind of wandering closer and closer.
And that's when they hear Clyde go, "It's a little man!"
So that's going to make you walk a little bit faster, right?
You hear the sound of dogs barking.
Your brother begins shouting about a little man nearby.
And Silby and Clyde finally get there.
And Silby goes, "I walk up and I see Bob and Fox.
And they're just losing it."
They're barking and doing that little thing
where they're jumping from side to side,
but not in an excited way, almost like in a way
of trying to intimidate something.
They're kind of digging their hands in the dirt
and doing all that weird stuff that dogs do
when they're ready to go.
And all I see-- I mean, I see the two dogs.
I see my brothers.
But standing against the fence row is a little man.
He goes, "The guy was about 18 inches tall.
And he was either all green
or he was wearing a skin-tight green suit."
He goes, "I couldn't really tell."
He goes, "There's either the type of suit
that a frogman would wear, like a diver."
He goes, "This 18-inch man was either a little green man
like you hear about."
Well, it's funny.
In 1914, the idea of a Martian was still so new.
You read about it in the newspapers.
We had newspaper hoax about Martians and stuff like that.
But these boys are a country.
They're not getting Jules Verne's novels shipped to them.
They're also not idiots.
You can obviously tell that this isn't normal.
There's an 18-inch man here who's green
or wearing a green skin-tight suit.
Sylvie goes, "He also had a wide-brimmed hat."
This little 18-inch man had a wide-brimmed hat
that was also the same color as his skin or suit.
And he goes, "It wasn't on his head.
It was actually kind of on the back of his head."
He goes, "It almost looked like he had taken the hat off,
but it was part of the suit.
It was just sitting there, kind of just there."
And he's looking at this little guy.
He says, "He is completely ignoring the dogs and us.
He's just looking north."
This 18-inch man is kind of just staring off,
even though he's towered over by all of these things, right?
Even the dogs are three, four times his guy's height.
Now, you would think that if your dogs were barking
and emotionless, for the most part,
they don't really say that he's like completely frozen in time,
but he's definitely not acknowledging anything that's going on.
If your dogs are barking at a motionless 18-inch man,
you would go, "Maybe that's not real.
Maybe that's like a toy or a doll."
Because it's not moving.
It's not reacting to the fact like I would be terrified
if two dogs ran up on me and I'm bigger than them.
But he's just looking north.
He's not acknowledging any of this going on.
And you could obviously start to think,
like, maybe we should pick him up.
Maybe we should figure out what this is.
But here's the thing.
And this is why we don't have a ton of details over whether or not
this was a suit or whether or not this was a skin,
whether or not the hat was always a fix to the back
or that's how this little guy wore a hat.
We don't have any of that information
because Sylvie, everything that he saw,
everything when he walked up, he had to take in all of that detail
in about five seconds, maybe 10.
Because according to Sylvie, he goes,
"Once me and Sid walked up and I looked down
and I saw that guy, once all three of us boys were there,
Bob and Fox ripped that thing to pieces.
They were worked up into such a frenzy that the second
the two other boys got there and Sylvie just had a moment
to really take in what he was looking at,
these dogs shredded it.
They took it into their jaws and were ripping him limb from limb,
tearing the head from the torso.
Everything, they annihilated this little guy.
And what's interesting is that you would think it's just a toy.
It was a little statue, whatever it was,
except for Sylvie's description of what happened.
And he said, this was his quote,
"Blood and guts went everywhere.
The blood was red and the guts looked like guts looked.
And that's super interesting because again,
if it was a toy, it'd be like,
"Oh, they tore it apart. There's a bunch of stuffing."
But this was a biological entity.
It sounds like such a simple statement to make,
being like, "Yeah, they ate it in like real blood shot out of it."
And it had intestines and a little heart and things like that.
But that does set it apart.
Whatever this thing was, it was a totally ignoring them.
It was a living, breathing thing.
"Blood and guts went everywhere.
The blood was red and the guts looked like guts looked."
This is so funny. He continues his quote.
And he goes, quote,
"We were all just country as hell and didn't know what to do.
The dogs just chewed him to pieces after they killed him.
And we just went back to hoeing."
That's fascinating and that's honest, right?
You have these kids in the middle of Texas in 1914.
They've probably heard about, you know,
fantastical creatures and fairy tales or nursery rhymes and things like that.
But it's the middle of the morning.
You have a job to do.
You just saw the dogs just shred this guy to pieces.
This tiny guy and they're like, "Okay, like what are we doing now?
I mean, the dogs are eating it.
The dogs are eating the remains of this thing.
Let's just go back."
This is one of those stories, like a story we covered yesterday,
the Dade City Flowers, where the person knows that something odd is happening,
something not normal just occurred.
But it's a different time.
They just go back to doing their job.
They go back to chopping cotton.
But again, they knew there was something weird about this,
but not so much that they're like, "Let's analyze the pieces.
What is this a piece of a skin or a suit?
Let me taste it."
That's synthetic.
That's synthetic plastic.
The dogs pretty much ate everything that they could.
And the boys went back to hoeing.
Now again, though, after they were done with their chores,
because that was their job, that was not just them out there for fun,
when they went back home, they go, "Hey, Ma, Pa, guess what?
You'll never believe what happened.
The dogs ate a little man.
The dogs ate a little 18-inch man, and the parents didn't believe them.
The parents were like, "What are you guys talking about?
Did you guys just chop in the cotton?"
"Yeah, we did, but the dogs ate some."
"Well, wash your hands and get ready for supper."
Sylvie said that day we went back out there a couple times.
We went back to that fence row, and we just looked around.
But after that day, we never went back to the fence row.
We never investigated it further.
It's a fascinating story on so many levels.
On the one level you have, this, you know, Sylvie, Sylvie J. Latham, has this story.
And it's something weird that happens to him, and I can almost guarantee he remembered it.
He always thought it was weird, but that happens in 1914.
When he's older, think about it, he was 13 when that happened.
By the time of the UFO flap, right, in the 1950s, when it really kicked off, 1947, to be specific.
But in the 1950s and 1960s, at that point he would still be like, "I know I'm bad at math, but in his 60s himself."
Wait, no, that doesn't make sense.
He was 13 in 1914.
And then, whatever, the point is that he would be an adult, and you'd be hearing about little green men.
You'd be hearing about these invaders from Mars, you'd be catching stuff at the local movie theater, and he'd be like, "Oh, that's what that was."
Like, I don't know, I'm just country's hell.
I just thought that was something that happens sometimes, that a little man will show up occasionally and get torn to pieces by dogs.
And then, he would go to the Lord, these dogs ate him.
They ripped him to pieces and spread his blood and guts everywhere and then enjoyed the meal that they had just created for themselves.
And Sylvie, it would take Sylvie time to put that into context and be like, "Oh, that's what that is. That's what they ate, was an alien."
A little green man.
Now, we don't use the term "little green man" anymore.
It's used as a pejorative nowadays to kind of dismiss people.
There are accounts of, they're not super common or not as common as, you know, the FBI and the CIA tried to make out when they would disparage these people through the media, right?
Oh, you believe in little green men? They're anal probes, all that stuff.
All of that stuff was not necessarily misinformation, because some of it happened, but mal-information.
It was put out by intelligence agencies to dismiss UFO sightings.
I mean, like, that's not even a conspiracy theory at this point. We know that's true.
They used the media to mock people who saw this stuff, and so people would stop reporting it.
But then you have people who saw something like before you even knew of the term "flying saucer."
Before, I mean, back then, the term "alien" meant someone from another country.
So you have that, but it's so-- like, what was this thing?
The idea that he was looking off into the distance and he wasn't acknowledging what was going on--
there's two ways to read that. Well, there's three ways. One of them is that it was a doll or a toy.
Someone had made it as a joke. It's kind of a super specific joke.
They placed this little doll out in the middle of nowhere.
Maybe some boys will bring some dogs along.
It's possible that there-- when I read this, because I read this a couple of times to get ready for this,
it's possible that what the creature, what this alien was doing, was not-- it wasn't aware of what was going on.
If it was coming-- this is going to sound, you know, probably a little esoteric, a little hippie-dippy,
but imagine it is moving from one dimension into ours, and the process isn't complete,
and he's still trying to figure, you know, like-- I don't know.
It just sounds like I'm making stuff up, but I was thinking that, like, what if he's crossing a barrier,
and normally he would be able to blink out or run away or something like that,
but in this case he's frozen because this process is still going on.
That's possible. What I actually think is happening, which is far more depressing than that scenario,
is I think this little guy realized that he was done.
He knew he wasn't getting out of this situation, and like a man at the gallows,
with his eyes fixed on the beautiful blue horizon, he's looking-- he's taking in one last look before he dies.
Like, he doesn't want to face the threat. He knows it's an inevitable death.
There's nothing he can do at this point.
He's just looking at the one peaceful thing he can see, because he has these giant humans towering over him,
these vicious dogs, right, all up on him just barking and ready to devour him, and he just is looking at nature.
He's just ignoring that, and he realizes I'm not getting out of this, but I'm not going to--
I don't want my last sight to be drool dripping off of an insane dog's jowls.
I'm just going to look-- I'm going to look north, and I'm going to think of better times and happier times
and my few remaining moments of life. I think that's what it was. I think he was resigned to death.
That's a fascinating story. This is Close Encounters of the Canine Kind Week.
On Monday's episode, we covered two dogs. It's actually interesting. It's such a similar setup to the Monday's episode.
Two dogs who encounter a UFO and the effect that that had on them. Today, we covered two dogs taking down an 18-inch man.
It wasn't a fair fight. It totally wasn't a fair fight, right? This guy was ill-equipped for country Texas life.
But on Friday, we're going to cover one more case of Close Encounters of the Canine Kind.
When a man and his dog go hiking high up in the mountains, the final showdown between man's best friend and humankind's worst enemy will begin.
But that's in a future episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
DeadRabbitRadio@gmail.com is going to be our email address. You can also hit us up at facebook.com/DeadRabbitRadio.
TikTok is @DeadRabbitRadio. DeadRabbitRadio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast.
You don't have to listen to it every day. I'm glad you listened to it today. Have a great one, guys.
[Music]