Is there any truth to the conspiracy theory that child protective services is not a government
organization to protect children?
It's actually a front for the shadow people.
Guess who came up with that theory?
And then it's prom night.
And while at first glance it may look like a standard ghost story, this one may finally
answer the question, when you die, do you get to choose where you hunt?
Today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Carpenter.
I'm having a great day.
I hope you guys are having a great day too.
I hope you guys have some awesome plans for the weekend.
We've got a ton of stuff to cover so we're going to get started right away first off
walking into Dead Rabbit Command as one of our Christmas livestream contributors.
Everyone put on your protective gear because in flies be.
Woohoo yeah come on, come on be fly.
It's a Dead Rabbit Command.
Be you're going to be our captain, our pilot this episode.
If you guys can't support the Patreon or support the show financially, I totally understand.
Just help spread the word about Dead Rabbit Radio.
That's another way you can help the show grow.
And then let's go ahead and take a look at today's Fan Art Friday submission.
This is from Micah, Patreon supporter Micah.
This image is actually from the original Discord that we had years ago when we shut
down because people spammed it with Diary-a-Porn.
So I talk about that in another episode.
I don't remember what episode it was.
I think it was like a classics episode.
But anyways, if you're like, "Well I want to hear about that story."
I'll put it in the show notes.
But that was the old.
Micah wasn't behind that.
Micah was like, "What did I get wrangled into that one?"
That's why we shut down the old Discord.
We have a new Discord for Patreon members.
But anyways, let's spend less time talking about Diary-a-Porn and more time admiring this
awesome artwork.
I love it.
I love it so much.
So thank you very much Micah.
Bee, I'm going to go ahead and toss you a little captain's hat.
Let's all hop on board the bunny battleship.
We haven't used this one a long time.
It might actually be new.
It might be a new vehicle.
We go ahead and pull this battleship out of Dead Rabbit Command.
We're going to sail all the way out to a bad neighborhood.
We've never done a buddy battleship.
I was like, "What noise is that?
What noise does a battleship make?"
Blowing stuff up.
We're headed out to a bad neighborhood.
We've made it exceedingly worse.
Methanphetamine use and the shadow people.
There's such a close relationship between these two.
Methpsychosis, they say, actually isn't.
What do I say they say in the meth head?
Say this.
No one else does.
But someone who's an aficionado of methamphetamine, they'll go, "Methpsychosis, it actually allows
you to see through the dimensions."
It's not that we've stayed up for three days straight.
It's not that we have formaldehyde pumping through our veins.
It's a superpower.
People actually fight these five cops at once.
You can see the true reality.
You can see through reality when you're on methamphetamines.
Now, I'm not saying that as a fact.
I'm not saying that as a scientific fact at all.
But you will be hard pressed to find a meth veteran.
Maybe a newbie.
He's like, "I don't believe in all that shadow people stuff."
And the people around him as they're passing the pipe, they're like, "You will, young man.
You will."
You can find accounts of these stories all over.
I remember at one point on Reddit, I was subscribed to the meth subreddit.
Because I thought it was funny.
I was always finding these great stories.
But I had to unsubscribe because I'm also subscribed to all these paranormal subreddits.
I lost track of who was talking about what.
So many people on the meth subreddit talk about things that are just casual paranormal
activity.
Ghost and shadow people and seeing things and paranoia, conspiracy, they're out to get
you.
Although in this case, they're not being gangstalked.
There's actually gangs stalking them and law enforcement trying to crack down on them.
Well, I came across this one.
This is a standard title for something in the meth subreddit.
It goes, "Meth opens a portal to another dimension inhabited by the shadow people."
I wonder, it's funny, because I know of paranormal researchers who are like, "Dude, you really
haven't researched the world around us until you start doing DMT or ayahuasca or drinking
a bunch of cough syrup."
We're preferably all three at once.
I wonder how many, because part about being a paranormal researcher is you're constantly
pushing the limits.
You want to know the unknowable.
You want to experience that which no man was meant to experience.
I wonder how many people who started off as paranormal researchers started doing meth.
Because they're like, "This is just helping with my research, honey.
I can stay up for three days straight."
You know how many articles I can read?
Plus, I vacuumed the entire house and the neighbor's house.
Anyways, in response to this statement, and meth opens a portal, and the person who posted
that said, "I want to hear about your shadow people stories," we're going to meet someone
who goes by the handle, "Inaire Nadine Raika."
I'm just going to call you Nadine for short.
Nadine is posting on the meth form, and here's the thing.
Every show often, a meth head is right.
Everybody can guess something eventually, and to be fair, they do spend a lot of time
staying up, thinking about stuff.
Most of the time, it's just how to fix a blender, and how to get a blender in the first
place so they can fix it.
They know how to improve a blender.
They came up with the best blender idea ever.
But every show often, I'm not going to say that people who do meth are always wrong.
They're right every once in a while, just like all of us.
Nadine tells the story.
Nadine goes, "Listen, it was 11.30 in the morning one day.
It was a Tuesday, and I was walking through a bad part of town with a friend.
Now, I wasn't familiar with this part of town.
I'm not normally out.
I'm an upstanding citizen.
I usually go to church five days a week.
But this particular day, I was high on meth at 11.30 in the morning on a Tuesday.
I'm walking through this neighborhood with my buddy.
And walking towards us is a little boy in a school uniform, and he's wearing a backpack.
Now this kid was about five or six years old, and using meth mathematics, I was able to figure
out, "Wait a second.
How was a kid that young walking down the street at 11.30 a.m. on a Tuesday?
This kid should be in school.
He definitely has on a school uniform.
Why isn't he in school?"
So Nadine looks around and she realizes there's no bus stops in the area.
The processing power of Nadine, fueled by meth I am quite envious of, she sees this little
boy walking down the street.
She scans the area.
There's no bus stops around, and there's definitely no school bus stops around.
So how did this kid get here at 11.30 in the morning on a Tuesday with no school buses
around?
But he wasn't alone.
This little boy wasn't alone.
He was with an adult.
He was with an adult man.
So you may think, "Dad?
Uncle?
Baseball coach?
Bus driver?
He's looking for his bus.
He's like, "Where did I put it, kid?
You were the last one on it."
But something else, something else sparked off in Nadine's mind that made her highly
suspicious of this duo walking towards them.
She said that they were not, she goes, "I'm not racist.
Not racist."
But they were not color related.
I think that she's implying, or basically saying, "One is black and one is white."
And that makes her suspicious, but she's not racist.
She's not racist.
But she did find it suspicious that at 11.30 on a Tuesday morning, walking in this not
very good neighborhood, is a five-year-old boy in a school uniform, but no school buses
around, and an adult who is not color related to him makes her very, very suspicious.
And she begins to feel like something is wrong here.
So she turns to her friend.
Now let's do a little interlude here.
You may go, "Jason, that actually is kind of suspicious.
I always look to make sure people are color related."
It is suspicious that kids not forget the color related part, but the rest of it is suspicious.
Even if they're both the same race, it is weird what are they doing out here?
Walking through this bad neighborhood.
Fine.
We can have that discussion.
We can come over to my house at three in the morning.
We'll smoke a little bit and we'll talk about it for 18 hours.
But to let us know, okay, so remember she's with her friend.
When she turns to her friend and goes, "I think there's something suspicious about that."
Her friend, who knows Nadine very well, says, "Just shut up!
Shut up!
What are you talking about, you big weirdo?"
He goes, "Mind your own business.
Just mind your own business."
So the two groups pass each other.
Nadine and her friend and the non-color related duo, they just walk past each other.
Well, it's only about 30 seconds that Nadine has now passed this kid and this adult.
And she's really freaking out.
She's basically full on panic attack because she realizes that kid is probably in danger.
And she says, "I wanted to chase them.
I wanted to chase them.
But I want to grab the kid.
I want to startle them.
I would just run full speed towards two strangers."
But she goes, "Listen, I want to run up and grab the kid or start screaming."
I would simply ask if everything was okay.
I would look at the boy, look at the adult, look at the boy again to make sure that they're
not the same color.
And then I would say, "Is everything okay?"
And if it's nothing, it's nothing.
What if it's something?
I love this quote.
I love this quote that she left.
You're like, "Jason, when do we get into the shadow people?"
You're all waiting for a paranormal story.
You're like, "Oh man, is he tricking us?"
She has this quote.
She goes, "Perse...
This is worrying.
Do you want to do methamphetamines?
Like, I'm not an advocate of it.
I've seen it destroy people.
It landed my cousin in prison for murder.
Not a fan of methamphetamines, but it could always be worse.
It could always be worse, right?
Let me read this quote to you.
"Personally, as a mother myself..."
So then I'm wondering, like, so where are her kids at?
Maybe her kids from a school bus going to school.
It's 11.30 at Tuesday.
A mother.
Anyway, think about it this way.
She's using her free time to either walk around that neighborhood or post on Reddit.
Both are equally horrifying.
"Personally, as a mother myself, that would not bother me.
As long as you don't reach for my child, pull out a weapon of any kind or come too close
then someone asking if everything is okay, that would not offend me, anger me, or cause
me to do anything other than let my happy-go-lucky toddler..."
So she does...
I was wondering how old this kid was.
My life...
She has a toddler at home.
She's walking around this bad neighborhood.
She actually goes, "Oh yeah, my toddler's strapped in my back right now."
And let my happy-go-lucky toddler answer for himself, "I don't believe that for an instant.
I believe that shadow people exist.
I do not believe if you walked up to this woman with her toddler and you go, "Is everything
okay?"
She would claw your eyes out.
She 100% would claw your eyes out.
No parent would put up with that.
I don't think.
Especially if they think you...
If you thought something untoward them.
That's a word, right?
Something that was bad about them.
I don't think.
I was like, "Oh, thanks for asking.
Yeah, no, I'm not kidnapping this kid."
See, we're the same color and they're like, "Oh, okay."
I think that you would...
I think most parents would get offended.
I think if the parent was a habitual meth user, they're most likely to get offended.
But anyways, she says, "Listen, if someone came up to me and asked me if me and the
toddler were okay, I would be totally fine with that.
If they asked me where my toddler was right now, I don't have the answer for that.
But I'm sure he's doing fine."
So she decides, "That's what I'm gonna do.
I'm gonna turn around and I'm gonna just ask if everything's okay."
Now, remember, this whole thought process is only taking 30 seconds.
And in that time, she also reinvented the envelope and discovered a new way to build
a bicycle.
But she turns around.
They're gone.
The man and the kid are gone.
At that point, Nadine completely panics.
She realizes that something bad is gonna happen to this kid.
She throws her backpack to the ground.
Hopefully the toddler wasn't in there.
And she takes off running.
She turns around the corner.
They're nowhere to be seen.
She believes so heavily that something bad's gonna happen to this kid.
She begins knocking on random doors in this neighborhood.
She said she knocked on every door within a thousand foot radius.
Then she says that was only three doors.
So I don't know if this isn't like a rural part of the country.
Thousand foot radius.
She knocked on three doors.
One didn't answer.
One only spoke Spanish.
And she goes, "I only know how to say pants, dog, and milk in Spanish."
Which I don't know.
I don't know how to say that in Spanish.
She has a leg up on me.
At what point in her meth-infused life did she go, "Okay, at some point, some Spanish
guy may ask me about milk."
Leche.
Actually, I do know that word, leche.
Anyways, she said she also knew a sales pitch that she had practiced in Spanish.
Again, why?
We don't know.
We don't know any of these details.
Finally, when she knocks on the third door, a woman and a child open the door.
And Nadine starts going, "Hey, have you guys seen anyone in this neighborhood?
An adult and a little kid?
Their colors don't match.
Their colors don't match."
And then, where's another door?
It's like, I don't know anyone in this neighborhood that matches that description.
There's no other kids on the block.
And then I can only assume the woman quickly shut the door and bolted it.
And the story ends with Nadine walking away and saying she was always going to hate herself.
Had she not waited 30 seconds?
Had she reacted the way that she should have originally running around the neighborhood
yelling at people who don't match colors?
Maybe she could have spared this kid some torment.
So while that might be the end of Nadine's incredibly eventful Tuesday, Tuesday mid-morning
adventure, and I'm sure that she had many more crazy stories that happened just that
day.
Maybe does come up with two really good theories.
Well, let me rephrase that.
She comes up with one really good theory and one insane theory.
Let's tackle the insane one first.
Is it possible that Child Protective Services is a front organization for the shadow people?
And it's pretty much what it is.
The shadow people in meth mythology, they make you hallucinate and you hear voices and they
can control your mind.
That's not what a shadow man is typically known for.
Minor actions with shadow men have been very observational.
Like, they don't even care that you're there.
I imagine it's kind of like what it must be like for a fox to notice a trail cam.
You can't really comprehend it.
It realizes something's there that shouldn't be.
In that situation, we're the fox.
When I ran into shadow people, I'll put the episodes in the show notes, but they're just
so alien and so obtuse to the fact that they were even standing there.
It's super fascinating.
But in the meth world, they're more demonic.
They're evil.
In my experience, they're neither good nor evil.
They're just there.
They move.
I mean, they're not just like, "Not just my shadow.
I haven't been tricked."
They're definitely something, but they are kind of standing beyond good and evil.
Anyways, is it possible that the CPS, who I can only heartbreakingly imagine if Nadine
hasn't had interactions with them before, it's coming, right?
That would make sense.
You would see Child Protective Services as this faceless organization trying to steal
your kids.
You're a good mom.
That's what they're telling themselves.
You're doing your best, and then this faceless organization comes in.
Is it actually run by the shadow people?
Is this a group that while the people may appear human, when they take the kid, it's
delivered to a darker supervisor?
No, not because they're not color related.
I didn't mean like that.
I meant like a demonic force, a shadow man.
That's Poppycock.
It's a great story idea.
I do love it from that angle.
But I don't believe that I will officially go on record.
I do not believe Child Protective Services is run by the shadow people.
She did have a super interesting theory though, which I love.
This one really kind of messes with your head.
She wonders if other people see her as a shadow person.
That's weird.
I don't think I've heard that before.
I've heard stories or theories that shadow people are an alternate reality kind of laid
over on top of ours, and there are certain times, there are certain places or certain
mind states we can actually perceive through that wall.
You know what?
I didn't think about this.
I did not think about this until I started saying it out loud.
That could be why the normal shadow man experience is more like mine, where they're just there.
Sometimes they're a little more sneaky, where they're like hiding behind a couch, poking
their head out down a hallway.
Sometimes they're just walking through the house like they own it.
Sometimes they're walking through the house like it doesn't exist.
They're just walking through the walls.
Sometimes you wake up and they're standing at the edge of your bed.
Sometimes when you look at the stories of the hat man, which is basically a shadow man
with a fedora, he tends to be a little more of a menacing figure.
But again, it's not like he's picking you up and throwing you out the window.
It's not like you're sitting there and you're playing video games and he's unplugging your
controller.
He's just scary.
He has a scary presence about him.
However, so that's the normal experience with shadow people.
The meth head experience with shadow people is they are very diabolical.
They are out to hurt you and make you hurt others.
They're out there to torment you.
What if I never thought of this?
Really, it wasn't until I was saying all this.
What if Nadine is right in the sense that when a normal person sees a shadow person,
they are seeing a shaded reality of the reality they inhabit, which, you know, I'm not saying
everyone's life is perfect by any means.
No one's is.
But I don't pick at my arm to try to get the spider eggs out.
If you have someone who lives in a chaotic environment, their shadow people would be
chaotic and evil as well.
That's interesting.
I've never thought of that before because you do have, it would be the same thing as
if two people owned a fish bowl full of goldfish.
But one person, the fish just kind of swam around normally.
The other person's fish bowl, they were cannibals and they were eating each other, eating a
fish.
You're like, oh no, I ran out of fish food.
Here, have this instead.
It's the same creature.
It's the same experience.
But the experiencer is changing the observation.
That's super weird.
I hadn't thought about that before.
I originally was just going to talk a little bit about how maybe people do see her as a
shadow person and how you would have basically two realities sitting on top of each other.
But I think that's just the tip of the iceberg.
I think that it may be the observer changing the observed.
Super interesting because again, the experience that is normal shadow people is that they
are not making you hallucinate.
They are not telling you to do evil things.
But to a method, that is how they experience them.
But to someone who's not on meth, they're just a weird force.
Again, they're creepy.
They are creepy, but they're not crawling on your ceilings and throwing up black blood
and then you realize it's just a hallucination.
And your new blender that she designs is a success, but now you no longer have a left
hand.
That's not what we see in normal shadow people stories.
So I'm going to actually look more into that.
That'll be really interesting to see.
I'm trying meth now.
That's it guys.
I got to go deep into this rabbit hole.
I'm going to go ahead and touch the keys to the carbonicopter.
Let's leave behind this neighborhood.
Make sure that Nadine is not stolen anything out of the carbonicopter while it briefly
lands and we load on board.
Fly us all the way out to California, which actually may have been where that first story
took place.
Specifically we're headed to Santa Fe Springs, California.
Be fly this carbonicopter over right there.
Right there.
I'm pointing at St. Paul High School off of Greenleaf Avenue, land on their roof.
We're walking around.
It's just a normal high school.
Kids are playing basketball, squeaky shoes.
Good shot, Jerry.
Thanks, man.
I've been practicing.
Then we walk past the library.
There's a bunch of people writing stuff down.
Hey, good sense and Jerry.
Thanks.
I've been practicing.
Shhh.
Then we walk out to the football field and we sit on the bleachers until the sun sets.
I guess we could have shown up eight hours later, but I wanted to walk around school.
We're sitting on the bleachers at this football field at St. Paul High School.
The sun sets, the moon rises, and we're just kind of sitting there.
Then all of a sudden you hear a "Hut, Hut, Hut, Hut, Hut, Hut, Hut, Hut, Hut, Hut, Hut,
Hut, Hut, Hut, Hut, Hut, Hut, Hut, Hut, Hut, Hut, Hut, Hut, Hut, Hut, Hut, Hut, Hut, Hut,
Hut, Hut, Hut, Hut, Hut, Hut, Hut, Hut, Hut, Hut, Hut, Hut, Hut, Hut, Hut, Hut, Hut, Hut, Hut, Hut, Hut, Hut, Hut, Hut, Hut, Hut, Hut, Hut, Hut, Hut, Hut, Hut, Hut, Hut, Hut,
Hut, Hut, Hut, Hut, Hut, Hut, Hut, Hut, Hut, Hut, Hut, Hut, Hut, Hut, Hut, Hut, Hut,
Hut, Hut, Hut, Hut, Hut, Hut, Hut, Hut, Hut, Hut, Hut, Hut, Hut, Hut, Hut, Hut,
Hut, Hut, Hut, Hut, Hut, Hut, Hut, Hut, Hut, Hut, Hut, Hut, Hut, Hut, Hut,
Hut, Hut, Hut, Hut, Hut, Hut, Hut, Hut, Hut, Hut
Hut, Hut, Hut, Hut, Hut, Hut, Hut, Hut, Hut, Hut, Hut, Hut, Hut, Hut, Hut, Hut,