When two friends are driving through Florida, they have no idea they're about to have a close encounter of the "turned" kind.
And then we travel to the home of a grieving sister.
After her older brother passed away in 2021, she's had a lot of pent-up feelings of remorse and anger at the entire situation.
But just when she might be working on putting the pieces back together and moving on, from beyond the nether, her brother begins to scream.
Today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
[music]
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host Jason Carpenter. I'm having a great day.
I hope you guys are having a great day too. I hope you guys have some awesome plans for the weekend.
I think I'm going to check out that new M. Night Shyamalan movie. I'm going to roll the dice. I'm going to roll the dice. It's always a roll of the dice.
It's always a gamble checking out that guy's films. I'm going to check out the new M. Night Shyamalan movie, "Knock at the Cabin."
We'll see how it is. We'll see if I come back next week with a Dead Rabbit Recommends.
But someone who I always will recommend walking into Dead Rabbit Command right now is one of our newest Patreon supporters.
Everyone give it up for Vince Garcia Velazquez.
Woohoo! Yeah! Walk on in! Come on in! No spoilers! Don't give it away!
"Knock at the Cabin." Vince, walk on into Dead Rabbit Command.
Vince has actually suggested a lot of stories to us.
He sent the one over about the earthquake that keeps happening in Mexico on that particular day.
I'll put the episode on the show notes. It was a really weird one.
Vince, thanks for sending that over and thanks for supporting the show. Vince, you're going to be our captain, our pilot this episode.
If you guys can't support the show financially, I totally understand. Just help spread the word about the show.
That helps out so much. And also, let's take a look at this awesome submission for Fan Art Friday.
This comes from Still Noided. Still Noided.
It's an interesting take on both the Ash Black Dead Rabbit Radio logo and the Grant Scott Dead Rabbit Radio logo with the, as above so below pose.
It's fantastic! This is so awesome. I love getting this stuff from you guys.
Thank you so much, Still Noided, for sending this on over. Really, really appreciate it.
Vince, let's go ahead and toss you the hair hang glider.
Everyone grab on to Vince's waist as he jumps off the highest point of Dead Rabbit Command.
Glide us all the way out to Florida.
[Hissing]
Specifically, we're headed out to a place known as Callahan, Florida.
It's August 26th, 1974. It's 9 p.m. at night.
And we're about to join two friends. Two friends.
One of them is Linda Stahlnaker and then her buddy, who she doesn't name.
She talks about being in the friend zone. You don't even get a name during your paranormal encounter.
She's just like, "Oh, he was just a friend. We're going to go ahead and call him Bobby."
So Lydia and Bobby are driving from Jacksonville to Callahan just friends.
And on this journey, they see a bright flashing light flying right above the tree line.
Now they're headed to Callahan. I'm sure they had plans. 9 p.m. is pretty early in the night.
You still got a lot of stuff to do. Maybe they were going clubbing. Maybe they were going to a coffee shop.
We don't know. Whatever your plans were, whatever they were.
If you see a UFO, maybe that's your plans for the night.
Maybe you've decided to be like, "Well, you know, we can catch Goldfinger in concert another week.
We just saw a UFO fly by. Let's follow that."
So that's what Lydia and Bobby do. They decide to follow the light.
And when they see it dip below the tree line, they can kind of figure out where it may have landed.
So Bobby is continuing to drive towards this light. But as they get closer to where this thing may have landed,
Lydia begins to feel cold. She feels the temperature drop around her.
And now she's actually starting to shake. It's so cold, her entire body is beginning to shiver.
And she asks Bobby to turn around. Turn the car around. I don't have a good feeling about this.
Can you please turn around? And Bobby does. And then are headed in the opposite direction.
But it's too late. Lydia is continuing to shake and shiver.
And it begins to feel like she's being smothered. She can't catch her breath.
Something physiological is happening to her. She's in full panic mode at this point.
A moment passes and all of the physical sensations are gone.
Lydia no longer feels like she's being suffocated. She's no longer shaking. She's no longer cold.
Bobby is driving down a completely different road than they were on just a second ago. Now he's on a completely different road.
Heading home, it's 12 a.m. Neither of them have any memories of what happened in that three hour time period. Zero.
They don't know what happened and how would you even be able to start to quantify that.
We cover a lot of missing time. It's fairly common in UFO accounts and this is no exception.
For the next few days though, Lydia begins to feel physically ill.
She's suffering extreme headaches. She can't concentrate at work. She's emotionally unstable.
She's kicking some of the books. She works at a daycare center. She's kicking the kids over. She goes, "I can't do this anymore."
She's emotionally unstable, physically sick. It's affecting her job and her personal life. She doesn't know what to do.
And she kind of thinks this could be connected to what might have happened that night.
They saw the light and the next thing they know, they're driving in another direction.
So she calls up Bobby to see if he's experiencing any side effects.
Bobby doesn't pick up the phone. In fact, she never saw Bobby again.
Now, according to this account, they were friends. I made a couple of jokes about them dating earlier.
I don't know if they were casual friends, if they were lifelong friends, if he actually was pining over Lydia.
I don't know any of that stuff, even though I made several jokes about it.
I don't know what the relationship status was, but if it was a casual friendship, she'd met him three weeks previous.
The fact that he ghosted her, well, whatever.
But if they were friends any longer, then it would be weird to just lose contact with one of your friends.
She's never seen him since. She tries calling him a couple of times, tries to figure out if he is also ill.
And to this day, to this day, she's never seen Bobby again.
But let's go back to this narrative here. We'll catch up to the modern day in a moment.
We're still back in 1974. Well, actually, at this point, it's spring at 1975, and Lydia can still not get her act together.
She's no longer throwing up every morning, but she still feels like something must have happened to her on that journey.
She can't figure out what it is, so she begins to see a professional.
She begins to see like a psychiatrist for what could have happened, and they put her under.
They use hypnosis to see, well, let's see if we can recover any memories.
She says what she remembered was that they did find the spacecraft, and it had landed.
They see the spacecraft, and it is touched down.
What's interesting is, remember the car turned around, and that's when she started feeling suffocated, and time seemed to stop.
So it's interesting, even when they turned around, were they then headed in the right direction?
Did they turn around at all in that moment? Like, what was mentally going on?
We don't know. Like, that memory itself is odd, but they did come across the UFO.
It was landed, and she felt compelled to board the spacecraft.
She got out of the car and began walking towards this landed UFO, and she doesn't give any description of the aliens.
She just refers to them as aliens, which would make us think they were human or humanoid.
Most like, Pleiadians would be my guess. That's the most humanoid of alien species.
But again, we've classified, like in UFOology, there's basically like five major classifications, but who knows?
Like, if you believe in the alien phenomenon, I don't think it can just be like, these are the Pleiadians, these are the Reptilians, these are the insectoids.
There's pretty countless possible species out there.
Anyway, she comes across these humanoids, she walks aboard this ship, they strap her down to a table, and it's basically this rotating...
It wasn't rotating when they strapped her down, they waited until she was secure, but imagine two gurneys, two of those like medical gurneys,
and they're basically fused together at the top, and she's laying down on one of them, and she's strapped down, and all the gurney that is, you know, on top...
Oh my God, I wish I could just draw a picture, which this was a video podcast.
Imagine if you had two gurneys pressed together, and you had a person laying foot to head on one,
and then the other person was laying foot to head on theirs, and your heads were facing the same direction.
And this is a device, and once they're in, once they're strapped down to this table, once Lydia, because the one woman is already on the table strapped down,
now they're strapping Lydia down, and then they put this device that enclosed both of their heads together.
I'm not even going to try to describe that, it's like some sort of glass thing.
And the two tables begin spinning.
[demonstrates]
And Lydia passes out.
Lydia said she started to come to as the tables were slowing down, and as the tables were slowing down, she felt this warm sensation pass through her,
starting at the top of her head, and pass through her entire body down to her feet.
And at that point, the device over her head that is also attached to this other woman's head is removed,
and Lydia is told that the other woman strapped to that gurney is Antron.
She's like, "Who's Antron? I don't know, I'm human. Is that some like pop superstar on your planet?"
They go, "No, no, no. Antron is just one of us. She's this alien."
And her consciousness has been transferred into your body, and she will be a part of your body for a period of time.
You will host the consciousness of this alien.
And the aliens around her, Lydia, said they seemed very pleased that the experiment went well.
I imagine these things can go south, no matter how advanced your technology is.
Every so often you're going to drop the vial.
They were very pleased that this went well.
They helped Lydia up off the gurney. She begins walking back to the car.
She sees Bobby in the car. Bobby never left. He was passed out in the car.
And she sees the car. She sees Bobby's passed out in the car.
The next thing she remembers, they're driving back home.
It's an interesting story. I found it on ThinkAboutDocs.com.
They got it from two UFO researchers, a Dr. James Harder and a Dr. Evelyn Brunson.
I actually don't know if Dr. Evelyn Brunson is specifically a UFO researcher.
I wasn't able to clarify that, but Dr. James Harder is.
Now, what's interesting is, as an abduction story, that's fairly unique.
This is so fascinating to me. We have this woman who has this UFO experience.
Now, there's a couple of different things you can do with that type of experience.
You could never tell anyone. I think that's probably the most common thing.
You can use it to kind of change the way you look at the world and realize that we are not alone.
You may take it as a social cause. The aliens may tell you something about saving the environment or whatever,
and then you just decide to like start saying, "Get oil. Get oil out of here," and all that.
Or you can become a huckster.
Now, I'm not saying that her claims are made up, but when you come in contact with aliens,
I definitely understand trying to make money off of it.
I don't necessarily agree with that. I mean, if you're writing books, that's fine.
You're doing speaking tours or whatever.
But then when you start talking about, "I have access to the seven universal truths by my book, and it'll change your life,"
that's when I'm a little like, "You're a huckster."
But let's take a look at what happened after this story, after the Think About Docs.com article.
There's a book written by Nigel Watson called, "Captured by Aliens, a History and Analysis of American Abduction Claims."
And in this book, we get a little more information.
She says, Lydia says that she was actually gained psychic powers from this transfer.
And she tells us that Anton actually came from a green planet in another galaxy,
and she traveled around in a glass tube in a spaceship. Basically, she lived in a big jar.
This is one of those things that sometimes the less information you have, the better.
If you ever get abducted by aliens and you have all of this really cool story to share with the world,
but then it also turns out that the aliens eat farts, don't tell people that.
Just keep that to yourself.
And the thing is, is that in 1974, the idea of intergalactic aliens, right?
Like, nowadays, it's hard enough to fly across the galaxy with modern UFO lore.
Even if you'd have to get into interdimensional stuff, which a lot of alien purists don't do that.
They talk about the aliens evolved on another planet. They're coming here.
From another galaxy is even more ridiculous. Flying around in a glass jar, she wasn't, her ship wasn't like an old mason jar.
But you know what I mean? Like, you sometimes just leave details out is what I'm saying.
If you ever get abducted by aliens, leave out the goofy details.
And then she says, you know, Anton was in my body. She was too powerful.
And I eventually had to just go with the flow because when I was fighting it, it was making it worse.
I retreated into my own mind and then eventually came to terms with all of it.
And then I found this tiny article in the United Press International.
It was just kind of a wire service talking about Lydia's story.
She has gone on speaking tours, which is pretty normal.
And she declares herself as I am one of, this is a quote from her quote,
I am one of the five most documented UFO abduction cases in the United States.
Have you ever heard of her before? I thought that was super interesting.
I read that that may or may not be true. I mean, you figure Betty and Barney Hill,
you figure a Whitley Striper, Fire in the Sky guy.
I forgot what his name was. Travis, what was it?
Let me look it up. Travis Walton, right? And two others.
Lydia Travis Walton, Betty and Barney Hill, Whitley Striper.
And then one more. I've never heard of her before. And I'm not saying that,
that she could totally be right. She could totally be right.
At the time, she was one of the five most documented.
Like she was legit. She was one of the biggies.
And that totally could be true. There's a ton of stuff I've never heard of.
That's why I have a podcast that's over a thousand episodes of stuff I've never heard of.
I'm discovering this stuff for the first time just like you are.
Or maybe you know better. You're like, Jason, she's super popular.
How did you not know about her? It's kind of ruining your reputation.
I've never heard of her and I think I know why.
Because you got to watch what you do. You got to watch.
I honestly believe that she probably had this encounter. I'm not poo-pooing
anything that she's saying. I don't think that it was fake. It could be.
But I'm not getting that read on it. The problem is that
she went to Huxtery.
She started to sell the secret.
Like you know, Whitley Shriver wrote books
and did speaking tours. People expect witnesses.
People expect abduction. Experiencers to do stuff like that.
But when you start talking about the seven powers of God
and you're selling the secret formula
to open up your life
for the better. And I have no problem with that. I have no problem with self-help stuff.
But you understand like that division. Travis Walton wasn't running around
saying, "I found out the secrets of the universe."
Those aliens were pretty brutal. They were trying to cut them open.
Betty and Barney Hill weren't saying, "Oh, we know all of this stuff and if you buy our
water, if you buy the water out of our radiator in our car
it will heal your wounds." That's the card of the aliens.
There really is a difference there. And really the last piece of information
I could find on Lydia cements the end of her saga.
This would pretty much just be the end of any story.
There was an ad in the Weekly World News
which, sorry to say, is no longer in production. I think their website is still
chugging along. But Weekly World News was one of
those tabloids you used to see at the grocery store and it had headlines
like "Batboy Runs for President," "Skeletons on the Moon."
We've actually covered Angels in Space. We've covered stories from Weekly World
News that have entered into paranormal
culture. They're totally made up. The Angels in Space is probably the most famous
one. I saw that on the internet as a legit paranormal phenomenon
and traced it back to the Weekly World News. And I was like, "I wasted an hour on this."
I wasted an hour. We did the episode on it.
It was fun. But I remember when I first saw that story. It was on a paranormal website.
I was like, "Wow, that's totally awesome." And then when I went to do more research for the
podcast, I was like, "Wow, what a waste of time. It's not true." And you'll still see
it pop up. Weekly World News, I loved it. I read it all the time as a kid.
It's great. It's a fictional newspaper. But in real life
it's made up stuff. And Lydia was buying ads in that
newspaper. It's not a good look. And in the
ads that she was selling, there was this ad from February 10th, 1981
where she is selling the Cross of Antron.
She says that Antron, she talks about this alien experience. And I'm
sure she probably did. I'm sure people in 1981, when they saw her name, they would remember
her. She's one of the fifth most documented UFO. I don't know if
that claims true. But let's just assume that it is, right? You recognize her
name? She says that Antron told her that God was real and gave her
the design for the Cross of Antron. It's basically a little
crucifix--it's a cross on a necklace. But it has pyramid designs
on it. It's not just a normal cross. It has these pyramid designs. And
in the middle there's this oval. And I mean, listen, this may have come from an alien.
She may not have had any choice at what this looked like.
But obviously, if you're selling something called the Cross of
Antron and you're talking about God being real, you're
selling it to Christians. It looks like a cross you're selling it to Christians.
It's probably not a good idea--or, more specifically,
Christians who believe in aliens. So you have a fairly small market.
It's probably not a good idea that in your cross that an alien gave you
in the design, there's also an upside down cross inside.
And there's like an S. It's quite complicated. And most Christians are not going to buy
a cross that part of it is an upside down cross.
That's just kind of logical. Now you could argue, Jason, it's an alien designed it.
An alien designed it. It contains the power of Antron. Well,
I will accept that Lydia's experience is real.
That's definitely going to happen. And this alien could have given her a cross.
But if you're trying to sell it,
maybe raise that part. You're like, "Oh, the alien got this part wrong."
Spookle, spookle, spookle. Here's a new one. I don't believe the cross is real. I don't believe the alien
actually gave her the cross. That's my thing. I think
at this point she was trying to sell the seven powers of
God. She was trying to sell this new lifestyle, this new hippie-dippy
nonsense. I could be wrong. Maybe the alien gave her the seven powers
of God and gave her the cross. But whatever, whether or not she made it up or the alien
gave it to her, she is far. I mean, again, I had a hard time
finding information on her. It wasn't impossible. I did find all this stuff.
You're like, "Jason, you found a bunch of stuff on her. You're like, "What, books, stuff like that?"
Obviously, if I typed in Whitley Stryber or Betty and Varney Hill,
I'm going to find a lot more. I think you can actually ruin your reputation as an
experiencer. Not if you try to make money off of it, but if you try to make the wrong
kind of money off of it.
You know what I'm saying? There's good and bad ways
to exploit your experience.
And you kind of have to navigate that. Again,
Whitley Stryber can write book after book about it and sell the movie rights and all that stuff. It's totally fine.
I'm not saying that game is to be sold, not to be
told. You do have an ability to make money off
your experience. But you've got to be careful
because if people smell a scam, even if an alien was like,
"Here, give this cross to your people. It'll bring them peace. It'll show them the seven powers
of God." If people smell a scam, they'll run away. You might get a
small, dedicated cult maybe following you.
But I think it did. I think she, these
decisions she made ended up, she may have been a super famous
alien abductee back in the day, but it just got too
weird. And it started to smell like a scam.
And you got enough of that running around in the paranormal community.
Fake ghost hunters, that's quite harmless.
Fake ghost hunting is quite harmless. People who lie about being abducted by aliens, again, it's quite
harmless. But when something starts to smell like a money-making venture,
at best, and at worst, the start of a cult, people will
shun you from the general community. So anyway, it's a very interesting
story. The UFO story is interesting, and the aftermath
to it as well. Where's Bobby? Where's Bobby at? Who knows where Bobby
is. But a fascinating story nonetheless. And I don't know if she's still around.
Like, I was able to find little scraps, little bits about her. But
an interesting story nonetheless. Vince, let's go ahead and touch the keys of the
carbonic objector. We are saying goodbye to Lydia. She's waving
to us. She's like, "You guys sure you don't want to know the seven powers of God?"
I think we can probably figure them out. Love your neighbor. Love your neighbor.
Do unto others as they would have to do unto you. She's like, "Oh, did you get to attack my aliens? How did you know that stuff?"
We're like, "Uh..." Just fly us out. Fly us out of
Florida. We're leaving that state behind. Take us all
the way out to a house in the suburbs.
[imitates the sound of the house]
This is a story that I found online. We don't have a specific
location for it. It could take place at any house.
Possibly yours. It's possible that you are the person
who...we're going to call Sheila. We don't have her actual name. We're going to go ahead and call her Sheila.
Online, she goes by the name T-Darn
96. But we're going to go ahead and call her Sheila.
Back in fall of 2021, her older brother passed away.
He had a heart attack. He was quite a young man.
He died of a heart attack. She goes,
"There was a seven-year age difference between us, and we weren't
super close. Not just because of the age difference. That did play a
factor, but we had different dads."
We had different dads, so obviously my dad
had issues with him. He was a very toxic
home environment for all of us. And
my brother had bipolar disorder, and it was not
diagnosed until it was too late.
He began using drugs in the sixth grade.
A lot of times, you know, you're trying to self-medicate. You don't know what
is wrong with you. It hasn't been diagnosed. You begin to self-medicate.
He begins using drugs in the sixth grade, man. That's super rough.
Well, in fall of 2021, he passed away.
Obviously, Sheila had a lot of...she's grieving,
but she also has a lot of...
It would be a crockpot full of emotions.
You'd be kind of angry. You'd be sad. You'd be angry at your parents that you didn't have a good
relationship with your brother. You'd be angry at your brother because he died.
You'd be angry at your brother because of the choices he had made that kept
you guys apart. It's just this huge cauldron of stuff.
Huge cauldron of stuff that you need to work through.
After he passed away, let's call the brother Tony. I don't think
we should give this guy a name. After Tony passed away,
Sheila ended up talking to a mutual friend.
And this friend said, "Listen, you know, Tony... Tony
confided in me. He wanted to have a better relationship with you. He really
wished that you guys were closer, but he didn't know how
to bridge that gap. He didn't
know how to reach out to you. He wanted to be closer with you for years, but definitely
as you guys are becoming adults, it's even more important.
At some point in life, siblings go from hating each other's guts to
being like, "Oh, you know, this is my best friend. Like, it's weird and it doesn't happen until like, your
20s, until everyone's like, older." When you're like, "Wow, we made it. We're
brothers together." And I can definitely understand Tony
being outside the family looking in and wishing he was part of it.
But when you start using drugs in the sixth grade, when you have
undiagnosed mental problems, it makes it hard. And that's just the stuff on the surface.
Again, different dads, who knows how many fights they got into that house,
how many arguments, how many ridiculous screaming matches over
inane things, and now Tony's dead.
All those fights are over.
But you remember every one of those fights.
And it breaks your heart when you think about it. You were yelling at a young man who was never
going to make it to be an old man. It's quite tragic.
And the friend goes, "You know, Tony wanted to be very close to you,
but he always just felt like an outsider to the whole family.
He never felt like he belonged.
So it wasn't just a matter of being able to reach out to you. It's like,
how do you even start that process when you feel like you're not part of the family?
Tony's not part of the family. He sees, you know, it's just this huge thing. Tony
has all these emotional scars. Sheila has all these emotional scars.
But he has a
home with Sheila now.
Now that he has passed away, Sheila has his
ashes in an urn and his
old high school jersey.
She has them in this place. I don't know if it's like, I don't know if the jerseys hung up
or something like that. I don't think it's just hanging off the mantle of the fireplace. But
she has this place in her home. If Tony couldn't be part of her
life in life,
she was going to make sure he always had a place now that he'd passed on.
He would have a home now with her.
But this is so, this is such a bizarre
story. This is such a bizarre story. And I, this
okay, let me let me finish this up because I, I
interpret this story completely different than Sheila does.
And one of these versions, okay, let's get it, let's get into
this. He passed away in fall of 2021.
There's been this urn of his ashes and his jersey
in Sheila's house probably shortly after that, right? He probably wasn't in some storage center,
but I don't know, maybe she did recently get the urn and the jersey. She doesn't say
but anyways. I like how the beginning is all this touching
melodrama where I'm really kind of trying to lay the brow
work where how tormented this young man must have been. And now I can't
say a sentence without giggling because this is just so weird.
I kind of gave it away in the intro, but let's get, let's get to this.
So Sheila's married now. She was married for the past couple
months when her husband, well I don't think this
happens every single time. But it might
because it just says when her husband is walking
near the urn,
he will hear an ear
splittingly loud
scream.
And he can clearly tell it's the sound of a man
screaming, which I'll tell you is 10
times more terrifying than a woman screaming.
Because we've been desensitized to the scream of a woman through horror movies
and when women get really excited they scream right in your ear even though
you're literally like six inches away from them.
You basically have to start tuning it out at a certain
point. But when's the last time you heard in real life
a man scream? When's the last time you heard in a movie
a man scream?
It's incredibly terrifying. When you hear a man
scream, something's seriously wrong.
It's creepy.
Because you never hear it. You never hear it in media. You never hear it in real life.
He's walking by this urn and he hears a man
screaming.
And it says, look at here, it says
when the husband is near the items he will randomly hear
a loud male scream. So it's not every single time. Because otherwise you would just be like, okay
I won't walk near that. He's all super thirsty.
He's all dehydrated. And Sheila puts out a little mini fridge
of water. She's like, oh, she's caring to do that. She's like, oh wait, my arms are
tired. I'm going to set it right by this urn. The husband's like, no
he's all wearing earplugs. So it doesn't happen every single
time. But randomly he hears the sound of a male
screaming at the top of his lungs
right in his ear.
Obviously terrifies this poor husband. It would be
the scariest thing. Now I'm saying
if I was at your house and I heard a disembodied woman scream, it's not like I would be like
I'm used to that. It would still kind of put me on edge if I heard a woman screaming
in my own house and there was no reason, there was no woman here. There's no reason
for me to hear it. That would obviously be upsetting. I'm not
saying I'd be okay with that. But there is something different
when you hear a man scream because you never hear it. And if a man
screaming in your ear, that's even worse. And if the
man is dead, it's a ghost.
It's a ghost screaming at the husband.
And this is so interesting to me because I read this story and she goes, yeah, my husband's
completely terrified about this. I don't know what it is
but she says, I think it's my brother. I think it's my brother trying to
communicate with me.
Sheila goes, I think my brother's trying to communicate with me. She went
because her husband just heard this the other day before she posted this.
She says, I went over to the urn and I said all the
things I've been wanting to say to him. All the
stuff that I've wanted to tell Tony before he died and
now that he's died, I needed to get all this stuff off my chest. I needed him to
hear it and I needed to hear myself say it.
And I'm just sobbing and I have a good cry over this whole thing but I needed
to get all this stuff off my chest and I needed him to know this.
And she said, I felt really good after I did it. It felt
so good to let all that emotion out.
And she says, if
this is his way of letting me know he wants to talk to me,
I will talk more often. I will visit the
urn on a regular basis and have these conversations
with my brother.
And she titled this post, I think my
dead brother is trying to communicate with me.
And that's how she sees this story. She sees it as
a message.
But I don't, this is, okay, so I'm going to be totally honest.
This is, I talked recently about
if somebody tells me that they had
a dream that a loved one, a loved one had recently passed and they had a dream and they
came to him and said, I love you. I wanted to say I love
you one more time and I hope you have a good life and all that stuff and
they fade away. I don't discount those ghost stories.
I won't ever say, I don't believe that happened.
If someone tells me, if someone's personally talking to me about a ghost story,
where they saw a loved one standing at the end of a hallway,
don't worry about me, Jimmy, there's nothing but a lot of fish to catch on the other side.
Don't worry about me, old grandpa Chuck.
I'll be catching fish forever and they fade away.
I'm not going to be like, well, did you check your carbon monoxide detector? I think you
actually have been hallucinating. For a couple reasons. One, I believe in
ghosts, but I even know people who don't believe in ghosts who don't invalidate
those stories because that's a very, that's a deeply personal story.
You're not going to be like, well, that was just a trick of the light. Your grandpa is
rotting in a grave somewhere and the worms are eating him. Maybe someday a fish will
eat that worm, but you're making that up or you're mentally
ill. And with this
story, it's a tricky one because I don't,
I love that she was able to get all this stuff
off of her chest. I love that she was able to talk
to Tony. That's heartwarming and it was definitely needed. If not
for Tony for Sheila, she needed to say this stuff out loud. I totally
understand that. As a paranormal
researcher, my take is, and here's the thing,
who cares about my take? Right? Who cares? My take
is, I read something online and I'm giving my opinion. If I'm wrong,
that's totally fine. She doesn't have to believe in anything I'm about to say,
but I will say this.
This is pretty creepy, the fact that her husband
is hearing the screaming, that it
manifests as a screaming.
If Sheila takes this,
takes the fact that her husband is having a man scream in her
ear as the ghost trying to
communicate with her, I just
don't. I'm glad that she was able to get this stuff off of
her chest, but I don't know if that's what this voice actually wants.
You know what I mean?
It's such an interesting
grief is complicated.
Grief is incredibly complicated, and it's such a horrible emotion to go
through, and it's necessary. It's part of the human condition, but
I'm not saying that she's wrong,
but listen man,
there are two types of ghosts. We talk all about different types of paranormal phenomenon,
and at the end of the day, there's two types.
They're scary and not scary.
On a basic level, if you woke up in the middle of the
night and your grandpa's standing at the end of the hallway, and goes, "Listen Johnny,
I died, but here I am,
I'm back from the dead." To tell you, "Don't worry about good old Gramps,
I'm gonna go fishing."
Whatever he does, they go fishing no matter what. Some little kid dies.
He's like, "I guess I'm a fisherman now. I'm gonna go fishing in heaven.
I got the pole. The reach is down from the clouds. I'm gonna get you
killer whale. I'm an angel. I'm super strong. I can wrestle
giant squids. I'm gonna kill a couple of those tonight. It's dead. That's awesome.
Johnny, you should try it. Join me. Join me on the other side.
See, that's the difference between...
basically a non-scary ghost that turned into a bad ghost.
I kinda ruined my own example. What I'm saying is if you woke up in the middle of the night and you saw a ghost of a
dead loved one, that is on just a basic level creepy.
That's scary. You wake up and you see your dead
relative standing at the edge of your bed. But then they say,
"I'm trying not to make any jokes this time. I wanna have a good example."
You wake up, there's a dead relative at the edge of your bed and they go,
"I'm on the other side now. Everything's perfect."
What? Mom, you never fished? She's like, "I do now."
Ghosts in and of themselves are spooky,
but when you sit back and think about the ghost, you go, "Well, that ghost wasn't trying
to scare me." Yes, it is scary to think that while I'm sleeping
there's someone standing over my bed. That's just creepy
in general, but then when you wake up and realize they just wanna go fishing,
that's not spooky. And then if you woke up in the middle of the night
and there was a ghost at the edge of your bed, but it was like a little girl. You don't know any little girls
who've died recently. And you just see the top of her head, she's kind of like
ducked down. So you look at the foot of your bed and you see like a top of
little girl's head and then she slowly is like rising up and her
eyeballs are gone. Just dark sockets staring at you.
And she starts going like, "Wring around the
blue rose." That's a scary ghost. That's scary
even if you didn't know a little girl who died recently.
Even if your niece died in a horrible fishing related
accident, she was super weird. A giant killer whale
got sucked out of the ocean and flew into the clouds, knocked over this boat, killed this little girl.
Even if you knew a little girl who died, even if she was a relative
of yours, she doesn't need to be hiding the edge of your bed singing nursery rhymes
with no eyeballs. There's scary ghosts and there's not scary ghosts. Even though
ghosts in and of themselves are scary, some act in scary ways.
For example, screaming. For example, screaming.
Right in somebody's ear at the top of their lungs. That's spooky.
That's a terrifying manifestation
of a spirit. It's
such an interesting sort of like, what is the phenomenon that's going on here? Why is it
only affecting the husband? And here's my take. We got to
wrap this up because I'll go on for hours about this thing. I find this so interesting but
what I think is interesting is that I'm trying to think. There was
a story or stories that I've read in the past. This is all starting
and I've just done so much reading over the decades about this stuff.
Where at a certain point, Sheila is going to have to think
if the ghost of my brother is screaming
in my husband's ear,
there might be something wrong with my husband.
I don't know if we've ever covered a story like that on the
podcast. We might have. One of you guys will remember if we did.
But I've come across stuff like that in the literature, in the lore over the years.
Where a ghost is trying to warn the living about
threats of other people who are still alive.
That's what I'm thinking. Here's the thing. This is either a good ghost
appearing in a scary way to scare the husband off
or this is a bad ghost
slowly beginning to manifest until this couple's lives.
I guess there's a third
one where this actually is the spirit of Tony and for whatever
reason he can't communicate directly with Sheila. He can only
communicate and screams from beyond.
It's possible. The world is paranormal
anything is possible but I'm kind of leaning towards the fact that
this is either Tony trying to ward off the husband. He knows something
that Sheila doesn't know. Or that this is some sort
of malevolent spirit
that is slowly taking shape in this house. Tony may be off
in paradise already. Tony may have passed away and moved on.
This is something using that grief and that anger
and it's after Sheila.
It's coming after Sheila and that's why it's manifesting as
this scream. Because it is a dark force.
Fascinating. Super fascinating story. I mean this was
just posted not too long ago. We are
knee deep in this phenomenon. It was posted about 16 days ago
from now. It was posted on January 20th. So most likely we'll never
hear an update. Whether it's good or bad it will probably
won't see an update pop up later.
People just kind of go on with their lives. If stuff starts to get dark it's not like
she's going to run to the internet and be like oh I have to leave stuff floating around her keyboard
and she's like hey I'm trying to post here. I mean stuff would have to get really bad
for her to do an update. Most of the stuff she's just posting on random
stuff online. I would be super cautious but again what are you going to
do? I mean I think if you're husband I don't think earplugs are actually going to help.
It's a scream from beyond the grave. But do you move
the urn? Do you move it out of the way so it doesn't have to walk by it so much?
Disrespect the remains to respect your husband.
I don't know it's a super interesting case
and we don't know which direction it's going to go and we
don't know how this is going to play out because it's happening right now.
As you're listening to this episode in the comfort of your own home or car there's
a man somewhere held by a ghost
by the ghost of a dead brother. And is it a playful
yell? Is it trying to get attention so he can talk to Sheila or is it
a scream of the pain that this husband
will see you endure himself? Who knows it's such a fascinating
ghost story and a perfect way to end this week.
And one more treat for you guys.
A custom outro theme song. A custom version
of Bella Royale by Blue Synth, Patreon supporter and active
member of the Patreon Discord. Here we go with a custom
remix of Bella Royale to send you guys off to have an awesome
weekend. DeadRabbitRadio@gmail.com is going to be
our email address. You can also win us up at facebook.com/DeadRabbitRadio
TikTok is @DeadRabbitRadio. DeadRabbitRadio is the daily
paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast. You don't have to listen to it every day.
I'm glad you listened to it today. Have a great weekend guys.
Aw shit, get your coat back man.
[Music]