A bizarre audio clip floating around the internet may give us a clue behind the phenomenon
known as "Missing 411."
And then we travel to Vietnam to meet a young woman about to buy a refrigerator.
As she pulls the money out of her wallet and hands it over to the cashier, little does
anyone know that they have just stepped foot into the world of the damned, today on Dead
Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Carpenter, I'm having a great day.
Hope you guys are having a great day too, like not after yesterday's episode dude.
That was pretty rough, yeah.
Yeah, it was pretty bad.
But someone who is never bad but always good walking into Dead Rabbit Command right now
is one of our legacy Patreon supporters.
Everyone give it up for Shawn.
Woohoo!
Yeah, come on in buddy.
Come on in Shawn, into Dead Rabbit Command.
Shawn, you're gonna be our captain, our pilot this episode.
If you guys can't support the show financially through the Patreon or whatever, that's fine.
It really is.
Just help spread the word about the podcast.
That really, really, really helps out a lot.
Shawn, we got a lot of stuff to cover today so I'm gonna go ahead and toss you a little
engineers cap and a shovel.
We're gonna hop on board the Carpenter Caboose.
We're gonna take this train all the way out to Pakistan.
Choo-choo-choo-choo-choo-choo-choo-choo-choo-choo-choo-choo-choo-choo-choo-choo-choo-choo-choo-choo-choo-choo-choo-choo-choo-choo-choo-choo-choo-choo-choo-choo-choo-choo-choo-choo-choo-choo-choo-choo-choo-choo-choo-choo-choo-choo-choo-choo-choo-choo-choo-choo-choo-choo-choo-choo-choo-choo-choo-choo-choo-choo-choo-choo-choo-choo-choo-choo-
We're looking for the tree.
We're specifically looking for the tree on Margala Hill Trail 5.
The dude's like, "You saw that video didn't you?"
And I was like, "Yeah, that's why we're here.
We're walking through the city of Islamabad.
We're on the opposite side of the train parked right at the entrance of the city.
It's three hours later.
We finally find this walking trail.
Just trees and nature, dirt and stuff like that, a couple birds.
Kind of boring.
But we're not here to see all that dumb stuff.
We're here to keep walking and then you hear...
What?
Did you hear that?
Where'd that come from?
Come this way guys, closer, closer.
We're gonna continue to walk through the woods and we hear...
What?
Isn't that crazy?
Really, Chase?
Just tell the story.
Tell that you found a one minute long video.
You found some TikTok.
I just got to the chase, bro.
So anyways, I found this one minute long video on TikTok.
What it is...
This is Trippy.
There's an actor.
There's a Pakistani actor named Ahmed Ali Akbar.
He's an actor and they were currently shooting a movie in this area and during a break in
filming he was walking through Margala Hill Trail 5 and he heard that sound.
Let me play the audio in full for you right here.
Ahmed is walking through this area.
Ahmed is walking through this area and he starts hearing that sound.
That sound.
And he identifies it as coming out of a tree.
And he said this tree was about a foot and a half in diameter and had a hole, a perfect
hole about the size of a coin.
And he videotaped this.
You can clearly see this.
I'll put it in the show notes, obviously.
But so that sound is coming out of the hole in the tree.
And he's videotaping it and he...
Listen, obviously people are gonna think it's fake and he goes, "It's not fake."
Now anyone who fakes stuff, they're gonna say it's not fake, too.
But let's assume that this is real, right?
It could obviously be a total forgery.
Someone can be like, "You know what?
I'm a famous actor but you know what?
I like to do my breaks.
Fool people!"
Well I guess actors do professionally get fake delight of people.
So maybe it is this hobby.
But anyway, so he came across this tree and it's making this noise.
He says it's totally authentic.
This kind of went viral, right?
Imagine a brat bit.
I was like, "Hey guys, you won't believe it.
I was walking around the Hollywood Hills and I found a chupacabra!
Here's a video of this guy running through the bushes.
Even if it really wasn't the chupacabra, you just saw like a tail.
People would still be talking about it.
I mean even if it was just like some stupid orb he picked up on camera, people would be
like, "Brat bit believes in ghosts."
It'd be a big thing.
So this went viral over in Pakistan and you had people come out and be like, "That's
fake."
You had people come out and say, "Whoa, that's super spooky."
And then you had other people come out.
There was an actress named Anushi Ashraf.
She responded to this and she goes, "There's actually a scientific reason behind this.
When trees are super dehydrated, they scream."
Did you know that?
Did you know that was a thing?
Well, here's the issue with that.
Yes, they do do that.
You're like, "They clearly don't.
I've never heard that in my life.
Hold on."
So I looked it up.
And according to the Smithsonian, they have a, on their website, smithsonianmag.com,
they have an article, "Trees make noise and some of those sounds are cries for help."
But if you look closer in the article, they say the trees do scream, but it's an ultrasonic
scream, which humans cannot hear.
So now we're back to square one.
The debunking didn't work.
So what is this?
What is this?
It's, the most likely explanation is some sort of natural phenomenon, but moisture
escaping from the tree?
Who knows?
I think, I'm not going to say necessarily like a, it sounds like a baby, right?
I'm not saying like a baby's soul is trapped in a tree or anything.
I wouldn't say anything that outlandish, but it could be something paranormal, definitely.
It's interesting as the video is taken during the day, which also lends at this very, oh,
I'm sure it's something normal vibe.
It's not in the middle of a spooky forest during the witch's hour.
It's like a, it's a coffee break from shooting.
It's like probably two, three in the afternoon.
So it could be something natural.
It could be something paranormal, but I think either way, it's not something they can easily
identify.
It's something that they go, oh, here's the answer.
And then people moved on, but they didn't read the article themselves that they were
posting where it says that it's an ultrasonic sound.
They just need microphones to check it out.
So I'm wondering if this is a super rare phenomenon that does happen and it's either dismissed
or it's never even really witnessed in the first place, unless you're walking through
the forest and you hear that sound, which does sound like somebody in distress, a child,
a baby, and you went to investigate it.
And you got lost.
Fall off the ravine, move too far off the trail.
You're never able to get back on it.
You're just kind of wandering around the wilderness until your supplies run out, which, you know,
you're just hiking.
You didn't think you were going to go on this big excursion, but if you were hiking on a
trail and you heard that sound and you thought it was a baby in trouble, you may break off
the trail to go find it, the source of that sound.
And then you get there and you're like, oh, just a tree.
Oh no, where am I?
Where am I?
And you're lost.
And you just had, you know, some trail nuts on you and a bit of water because you didn't
plan on being out there for four days, braving the elements.
I'm wondering if something like this, we, it's interesting because in the paranormal
world, we come across the sound of babies crying a lot, like crybaby bridges or children crying
in the darkness or strange voices from the forest and people being lured out there.
And then when you look at stuff like missing 411, we don't know how they disappear or why
they disappear, but it could be something natural like this that's drawing you off the
trail.
If I was walking, if I was hiking in the middle of nowhere and I heard that sound, I would
keep hiking.
I would be like, sorry, baby, I'll get to where there's some cell phone service.
I'll tie a little string on this tree, tree so I can find my way back.
I'm not walking through that bramble for a possible baby.
If it was a real baby, if it was a baby going, no, it's really me and I can see your shirt,
you're wearing a black shirt and white shoes.
I'd be like, okay, that's obviously a baby.
Like, no, Jason, that's even more suspicious.
And a baby can talk and it can describe your clothing.
If I heard what sounded like it could be a baby, I wouldn't say that.
I mean, if it was in front of me, I'd pick it up.
But if it was like, I couldn't see it like somewhere in the bushes I heard it.
I'd be like, that might not be a baby.
Like I can't clearly see what's making that noise.
So I'm going to keep on walking.
If I could see that it was a baby, I wouldn't be like, I'm closing my eyes.
I'm like, what?
What's making that noise?
I'm all stepping over the baby.
He's grabbing my pant leg.
Obviously if I saw the baby, I would rescue the baby.
But if I was walking and I heard a baby noise and I couldn't see the baby, I'm not going
to get off the trail to go save the baby.
So this noise, I mean, that makes me smart, right?
I'm never going to disappear in the middle of the woods.
A bunch of babies may die.
I may be responsible for the deaths of many lost children, but I won't get lost in the
woods.
But I think if you were hiking and you heard that sound, you may leave the trail.
Never to be seen again or simply to not be seen for a while, right?
You just die and they find your bleach bones out in the woods somewhere.
And I'm standing over your bones.
I'm like, you got fooled by that screaming.
There's a bunch of baby bones around him.
I'm like, I'm going to ignore those.
It must have been the trees that tricked you.
And I walk away.
Yeah, who knows, right?
The thing with the missing 4011 phenomenon, it's always like, what is causing them to
disappear?
And it could, you know, some people say it's like the government wearing these invisible
predator type suits.
Some people say it's Bigfoot.
Some people say it's interdimensional.
And those could all be possible.
But it could also be we could have people leaving the trail because they hear something
like that.
I think that would draw people off the trail.
And they're never seen again or they're never seen alive again.
We talked about on a recent episode, the world of the paranormal is told in the survivors'
stories.
The blue encounter of these entities or this phenomenon who don't make it, we never hear
their story.
We only know the stories of the times people get abducted by aliens and brought back.
Or the people who interact with some sort of monster, some sort of cryptid, some sort
of void, and come back.
So who knows what else is out there that we have no idea that's out there.
Let's go ahead and switch gears.
Sean, I'm going to go ahead and toss you the keys to the carpenter copter.
We are going to leave behind this forest.
Make sure any babies you brought with you for that first segment.
Make sure you still have them because I'm not responsible for them.
Let's hop on aboard the carpenter copter Sean Flyas all the way out to Vietnam.
We're in the city of Hai Phong.
The year is 2009.
We're walking around this mall.
It's called the Big C Hai Phong Mall.
Let's head on down to the Big C is what they say in Vietnam.
Let's go.
So we're walking around with our shopping bags and we're looking at shirts and buying
pineapples and everything like that.
And a pretty girl walks in.
This pretty girl, pretty young girl walks into the mall and she walks up to a clerk
and says, "I want to buy a refrigerator.
Can you show me what you have?"
And he's like, "Yeah, sure.
Come this way."
And they're looking and he's like, "This one keeps food cold."
And she's like, "What about that one?"
And he goes, "That one does it too.
They're both fridges."
Well, eventually she decides on which fridge she wants to buy and she goes up to the cash
register and they said, "This is insane.
This is so insane.
This actually isn't the weirdest part of the story."
It gets weirder.
It costs 3 million Vietnam Dong.
That's the name of their currency.
The Vietnam Dong.
3 million Dong.
That's $130 in US money.
That's always so weird to me.
How do you carry that much money around?
You carrying briefcase?
You have this huge briefcase.
You're like, "Let's go to McDonald's, kids."
Get the forklift.
I'm sure they have a bill that's 1 billion Dong and you're buying coffee with it.
It's just weird.
I would just change my money.
I would say Vietnam Dong, we're not going to call 3 million 3 million anymore.
We'll call it 7.
It would just make more sense.
But anyways, so this woman walks in with this giant crate of Vietnam Dong.
She's like, "Hope you can count to 3.
I hope you can sit here and count these $1 Dongs 3 million times."
So anyways, they bring it in.
It's only $130 for a fridge, which actually is pretty cheap.
And the young woman says, "Can you deliver it to my house?"
And they're like, "Of course."
So they're writing out a receipt.
She doesn't cut.
They're writing out the receipt, the address and everything like that.
Give it to the young woman and she leaves.
Well shortly after that, a delivery man from the Big C Mall comes up in his delivery truck,
gets out of the car, goes to the address, "Ding dong."
At the door stands an old woman, not like super old, not like 90s, nothing like that.
But you know, like she's middle-aged.
Delivery driver walks up to her and says, "Hey, I got this fridge delivery.
I got this fridge delivery.
And where do you want me to put it?"
I'm assuming the kitchen, but like, "You want to do this now?"
Or the woman goes, "I didn't order a fridge.
I mean, I need one.
It'd be nice, but I didn't order one.
There must be some sort of mistake."
And the delivery driver goes, "Oh, no, no, no.
It's actually already been paid for."
Here, look at the receipt.
And he hands the receipt, the delivery receipt, over to the middle-aged woman and she looks
at it and she immediately bursts into tears.
She begins sobbing.
Delivery driver's like, "Dude, what's the matter?"
And she goes, "I don't know how this is possible because I see that this was just purchased
like a couple of days ago, but this is my daughter's name on this receipt.
My daughter's been dead for months.
And before my daughter died, the day before she died, she told me, "Ma, you know what?
I'm going to buy you a new refrigerator."
Those were her famous last words we had on her tombstone.
She died in a car accident a couple of months ago.
How is this possible?
And the mother's just sobbing and she's perplexed and she's like questioning delivery driver
and trying to figure everything out.
And delivery driver is freaking out about this.
Like the mom obviously, I mean this is either the cruelest slash best joke in the world.
Like yeah, sure, you're impersonating her dead daughter, but you get a free fridge.
That's pretty good.
That's going on.
But the delivery driver's just like, "Oh my God, is there a ghost?
I don't have anything to do with ghosts."
He got this job because it was the least ghost job possible.
If I'm in a delivery van, they can't catch up to me.
He freaks out.
He actually leaves.
He doesn't leave the fridge there.
That's not on the van, but he runs, he gets in his van, he drives back to the mall, tells
his boss, "Guys, you guys aren't going to leave this.
Remember that fridge that you wanted me to deliver like 20 minutes ago?"
Well, a ghost bought it.
A ghost bought it in the bus.
Like what are you talking about?
He goes, "I don't even know.
I don't even know how to explain this."
A ghost bought it because the name on the receipt is of a girl who died months ago.
And the day before she died, she told her mom, "I want to buy you a new fridge."
And the boss is like, "Dude, I'm way too busy.
I'm running an entire mall right now.
I'm way too busy to figure this out."
But the boss goes to the clerk.
It goes to the girl who rang up the transaction.
She goes, "Hey listen, Bob, back in delivery, is flipping out saying that a ghost bought
a fridge the other day and when he went to deliver it, the mom said the girl had been
dead for a couple months.
Do you remember selling a fridge recently?"
She says, "Yeah, this young woman came in.
She bought the fridge.
It's three million dong."
She's like, "Wow, that's a lot."
But you do remember selling it.
Oh yeah, I totally remember it.
She came into the store and the boss is like, "Okay.
Well let's go and see what we can pull up."
And they go and they watch the CCTV footage, the security cam footage.
There's no trace of the girl in the mall.
But that's not even the weirdest part.
Because the boss then goes, "Well listen, she bought it, even though we don't have it
on video.
She bought it.
She gave us money for it.
And we have a fridge sitting in our delivery truck.
Let's go to the money counter."
I'm assuming that's some sort of like cash office where they're putting their deposits.
Because I don't know if this story, I know in America when you buy something, it takes
days for it to get delivered.
I don't know if it's more efficient in Vietnam.
But this story, it's very popular in Vietnam.
I don't know if it all took place in a single afternoon or over a day or two in America.
It would take like three weeks to finally get your fridge delivered.
Anyways, the boss goes, "Let's go count the money."
Obviously, she gave you $3 million, right?
And the clerk's like, "Yeah, I mean she might not show it.
She might be invisible to cameras."
But she didn't give me money.
So they go and they go to count the money.
And as they're counting it, they find $3 million, but it's what's known as ghost money.
Ghost money in the Vietnamese folk religion tradition is when somebody dies, you have
this fake money that you burn to send with them in the afterlife.
And there's exactly $3 million in Vietnamese dong in the money counter that is singed ghost
money.
Money that must have been made as an offering at the young woman's funeral.
The same moment that they realized they registered $3 million in ghost money in it.
In the delivery bay, the refrigerator she purchased burst into flames.
It's an interesting ghost story.
This is a very, very popular tale in Vietnam.
You have no names associated with it.
So there's a lot of debate over how real the story is.
The skeptics obviously go, first off they just go, "Ghost don't exist or even waste
my time talking about ghosts."
The skeptics, the ones who do want to engage in conversation, they'll say, "Here's the
thing, we don't have the names of anybody so we can't verify any of this story.
We don't have the name of the clerk, the mother, the delivery driver or the boss.
And any one of those could verify somehow these events happened in one way or the other."
My push, that's true.
And we do encounter that a lot, especially in ghost stories and in paranormal stories
where people don't feel comfortable giving their names.
So that is true.
My counterbalance to that is we do have a date, a city in a specific location, the Big
Sea High Fong Mall.
And we cover stories all the time that I'm like, "I have no idea where this story took
place."
Anywhere in the world.
So that's nice that we have those details.
You have to wonder, let's assume the story is true because I do think it definitely seems
to have the qualities of both like an urban legend, like a Phantom Hitchhiker type story.
But those stories in America, you pick up a pretty young hitchhiker, she's in the back
seat of your car and when you get to her house, she's gone and she left like a wet jacket
in your back seat.
This story involves the exchanging of currency, involves shopping for a while, and then having
a fridge delivered to your mom because you said you were going to get her a fridge and
then the fridge exploding.
You have all these other dramatic elements going on other than just a wet sweater.
I don't know if this story is true exactly, but it's definitely a fascinating one.
This ghost is doing things that ghosts normally don't do.
Shopping malls for one, like obviously she was walking around, she was interacting with
multiple people for this to even take place.
But what's interesting is we recently have that video footage and I was going to cover
it, I didn't get around to it because it just became so popular.
There's a lot of stuff I don't cover not because it's not awesome, but because you
can read about it everywhere and I was like, "Oh yeah, everyone else is already read about
that."
Let me pull up the city real quick.
I didn't plan on doing this, but as I was telling the story, it reminded me of this.
I'll put it in the show notes.
In Argentina, recently there was that security guard who he's sitting at his desk and it's
like late at night, the front door's open and he gets up and he is interacting with
somebody who is not there.
He's talking to him for a bit and then goes back to check something and then he moves
something so she can walk by and then he goes and sits back down and continues with his
day or night, continues with his shift.
And it went around the internet as a man interacting with a ghost.
What happens is that through a series of events, the guard finds out that the woman he saw walk
in that night had died a few hours earlier.
He says that this elderly woman came in and said, "I forgot something in my room."
And he goes, "Oh yeah, sure, go ahead ma'am.
Let me move this out of your way."
He writes it down in the log and she goes into the hospital, but then as this was being investigated,
he finds out she'd been dead a couple of hours before that.
Now the video went around and then you immediately began seeing the debunking and then it stopped
and the debunking is weird.
One of the ones was, obviously people are saying he's just making it up.
He was putting on a little show.
You know how security guards do it three in the morning, put on his show for no one?
They said that the front doors were broken so they kept opening and closing and so this
man, the security guard, and this is all on video.
You can watch it yourself, open the show notes.
If you guys haven't seen it yourselves, it was everywhere.
The officials of the hospital go, "Listen, he was making it up.
What happened was the door was broken so it was opening and closing so many times at a
certain point he decided to get up and pantomime somebody coming in who wasn't really there."
That's what officials of the hospital are saying.
That's not what he's saying.
So it's such a bizarre story in and of itself.
I probably should have done a full segway on it.
But that just happened earlier this year.
I mean, this is what I imagine it would have been like.
They say that they watched the CCTV cameras.
They said there was no trace of the girl, but I'm wondering if there's video footage
of the clerk pantomining the transaction and that's why they said, "Well, let's go check
the money."
Because obviously it looks like you're taking money from someone, but there's clearly no
one standing there.
So then they would go back to check the money.
And I'm wondering if that happened.
Now what's interesting too is the reason why this video from Buenas Aires, from this hospital
in Buenas Aires, the reason why it made the rounds is because it got out.
It went viral, right?
Someone videotaped the videotape and sent it out.
This ghost story about the young woman coming in to buy the fridge for her mom, the reason
why that became popular was because, again, if the story is true, the mother said, "Hey,
this isn't mine.
I didn't order one and oh my god, that's my daughter's name on that receipt."
I wonder how many times ghosts do interact with people on a daily basis because here's
the thing, if nobody ever questioned the security guard, he would just say, "Yeah, some lady
came in."
He wouldn't even mention it to anybody.
It wouldn't be until it was brought to his attention and be like, "Hey, why did we see
on video you talking to nobody?"
And he's like, "What?"
"No, I was talking to someone.
What time?"
"Yeah, I wrote it down in the logbook.
She was in room 915, right?"
And they're like, "Yeah, she was dead already, dude."
You may be at your work, you may be walking through the mall or out in public, and you
may have a full interaction with a ghost and you don't know it.
You have no idea what's going on.
Now, obviously, if it was your grandpa, if you're sitting there drinking a smoothie and
your grandpa shows up, it was like, "I got one more last thing to tell you, Jimmy."
You're like, "Grandpa, you've been dead for 20 years.
You know that's a ghost."
But if it was a ghost of someone you didn't know and you're at work and someone shows
up and they're like, "Hey, do you have a slim gym so I can get into my car?"
I locked my keys in my car and you're like, "Sorry, ma'am, we don't have slim gyms here."
She's like, "Okay."
Would you ever know you interacted with a ghost?
You're the only person sitting there.
Apparently, you weren't going to gas station.
You're like, "What?"
"I didn't know that."
You weren't going to gas station.
Someone comes in and asks you for a slim gym.
If you don't know what slim gym you're like, "What?
You're not feeding this poor lady?"
Slim gym is a tool you use to pop open car locks.
Slim gyms.
I don't even know if that's a term anymore.
They're pretty illegal to carry unless you work at a auto shop.
But we used to use them.
You get a slim gym.
So you imagine that that could happen.
And what happened was 40 years ago, that young woman locked her keys in her car and she couldn't
get in and some madman buried a hatchet in her neck.
You don't know.
I mean, obviously, now you're super paranoid.
Never someone's talk to you.
You're like, "Okay, wait.
Before we continue this conversation, are you a soul of the damned?"
What?
And they go, "Yes."
And they disappear in a puff of smoke.
You're like, "Ugh."
It's the third time this day.
I wonder how often it happens.
Again, we had checks and balances with the Argentina story and with the Vietnam story.
But it's possible that people are interacting with ghosts all the time and they don't know
it.
But this Vietnam story I love because you have this idea of the ghost spending money,
spirit money, which is a huge thing in Vietnamese culture.
You burn it.
It's not just at the funeral.
That's a big part of it.
But it's at the funeral.
It's on the annual memorial of the funeral and the first and the 15th of every month.
You buy this fake money and you burn it.
And the idea is that you are using it to pay off the debt of the dead or to use it to bribe
the God of the dead to bring you back to life.
Super interesting ritual.
I actually have a follow-up story about that.
I want to save.
We're running out of time here.
But it's a fascinating story.
Can it ghost interact with us?
That's always the big question.
How much power do they have on earth?
We have people just walking around houses and you go, "Yeah, I just have a weird feeling
here when I go in a certain room.
It's cold."
And I'm not discounting those.
I'm not discounting those experiences.
But I'm just talking about different power levels of ghosts.
You can be in a house and you go, "No, no, it totally haunted.
I've never seen anything."
But trust me, you feel it.
And then you have other ghosts that can appear as just the head floating down the hallway.
That was a particularly terrifying story.
Put it in the show notes.
We also have full body apparitions.
We have ghosts that can throw things around.
You see how we have this power level growing?
But it's super rare.
I mean, this might be a one-off case where a ghost walks into a mall carrying currency,
which doesn't look all burned up when she hands it to the cashier.
This is a reality warping spirit.
Fascinating story.
But there's any truth to it.
This would be one of the most powerful ghosts that we've come across.
It's very rare.
I know it's popular in movies, but it's very rare that ghosts kill people.
And this would be even more rare.
A ghost that can exchange currency for goods.
And what really cued them off was the mom saying my daughter's been dead and the refrigerator
bursting into flames.
If that didn't happen, if those things didn't happen, if she just came in and bought some
watermelons and carried them out and she de-manifest the watermelons, she goes *blows*
No one's gonna watch surveillance footage to see why that woman threw the water.
They just see some watermelons laying on the ground and some guy would walk out and be
like, "Ah, I need to sweep them up, mop them up, and go about his day."
On the one hand, this is incredibly rare.
I've never come across a story like it before.
But on the other hand, this might be fairly common.
This might happen more often than not.
We just don't have a chain of events where we can look back and go that was a ghost.
Ghosts could be interacting with us on a daily basis, and they just seem like everyone else
around us.
We can't even tell.
And there's no reason for us to tell that that guy who's standing in front of us to
get coffee, who gets his coffee and turns around and walks out of the coffee shop, you're
gonna be like, "I wonder if that guy was dead."
You would have no reason to think anything about that.
But he was dead.
He died four years ago.
But he was able to come in and get a hot cup of coffee and walk out.
Just leaves, you never see him again.
Okay, guys, I gotta be honest.
I gotta be honest with you, I'm having a really hard time with indians lately.
Like I can't even come up with a good spooky indie.
There was a golden age of indians for Dead Rabbit Radio.
There was a time where after I got done doing an episode, I was like, "Oh man, that ending
was dope."
That was like a little short story.
Nowadays, it's just a dude walking in coffee.
That's it.
That's all I got.
Oh, Dead Rabbit Radio.
I gotta figure something out about these indians.
DeadRabbitRadio@gmail.com is gonna be our email address.
You can also use it at facebook.com/DeadRabbitRadio.
Big talk is @DeadRabbitRadio.
DeadRabbitRadio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast.
You don't have to listen to it every day.
I'm glad you listened to it today.
Have a great one.
Bye.
(upbeat music)
[MUSIC]