When four young men learned the location of a fabulous pirate's treasure, the only thing
standing between them and untold riches is the Glauchester Ghoul.
And then we travel to Moscow, Idaho to take a look at a true crime story that's taken
America by storm.
Four college students were brutally murdered in one night.
In this otherwise sleepy college town.
But is it possible they were not killed by a human, but by a giant creature that emerged
from the bowels of the earth?
Today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host, Jason Carpenterder, I'm having a great day.
I hope you guys are having a great day too.
I hope you guys are having tons of fun out there in the world and have some cool plans
for the week and I am feeling much, much better.
95% I'm just so sleepy.
That's really what I've come, that's really what I've come away with after my COVID bowels.
Just sleepy.
I'd rather be sitting in a chair with a heating pad on my back napping.
I guess I was like that pre-COVID too.
I guess this is not a big difference from how I normally am.
But someone who's always ready to tuck me in and put a heating pad on my back is one
of our Christmas livestream contributors.
Everyone give it up for IANA Paul.
Woohoo!
Yeah, come on in!
Yay!
Come on in to Dead Rabbit Command, IANA.
You're gonna be our captain, our pilot this episode.
You guys can't support the show financially if you don't want to touch me while I'm trying
to fall asleep.
That's fine too.
Just help spread the word about Dead Rabbit Radio.
That helps out so much.
And then look at this.
We got this submission for Fan Art Friday.
This was made by Minimum Zucchini.
Minimum Zucchini sent over this fairly apocalyptic and disgusting picture of a bloodied Dead Rabbit
doing his best to still listen to the show even though all of humanity has fallen.
Minimum Zucchini, thank you for sending that over.
That's totally awesome.
I love that little guy.
He's pretty gross looking.
But I still love him.
Let's give him a heating pad for his back.
Let him get a good rest after the apocalypse.
IANA, let's go ahead and get this episode started off.
I'm gonna toss you the keys to the Jason Jalopy we're gonna leave behind Dead Rabbit Command.
Why don't you drive us all the way out to Rhode Island.
Nice little leisurely journey in the Jason Jalopy across the United States with IANA
at the wheel.
This story was actually recommended to me so I want to give a shout out.
In a roundabout way by a longtime Dead Rabbit radio supporter and Patreon supporter Zachary
McCree, he sent me a link to a book and he goes, "Hey, do you think this book would be
worth reading?
Do you think this would be a cool book?"
It was called The United States of Cryptids, a tour of American myths and monsters.
I didn't read the book.
He sent me the link.
I didn't read the book, but it had a couple of different monsters listed that they were
gonna talk about.
I was like, "Oh, I've never heard of this one, the Glauchester Ghoul."
So I would probably recommend the book even though I've never read it and I've never
liked it because we did get at least one cool story out of it.
And I want to give a shout out to strangenewengland.com.
I didn't read the book, but I did go to this website and I got less of my information from
that so I'm giving them a shout out as well.
You want to know what's really weird?
I've lived in this place for about 10 years at this point.
There's never been an owl outside my window.
I don't know if the mic's big enough to pick that up.
I'm recording out in the living room.
I woke up to an owl.
I wish it was in my bedroom.
Bring me a little magical note.
But I didn't hear it.
I just outside my window.
Who, who, who?
And it's weird.
There's an owl outside my window and anyone who knows anything about the paranormal knows
that the owls are not what they seem.
So it's kind of interesting to me from getting up to my aliens at night.
Who knows?
Hopefully not.
Hopefully not for them because I beat them up.
We're hanging out now on Glauchester Road Island.
That's so weird.
He's still hoon out there.
It's summer 1893.
So put on your pioneer clothes and your little straw-fatched hat and we're walking around
town.
They're like, "Dude, that's totally a different time period."
We're close to the beginning of the 1900s.
We're wearing pants that were sewn by people.
We're not dressed up like a bunch of hucked fins.
And we're walking, we're not listening to them.
We're walking around as much hucked fins as we write in their history books.
We're walking around Glauchester Road Island and we're about to meet this young man.
His name is Albert Hicks.
He's a 19-year-old kid who grew up on the East Coast and he had always heard stories
about pirate treasure hidden everywhere.
He grew up with these stories and he always wanted to have his own pirate treasure.
But he's like, "You know what?
I could, though I'm become a pirate, I could go out and murder a bunch of people and steal
their money or," Albert thinks to himself, "What if I simply stole money from a pirate?"
Which is an even worse idea, right?
That's like being like, "Oh, I could be a drug dealer or I could just rob drug dealers.
That seems easier.
It's not, it's far more dangerous.
What if I stole the treasure of a pirate who's already dead and I don't want to worry about
nothing, right?
That's, that's using the old nog in Albert.
Albert had heard stories about Captain Kid, world famous pirate Captain Kid, and apparently
he had buried his treasure in Glauchester Road Island.
And Albert had also heard stories that at one point there is this farm in Glauchester
where some old Spanish doubloons were once found.
Some of them were out tilling the field in their huckfin hat.
And then all of a sudden, "Mawr, what's that?
Bessie, quit pulling this hoe.
Let me stop and jump out off of you, your back or however I did this."
Farmer Joe gets down.
"Well, tarnation, what's this?
This ain't corn.
This looks like one of them doubloons."
And then he finds a couple more and then he's less excited the next couple of times.
Like, "Oh great, more Spanish gold.
I just want to get corn."
So Albert goes, "I think I know where the treasure's probably buried.
It's probably buried near that farm where people keep finding gold coins."
It's just a guess, guys.
Albert Hicks gets a couple of his buddies together.
They said, "Let's go out there at night and dig up this gold."
So it's late at night, summer of 1893.
They got their shovels, probably a couple pickaxes too, in case you find a rock.
You want to smash it up real good.
They're digging it up and every show, often, of course, one of them would kind of poke
their head up and kind of look around, make sure no one sees them and they dig a little
bit more and then someone else would kind of look around.
And they just saw, you know, the night sky has enveloped the entire area.
They see the farmhouse in the distance.
They look to their left, they look to their right.
There's forests all around this farm as well, but they just keep digging and then all of
a sudden they hear a strange sound.
They don't say exactly what the sound is.
I'm sure any sound other than a shovel hitting dirt would put you on alert.
They hear a strange sound and everyone kind of looks up in the direction of the sound
and that's when they see it.
The Glauchester ghoul.
So what it's known as.
This was the very first sighting of this creature.
Albert Hicks described it as, this would be quite frightening, really.
I mean, any monster coming out of the woods in the middle of the night would be scary.
But this one's the size of a cow, which are huge.
Like I don't think most people know how big cows are because they don't see them every
day.
This thing comes out of the woods.
It's as big as a cow with these massive eyeballs.
Let me finish.
You're like, okay Jason, everything has an eyeball.
That's not that spooky.
But you didn't let me finish.
I know it took a kind of a long pause there.
It walks out of the woods and it has these massive eyeballs that look like flaming orbs
stuck in its socket.
See?
You let me finish.
You let me get to the flame.
It's always scarier.
And to be fair, any giant thing, even if it was just a cow in the middle of the night,
that would be alarming enough.
But this is this giant creature.
As this creature is walking towards them, they notice that every breath it takes, flame
shoots out of its mouth the nostrils.
So any illusion that this is ordinary at all, right?
If you saw something with big flaming eyeballs, you might go, that's weird.
But maybe it's just a trick of the like.
Maybe it's this old timey LSD I've been taking.
You could look at something that was spitting out flame and had flaming eyeballs and I
mean it would be terrifying.
But the fact that the flames are burning the bushes around this beast as it's walking
out of the forest shows that this creature simply doesn't have the appearance of flame
or it's some sort of bizarre optical illusion.
No.
It's fire shooting out of this creature and it's burning the brush around it.
The bushes and the foilage are actually becoming singed as this creature is simply moving through
the area.
The creature is also described as having massive wings, these two big black leathery wings
sticking out of its back.
Giant spiral horns as thick as a stovepipe?
I don't know how big a stovepipe this is either.
I'm sure that's impressive.
But anyways, I imagine like two Abraham Lincoln hats on this guy's head.
That's the best I can imagine.
Then that's just kind of funny.
The Gloucester ghoul also had feet that were webbed like a duck.
Okay, wait a second.
These guys are standing in the middle of the night.
They never say how far away this thing is.
The detail in the description would make me think it's pretty close.
I'm thinking within 20 yards.
But if something was coming out of the darkness, it was big as a cow, it was breathing flame,
it had giant wings.
I don't think I'd be like, "I wonder what its feet look like."
It would be hard to notice is what I'm saying.
It would be hard to see what type of feet it had.
It almost sounds like a tall tail at this point.
These kids are out there trying to dig up some gold and they see this big monster coming
out with duck feet and everything else, two Abraham Lincoln hats.
But maybe, I mean this thing is putting off an awful lot of light.
It keeps setting stuff on fire.
So maybe they got a good look at its feet.
It had webbed feet like a duck and it smelled, this is an old timey smell.
This is something that no modern person would know what it smelled like.
They just, it would have been close too for them to smell this.
They said it smelled like burned wool.
What was that word she just said?
This is one of those words that people say I mispronounce and I'm pretty sure I'm pronouncing
it correctly.
Wool.
Like, you know, you make a wool sweater out of sheep wool.
You shave it off and then you sew it all together.
You just sew it on me.
I look like a giant sheep and run it on the street.
Thanks mom.
Wool.
So it smelled like burned wool.
And again, that's, I don't think anyone knows what that smells like.
You're like, yeah, Jesus, nobody knows what wool is.
It's not a Ypres answer.
I'm pretty sure I got it right.
Burned wool.
It's a very, very detailed description of a cryptid, but the reason why I really love
this particular monster is we get a detail that we don't often get with cryptids.
It's one of those things.
You don't think about the absence of this detail until it appears and you go, hmm, that's
interesting.
Like how come more cryptids don't have this?
How come we don't know this about more cryptids?
It's very, very interesting.
The question is what sound does it make?
And I'm not talking about its battle cry or, you know, it's like screaming at the edge
of the river or the Bigfoot call from the woods.
No.
Because a lot of cryptids are, it should make some noise.
They should make some noise just naturally moving about.
Let's read this description that Albert told us, quote, "The body was covered with scales
as big as clamshells, which made a rattling noise as the beast moved along.
We very rarely get a sound of a chupacabra scuttling."
Well, here's stories of like a Bigfoot marching through the woods and things like that, but
a lot of times it's interacting with the trees and things like that.
But for the amount of cryptids that are out there, very rarely do we get someone describe
what the sound is like when they move.
So it's very, very interesting detail.
It's not absent from all cryptid stories, but it's absent from enough that it does make
you think, are these things actually some sort of biological entity or is this from
somewhere else?
Anything on earth is going to make noise.
I'm sure cows make a noise when they walk.
They definitely would if they were covered in armor.
They definitely would if they were covered in these shells.
They're kind of clinking and clinking against each other.
So just an interesting detail.
I really like that.
And let me go ahead and continue because there's another really cool detail with this.
For a creature that's emitting this much flame.
It's going to be, where's it coming from?
Right?
It's coming out of its mouth.
It's coming out of its nose.
Its eyeballs look like they're on fire, but let's look at this detail.
"The body was covered with scales as big as clam shells, which made a rattling noise as
the beast moved along.
The scales flopped up and down.
The thing had lights on its sides, like those shining through a tin lantern."
So what Albert and his friends are seeing is the light, there's so much flame being generated
in this thing.
It's actually penetrating the skin, the actual glow is penetrating the skin.
And they're seeing it in between the shells clinking and clinking against each other.
It actually looks like there's a lantern in there.
That's a really fascinating detail to this thing.
That makes it feel more biological rather than just fire shooting out of the nose.
That's kind of dragon, that's kind of mythological, right?
You can go, "Well, I wonder where the fire came from and we can kind of make up stories
about how a dragon could breathe fire."
This one, whatever flame it's breathing out, is actually being generated within a biological
form.
And because there's so much heat and energy in there, you can see it through the skin
and you catch glimpses of it in between the armor, in between those scales kind of flopping
up and down.
You can kind of see inside this glow.
Fascinating creature.
And Albert and his buddies, they see this thing, it's relatively close to them, they don't
give us an exact measurement, but it's close enough to smell.
It's close enough to notice these details.
And Albert said as this creature was getting closer, he felt like he was being suffocated.
This creature doesn't even have to get them, doesn't have to set on fire, doesn't have
to trample them, doesn't have to eat them.
Just being in its presence is sucking the wind out of their lungs.
Very, very powerful creature.
Albert and his friends, they go, "You know what?
We don't even know if the gold's here in the first place.
Let's leave."
And they actually took off running, disappeared in the night.
Albert said, "We never saw where the creature went."
He almost disappeared as quickly as he appeared, but I don't know where he went.
I never went back there.
I'm pretty sure there's some fiber gold in it on that farm, but I'm never going back
there.
I believe, the reason why he put two and two together, he said, "I believe that this
creature was there to guard Captain Kid's gold."
We have a lot of stories of hidden gold, hidden by Native Americans, hidden by conquistadors,
hidden by pirates, and there is some sort of creature there, guarding it.
There's stories of long lost gold mines that are guarded by, I think we did an episode
on it, there was like a glowing skeleton in the area that was to ward off people.
That might have been a different glowing skeleton, but I know in the Southwest, the American
Southwest, there are stories of lost mines.
The Native Americans are like, "You guys can't come back here."
And there's a guardian spirit that will kill prospectors trying to find that.
And even this is unusual for a pirate treasure to be guarded by a ghost or some sort of beast.
I'm sure that there are magics that one can learn and one can use to create a cursed location
like this.
The farmer could be out there all day long and never see this creature.
He's trying to hook up a big hodowit.
What are those?
He's trying to hook up a big plowdowit.
He's like, "Come on, Betsy, let's go.
He's all burning himself as he's getting close to it."
I was like, "Oh man, it smells like burned wool."
But I'm sure there is some spell you could cast that could curse the area if you came
looking for the gold.
What's interesting is there is only two accounts of this Glauchester ghoul.
It's only been seen twice.
Both times in the 1800s, the last time, really the second and last time it was ever seen,
was on January 13th, 1896, a fellow named Neil Hopkins.
He said he was on his way home from work.
And this is old time.
So like he was working in another state and then walking back to Rhode Island.
He was like coming from New Hampshire or something like that.
He was passing through the area on his way home from work at night and he saw the Glauchester
ghoul.
And then the other sighting of it.
Now, that kind of sinks my own theory that you can only see if you're looking for the
gold.
But maybe as he was walking through the area, he's like, "Oh man, you know, I probably
should work in the same state that I live in if only I had some gold."
It's interesting, he describes the same beast down to the clanking of the armor.
He describes it in the same way.
You could hear it coming.
He said when the shells, when the chain armor, you know, that kind of that description, it's
a little like piece overlaying another piece, overlaying another piece.
He goes, "When it was walking towards me, it sounded like steel striking steel."
That's how heavy this armor was.
And when he saw it, it was not the size of a cow.
It was the size of an elephant.
Big difference between the two, right?
It was the size of an elephant and it didn't lazily walk through the area.
This thing chased him.
This thing started pursuing him through the area and he ran and eventually said, "I turned
around and disappeared."
He just wasn't there anymore.
The only proof was my stained pantaloons that this experience ever happened.
The Glauchester Ghoul.
It's never been seen since.
It's fascinating creature though.
I love it.
But it's fascinating cryptid.
I just love the amount of detail we get from it.
Is it still out there?
Is it more of a ward that is protecting this treasure?
If it is, it's so detailed.
Again, like making the set.
The other one was just like a glowing skeleton going, "Oh, I can stay away."
He didn't even talk.
I mean, I guess if it's a glowing skeleton, you're not going to be like, "Well, you know,
he is in the location of this hidden treasure.
I wonder if he might be having to do something else."
If only he could speak and tell us.
A glowing skeleton would be bad enough.
But you have this creature with all this detail.
Absolutely fascinating.
That's the story of the Glauchester Ghoul.
As we're packing up all of our stuff, we stole the treasure.
We found it with our grand penetrating radar.
As we're packing up all our stuff to leave, we see Albert Hicks kind of wave into us in
the distance, waving goodbye.
We're like, "Hey, see you later, little Albie."
Man, that guy sure was helpful.
I wonder if he'll ever pop up in some terrifying true crime story in a future episode.
He just kind of shrugs his shoulders and he walks away.
We're like, "What?
How did he hear that from that far away?
He's super far away."
Well, bye, Albert.
Hope you don't have a super tragic end anytime soon.
Ionapole, let's go ahead and toss you the keys to the carbonicopter we are leaving behind
Rhode Island, fly us all the way out to Moscow, Idaho.
Ionapole land this carbonicopter here in Moscow, Idaho.
It's November 13th, 2022.
I've been talking a lot about this story on my YouTube shorts and my TikToks.
It's a very fascinating true crime story, but if you guys aren't up to speed on it,
I'll give you guys a quick overview.
On November 13th, 2022 in Moscow, Idaho, you have the University of Idaho and then you
have off-campus housing.
People are always hanging out, doing homework, partying, just growing up, right?
Just living your best life.
In this particular house, there were five people who were living in it.
We had Madison Mogan, Kaylee Goncaves, and Zana Kernoodle.
And then there were two other unnamed roommates that were living in this house.
And it was a party house.
People in the area go, "They're all party houses."
But a lot of people were in and out of this house over the years, really, even before
they moved in.
It was just off-campus housing for a college.
On November 13th, we had another person staying the night there, Ethan Chappan.
That was Zana's boyfriend.
He was spending the night over at his girlfriend's house.
What happens is when the sun rises, later that morning, four people are found murdered.
Madison, Kaylee, Zana, and Ethan.
They're all dead.
They've all been stabbed to death in the house.
I've heard reports that they were beheaded as well.
I don't know how authentic those are, and we'll kind of get into that.
We're getting a lot of little pieces of what could be coming out of this story.
But I also want to focus more on the cryptid part for this.
I'm just giving you a quick overview.
It was super interesting because I remember when this happened, you're starting to get
these little bits of information coming out saying four people were murdered in a house.
And you go, "The first inclination is drug deal gone wrong.
These kids got into something.
They were selling Xanax on the sly.
And they thought that they could get away with robbing some drug dealer."
They were all killed.
The first thing that I thought of, because you don't think, "Oh, it's just scream six.
It's just a horror movie.
That's real."
But as the days end, the police said the public is in no danger.
They made that statement the first day, which normally means they know who did it, and the
victims caused it in one way or the other.
Not saying that they deserved it, but they pissed off the wrong person.
So the average housewife doesn't have to worry about it.
This was a situation which is something.
They eventually changed that.
They go, "Well, we can't promise that we can't.
We as the police cannot promise no one's in danger."
Because it turned out that they didn't know who did it, and they didn't have a motive.
And for over a month, nobody knew what was going on.
What we knew of was that, this is what we were told, four people were killed in a house,
and two roommates slept through it.
So you're starting to think, "How do you kill four people with a knife?
Maybe they're not beheaded, but how do you kill four people with a knife?"
Without waking up two people in other rooms.
Now it was a multi-story house, but still, you can stab a couple people in your sleep.
Don't get me wrong.
But four, and if someone was able to successfully stab four people in their sleep, you would
assume that this is an experienced killer, aka drug deal gone wrong.
What's interesting?
What we found out was the police eventually did have a suspect.
His name is Brian Coburger.
His 28-year-old man, he was arrested in Pennsylvania where his parents lived, but he did go to
school in the area.
He didn't know them.
I know there are stories coming out now that he dated them and that he might have stalked
one of them.
We don't know, but what we do know is that he was a criminal justice major.
He was really into the psychology of the macabre.
What could cause a man to kill that type of stuff?
Which there's nothing wrong with that, but it also can lead, we have seen cases in the
past where those people go, "Well, I'm smarter than the cops.
I'll pull off the perfect crime."
Now he's arrested.
He's been arrested.
He did, I mean, allegedly, right?
There's been no trial yet, but they basically have a knife sheath.
There was a military-style knife sheath found at the location of the murders that has genealogical
DNA on it that connects to him.
They have not officially said that it's his DNA, but they use that DNA to go through genealogical,
you know, the 23andMe type things and they found his dad.
So that's kind of concrete, unless his dad was also in the area.
They connected it to him.
They also were able to ping his phone.
We talked about this on a recent episode, the geocaching, or geofencing is what it's
called, I'm sorry, where they can look at a particular area and see where their phones
are and it appears that he was in that area quite often before and a little bit after the
murders, but not on the day of.
And we also have learned now that the police were holding information back from us.
One of the roommates wasn't asleep.
They didn't reveal this because they didn't want the guy coming back and killing her.
She had woken up in the middle of the night and had heard one of the young women crying
and she heard an unfamiliar male voice say, "It's okay.
I'm going to help you."
She also heard another one of her roommates in this same time period.
One of her roommates, one of the murder victims was on their phone on TikTok.
We believe that this was Zana because we see that she was on TikTok at 4.12 in the morning.
But she hears what is presumably Zana on TikTok and Zana says, probably to someone on the
phone, probably to someone on the TikTok app, "There's someone here."
And the roommate is hearing this kind of going on.
She's hearing a dog bark and she's hearing these weird comments.
There is the sound, security cameras in the area at 4.17 picked up the sound of someone
or something whimpering, a loud thud, and then the sound of a dog barking over and over and
over again.
At one point, the roommate opened up her bedroom door and she looked out into the darkened
interior of the house and she saw a man wearing all black with a black face mask covering his
nose and his mouth walking towards her.
She froze and he just kind of walked by and then walked out a sliding glass door.
So he may not have seen her.
Maybe he did.
We don't know.
She said he was about 5'10.
He had bushy eyebrows.
That's all I knew.
He was a white dude.
That's all she could gather from that.
What's super weird?
You can kill four people.
We now know that one of the roommates was awake, did hear this stuff.
The roommates did not report the murders until noon the next day.
They actually called their friends over to the house.
The story is weird.
The story is so weird.
They called their friends over to the house and all these kids are stomping all over the
crime scene and then they called the police.
So there may be more information.
There may be other arrests coming out.
We don't know.
But that's a quick overview of the Moscow murders.
But that's not why we're here today because I covered this stuff on my TikTok channel.
We're here today because it's taking a turn for the weird.
I want to dig into this conspiracy theory.
This makes sense, right?
We have this case that millions of people are interested in and we're getting this drip
drop of details and even after we get affidavits some of the details still don't make sense.
Why did they wait so long to call the police?
Four people had been butchered.
There's blood everywhere.
The cops came in and they go, "There's blood on the walls!"
It's not like they came in and be like, "Hey, we can't wait Kaylee up.
Call her a friend.
Maybe Kaylee's friend can help wake her up."
They were bloodied.
Anyways, you have a story that's this big.
Of course you're going to get conspiracy theories about it.
Did the roommates have anything to do with it?
Is Brian the soul murderer?
Is he even the guilty one?
What could possibly be going on?
Then we take a look at the crazy academic.
This person posted a theory online recently that maybe they were killed by Bigfoot.
Hold all your questions till the end and they will be numerous.
I probably won't be able to answer most of them.
But I find this so fascinating.
Let's put on a conspiracy cap on early on this segment.
I do want to say, yes, Bigfoot is not known to be walking around the roads.
He's a forest creature, a rural creature.
But I do want to say this.
We focus so much on missing 411, these mysterious disappearances that take place in the woods
every so often.
They're quite rare.
People go missing in the woods.
They're never seen again.
Is it some sort of unknown force?
Is it some sort of cryptid?
Is it some sort of portal?
Way more people go missing in the suburbs in the inner city than ever go missing in the
outdoors.
So keep that in mind because I will say you might have missing 411, but this is missing
911.
These are mass disappearances in urban and suburban environments and murders and things
like this.
So while I don't think, I don't want to play my cards too early, but while I don't think
Bigfoot actually murdered these four people, I think it is possible that there is a cryptid
crime wave going on and we are not aware of it.
Let's take a look at the crazy academic story.
He says that it was Bigfoot.
He said it was Bigfoot or the Nephilim, the half human half demon or technically half
human half angel giants that once walked the earth.
Now I don't know how tall the population is at University of Idaho.
I don't know if there is any 13 or 18 feet tall monstrosities currently walking around
the campus.
You know it is interesting because his conspiracy theory while intriguing, gosh darn it if you
don't believe that there are some holes in the theory that a cryptid might have killed
these kids, but one, he said, I mean I guess I have heard this before, but I didn't know
it was mainstream.
He says that the Nephilim or the giants live in the hollow earth.
What?
I mean I have heard, I know we supposedly found graves of giant skeletons, stuff like that.
We have done a dozen episodes on that phenomenon, but you have the giant skeletons.
I guess I never heard so much that they lived in hollow earth.
That would be the worst place for a giant to be that the ceilings are much lower.
You are underground.
Why would you be underground?
If you were half human half demon, if you survived the great flood, you would just be
like welcome back boys, you would just be kicking tanks over and throwing jets at the
White House.
Like why would you hide underground?
I know the theory of hollow earth and I know the theory of advanced civilizations.
I guess I am just, is that a new thing?
Is that a new thing that people are saying that that is where the Nephilim went underground?
They are living underground.
But anyways, so that the Nephilim burst out of the earth, at least one of them, and made
his way through this college town.
He is all stuff and he is getting a couple of drinks and he is hanging out.
He has all these Mardi Gras beads around his neck and then he is walking through town.
He, a Nephilim burst out of the earth or Bigfoot burst out of the earth.
You are like what?
Okay, you are going to do a lot of head scratching here.
Or Bigfoot also pops out of a hole in the earth.
You are like what is this fascination with holes in the earth?
I don't know.
It is not my theory.
Anyways, that Bigfoot burst out of a hole in the earth.
I have never heard that theory that Bigfoot lives in the earth.
I mean, I guess it would make sense.
He would explain why he is so hard to find, but the ceiling is too low.
He jumps out of a hole, which would be so awesome to see if I ever see Bigfoot.
I hope he is not just walking through the forest.
I hope I am just standing there admiring nature's beauty.
Then all of a sudden I see Bigfoot jump out of a hole.
He is Michael Jackson getting ready to start his show in Vegas.
He has like this springboard contraption that throws him 20 feet into the air and then he
lands in front of me and then grabs his crotch.
Bigfoot jumping out of a hole, Nevilleen jumping out of a hole.
This is his proof that these people weren't killed by a human.
He says, "One, there is video footage of strange entities in the area."
There is not.
I watched the footage he was talking about originally, so there is footage that was taken
of a street and there is like a police dashcam or something like that.
This footage though from a street and you see four, not one giant, not one huge Bigfoot.
Again, people would notice it.
They see four little shadowy figures walking off in the distance.
But I mean it looks blurry.
Anyone who knows anything about cameras and a lot of people who don't know anything about
cameras knows that stuff in the dark far away is not going to be picture perfect.
But again, that blows his own thing.
If he thinks it's Nevilleen, they were ordinary looking blobs walking out of the street.
The fact that you found the knife sheath at the murder scene, which was a military styled
knife, like probably like a K-bar or something like that.
The academic, the crazy academic says that that is proof of a quote "sophisticated military
operation."
So it wasn't just that someone just went and bought a K-bar off Amazon.
It's that they sent in special forces and they engaged this creature in the house and
after the battle between man and Bigfoot was over, the guy left his sheath there.
That's his takeaway from the fact that they found the sheath there.
I was reading an article, the other in Fox News, they said, "Brian might have left it
there on purpose.
This might not have been his very first killings."
It's really interesting to go from zero murders to four in one night.
We do see mass shooters obviously do that, but it's still odd.
The whole story is odd.
But anyway, so it's not so odd that I think Bigfoot was there as interesting as that would
be.
The knife sheath being left there is a sign that there were military operatives there that
were killing this creature or chasing it off.
I mean, I guess you could even argue that these four people saw proof of the Nephilim
coming out of the middle of the earth and then the military went and silenced them and
left their sheath there.
Remember of this worldwide conspiracy to stop all knowledge of cryptids and they're like,
"Jeffrey, did you leave your sheath there?"
And he's like, "Oh no, oh, oh, spaghetti!"
Like he's capable of covering up hidden beasts from man's prying eyes, but he can't remember
to pick up his sheath.
But proof that there were military there in the theory of the crazy academic, there was
one thing that he said, which I think this conspiracy theory, I find it very evocative.
That's why I wanted to talk about it.
I don't think it's true.
I do think you could chalk up some missing people in suburban and urban environments
and some people who are brutally killed in those environments as well.
I think you could chalk up a very small portion of those two cryptids.
A very, very small portion of them.
If they exist, right, if we believe that these creatures exist, every so often you'll hear
a new story about an orangutan just tearing butt through the middle of Charleston.
Every so often you'll hear about like a crocodile loose in a daycare center, which actually
sounds hilarious.
But anyways, I don't know if I've actually ever read that news story, but that would
be fun.
So why not?
If you can have a natural creature outside of its habitat, you could easily have a Big
Foot wander into a town or some other unknown cryptid wander into a town and snack.
There's been a ton of sightings of the, I think, what is it?
Off the top of my head, the Illinois.
I think we see a lot of it in Chicago.
We did an episode on it before, The Winged Beast.
They call it the Mothman or the Batman, but I think a lot of people get it confused with
the Mothman, the more famous Mothman, from Point Pleasant that predicts catastrophes.
No, this is just some weird monstrosity that's been seen flying around the city of Chicago.
So we do have urban cryptids.
We've covered one or two on the show.
See if I can find those episodes for the show notes.
But yeah, I'm not against the idea in and of itself.
I find it fascinating.
It's in poor taste, but that's never stopped me before.
We do, though, have this.
This is something I didn't know about.
And I want to end the episode like this because we are officially running long.
He said that there's been, this is why he was so fixated on the inner earth and things
blowing up.
He said that there had been a series of explosions in Idaho recently.
And what that might have been was the creature or creatures blowing a hole through the earth
and jumping out.
I mean, again, if you're going to be, I talked about a cryptid maybe living on the outskirts
of Minneapolis and just grabbing homeless people to feast on before eventually it heads
back to its natural environment deep inside a national forest.
That's the, you know, they don't have spectacular entrances.
They don't have the Michael Jackson-esque jumping out fireworks going up.
But his do.
So I mean, maybe that's just more exciting.
But he's saying that it's possible that you have these explosions going off that are creatures
coming to the earth.
And I was like, what explosions?
And I looked it up and this is weird.
There have been explosions all over, not just Idaho, all over America.
And one of the great things about Ring Doorbell Cams, as hard as it would have been to be
a criminal back when I was, that legally wasn't a criminal.
No, I was never a criminal.
But as much as Ring Doorbell cameras, I'm like, man, poor criminals today.
They just can't get away with anything.
They're great for, they're great for seeing mysterious explosions in the distance.
There's tons of footage of these Ring Doorbell cameras all over America, just filming a porch
at three, four in the morning.
Then all of a sudden there's a bright flash far on the horizon.
And then there's probably about a minute of nothing.
And then the shockwave hits and you hear it like this is a explosion.
They're picking up these explosions, these loud booms.
Now I want to shoot down, crazy academic, I really did enjoy this conspiracy theory.
I know we've been joking about it, but I think it sounds really cool.
I mean, I'm not saying again, I think it's sad that these people died.
But I find it fascinating.
Unfortunately the explosions in Idaho happened on December 3rd.
So that was, the murders happened on November 13th.
So not even close.
And they were 85 miles away from the area.
So I mean, I guess if you're a Nephilim walking 85 miles is nothing.
But still they happened way after the murders.
So it doesn't line up.
But what I thought was super interesting was I started looking up these mysterious booms.
They're happening everywhere.
And nobody knows what they are.
There have been some theories.
Like there were some explosions in Florida and apparently the top secret Air Force fighter
jet reconnaissance plane, whatever, returning to base is breaking the sound barrier.
Not top secret anymore government.
You have that.
It's so interesting because I'm reading all these articles and I'm looking into this.
And each article has a different theory that basically like, yeah, kind of answers it.
But people go, I don't know.
A lot of them say they are meteorites coming in being picked up on these ring doorbell cameras.
You're seeing a meteorite explode.
It's like an air burst meteorite.
There was another thing I found.
I didn't know this was an actual thing.
I don't, I didn't write down the exact term that they use, but what it is basically an
ice quake where you don't need, you don't, you don't need to be an Antarctica for it.
What happens is when a place gets super cold, super fast, it can actually, yeah, probably
should have probably should have taken notes on it.
I was like, wow, that's fascinating.
And then I didn't write anything down.
But basically it's just, imagine when you put a freezing, imagine when you put a Coca
Cola in your freezer and you forget about it and then it explodes.
It's that, but it's happening to the earth.
Not the earth is a whole.
You're not chasing.
I think I would have heard about that.
The earth blew up.
I'm pretty sure you're just making stuff up now.
No, no, no, it's not the whole earth.
But they said, and we did have this huge cold snap this winter.
They said if the temperature drops too quickly, it can actually create a loud cracking sound
coming out of the ground.
So that could count for some of the booming sounds as well.
All of them?
No.
But some of them, some of them might be military equipment.
Some of them might be meteorites.
Some of them might have been these ice quakes that you guys are researching.
You're like Jason, I'm pretty sure you got something wrong.
Maybe.
But the point is, is that the phenomenon is real.
These loud explosions are real.
They're so real that the media asked or addressed them and they're happening everywhere and
there's no one answer.
And I thought that's so interesting because this could have been something that the government
has been trying to cover up.
I'm sure there's a lot of stuff.
I talk about poor criminals out there getting caught by ring doorbell alarms.
I'm sure there is stuff that the government has covered up for decades.
And it used to be that they owned access to all the video cameras and now everyone has
a video camera in their house.
They still have access to it by the way.
The police can log into your camera with no warning and get your footage.
But now everyone has a camera.
Everyone has proof of these things.
Before people would wake up and be like, "Hey Johnny, did you hear that loud boom last night?
It was like three in the morning.
The guy was like, "Well I heard something but I think it was like two in the morning."
And, "Well you just kind of go about your day."
Stufffighter is flying in and it's super top secret and you heard a noise.
And now there's video footage.
There's actually time stamped footage of when the sound happened.
And everyone in the area, you'd say even if 10% of them had these ring doorbell cameras.
Government's like, "Okay fine, that was our stupid stufffighter.
We're trying to keep it in for the rest of the world guys.
Things love for exposing it.
Can't we just land a supersonic plane in peace?"
I'm wondering how much stuff like, I don't know what these noises are.
And it's funny because nobody does.
The one in Florida they've pretty much been pointed was that jet.
But the ones in Idaho, the one everywhere, these are happening everywhere.
Nobody knows what's causing them.
Might be able to explain some of them but can you explain all of them?
It's a fascinating story.
Add it on to a crazy conspiracy.
Is it possible that four college students were murdered by Bigfoot or some other legendary
creature that erupted from the bowels of the earth?
I can see where he got it.
I can see where he put those pieces together to come up with that theory.
I don't think it's true.
It definitely sounds interesting.
It sounds terrifying.
Because it's bad enough that we gotta worry about some crazed weirdo breaking into our
house in the middle of the night and plunging a knife through our throat.
You wake up with a blade that's already pierced your voice box.
You can't even scream for help.
That's bad enough.
Actually, that's so horrific.
I was gonna go, "What if it's Bigfoot?"
You're like, "Jayson, I'd much rather have Bigfoot breaking into my house."
Maybe he strangles me.
Maybe he rips me apart, limp from limb.
That's way less terrifying sound than what you just said.
What do you have to add in that part of the voice box?
Do you lunatic?
Yeah, I probably would rather wake up to have Bigfoot ripping me limb from limb.
It was kind of...
It means I didn't mean to paint such a horrible picture.
That was a little grimmer that I thought it was gonna sound when I started saying it,
but such is life.
DeadRabbitRadio@gmail.com is gonna be our email address.
You can also put this up at facebook.com/DeadRabbitRadio.
Tick-tock is @DeadRabbitRadio.
DeadRabbitRadio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast.
You don't have to listen to it every day, but I'm glad you listened to it today.
Have a great day.
Thanks.
Bye.
(upbeat music)
[MUSIC]