When a man finds himself abducted by aliens, he has no choice but to suck on the tube.
And then we join a young couple at home, enjoying a little bit of time together.
But as they're walking into their kitchen and they hear a loud, yet muffled boom somewhere
off in the distance, they have no idea they're about to tumble into another world.
Today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Carpenter, I'm having a great day.
Hope you guys are having a great day too.
I hope you guys had an awesome weekend.
We got a lot of stuff to cover so we're gonna get started right away.
First off, walking into Dead Rabbit Command.
Everyone giving up for one of our legacy Patreon supporters.
Mikey, Rattamaker.
Woohoo!
Oh yeah, come on in boy!
Come on, I don't know why I always sound like a cowboy.
Cowboy leaning on a bunch of cows.
Do they have to cowboys traditionally clap?
Mikey, you're gonna be our captain or pilot this episode.
If you guys can't support the Patreon, I totally get it.
I really do.
Just help spread the word about Dead Rabbit Radio.
That is another way you can help the show grow.
Mikey's been a longtime contributor to the Patreon and you also have never given me your
address to get your Dead Rabbit Radio supporter stickers.
So if you guys are a supporter of the Patreon and you've never gotten a sticker, you probably
didn't know that you could get one.
Send me your address, send it through Patreon email or any other way you get ahold of me.
And we'll send it out to you because those stickers are cool.
David, I'm gonna go ahead and toss you the command codes for the Dead Rabbit Rocket Ship.
Everyone get on board.
Hope you got your space suit.
I hope you know how to breathe without a space suit.
If you don't have one, hit those buttons and launch us out of Dead Rabbit Command.
We're headed all the way out to an alien spacecraft.
Pfft.
As we are headed straight up to this alien starship, below us on the blue glob known
as Earth, there's a dude.
He doesn't give his name.
He posted this report online.
We're gonna go and call him David.
It's December 29th, 2022 and he said, "The other night I had this dream, but I don't
think it was just a dream."
I don't think it was just a dream.
Now let's take a look at this scenario that he found himself in.
David goes, "To be fair, the first part is a dream.
I fell asleep.
And when I woke up, I was being abducted by aliens."
He describes them as standard gray alien type creatures.
He's walking in this room.
He calls it like a rectangular room that had a glare from all the walls.
There was no identifiable light source.
The whole space seemed lit up.
These are all very standard things we see in alien abduction scenarios.
Those are also things that if you watch enough movies, they could give you the dreams that
would mimic a standard alien abduction scenario.
So right now he could be dreaming.
He could actually be experiencing this.
The gray aliens speak to him telepathically and they tell him the procedures they're
about to do.
He goes, "I don't remember the exact words they used, but they were very polite.
Very polite aliens.
Let me know what I was about to undergo."
And then out of somewhere, he's standing in this room.
Out of somewhere, a hole opens up.
This hose is kind of like floating around.
And it goes into his mouth.
Gull.
And he starts like, it's one of those translucent hoses.
He can see through and he sees this thick red liquid coming slowly towards his mouth.
He's watching it come through the tube towards his mouth.
And he goes, "It was like a reddish liquid and there were darker red particles in this
tube."
It's coming into his mouth, right?
Standard alien stuff.
Totally typical gray alien abduction experience, right?
And then, I don't think I can put this any better than he writes it.
This was posted online by a guy using the name Naze16.
He writes, "Then a liquid began flowing down the hose and into my mouth.
As soon as it hit my taste buds, I couldn't help myself."
And moaned loudly, "Ugh!
As I began greedily chugging it all down, it was the best thing I'd ever tasted."
You go, Jason, why are you- wait, did you find- did you-
I've been to f*cking somebody posting their bizarre fetish disguise as an alien abduction
experience.
That is not for me to decide.
I would never read something like that and think, "Wow, this guy has a fetish."
This is just started.
The story's just started.
And you can't call it a fetish yet.
He does say, as he's telling us about his alien abduction experience, he said that even
now just typing it out is making his mouth water because he loved the taste of this liquid
so much.
Let's continue though, because we want to know about the alien abduction stuff, right?
Quote, "I must have been standing there between a few seconds and a few minutes, but I had
swallowed so much of the liquid that my stomach had began to push out.
And I was expanding."
You have that- listen, man, I don't know if this guy has some weird expansion inflation
fetish, but I will say this.
That is such a small niche of a fetish that if this guy had that fetish and got abducted
by aliens who wanted to do this to him, talk about a match made in heaven.
Because I mean, that's awesome.
If you didn't love getting inflated and the aliens were doing this to you, it would suck.
There's no pun intended as you're sucking down that delicious red liquid.
But then you wonder, could the aliens have given him the fetish?
What do you think about that as I continue to read?
I'm not done.
Okay, quote, "I must have been standing there between a few seconds and a few minutes, but
I had swallowed so much of the liquid that my stomach had began to push out.
And I was expanding rapidly.
I could do nothing but swallow it.
I was enjoying it so much.
I grew bigger and bigger, reaching a size well over that of someone nine weeks pregnant.
I was getting heavier and had to arch my back and hold my hips to prevent myself from falling
forward.
I could hear my belly gurgling and could feel it churning as it continued to swell."
I have no way to follow that up.
I was trying to think of something.
I was like, "That's just perfect, right?
This guy either has an inflation fetish or he has one now.
What?
I just read you some perverts ramblings online?
No.
This is the Arab radio.
This might have been an actual alien abduction because then what happens as he's slurping
up that sweet, sweet crimson goo, he wakes up.
He wakes up.
That was all a dream.
He wakes up and he's lying on his right side underneath the covers and he fills his entire
body vibrate with energy.
Then he hears what he can only describe as an angry alien's voice screaming in his left
ear.
At that time, David starts to realize he's about to be abducted again.
So it wasn't just a dream.
It was real.
And now that he's awake, he's going to get abducted again and this alien is screaming
louder and louder and louder in his ear.
And then he wakes up.
That was a dream too.
That part was a dream too.
But this time he wakes up and he's screaming so loud.
He didn't want to get abducted again even though he did love getting filled up.
He did probably want to drink some of that goo but he started screaming.
He was screaming so loud he woke himself up and this time he wakes up for real and his
stomach is bloated.
Like in real life, he says that his stomach is noticeably bloated and it's gurgling.
So he goes, "Oh man, maybe that wasn't a dream.
Maybe that wasn't a dream."
He also thought it was weird when he woke up for the final time or as far as he knows
this whole podcast might be a dream for him too.
He wakes up from the first dream laying on his right side with the alien screaming in
his ear and then when he wakes up for the final time, he's on his right side as well
and he thought that was weird.
Like he was on the same side both times.
Anyways, let's get back to his stomach.
Let's get back to his gurgling stomach because he likes to spend a lot of time on this.
He calls himself, when he wakes up, he's "noticably bloated."
And then he, that's an intro, what's noticeably bloated?
Right?
Like I don't know how you would define that.
I'm also morbidly obese.
I mean it might be hard for me to notice it.
But maybe if you're like 90 pounds you could tell if you're noticeably bloated.
But David says that he hadn't eaten much before bed or even that whole evening and he didn't
feel hungry at all, just "mildly bloated."
So apparently there's a difference between mildly bloated and noticeably bloated.
I don't know what that is.
And here this is again, I'm not gonna say that this guy has an inflation fetish, but
you're spending a lot of time talking about how bloated you are and drinking it in that
goop.
But you know, again maybe the average listener right now that are patting their tummy and
they're like noticeably bloated.
I know what that means.
Anyways, if you're worried about David's safety, don't worry.
Just a couple hours later his stomach was now just slightly bloated according to him.
That's a lot of different variations of bloated.
I've only heard people go "I feel bloated."
And then they don't.
They're not like "ah man, slightly bloated."
But at least it's not noticeable as they're touching their stomach.
He said he's also, he did a follow up post to this.
This wasn't just a single post talking about him ingesting this liquid that makes his mouth
water when he writes about it.
He wonders, it's an interesting question because obviously it's written like inflation fetish.
Some of you may not know what the world's an inflation fetish right when I said it,
but 10 minutes ago and now you've seen 100 photos of your favorite cartoon characters
blowing up like a blimp, floating around.
Sorry about that.
But anyways, it's written like inflation fetish porn with the groaning and the arcing of the
back or arching of the back, however you say it.
The stomach gurgling is really written like inflation fetish porn.
What's very interesting is despite that he has some of the similar questions we see in
standard UFO stories.
And that's why as much as I love this story because it allowed me to talk about a man
sucking on a tube until his stomach swelled up.
But then you have this, he asks these are super interesting questions because he does
start to go like what are the long term effects of that liquid?
Like if it wasn't a dream and we do see a lot of alien abduction encounters, they are
in that weird cycle.
That's why a lot of skeptics go well they're just dreaming and sure some of them might be,
but when you're falling asleep and then you wake up and the gray aliens are standing around
your bed.
Sometimes it's dream like.
Sometimes you can clearly state that was a dream but this is reality.
But then you have scars on your body that are unidentifiable.
Where'd you get them from?
If it was just inflation fetish porn, it really well could be, but if it was just that then
that's just kind of funny.
But if we're looking at the story he asks the questions, he goes what did they pump me
full of?
Like let's assume that this story is real because he woke up with these other physiological
effects.
He goes what in the world do they pump me full of?
What's the long term effects of having this in me?
Because I drank a lot of it.
It was delicious.
My mouth is watering just talking about it.
He goes what was the liquid, what are the long term effects of me having the liquid
in me and where did I get some more?
Did they sell it at 7-Eleven?
Do you have some on you?
He also says he's worried about will he ever be abducted again.
He thought it was weird.
He goes why was the alien screaming at me?
In anger.
He goes I could detect anger in the voice of the alien screaming in my ear.
It's like and then I felt like they wanted to take me again but then I didn't want to
be taken again.
Despite his love for the goo, he didn't want to get abducted again.
So it's super interesting.
And he did a follow up post to this where he, it was actually a completely separate post.
He said that he is suffering some physiological effects long term.
He goes well not long term but as of now he's starting to have joint issues, joint inflammation
and muscle pain.
It's a super interesting story.
It's quite funny for us to read it.
But this would be kind of terrifying to go through in a sense because there's so many
different ways we could look at it.
The way it's written it is written like if inflation fetish points.
So you wonder like could, if this dude was completely normal before this but then he
got abducted by aliens and he was getting aroused.
He never says he was getting aroused.
I'm adding that in.
He never said he popped a bone or anything.
But I'm just saying like if he did get aroused by inflating like a balloon.
Like Jason he didn't say that.
There was no part of the story.
Why are you making that hypothetical thing?
I'm gonna have to put into the show notes my episode about the bridesmaids inflating.
But anyway Jason I'm not listening to that episode.
I'm barely listening to this one.
I'm fast-forwarding through all this.
Let's just say for sake of argument he was getting aroused while he was inflating.
But it would have been against his will right?
It would have been because the goo was so delicious.
And so he's moaning.
So I think we can assume he's aroused.
But imagine you didn't want that fetish.
Imagine you lived your life totally normal and then you have this quote unquote dream
you're rejected by aliens and they give you an inflation fetish.
You're like what if for some you'd be like what is that?
And you'd have to research and you're like oh no I don't want to be attracted to this
stuff.
Like could the aliens do something to you that would give you a fetish?
You know the weirdest thing about fetishes is how they develop.
Generally your young kid and your sister tackles you and goes smell my feet, smell my feet.
Henry smell my feet.
And you're like no no I don't want to smell your feet.
That's generally how fetishes happen.
I'm sure you can develop one later in life if there was something that you really, you
didn't know was a thing right?
You didn't know that having sex with balloons was a thing when you were a kid.
You remember being at a birthday party when you were a kid?
And some hot lady smothered your head with a balloon and showed the static electricity
and everyone was like wow Billy look at your hair it's sticking up in the air.
And you just feel a balloon on your head and you got this big pair of clown boobs right
in your face and you don't have context for anything that's going on.
But you don't really think about it but then you're 50 years old and you happen to be looking
around the internet and for whatever reason you were looking for balloons and then a video
popped up of a dude having sex with a balloon and then you could have a full blown fetish.
But even then I would argue in this hypothetical situation that's never happened in the history
of mankind that the fetish started when you were young.
They all start when you were young but what if aliens could give you a fetish?
What if like if I, oh let's even leave aliens out of it.
Let's say I kidnap you and lock you in my closet.
And then, okay this one.
I think we just need to end this segment because it's going to get real dark.
Real fast.
It's going to get okay so how about we just look at that.
David that was such an amazing story.
I hope you're okay.
And who knows?
I mean yes the long term effects of sucking on red fluid coming out of an aliens tube.
We don't know.
This is one of these stories that it could 100% be disguised fetish porn.
But the way like the fetish porn is in the middle and the rest of it is a standard UFO
story.
I'm questioning whether or not something happened to this guy because those are legit questions.
He didn't go what's the long term effects.
Am I always going to get inflated?
Am I always going to feel as good?
No he's like my joints hurts.
This isn't pleasant.
What happened?
It could really be a legitimate alien encounter.
So we'll just end it like that.
Before I threaten you with giving you fetishes in my closet, Mikey Radamaker let's go ahead
and toss you the keys to the carboner copter.
We're leaving behind my closet.
I didn't kidnap you.
You came here willingly and you brought your own balloons.
Mikey Flyus out of my closet.
Let's head all the way out to a house in the suburbs.
It's March 22nd, 2022.
We're at this house in the suburbs.
We're just kind of sitting up on the roof and we see a car pull up.
Open in the door and we see a young couple get out of it.
We're going to see Sarah.
They don't give their real names but Sarah and then her husband Joe.
She calls him Joey though.
Sarah and Joey they walk into the house.
It's March 22nd, 2022.
It's 2.50 in the afternoon.
It's just a standard day in this nice suburban neighborhood.
When they get home they go into the kitchen and Sarah says, "We're walking into the kitchen.
Joey is in front of me and he's standing right next to the refrigerator.
I'm looking at his back."
I was about halfway into the kitchen myself and then off in the distance I hear a muffled
boom.
And then off in the distance I hear a boom.
She described it as sounding like a muffled boom coming from somewhere.
And even she at the time didn't remember this noise.
It was only when she looks back on it.
She goes, "I remember that noise."
But at the time she didn't really perceive what was going on.
But there's a muffled boom somewhere off in the distance.
And then Sarah said it felt like somebody hit her across the back of the thighs.
As if someone took a broomstick or a board and just slapped right across the back of
the thigh.
She moans.
She's like, "Oh."
No.
She's standing there and she feels the impact of something slapping against the back of
her thighs.
And then the world tilted.
That's exactly how she described it.
She felt this physical force hit across the back of her thighs and quote, "The world tilted."
The whole kitchen floor tilted so hard Sarah is now standing at at what she could only
gauge at like a 90 degree angle.
The floor is flipped so hard that she's actually physically leaning in the opposite direction
of the tilt to avoid just tumbling on forever.
Like the whole floor goes, "Zzshh."
At the same time where she's trying to write herself and really shh.
This is so chaotic.
What's happening with her senses is so insane that she can't really make sense of what's
going on.
Her body almost instinctively leans to the opposite direction to try to steady herself.
As Sarah is trying to make sure she doesn't slip and fall down this sharp angle, she notices
her husband in front of her is holding onto the fridge for dear life.
He's fighting the tilt too.
30 seconds pass.
They're frozen in this motion.
They're trying to not fall.
On a floor that they've walked on a hundred, a thousand times.
A totally normal floor.
It's now tilted.
And after 30 seconds, in an instant, the floor has returned to normal.
Sarah is now able to fully stand up.
She's no longer having to kind of crunch her body down and try to maintain this pose.
She's able to fully stand up.
And at the same time, her husband lets go of the fridge and turns to her.
And he's out of breath.
And she asks her husband, "Are you okay?"
Joey looks straight into Sarah's eyes and says, "Yeah, yeah, I'm okay, but I don't
know what happened, but for a moment there I thought I was just gonna fall flat on my
face."
I had to grab that fridge to keep that from happening.
Sarah is now realizing whatever happened to her happened to him.
She's confirmed it.
She saw him grab onto the fridge, but now he's confirming that the floor was also wrong
for him.
And then he goes on to say, "I don't know what happened.
I was walking towards the fridge and all of a sudden it felt like something just BAM
hit me in the back of the legs.
And it hit me so hard I stumbled forward."
And the next thing I know, the floor was slipping out from under me.
And Sarah had the same sensation when that force hit her, she felt herself kind of stumble
a bit and then the floor flip.
And they both stood there like that for 30 seconds until everything returned to normal.
Sarah was posting about this online.
She was posting about it under the username "Hellcat'swife."
And she goes, "Ever since then, things haven't been right.
For one, both of us for the next several days could still feel where that force had hit
them in the back of the legs.
It felt sore as if whatever slammed into us hit us with enough force not just to make
us stumble forward, but to leave a not a mark but a lasting impression.
They could definitely feel the physical touch of it, the physical pain of it after all these
days."
But that's one thing.
We see physiological effects after high strangeness that does happen in one way that gives the
experiencers a little bit of proof of what happened, right?
The Irving Lane Stomachs, for example, or in this one, your legs hurt for a couple days.
Having another witness in the event is a big thing as well.
It was just Sarah or just Joey.
This story may have never been told.
They might have just chalked it up to some issue.
Most likely medical.
If this happened to you alone, you're walking into a kitchen and everything tilted, you
might make a doctor's appointment.
You might go, "Whoa, is that what a stroke feels like?
Is that what a heart attack feels like?"
But if this was just the story of the kitchen tilting, which would be weird enough, if it
was just two people experiencing it at the same time, which would be weird enough, if
it was just feeling the physical pain later, that'd be weird enough, but we're not done.
Sarah goes, "Ever since the incident, both of us feel off."
Maybe that's not the best way to put it.
Maybe it's not that we feel off.
It's that everything else is off.
She said, "Other than myself and my husband, our children, and our dog, the world is weird."
These relationships we used to have, not with our immediate nuclear family, but old friends,
coworkers, some things, off.
We've developed new hobbies to replace the ones we no longer love.
It's like a complete 180 took place, is how she put it.
A reset button on life.
You got a lot of people responding to this as to what it could be.
Obviously, people started talking about carbon monoxide detectors.
Other people were saying there's a possibility of if there's a low intensity blast in the
area, the shockwave could cause some perception issues, things like that.
You have these different theories going around, but those were the skeptic theories.
Maybe it was just something exploding nearby that the government covered up.
Maybe it was carbon monoxide, maybe it was all this other stuff.
Then of course, you had the believers come in and their opinion was they slid into an
alternate universe.
Just the tilting of the floor wouldn't explain that, but the fact that now they find all
these things different, things they used to love they don't love, relationships they
used to cherish they no longer care about.
That was what was kind of making people angle towards them.
Maybe you're in an alternate reality now.
A couple days later, Sarah came on and did an update because people were like, "Check
for things that have changed.
Things that you can actually measure.
It's hard to measure how much you cared about your coworker prattling on about days of her
lives or whatever.
But what's something you can measure?"
She did return a couple days later to post again, an update to the original post is how
she put it.
She goes, "I have found one thing that's different."
Really the only thing that I could really notice.
She goes, "We've lived in this house for years and we had this lamp.
And it was the lamp that was right next to the couch that we had always shut off when
we were getting ready to watch a movie.
And the other day I was sitting there and I went to shut it off.
I turned the knob, click, and the light got brighter.
I turned it again, click, and it got dimmer.
Turned it again, click, it went off."
She said the lamp we've had for years was a single switch lamp.
You turn it on, you know, lights up.
Click it again, you know, shuts off.
That's the lamp we've had all of these years.
And when you'd be sitting there and it's time to shut that light off to watch a movie,
and we've all done this a hundred times, you'd reach up and you'd shut it off.
You'd just click it once and that light would go dead.
She goes, "But the lamp in our living room now is a three-way lamp with a three-way light
bulb."
You have to keep turning it until you shut it off.
She goes, "I know that's not the lamp that was there.
I know that's not the lamp that was there for years and I know that's not the light bulb.
And I have a thousand memories of flipping that switch once and that light shutting off."
She goes, "Right now that's the only difference I've found."
This is obviously a fascinating story.
We're looking at a possible experiencer, people who remember shifting into another dimension.
If the story's true, it could be made up.
If the story's true, that's what this would perfectly detail.
We've covered a story like this before where the guy got in the horrible car accident and
he ended up in this weird realm where the giant sorting wheel was like destroying the
landscape.
I've covered a thousand favorite stories that I've done out of two thousand stories we've
covered.
I'll put it in the show notes.
That's what this feels like to me.
What it sounds like to me is they're in the kitchen, their kids and their dog are nearby
if not in the house in the neighborhood, and a bomb went off.
And it vaporized everybody around them and it would make more sense if the dog and the
kids are at home and they were all vaporized in the same blast.
That's what that explosion was.
And everything tilts and that is them in that sorting wheel type of thing.
That is their reality actually freaking out.
We don't know how old the kids are.
We don't know if they're like, "Hey Johnny, did you get thrown into another dimension
lately?
Did you figure out that your feet were totally off or whatever?
How would you explain that to a kid?"
Some explosions, some disaster happened in their original reality and now they're in
ours.
But the way the alternate reality works is that it's actually quite possible that Sarah
and Joey got thrown into our reality where in this world she notices there's a three
way light bulb and in that reality there was just one way light bulb.
And it could be in this reality when they went to the store that was the only one available
so they got the three way light bulb one.
And that's the way the Mandela effect works or the way that we know about alternative
universes, quantum, immortality, things like that is this idea that you can recognize little
things that weren't there before.
Things can be different.
But then you think, "What if..."
Let's put our conspiracy caps on for the second time this episode to wrap this up.
What if this could explain some for the Spotify sensors out there?
I don't have to worry about YouTube anymore but Spotify.
Some that the alternate universe theory explains some mental illnesses.
Recently, I covered this story on my true crime TikTok YouTube channel.
Told the story in about a minute.
It's not a lot.
I'll probably tell it in a minute here as well.
Super recent true crime story.
December 13th, 2022 so incredibly recently in Mitchell, the city of Mitchell in Indiana,
there was a man named Sean Hayes.
Me, my life's a little messed up right now.
I'm pretty sure my dad got kidnapped.
He's been replaced with a robot.
So can I get your help with this?
Now that would be alarming enough if you were his friend.
If he's in your top five, it's popping up right in the front and you're like, "Oh, great,
Sean."
This is how he ends this post.
He goes, "I need to know for sure that that is a robot that looks like my dad before I
shoot at it."
We don't know whether or not they alerted authorities about this because obviously that's
pretty alarming.
You're building your own robot right now.
You're like, "God, zoops.
They beat me to it.
I'll have the authorities stop them."
No.
You're like, "Oh my God, I think Sean Hayes is about to shoot his dad."
I don't know though if they actually called the authorities or not, but on December 20th,
2022, the police do a welfare check of the Hayes residence.
So they may have been alerted or people may just thought it was weird that they hadn't
heard from Richard Hayes, 73-year-old father of Sean Hayes.
So the police show up at the house and they see Sean Hayes running out of the house to
get in his pickup truck and the police see a shotgun in the pickup truck.
There's a scuffle that breaks out.
The cop grabs the shotgun.
Sean Hayes starts fighting these cops off.
Finally they subdue him.
And then they see Lane in the front yard of the house is the body of Richard Hayes.
He had been shotgunned in the chest and in the head.
His body had also been mutilated and partially dismembered.
Apparently Sean Hayes was looking through his dad's intestines trying to find the wires
to prove that his dad was a robot.
Trying to find some.
That's a tragic story.
It's a tragic story.
Don't get me wrong.
But what if not making light of this, okay?
Conspiracy cap.
You can't come at it conspiracy cap stuff.
What if in an alternate reality Sean Hayes' dad was a robot?
In an alternate reality he actually was a robot.
And then Sean Hayes slid into the universe where he's not a robot but thought he was
still a robot.
Now I want to be very clear.
You shouldn't murder him at all whether or not he's a robot.
But what if, that's all I'm saying, is people who suffer from these mental delusions that
their loved ones have been replaced with zombies or clones or people who are complaining about
being gangstalked, what if they came from an alternate universe where they were being
gangstalked and now they're all here.
It's a fascinating story.
It's a fascinating story of alternate realities, of unlived lives and yet tiny changes within
these lives that we may not notice.
There may be a lot of changes that would indicate we actually were from an alternate universe
and not something as big as the Berenstein Bears.
Not even something as small as being able to detect your light bulb.
But text changing in a book you've never read.
You have a book on your library, you have a book up on your library shelf at home, you
never read it, it was a gift and simple text changed in there, you would never know.
The changes could be minute, the changes could be huge.
The question is, when it happens to you, because if we're talking about quantum immortality,
we're talking about this happening to everybody at some point.
When you die you simply shift into a universe you haven't died in yet.
If that theory is true, when you shift, will you be able to tell what changed?
I mean technically at this point, like I'm 46 years old, I can identify quite a few times,
maybe 6 to 10 times, where I legit should have died in that situation.
Like miracle beyond the heavens that I didn't die.
And I'm still here.
But it's possible that I've shifted 6 to 10 times already.
And those are the ones I remember.
I'm thinking about the time when I was a baby, apparently I had a heart attack when I was
born.
A little baby boy going eeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeee
The
question is, is like when these changes happen, will you notice them?
When these changes happen and they will happen, if this theory is true they'll happen to us
multiple times and as we get older and our lifespan gets shorter, they'll happen more
and more often.
Slip in the bathtub?
No you didn't.
You caught the Rayleigh in just the right time.
But the universe is slightly different.
Trip in the garden?
Land on the rake?
Face first?
No you didn't.
You didn't put the rake there.
You did fall down.
You got a mouth full of earthworms.
But the rake didn't pierce your brain.
Car accident?
You're an elderly person driving a car and you can't really see that well.
You did cause that huge car accident because you couldn't see really well.
Those cheerleaders are going to need to go to physical therapy for a while that you ran
into but you didn't die.
You kept on driving.
You kept on driving and you didn't even know you hit those girls.
And all of these things happen.
You didn't have a heart attack in the middle of the night.
You woke up totally fine.
But all around you the universe is completely changing.
And you're dying so often the older you get it's changing more and more frequently.
And at what point does it become unrecognizable?
At what point is it not oh the lamp's different or this book title's different?
At what point does it become completely unrecognizable?
When you wake up and you don't recognize anybody around you, you don't recognize the house
that you're in, you don't know what's going on.
And we see that in people and we think they're insane.
They're raving lunatics.
They're walking down the street and they're talking to no one about Russian spy satellites
beaming messages into their brain.
But what if these are just people who live the life so hard they died so many times that
they're now in a world that while it's normal to us it's unrecognizable to them.
It is the kingdom of the insane.
We totally see it as a normal reality, a normal planet, but to them it is so divorced from
the world that they knew.
And even though every time they died they moved just a little bit farther away inches, inches
away into alternate universes, eventually they've died so many times they're in something
that is unrecognizable to them.
Something that induces insanity.
It's that alien to them.
We pump them full of drugs and all that does is calm down the chemicals that are screaming
in their head.
None of this is real.
This is not the world you remember.
Is that the fate of what happens to someone who has slid through reality time after time
after time after time after time?
They move farther away from a world they actually recognize to a world that nothing is what
they know of it.
Is that why mad men walk the streets screaming at the top of their lungs?
They've witnessed a reality that never should have existed in the first place.
But to us, it's just home.
And if that's the case, what happens to us when we slide too far through the alternates?
What happens to us when we realize we're in a world that has many more differences than
just the lamp?
Couple movie titles.
Couple quotes.
What happens when we keep going deeper and deeper?
What happens when we die time after time after time and it's tiny changes compounded by more
tiny changes compounded by more tiny changes until one day we pick ourselves up out of
the garden, wipe the fresh soil off of our faces.
We look at the neighborhood we've lived in for years.
We don't recognize a single person walking down the street.
Nothing is as it seems.
Nothing is as you remembered.
Everything is wrong.
You know it.
And no one can tell you otherwise.
And as you're screaming and ranting and the police are called, the doctors are called,
and you're pumped full of medicine and you're strapped down and you are treated as just
one of a countless number of mental patients, the people who are doing the strapping, the
people who are putting the medicine in your body, the police officers who arrest you,
all of the residents of the neighborhood, all of them will eventually share your fate.
Plunged through a sea of alternate realities until finally they go mad in a world different
than the one they always knew.
And if you think that's bad, wait until you die again.
If you thought this last world drove you mad, the next one's going to be a scream.
DeadRabberRadio@gmail.com is going to be our email address.
You can also visit us at facebook.com/DeadRabberRadio.
Tiktok is @DeadRabberRadio.
DeadRabberRadio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast.
You don't have to listen to it every day, but I'm glad you listened to it today.
Have a great one, guys.
Bye guys.
Bye.
(upbeat music)