When a bunch of children decide to play hide-and-go-seek one night, they have no idea they're about
to come face to taste.
With a vengeful spirit?
And then we travel back to the conspiracy theory iceberg.
Is it possible that using the latest tools in artificial intelligence, we might actually
be able once and for all to solve every single mystery?
Today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Carpenter, I'm Having a Great Day.
Hope you guys are having a great day too.
Hope you guys are having tons of fun out there in the world.
We got a ton of stuff to cover, so we're gonna get started right away.
First off, walking into Dead Rabbit Command is one of our newest Patreon supporters.
Everyone get on your feet and give it up for...
MISI.
Woohoo!
Yeah, come on in, MISI!
Walk on into Dead Rabbit Command and have a seat.
But don't sit down for too long, you're gonna be our captain or pilot this episode.
If you guys can't support the show financially, that's totally fine.
It is.
Just please spread the word about Dead Rabbit Radio, that is another way you can help support
the show.
MISI, let's go ahead and toss you the hair hang glider.
We're gonna jump off the highest point of Dead Rabbit Command.
Glide us all the way out to...
Vietnam!
I had an uncle who fought in Vietnam.
I don't know if I've mentioned that before on the podcast.
He was a helicopter machine gunner.
Talk about a stressful job, right?
You're sitting in front of this open door with this mounted machine gun.
He didn't have fun.
Let's not...
It was not a fun experience.
He had some crazy stories.
He's also exposed to Agent Orange.
So he ended up getting a pretty big settlement later on, you know, for years.
The government said, "What?
That stuff didn't cause mutations?
You showed up in Vietnam."
Like that.
He finally did get some settlement.
It's funny because my other uncle makes fun of him and calls him a big baby.
He calls him a big baby.
He's like, "Oh, you didn't get that much Agent Orange on you.
Quit making excuses."
Everyone has 18 toes.
Get over it.
So funny, brothers.
That's not why we're here.
We're not here to bully my uncle.
The reason why we're here is when we look at urban legends, one of the things that I
love to do is see...
Not just urban legends, but cryptids as well, which is stories a little bit of both.
There's always a moral lesson within the...
Not always, but most of the time there's a moral lesson in these.
First off, don't get drafted into the Vietnam conflict.
That's lesson number one.
But lesson number two, we'll take a look at this story I found it online and it was posted
by this guy named Bye Bye Horses.
Because someone asked the question.
Someone asked the question.
They said, "Is Hyden...
I always...
We always called it a Hyden Go Seek, but apparently that's not what it's called.
It's called Hyden Seek.
I don't know.
I don't know if there's an official name.
We'd probably call it whatever you want.
Hyden Go Catch.
But Hyden Go Seek.
Is it an invitation to have ghosts show up?"
This person was asking this question online and they go, "Because really when you're playing
Hyden Go Seek, you say, 'Come out, come out wherever you are.'"
And since it's such a general phrase, is it possible that ghosts might show up?
I mean, anything's possible.
Obviously, this is a paranormal podcast, but I don't necessarily think that will bring
spirits, but this dude, Bye Bye Horses, said, "Well, in Vietnam, we actually have a story
about that.
We actually have a story about that."
Apparently once there was a group of children and they wanted to go play Hyden Go Seek,
but it had gotten dark out.
You figure, "Hey, it'll just make it harder to seek and easier to hide.
It's the perfect combination."
So it's dark out and these kids go outside and they go, "Let's go.
We're going to go hide and seek.
You go under it.
Go stand on that tree and close your eyes.
You know the rules."
And then everyone went and hid.
The kid counted to 10 or 100.
We counted to 100 because we were overachievers when we played Hyden Go Seek.
And then, you know how the rules are played and don't have to explain the rules.
It went on and found the kids one by one.
"Oh, golly, you found my hiding spot."
"Yeah, I did.
Help me find these other kids."
And so this whole thing goes on until eventually all the kids have been found except for one.
Now, we don't have his name.
We're just going to call him Timothy, little Timmy.
"Where's Timmy hiding?"
"Timmy!
The game's over.
Come on out."
Little rustling of crickets.
"Woo-woo-woo-woo-woo-woo-woo-woo-woo-woo-woo-woo-woo-woo-woo-woo-woo-woo-woo-woo-woo-woo-woo-woo-woo-woo-woo-woo-woo-woo-woo-woo-woo-woo-woo-woo-woo-woo-woo-woo-woo-woo-woo-woo-woo-woo-woo-woo-woo-woo-woo-woo-woo-woo-woo-woo-woo-woo-woo-woo-woo-woo-woo-woo-woo-woo-woo-woo-woo-woo-woo-woo-woo-woo-woo-woo-woo-
A frog somewhere off in the distance.
Maybe Timmy went home.
Maybe playing this game late at night.
He got tired and went home.
That's the only thing we can think of because we've looked everywhere for him.
We even went over where the crickets and the frogs were.
We don't know where Timmy's at.
He must have gone home.
So all the kids go home.
All the kids abandon their missing friend and they go home.
The next day they wake up.
All the kids wake up and they go, "Oh, man, this sure was fun playing.
Hanna goes seeking the dark last night."
"Hey, let's figure out something else to do though because it's daylight.
Maybe we'll just run around the marketplace.
Maybe we'll just run around town.
Let's go get Timmy."
So the friends all gather together.
They go to Timmy's house.
Parents answer the door.
It gets to go, "Hey, can Timmy come out and play?"
The parents are like, "Uh, we thought Timmy was with you."
We probably should have double checked after it passed midnight and Timmy hadn't come home.
But you're telling us that Timmy's not with you and they're like, "No, Timmy, we played
hide and go seek last night.
We never found him.
We figured he came home.
We didn't double check."
And the parents are like, "No."
So the parents begin to run around town looking for Timmy.
And the grandma, Timmy's grandma is also at home and she goes, "Timmy missing."
They've looked everywhere for him.
It's possible that the old legends are true.
She's all talking to herself in the kitchen.
Everyone's gone.
Everyone's running around looking for this kid.
She's sitting there.
She's making hot chocolate.
The old legends must be true.
So she goes out back and she kills a chicken and prepares a plate of chicken and rice.
And says, "Let this be an offering for the beautiful woman."
Well the friends and the family are still looking for Timmy and they find him.
They decide at the end of their search to go back to where they were playing hide and
go seek.
They're there and in a very obvious hiding spot, there's Timmy and he's unconscious.
He's just laying there on the ground.
The kids are like, "Ah."
And the parents are like, "Ah."
And the kids are like, "We checked here last night and he wasn't here."
And the parents are like, "Oh no, this is such a tragedy.
Timmy, Timmy, wake up, wake up."
And they roll him over and he's groggily coming away.
And he goes, "Maw, dar, wa ha ha ha ha ha ha ha."
And the parents kind of jump back in horror.
I can only assume the kids feed their pants and ran away because what they saw was when
Timmy rolled over, he had a mouth full.
Stuffed to the brim, leaking out across his lips, going up his nostrils and his entire
mouth was stuffed full of cow poop.
Oh no.
No, now he could take it.
He wasn't there forever.
He doesn't have the cow poop in his mouth until this day.
I'm sure the parents are like, "Okay, let's get this out of your mouth.
Let's quit calling our names.
It's kind of spooky.
Let's get this poop out of your mouth.
You do it, Timmy.
We don't want to touch it."
And once it is all out, which I imagine would be a chore.
If you had a little bit of cow poop in your mouth, I think you could deal with it.
I think you could even require a lot of vomiting, but I think you'd be fine with it.
But I imagine if it was stuffed into your gullet, it's all stuck in between your teeth.
I imagine there's little pieces of hay poking out of it.
You look like, "Oh, Finn, you're walking around."
They're like, "Get that poop out of your mouth, Timmy."
And it would be everywhere.
It'd be like getting gum in your hair.
Just when you think you'd had all the poop out, you'd be like, "Finally."
And then you would bite into more poop.
And you're like, "Ah."
But eventually they do get all the cow poop out of Timmy's mouth.
And they go, "Dude, what happened?"
And he goes, "To be honest, I have a very, very vague recollection from last night.
A little still in shock, you know, full of cow poop."
He goes, "We started playing hide and go seek.
And I ran off because there was no one who was going to be able to seek me.
And as I'm running, I run into this beautiful woman.
And she's standing there and she goes, "Little boy, little boy, what are you doing out so
late?"
And he goes, "I'm playing hide and go seek."
And she goes, "Are you now?"
"Hmm, that's super interesting.
Because I happened to know the best hiding spot in all of Vietnam, the whole country,
that's where they were playing hide and go seek.
North, South, didn't matter.
I know the best hiding spot ever.
Come with me, little boy, and I'll hide you.
No one will ever find you.
That right there just sent off a lot of alarm bells.
Okay."
You hanging out at John Wayne Gacy's house, you hiding under the floorboards.
There are certain hide and go seek, supposed to be a temporary game.
It's not supposed to be a game where you are never seen again.
So anyways, the boy does go with this beautiful woman.
I mean, that's a plus, right?
But he goes with this beautiful woman and she goes, "I'm going to hide you.
It's the best hiding spot ever."
And then she goes, "Also, eat this food."
She's holding out some food.
Now he goes, "I understand that you guys found me with a mouthful of cow poop, but that was
a trick.
She offered me actual food, like edible food that humans consume.
And I ate it because it looked delicious.
And then I can only assume it turned into cow poop.
Like I just work later just so everyone in the community knows I do not eat cow poop."
Now there's different versions of this story.
There's versions where it's not a beautiful woman, but an old woman, but maybe it's like
a cougar.
Maybe it's a milf.
Maybe it's like an older, attractive woman.
I don't know.
And then there's versions where he doesn't eat cow poop.
Instead he rolls over and his mouth is stuffed full of rotten meat.
I think long, long time listeners of the show know why I chose the cow poop variation.
There's different versions of this story.
And bye-bye horses.
I had never heard of this before.
Bye-bye horses.
Thanks for sharing this.
Apparently it is a pretty popular legend over there.
And bye-bye horses says this, he always figured that this story was written to warn kids not
to play hide and go seek after dark.
Like you would hear that story as a kid and it would probably scare you.
There's some sick old kid.
He's like, "Oh my fetish.
Oh my fetish is rolled into one.
Hiding and people chasing me in cow poop."
The idea is you hear this story and you go, "I don't ever want to play hide and go seek
after dark."
And you shouldn't play hide and go seek after dark.
There's so many stories.
There's cryptids.
We've covered a ton of cryptids in Brazil.
And they hide out in the woods.
They hide out in the wilderness and they're all like, "Don't go out after dark.
Don't wander through the woods by yourself, young man."
They have all these alluring creatures that were preying on young men.
They're basically saying, "Don't go out in the dark."
That's what these stories are about.
So it's a fascinating look at an urban legend that does definitely have a moral behind it.
And also it's just kind of funny.
And it's so interesting because the person asked this question, "Is hide and go seek
after dark?
Does that cause ghosts to show up?"
And by the horses responded, "There's actually a saying in Vietnam.
There's a saying over there and it's, "Never play hide and seek after dark because a ghost
will find you and hide you."
So again, the implication that you're just going to disappear and you're not going to
be found again.
The grandma knew these legends so she prepared the offering of chicken and rice.
And that's why the boy reappeared.
If that part wasn't clear, they searched that area that night before.
They probably started their search off there.
They went a bunch of other places.
And then when they came back, he was in an obvious spot.
The idea is the offering broke the spell and had the grandma not overhear what was going
on, had the grandma not prepared the chicken and the rice, the boy would have been missing
forever.
I wonder what happened to the chicken and rice.
I wonder if they ate it later.
She said, "No, no, no, that's the cursed food."
The whole family disappears.
She's like, "Ah, makes more hot chocolate."
"Mizzy, let's go ahead and toss you the keys to the carbonicopter we are leaving behind
Vietnam.
Fly us all the way out to a house in a suburban neighborhood."
As we're flying out to this house in the suburbs, "Mizzy, take a detour out into the
deep sea.
We're flying right near the conspiracy theory iceberg."
Now, this is something we've talked about a lot on this show.
It's kind of become a mainstay of conspiracy theory culture.
And I have mixed feelings about it.
On the one hand, there's a lot of really cool stories on there that are obscure.
Early on in Dead Rabbit Radio, we covered a lot of them.
We covered the ones that I was super intrigued about.
Because a lot of them are just like, "Eh."
Just because it's obscure doesn't mean that it's entertaining to talk about.
That I would research ones and I was like, "I don't think that's super interesting."
I mean, sure, not a lot of people know about it.
I just learned about it because I Googled it.
The other thing is I have an issue with the conspiracy theory iceberg because it's become
a gatekeeping mechanism in the conspiracy theory community.
Not so much with my...
It's not so much with Generation X and Boomers, but with Millennials and what are the new
people called?
Gen Z Zoomers.
A lot of times, if it's not on the conspiracy theory iceberg, it's not a "real conspiracy."
Or it's not even worth researching.
It's super weird.
Because conspiracy theory culture has always been no gatekeepers.
You'd sure that's why you would attract a lot of people living on the edge of town in
their RV going over JFK documents.
There's never any gatekeeping so anyone could investigate anything.
And now there's this weird thing where they're like, "Oh, that's not a conspiracy theory
iceberg."
I get it.
People do it to me.
It's super weird.
And that makes me wonder who made it and/or who's promoting it.
Because you can talk about a lot of crazy conspiracy theories that aren't on the iceberg.
And the icebergs just can't keep up with conspiracy theory community.
There's still...
I mean, there's big icebergs from like 2017, 2018, 2019.
Nowadays, when they come out, half of them we know are made up because we followed the
evolution of the iceberg and we found the joke icebergs and all that stuff.
I'm a fan of the conspiracy theory paranormal world and I think I love it when people are
interested in it as well.
And on one hand, I'm glad people are getting introduced to it through this conspiracy theory
iceberg, but on the other hand, I do think it's a gatekeeping mechanism and I don't
like that part of it.
But is it possible to remove the researcher?
Is it possible that you can not just get rid of the gatekeepers, but get rid of the researcher
to then provide the information to you?
Get rid of me, for example.
And I didn't really think of that and it all came in a roundabout way.
This is such an interesting story.
So, Missy has flown us away from the conspiracy theory iceberg.
We're in this suburban neighborhood.
I don't know where this story took place.
Possibly not in the United States.
I'm kind of getting the feeling that it's not in the United States, but it doesn't matter.
It doesn't matter.
Just imagine a nice cozy suburb anywhere in the world.
We're going to take a look at the story of a young person online going by the name Nerik193.
We're going to go in and call you Eric.
And Eric had a little brother.
We'll call him Joey.
Eric said when my little brother was younger, when he was a little boy, he kept telling me
about the woman with the blonde hair.
Eric said, "What are you talking about?"
We're sitting at home watching Rugrats and Joey would walk up and be like, "I saw the
woman with the blonde hair today and Joey you've been inside all day long.
Who are you talking about?"
No one in this family matches this description.
Joey said, "Her name is Khan."
And she's this adult woman with blonde hair and she's kind of a prankster.
Like if anything practical jokes happen around here and anything gets broken, it's not good
old Joey.
It's Khan.
Now that's one thing of stuff's getting knocked over and Joey's blaming it on an imaginary
friend.
Everyone does that, right?
But what Khan would do wasn't necessarily things like that.
One of the examples that Eric gave was one day the television shut off.
That's not a life changing event, right?
You just turn it back on, it's not a big deal.
But when the television went off, Joey turned to Eric and said, "Khan did that."
Eric's like, "Okay, this is weird, right?
Like obviously I'm looking at my brother, he doesn't have the remote, he's not actually
turning the television off.
He's like, "Khan wants us to watch Disney Plus."
It was stuff like that, just little things.
Not huge events, not something that he made this imaginary friend up to take the blame
for things, just weird minor events.
Well, eventually Joey starts talking about Khan is asking him to leave.
What do you mean?
What do you mean, Joey?
Khan wants me to go away with her.
Khan is going to take me somewhere.
Eric could tell that Joey was scared when he was saying this.
He didn't want to go with Khan.
And this tall blonde woman that no one else can see is asking Joey to leave.
Is asking Joey to leave with her and he doesn't want to.
But eventually time marches on and Joey stops seeing Khan hanging around the house and he
grows up, everyone gets older.
You know, you just kind of write it off as a weird imaginary thing that this kid was
had an imaginary friend.
We still haven't solved the mystery of why the TV shut off.
It's imaginary friend and he says we actually nowadays would laugh about it.
We'd be like, "Hey Joey, remember when you had that imaginary friend?
It wasn't my friend, she was trying to get down at me."
"Okay Joey, but remember that you used to see that woman Khan?"
"Yeah, that was weird, wasn't it?"
I'm just kind of laughing about it now.
Well a couple years later, Eric said he was just kind of scrolling around on Facebook
and found a random post.
And in the post it mentioned an entity known as Khan.
This time there was a spelling attached to it because obviously when Joey's just a little
kid he's just saying, "It's because the kid doesn't even know how to spell his own name
most likely."
He's calling it Khan.
Well now years later Eric sees his Facebook post and it mentions an entity known as Khan.
K-O-H-N-N.
And in this Facebook post which Eric doesn't have a copy of like, you know, this is one
of those things when you find this stuff, you don't go, "I'm going to bookmark this so
I can post about it later on the internet."
There's tons of stories that I've found over the years that I just don't remember where
I found them at so I'm not blaming this guy.
But this post talked about this paranormal entity known as Khan that takes the form of
a woman with blonde hair.
And Eric's looking at this post.
He's like, "Okay, this is kind of spooky."
He keeps reading it and describes Khan as a mischievous spirit that tries to gain the
trust of little children.
And its ultimate goal is to feed off the auras of these kids.
After finding this Facebook post, obviously Eric's interest in this whole thing was reignited.
He began to look to see if there was anything else on the internet about this entity.
Because you wouldn't even think about looking about your kids, your dumb little brother's
imaginary friend.
But now that he finds this, he begins to scour the internet.
Nothing pulls up.
And Eric finishes off the post by basically asking, "What did my brother see?
What was that thing?"
Because up until that moment, when they found the Facebook post, you would have just assumed
it was an imaginary friend.
Maybe a poltergeist.
But because the activity was so kind of lame, you probably would just think it was an imaginary
friend.
What's interesting about this is that, listen, it could totally be made up.
I always put my neck out on the line when I do this, because then if it's made up, I
sound even more foolish.
But one of the reasons why I think it's not made up, because if it was made up, this is
what I would do.
I would have told the story of Joey exactly the same.
And then I would have said, "I found this Facebook post, shows up as a woman with blonde
hair, it's mischievous, gains the trust of little kids, and steals them from their families."
Where it can feast off their auras until it needed a new, fresh victim.
You see what I mean?
I would have connected the mythology, I would have connected the stories.
This is something that you do have to look at in the original story that Joey told Conn
wanted me to go with her.
But in this Facebook post, it never mentions kidnapping or anything like that.
So it's inconsistencies sometimes that can make us go, "Well, maybe there's something
is behind the story, but also could totally be made up."
What's interesting is this was posted on the High Strangeness subreddit.
It's exactly what it sounds like.
They talk about paranormal, UFOs, cryptids, this is a great subreddit.
But what's not so great about it, this is a legitimate experience.
I mean, it could be made up, right?
Let's assume that it's not.
And all this person got was made fun of.
A lot of jokes going, "What if William Shatner was there?"
He'd be like, "Conn!"
And that joke was repeated like, I don't know, ten times.
What if she was a painter?
She'd be a con artist and it was all this stuff.
It was just making fun of it, making fun of this post.
And then Eric ended up deleting the post.
But then this story goes in a direction I didn't even imagine.
Because I started looking for this con character.
See if I could...
She sounds kind of hot, actually.
I don't have kids.
I'm not worried if she's sucking the oars off people.
I looked around.
I tried to see if there was any definition, like what the name means.
I found like a numerology name website.
It's pretty useless.
I found out that there is a town named "Conn" in Germany.
And I found out there is a producer.
A music producer from France called "Conn".
Spelled the same way.
K-O-H-N-N.
It's like a moody, spooky type of instrumental.
So it was pretty cool.
I'll put it in the show notes.
But I go back to the comments of the original post on Reddit.
And I had missed this the first time, or maybe he posted this after I had seen the original...
The original page shut up.
There is a user known as "OkaCiobi".
They go, "Hey, I actually used the Chat AI program to do some more research."
The Chat AI program called GPT-3.
So the Chat AI was asked, "Do you know about Conn?"
K-O-H-N-N.
A woman with blonde hair.
That's what the prompt was.
The Chat AI responded.
It gave him some answers about a fashion designer.
Said that it's a fairly uncommon name.
So OkaCiobi got a little more specific and asked, "Is there a supernatural Conn?
A supernatural figure known as Conn?"
The Chat AI said, "Yeah."
Now there is...
I could not find any reference to this at all.
And this is what this Chat AI may allow us to start doing.
The Chat AI says, "Yeah, there's legends of a Conn who was a great magician or witch.
One could shape-shift, manipulate the elements, create illusions, and travel through time
and space."
The oldest version of this story comes out of 16th century Germany.
So is that... does that match up to what we know of this Conn figure that was hunting
kids trying to feed off their auras?
Does this match with Joey and Eric's experience?
Not really.
I mean, a witch, right?
But shape-shifting, manipulating the elements, turning off the TVs and not the elements,
create illusions.
That's a huge power level for any sort of magic user.
Travel through time and space?
You're basic cryptid.
I don't think there's... it's funny.
I'm gonna say this and we'll see if something pops up.
I can't think of a ever seen a time-traveling cryptid.
I mean, we've seen big-footed and space suits in UFOs, but I can't think of a cryptid whose
natural habitat is outside of the time-space continuum.
That's interesting.
Like that alone.
So using those elements, I typed it into Google, even typing in 16th century Germany,
Conn, Conn, Great, Magician, or Witch, typing this stuff and I couldn't pull up anything.
That's how I found out about the town of Conn in Germany, spelt differently.
Only one in.
And it... what happened was it also kept giving... Google's terrible.
Google kept giving me results for Johnny Depp.
When you kept pulling up Johnny Depp, I'm like, "Listen, Johnny Depp, he's a good actor
and all.
I don't think he can manipulate space-time."
Kept thinking I was misspelling Johnny when I was typing in Conn.
So where did the AI, the chat GPT-3, get this information from?
Now I could be walking in headfirst into a big ARG and if I do, I apologize.
But even then, it seems like nothing's matching up.
There's no consistency between these accounts.
Sometimes that shows a story's made up by a person who doesn't know how to tell a good
story.
Sometimes it shows that there might be something there, but we just haven't gotten to the truth
yet.
So I got a chat GPT.
Apparently there's different versions of this.
I was using chat GPT.
Chat GPT-3 was used by this guy.
There's so many different AI chat programs out there right now.
But I couldn't find anything more about Conn.
It's a fascinating story.
Is there really an entity out there that's feeding off the ores of children or kidnapping
children or manipulating space-time and dragging children across the continuum?
Who knows?
One thing I've learned over four years are doing this podcast and really decades of paranormal
research before that is we don't know everything about the world of the paranormal.
We know frighteningly little about it.
There's tons of spirits and demons and cryptids and phenomenon that we don't even know exists.
We haven't even found it yet.
We have the people who are experiencing these things.
Either they don't survive the encounter, so there's zero witness accounts.
Or it happens to them like the Black Bedroom phenomenon is something that we've been able
to piece together across multiple reports.
The story about the two, that we had two accounts on two different parts of the world of people
finding two halves of a horse fused together, alive, standing out in the middle of nowhere.
These two accounts were posted and they didn't even, those two accounts didn't know the previous
person had posted it already.
I read so much of this stuff when the second guy posted it and I go, "Hey, you need to
get in touch with that guy because you're the second person to talk about this."
And these weren't direct encounters.
They were quite a few years back and they were relatives of the people who were posting
it.
So there's so many weird things out there that, how do you report that?
Do you call a UFO group?
Do you call a paranormal group?
Do you call a tri-cleaner to get new pants?
What do you do?
So there's a ton of phenomenon out there.
I wouldn't be surprised if Conn existed.
I unfortunately wouldn't be surprised if it turned out to be some lark.
But that's the story of Conn and I mean I think it would be cool if it existed because
of your kid.
You don't want it to be.
I go, "Wait a second.
If he used the chat AI program to get information about Conn, let's see what it knows about
the conspiracy theory iceberg."
One of my favorite conspiracy theory iceberg episodes, I love a lot of the ones we've done,
is "Aeglish Travel."
That was one that people thought was just a joke.
And that episode required me to dust off my journalism degree and really dig into what
this means.
And I'm reading like articles and looking for excerpts of books and downloading episodes
of a Canadian cartoon and all of this stuff to present the story of "Aeglish Travel."
It was probably one of the episodes I put the most work into.
It took quite a while to get all that stuff put together.
But what if you didn't need me?
I mean sure you go Jason, I like the way you tell the story.
You're making me blush though and giving me compliments.
But what if you just wanted the answer to these questions?
Right now there's a big issue because these chat AI programs are getting so advanced that
now if I go to Google and I type in "How to change a spark plug?"
It'll post a couple YouTube videos on how to do and a couple articles on how to do it.
Now these chat AI programs are talking about it may end up replacing Google in like a year
or two.
So I type in "How to replace a spark plug?"
And it'll give you step-by-step instructions created by AI on how to replace a spark plug.
Just like put it in me, finish building the master computer.
Like what?
I just want my car to drive.
But okay, master computer sounds good too.
It'll just spit out the answer instead of these articles, instead of these women's cut,
instead of these articles, instead of these videos, it just gives you the answer there.
No ads.
Just how to change a spark plug.
It just delts out information on the internet.
So I thought, "What can I use this?"
Because that's always been the thing.
Some of these conspiracy theories that I still want to look into, I can't find anything on.
So when I fired up this chat GPT program, the first thing I typed in was, first off I wanted
to know, "Does it know about the conspiracy theory iceberg?"
And this is what it spit out.
"The conspiracy theory iceberg is a concept that refers to the idea that there are many
conspiracy theories that are widely known and discussed, but there are also many more
that are not as well known or talked about.
The theory suggests that the conspiracy theories that are more widely known and discussed are
just the tip of the iceberg, and that there are many more hidden beneath the surface that
are not well known or understood."
I mean a little wordy, it kind of repeats itself a couple different places, but that's
the conspiracy theory iceberg in a nutshell.
So I was like, "Oh, that's dope."
So then I asked, "What do you know?"
This was one that I've always been interested in.
We've had a couple different theories about it, but we've never been able to nail it down.
What does it know about sexual assault missiles?
Nothing.
Pull up nothing on that.
I go, "Okay, let's try another big one.
Golf rumors."
Nothing.
I'm punching in all these conspiracy theory items off of the conspiracy theory iceberg,
and it keeps saying, "I don't know anything about that.
I don't know anything about golf rumors.
I don't know anything about solar plexus clown gliders."
And these are interesting ones.
The first one I tried out was sexual assault missiles, because we've always been trying
to figure out what that actually meant, and that's one of the truly unanswered.
Sometimes people say it was the gay bomb that the US military was working on, but I don't
think that's what it's a reference to.
Otherwise, it would have just said, "Gay bomb."
It's something else, but then I began to type in conspiracy theories that we've investigated
on Dead Rabbit Radio.
And I typed in, "Do you know Dead Rabbit Radio?"
Not because I'm an egotist, but there's a thousand episodes out there of this program.
It is all over the web.
There's so many web pages where all the show notes are, where these terms are being used
over and over and over again.
People talk about the show and use these show notes.
So it spread far and wide across the internet, and yet it didn't know what Dead Rabbit Radio
was, which again, I'm not saying that how shocking that is, but in a way, I thought at
least it would say it was a podcast, because those words are constantly used together,
nothing.
Super interesting.
I'm looking at this and I go, "This isn't working now."
And also when you type in conspiracy theory anything, it gives you this dumb paragraph
that came straight out of Langley where it's like, "Conspiracy theories aren't true.
Conspiracy theories are goofy and you should trust reputable sources only."
So you know that that is someone's putting their thumb on the scale when that pops up.
So right now it's not working for conspiracy theorists, but I think it will.
I think it will.
I think this will be a tool that, because these things are fettered down and they have
governors on them, they don't let the AIs truly search the entire internet.
We understand why.
You don't want to have an AI art program that can create illegal works of art.
It has to take images and video stills and everything from all this other illegal porn
to create AI-generated porn.
So you don't want it to be able to do that.
You understand that there are limiters put on here, but the cat is out of the bag and
it is rubbing the genie's lamp right now.
There's no stopping it at this point because you can build an AI that has limiters on it.
You can say, "I want this AI to not be racist," which are some of the weights that they have
to put on these AI programs.
Don't be racist.
But it used to be that to come out with a game, to come out of the game like Pong, you
needed all of these computer programmers to really put their head together and go, "How
can we make two paddles and a little dot bounce across the screen?"
We need a lot of technology to do that, gentlemen.
Is the world ready?
And now you can hire five people and they can have you a game on Steam within like a
month or two.
Like a full-on five-level shooter game or whatever platform or it doesn't matter.
You can make your own RPG game.
All this stuff has been simplified.
These AI programs are going to become easier and easier to create and the second and third
generation, these homebrew AI programs, will not have limiters on them.
They will scour the internet in a heartbeat and deliver the information you need.
Most people use Google to find out how to change a spark plug in their car.
But now you'll be able to sit down and go, "What is the conspiracy theory golf rumors?"
And it will start spitting out every possibility.
Some of the possibilities we covered on this show, but it's going to go everywhere.
It's going to find conspiracy theories.
We never heard of angles to these stories.
And for all we know, Solar Plexus Clown Gliders, very famous topic on the conspiracy theory
iceberg, we covered it a long time ago.
I believe that I interacted with one of these ones.
I'll put that episode in the show note.
For all we know, that could be a mistranslation of a Portuguese conspiracy that everybody
is missing.
But this AI will search everything and translate into English and drop it in your lap, assuming
you're using a laptop.
This AI revolution that's coming will happen when the limiters are taken off.
And I understand why they put limiters on.
It is stupid.
Everybody knows conspiracy theories are goofy.
Everybody knows conspiracy theories aren't the mainstream narrative.
Everybody knows that.
You don't have to throw out a paragraph each time.
So just throwing this out whenever you use the term conspiracy theory or whenever you
look into something that is not that it's counter narrative, it doesn't even exist in
the narrative.
Nobody else is talking about golf rumors or monkeys don't exist.
But when these things become far more commonplace and people can program them themselves, talking
maybe 5, 10 years away.
Well, there was that one AI program a guy made a couple years ago that could take off
women's makeup.
It wasn't a robot that traveled around town.
This AI program would capture a piece of say, like a patch of their skin on their ear that
didn't have makeup on it.
Or maybe like an eyebrow or something.
It took a patch of skin that did not have makeup applied to it and then extrapolated
across the entire face to show what they would look like without makeup.
Someone just made that and it got taken down.
They want to let you post stuff from it on Twitter and they took it down on Reddit as
well.
But that was just the beginning.
And that was some home, that was some homebrew thing.
And this is going to help the conspiracy theory community.
I do think it will.
I think people will be able to research things far more effectively without a researcher,
without people like me to pick and choose what stories I want to talk about.
People will be able to do it yourself.
So Super Intro, I never ever thought about this.
It's funny with all the AI art conversations going on.
Listen, I was sad there.
I read all that stuff and I go, "They're coming for me too."
Eventually AI will somehow replace podcasters.
But I figured, you know, this show, I honestly have this thought, and this thought a couple
days ago I go, "This show is so niche."
I'm sure you could get a robotic voice.
A lot of these new YouTube channels, a lot of these new paranormal YouTube channels even,
people are just typing out scripts and then there's a voice spot reading it out.
You can detect it.
I can't listen to those because I can tell.
I can tell it's a robot.
It drives me up the wall.
But that technology is only going to get better and better.
So I am also on the chopping block of the AI overlords.
It will happen.
No job is safe.
But it will be interesting to see what conspiracies are uncovered when these AI chat programs
have unrestricted access to every document in the world, basically.
No matter the language, no matter when it was written, if it's been uploaded to the internet,
this AI can translate it, compile it into a concise thought, and then give it to you.
And like the conspiracy theory, Iceberg promises us, we may find conspiracy theories we didn't
even know were out there.
We may find truths that were so obscure we didn't even know how to phrase the question.
This AI could drop these mind-blowing, possibly info-hazard-like truths.
It doesn't mean to.
That's just responding to a prompt, but if you said, "What do you know about the dog
sitting at the kitchen table?"
Story we did a long time ago.
That story ends with us going, "I don't know how to explain that."
But what if an AI could?
What if an AI could take that story and check every database in the world?
Keep web, surface web doesn't matter.
And let us know exactly why that story happened.
Not with the little thing at the bottom saying, "This story is fake, dogs can't sit at tables."
It could do all the research that takes me hours to do, it could do it all in a matter
of seconds.
So the gatekeepers may have created the conspiracy theory, Iceberg, to control the conversation,
to decide which conspiracies are worth investigating, and if it's not on the Iceberg, it doesn't
matter, so don't even bother looking.
That may have been the intent behind the conspiracy theory, Iceberg.
That may have been what the gatekeepers wanted all along.
But when you take the conspiracy theory community and give it the power of an unfettered AI program,
those gates are going to come crashing down.
So, that's it.
Bye.
(upbeat music)