A woman opens up her closet one morning and finds something unusual.
And then we take a look at the creepy world of children, everyone's favorite little goblins.
We need them to repopulate the earth, but why are they so creepy and weird?
We don't know.
And we're going to take a look at a story of a young child who all of a sudden develops
a new habit.
But is it possible that this kid is just going through a bit of growing pains or has the
world of the supernatural taken them over?
Today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Carpenter.
I'm having a great day.
I hope you guys are having a great day too.
I hope you guys are staying warm wherever you're at.
Having fun, that's secondary as long as you're warm.
I'd rather be warm and bored than cold and having fun.
But someone who knows how to do both, I think most people know how to do both.
But this guy in particular does, walking into Dead Rabbit Command right now is a long time
legacy Patreon supporter.
Everyone give it up for AZ.
Woohoo!
Yeah!
Come on in buddy.
Look at him.
He's playing Parcheasy and he has a jacket on.
AZ, you're going to be our captain, our pilot this episode.
If you guys can't support the Patreon, I totally get it.
I do.
This helps read the word about Dead Rabbit Radio.
That helps out so, so much.
And a quick update.
Pretty soon the end of season 20 is coming.
That's where I take a two week break.
And that does coincide with my appearance at the Oregon Ghost Conference in Seaside,
Oregon.
It's a three day event.
It's like $15 and that includes all three days of speakers and vendor tables and all
sorts of fun stuff.
I will be giving a lecture speech.
I don't know what the best term is for it.
But I've written it.
I haven't written it yet.
I'm not going to write it.
I'm just going to write some notes down like I do with the show.
We see how well these go all the time.
I will be giving a presentation.
That was the term I'm looking for.
A presentation.
Why are there no fat ghosts?
And that will be on opening day, March 24th at 6pm in Seaside, Oregon.
So I'll leave all the info in the show notes.
It would be so awesome to have you guys there.
I'm pretty sure they think I'm trolling them at this point because they asked for a bio
photo.
They asked for a bio photo.
And I think for this episode's art I will include, I will do like a little montage of
the three pictures I sent them.
I don't have any photographs of myself.
I never have photographs of myself.
Pictures I sent them was a promo for a play I did where I was a king, King Richard or
Prince Richard I think at the time.
A photo of me putting on an Easter Bunny outfit so I don't have the head but I'm wearing
a big white fuzzy suit.
The giant yellow bow tie.
And oh the other one was me in the winter wearing an eye patch.
I'm pretty sure they think I'm trolling them at this point but I'm not.
Those are the three best photos of me doing stuff that I don't do.
I'm not a prince.
I don't normally wear an eye patch.
I do when it gets cold and I'm definitely not the Easter Bunny or am I.
But let's go ahead and get started here.
AZ, I'm going to toss you the keys to the Jason Jalopy.
We're going to leave behind Dead Rabbit Command.
Drive us all the way out to Georgia.
Nice leisurely ride all the way out to the Peach State.
The reason why we're headed out to Georgia is we're about to meet a mother.
We're going to go ahead and call her Nancy.
That's not her real name.
We're giving her that name.
She just recently posted this online.
February 21st is when it went up and she goes "I can't make any sense of this."
This is to be fair an incredibly puzzling story and really there's a few options we
have but let's take a look at the story itself.
Sounds completely armless but let's take a look at this because it's just so weird.
Nancy said a few weeks ago she went to her closet to retrieve an article of clothing
and in her closet is a coat.
But it's not where she normally puts her coats.
Okay you're like Jason seriously?
Seriously?
I misplace stuff all the time.
Let me finish.
Let me finish because it's going to sound like this is super mundane but the deeper I get
into it you're going to be like that is super weird.
Nancy found it.
She opened up her closet.
She found a coat where she normally doesn't put her coats.
So she has like a pretty organized closet.
I don't.
I don't know if it goes on a hanger it's in there.
She said that this coat was a heavy winter coat and she lives in Georgia.
She goes "I would never buy a heavy winter coat because I live in Georgia it's the sweatiest
state known in the universe.
It's a heavy winter coat.
It's a Calvin Klein coat."
She goes "This coat is way out of my price range."
And then it's a petite size.
And she goes "Listen I know I don't have a photo of myself up on the internet but trust
me I'm not petite."
She goes "I'm five foot eight.
I'm 200 pounds.
She's a veteran."
She's not a petite.
Not saying that petite people can't be veterans.
Maybe they can.
Probably it's a height requirement to join the military right?
I think there's a height and a weight requirement.
Anyway she's five foot eight she's 200 pounds and she goes "I'm looking at this coat and
I'm thinking there is no way I bought this coat."
It's the wrong type of coat for Georgia.
It's too expensive and it would never fit me.
But yet here is this coat hung up in my closet still wrapped in the plastic to protect it.
This isn't my coat.
It was really interesting to read her post because she is basically debunking it as
she's going by saying all that stuff like I couldn't afford it.
But she goes "Listen I gotta be honest.
I did see some stuff when I was a veteran.
I have PTSD and I don't have the best memory.
But you know what does have a great memory?
The computer.
So she will allow herself.
Maybe I bought this maybe one time I was a petite she's like "What?
I woke up one morning and I was five foot eight."
She went to her computer she began looking at she began going through her emails to see
if she could find an online order.
And that was the other thing she also goes in pretty much a hermit.
I am in the house 90% of the time.
I don't ever really leave very rarely do shopping in the real world or release clothes shopping.
She doesn't buy everything online.
So I went I started looking through my emails for any proof that I had ordered this jacket
because I'll be honest with you guys.
Maybe I forgot.
I didn't mean that I have poor memory and that I suffer from PTSD.
It's possible that I bought this jacket that was I mean think about it I mean it's possible
that I bought this jacket that's the wrong size that's too much money I can afford it.
Had it shipped here opened up the package go huh and then hung it up and forgot all of
that stuff but the computer never forgets so she's going through her emails to see if
she can find any record of ordering a Calvin Klein jacket whether from a Calvin Klein
retailer or eBay or whatever there's nothing.
But because she's holding this jacket she knows that it's in her house and she didn't
order it she actually goes to the point where she's like calling up her bank and she's like
hey this is going to sound super weird.
Actually I don't think she goes oh this this coat magically appeared in my closet help
me US bank probably not she probably just said hey were there any transactions and I
miss anything like that because she has the tags are still on it so she can see the dollar
amount she can look for transactions in that amount nothing.
This money never came out of her bank account she never ordered it so even if she had mistakenly
you know I people will get drunk on eBay and they'll buy a bunch of stuff and the next
day they're like what why do I own the entire 1988 line of micro machines it wasn't that
now if all the micro machines just showed up at your door or it wouldn't even be that
imagine if you walked into your living room one day and there was a micro machines play
set set up in your living room with all the micro machines you're like oh no what is this
home alone trap you you would be like wait what where did these micro machines come from
but that it's not as cool as micro machines it's just the jacket it's a jacket that doesn't
fit that's even like the funniest part about it right if someone delivered a bunch of micro
machines to you at least you have someone to play with while you're trying to figure out
a mystery you're like mystery solved the answer was fun she has a tiny person's jacket it
won't fit her it will never fit her it will never ever fit her even if she lost weight
it would basically be like a crop top if she could get her arms through it she's just too
tall even if she lost weight so she has this petite slash extra small jacket now you go
obviously I think we're thinking first of your body Jason's really running out of material
no I find this absolutely fascinating I know this sounds so benign but that's kind of what
I love about it this and it happens in her house like this is a what I think this is
is like some sort of dimensional rift but let me keep let me keep going on there's not
much more left of the story as she's pre bunking it basically but she's saying it could be
this it could be that it could be this but she's wiping all of those off she goes but
it's not that because of this she goes listen I do have a daughter I have an adult daughter
and she comes by my place a couple times a month and you go mystery solved Jason it's
obviously her daughter her daughter is bigger than she is her daughter is five foot ten her
daughter is taller than she is she also cannot wear a petite slash extra small and the daughter's
like I didn't buy that I want such a tiny jacket what is that jacket for an American
girl doll so it's bizarre and she goes like you know going back to begin at hermit like
I don't leave the house I didn't pick it up like I couldn't have such bad memory problems
that I got in my car and drove to the Calvin Klein store or to Nordstrom's or wherever
and bought it and drove back and hung it up because again even if you would allow that
right people do have memory problems where'd the money come from how did how did she buy
it it's funny because now I think about you know I go it could be a dimensional shift
right in an alternate world there is someone who fits in that jacket in that same place
which actually kind of hilarious to think about because they just bought an expensive
jacket and they're like oh hang it up right here and then they went into their closet
and it was gone like vanished and they would never find it they wouldn't be like well I've
checked the closet and I've checked my car possibly it's in an alternate dimension let's
fire up the rift generator no you would just eat the cost you would freak out and be like
what happened to you probably use people of stealing it all your petite friends who are
a little bit poorer than you would probably that would be the rift you wouldn't need a
rift generator you'd lose friends over it the that girl's jacket transported to our universe
and it's in this woman's house it's funny to think like what if Nancy could fit into
the jacket I guess that's not the most mysterious thing it's not like she pulled the sword out
of the stone she's like now I'm queen of England because I fit in with this jacket but you wouldn't
notice it as much you'd be like that's where where did this jacket come from I do have
memory problems but it fits really well mystery solved oh well I mean you might investigate
it a little bit more than that but it doesn't fit her and that's like the sticking point
it doesn't fit her and she couldn't afford it that was the other thing where to come
from so it had to come from somewhere did it come from another universe but it was funny
because that was my original thought but as I was saying this a long time ago I don't
know what episode it was I talked about on Dead Rabbit Radio what would be scarier if
you came home and you're like you left a pillow on the couch it's always been on the couch
you always know that it's a couch pillow it's not a couch cushion but it's like a couch
pillow you leave you come back an hour later and that pillow is missing what would be scarier
that or you leave for an hour you come back the original pillow is still there but there
is a new pillow you've never seen before also on your couch now what's scarier and pretty
much everyone said it's the extra pillow because then you know somebody was in there you 100%
know that somebody came in without your knowledge stuff goes missing all the time but finding
new items in your home it's funny we've covered basically two stories that have a kind of
a similar been this one where you have a new item not like a ghost materializing a coin
which it can be I don't want to say common but it does happen we have this one and then
we covered that story recently it's not really the same but the omnivore trials and that had
a woman whose blanket was missing her favorite blanket was missing they went to the movies
they came back and her favorite blanket was folded up neatly sitting on her couch and
that's when they knew something really really weird that that whole omnivore trials thing
there was all this nonsense people slamming doors and silhouettes staring at them from
the backyard and people just like I don't know what it is I don't know what it is it's probably
just the wind probably just the wind making the shape of a human silhouette but it was
that blanket being folded up missing and then being folded up on the same place where she
had left it and looked for it and didn't see it it is creepier everyone said Jason that
the dumb question of course is creepier to find something so I think there's the I mean
I would say paranormal rift I would say some sort of dimensional shift but it was only
big enough for a single jacket to go through but I host a paranormal podcast and I believe
in the paranormal and it could be that it could be that completely unbelievable thing
but I believe it or it could be some the beginning of some weirdo stalker what if it is like
the omnivore trials not to give that episode away but what if there's someone in Nancy's
bedroom right now being like oh you don't fit that jacket yet but then he's all sharpening
knives under her bed he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he
he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he
he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he
he he he he he he he he he he he
he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he
he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he
he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he
he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he
he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he
he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he
he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he
he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he
he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he
he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he
he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he
he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he
he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he
he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he
he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he
he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he
he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he
he he he he he he he he he he he he he he
he he he he he he he he he he he he he
he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he
he he he he he he he he he he he he he he
he he he he he he he he he he he he he
he he he he he he he he he he he he
that's how every episode ends
I don't know but anyways that's the story of Nancy
and interesting where did this jacket come from
now you're imagining Zach back and talking about the big boner
hey don't blame me don't blame me she's the one who said that
can't sue me either I'm just repeating
I'm just repeating an unfounded accusation on a show that I don't watch
AZ let's go ahead and toss you the keys of the world
famous carbon helicopter we are leaving behind Georgia
flying us all the way out
to a house in the suburbs
da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da
we're flying all the way out there and shhhhhh
it's late at night we're walking into this house
luckily I have a key I have a key to every house in the world
click click click we walk in and we see
a family sitting in the living room
you have a mom and a dad and then Sophia
who's only a year old
it's late it's like 2 in the morning we're like hiding
we're all stuffed in one of their closets and we're kinda looking out all creepy and stuff
I don't know why we are, I don't know why we're so creepy
I don't know why we just didn't be a third person but anyways we were stalking this family
little Sophia is sitting there
and she's eating a snack
like crackers and we're like this is weird it's like 2 in the morning
what's she doing up
eventually she gets done with the crackers and she lets out a big little kid yawn
wow
and the parents pick up Sophia
she's one right I don't think you walk when you're that young
they pick up Sophia and they go back to bed
the reason why we're showing up at this house
we don't have an exact location for this story
the person who posted it actually deleted their account
I don't think it's because of the story I think it's just because they found out reddit sucked
they posted this story
and it's the story of their daughter Sophia
so you have mom and dad and Sophia living in this house
and they said
we'll say this is stories from the mom's point of view and we'll call her
Jody
Jody said
Sophia is what's known as a unicorn baby
not that she has like a cool horn
but it's a term used for a baby who sleeps through the night
which is what babies are not known to do
they're known to be really loud poop factories
at every single minute of every single day
but she goes Sophia was a unicorn baby from about 2 months
to her first year slept through the night
slept like a log it was awesome
we'd always heard all these horror stories about babies waking parents up in the middle of the night
marriages just crumbling underneath the weight and the sleep deprivation and the stress
she said not for us not for Sophia
she slept all night long
until she turned 1
and she said what happened was after she turned 1
Sophia would wake up in the middle of the night
which means we would wake up in the middle of the night
and Sophia would want a snack
a late night snack
so they would walk Sophia down to the
because they don't have a snack available in their bedroom right
they'd be eating it
you can't have food in your bedroom otherwise you would eat it
you're like oh this delicious this delicious
butternut squash mashed into a baby food jar
when you're one I don't think you're eating baby food anymore
you're eating normal stuff
but if you had a bowl of like animal crackers right next to your bed
you'd eat them you'd eat them
you couldn't help it and if you if you didn't the ants sure would
the ants must have a field day in a house with a baby
anyways you don't have a snack in your bedroom
you keep them in the kitchen like a normal human
so you walk Sophia down
to the living room and you go you wait there Sophia
I'll get you a snack
but as you're walking to the living room you notice
Sophia looks over at this chair
it just sits in your living room
it's been there for a long time it's not a new chair
but Sophia walks by and she looks at this chair
and she waves to it and goes hello
and then sits down and waits for her snack
and then you come out with a little bowl of crackers
you set it down and she's eating them
and you're just kind of just sitting there
you can't be like hey good luck eating those crackers
and you know how to swallow
so you don't want to morning you gotta wait there
so she doesn't die
or make a mess or get carried away by ants
so Jodi or her husband would be sitting there in the living room
and as Sophia was eating these crackers
she would carry on a conversation with the chair
it wouldn't make any sense
it would be like I mean she can talk
but how big of a vocabulary do you have at age one
and she's a kid she's a kid
she's not asking about like oh did you see whatever in the news yesterday
nom nom nom nom
it's just nonsense
imaginary friend talk
goofy stuff
the parent would sit there
and Sophia would eat the snack
and when Sophia was done
bye
and Sophia and the parent would walk back to the bedrooms
and Sophia would go back to bed
the first time it happened you go that was weird
like she's always slept all the way through the night
she doesn't normally talk to chairs during the day
or she has an active imagination
like all children do but that's weird
but when it happens again to the next night
Sophia wakes up
parent walks down the hallway with him
they get to the living room
Sophia goes how wow
and waves at the empty chair
and sits down waiting for her snack
another full on conversation with nothing
the parents are like okay this is weird
the first time she woke up in the middle of the night
and wanted a snack that was weird
but you know now it's happened twice
could this be the start of something new
but this goes on
and on
this lasts four months
and it's always the exact same thing
the parents actually start pre-making the snack
before they go to bed
so now there's a bowl of crackers
or cereal whatever it is
on the table
when they go to bed
so when Sophia wakes up
and they walk down the hallway
the parent doesn't have to worry about putting it together
because this goes on for months
they're like okay this is obviously part of this kids development cycle
it's weird
and every single time Sophia would walk in the living room
and go how wow
and wave to the chair
and then sit down
and carry on a conversation
and again
these were two to three word sentences
that Sophia was using
so it's not like
you could gleam any sort of information from it
it's also one sided right
it's just your little girl going
yeah and then Pony
oh Pony go boom
you're like what does that mean
I mean obviously that means she's making up a story about some dumb
cartoon horse
but it's not like
it's not
well we'll get to it
because obviously if we knew both sides of the conversation
this
the climax probably would have happened much sooner
I would think
if the parents had any idea that this wasn't just a weird
quirk of Sophia's childhood
they probably would have done what they're about to do
much much earlier
because this goes on every single night
for months and months and months
until one night
Sophia wakes up
they're walking down the hallway
pre-made snack already sitting on the table
and Jodi the mom was with her at this point
they're walking down the hallway
and all of a sudden
Sophia stops
she stops cold
in her tracks
and with a frightened finger
she points at the empty chair
this chair she's been talking to for months
she greets with the wave every single night
ignores it during the day
I mean it's just a chair
she probably sat on it from time to time
but she didn't definitely know wave at it
she didn't carry on conversations with it
usually she greets it with a wave and a "Hello!"
this time
she freezes dead in her tracks
she points a finger at the chair
and lets out
a terrified scream
and she's screaming
and screaming
it's the middle of the night
and her cries of terror are filling the home
Joe at this point
the other parents up now
the husbands up now
they're both like
what in the world is going on
and she's screaming at the top of her lungs
horrible terrified screams
is how Jodi
described it
and she's pointing at that chair
screaming, screaming, pointing
frozen in place
refuses to move
until Jodi scoops up
Sophia in her arms
and takes her to another room
trying to calm her down
it takes a while
because Jodi can't say really what she saw
she doesn't have the vocabulary for it
all she can do is scream
and even then when she's been removed from the living room
when Sophia's in her mother's arms
and they're in another room
and she's being soothed by her mother
she still can't say what it is
but the screaming just turns to sobbing
this poor little girl is terrified out of her mind
the dad
you have to wonder like again
I think they weren't explicitly
the parents weren't saying
that there is some sort of paranormal activity going on
but as the months went by
and as they saw these conversations take place
you have to figure they did start to think
maybe it's something
maybe this just isn't a imaginary friend type of thing
because what happens is
when that goes on
when Sophia stops and points at the chair and screams
the dad takes the chair
and removes it
from the living room
like he feels like the chair caused that
not that she was having a waking nightmare
not that she had seen something spooky on television that day
he 100% was like
"okay, I'm getting rid of this chair"
which is probably something that he'd been wanting to do for a while
because it was probably creeping him out
maybe he didn't specifically say that to his wife
but I believe at this point they were taking turns
you don't need both parents to be up in the middle of the night
to feed the kids
so there would be some nights where it would just be the dad
sitting down there with Sophia
having an imaginary conversation
or a real conversation
see, that's the thing
you could say it's an imaginary friend
I believe in the father's mind
no, she's talking to something
like this is a... she's having real conversations
I can't see it
but she can
and I'm sitting down here in the middle of the night
in the middle of the night which is already creepy
with what
at best is my daughter's
imagination running wild
that's sweet, that's cute
but at worst there's some sort of unseen phantom
sitting just a few feet away from me
that my daughter is just carrying on with
now maybe it's a ghost of an old grandpa
maybe it's the ghost of an engineer
who died on this very spot
but it's so creepy, I don't want him there
I definitely don't want him talking to my kid
and the dad took this opportunity
to remove the chair from the living room
he's like, nope
that's kind of what I've been waiting for
I thought I'd be the one doing the screaming and the pointing
I imagine that one day I would come down the hallway
and see something terrifying but Sophia saw it
so I'm gonna remove this chair and
the very next day he threw it away
that night he just moved it out of the living room
and the very next day he held it off to the dump
and what's interesting about that story
the little kid seeing the ghost
that happens
that's actually a big part of
paranormal research
the belief that babies
and children can see
paranormal entities much easier than adults can
because they've been told they don't exist yet
they don't understand the rules of the universe
I don't understand the rules of the universe
a normal adult brain
I shouldn't say normal but I'll say it again anyways
a normal adult brain has filters placed on it
by society, by belief systems, by experience
so that creepy half-naked old woman
who's standing in your kitchen right now
if you went in there you wouldn't see her
but if you were three
you might
if you were six months old
you probably definitely would
there's no signs in the back that I would have a chart or anything like that
but you know what I mean
the idea that we go ghost aren't real
even people who believe in ghosts have so many filters
it's a big thing with the law of attraction
a big thing is you have to believe it works
you can't ever believe it won't work
if you believe it doesn't work it won't work
and they say if you're studying the law of attraction
don't read anything that says it doesn't work
don't go "well I want to see what the other side has to say about it"
because they go "it won't work"
it's a filter
you place your own filters over things
so that's interesting in and of itself
and that's pretty normal in the world of paranormal
that children can perceive ghosts and spirits
far easier than adults can
so it's interesting on that level
it's interesting on the level again where this account's been deleted
we can't do any follow-up questioning
but I do think it's interesting that you have the two parents
I would say
that you probably did have a schism
where the father thought
this is ghost
like she's talking to a ghost
and the mother would be like
well you know she's just it's imaginary
it's not real ghost
it's her imagination
for whatever reason she's developed this imaginary friend
that only shows up at the creepiest time
night time
but
he was ready to get rid of that chair
it wasn't even like
well you know what I mean like
when she pointed it
and started screaming
it could have been anything
like I said it could have been a nightmare
she could have seen something
a creepy shadow or something like that
but the second she got upset by that chair
he got rid of it
he did not even wait
she was still sobbing in the other room
when he's like
nope you're out of here
I'm getting rid of you
I think there probably was that schism
where one person thought
it was totally normal
to talk to an imaginary friend
and then the other parent was like
no there's something creepy going on here
so that's an interesting
because that happens in real life right
that they
on the war trial
story
the wife was like
I think there's an intruder in our house
I think he's living in our walls
and the husband kept going
it's just a wind
and they almost
they almost got all of their hands chopped off
that's a crazy episode
I'll put it in the show notes
now I've brought it up twice
but I really like that story
but the thing that I
really the reason why I really wanted to cover this story
and we got to wrap it up
I don't want to go on too long
but I find this absolutely fascinating
is
remember how this all started
it was the late night snack
this child slept through the night
from two months old to one year old
but when
when Sophia turned one
I don't know if it was exactly on her birthday
but you know around there
she began
to crave a midnight snack
it was something that she had never exhibited before
and
she would walk in the living room
she'd go how wow
and then she would sit down
and eat her snack
and my question is
did whatever was in that chair
and what I believe
that what she saw that night
was its true form
she probably did see some sort of friendly spirit
it may not have even looked completely human
or humanoid
it may have been like
something that resembled something that a child
would want to talk to an imaginary friend
they dropped dead Fred-esque character
but that night
when she came down
it looked more like
the demon from Little Monsters
starring Fred Savage
she saw a horrific
she saw it without its mask on
she saw this terrifying horrific
entity sitting in the darkness
waiting for her to come down
she saw its true form that night
and what I think is interesting
is
did that spirit
did that entity
make her
hungry
and
because if she just slept through the night
she would never see it
remember this thing didn't show up during the day
he was sitting in that chair
and we don't know how long they had the chair
again there's some cool follow up questions
I'd like to ask
but the person deleted their account
but it didn't sound like they got the chair
from a garage sale that weekend
it was a chair that had been there
so if he has to sleep
this thing wants to make contact with her
but it can only manifest at night
if it simply wakes her up
then she wakes up and the parents
swaddle her
and rock her back and forth
or whatever you do to a one year old
and then she goes back to sleep
the entity is still sitting in the darkness
in the living room
what it had to do was
it had to bring her down
it had to create
a habit
a need
that she did not have previous
it had to wake her up
and make her hungry
in the middle of the night
that was the only way that the parents
would have let her walk down there
and spend enough time down there
to talk
right isn't that so
that to me
this story seems kind of just a creepy kid story
little innocuous
but that's creepy because you think
what is really the power level of the paranormal
sure we talk about demons
being able to possess people
turning into a murderer
rapist
some sort of hardened criminal
and that sucks
that's not good either
but
is it possible for a dark spirit
to simply give you
a habit
to make you do a particular thing
and you start to think
like I stay up late
I go to bed
around
I lay down around midnight
I'm asleep by one in the morning
I'm up at 5.36
to go to work
and you think
I've been doing that my entire life
but you think
is it
like that's
I've always
people think I'm crazy for doing that
and they go it's super unhealthy
I take naps
but you know
people go
that's unhealthy
your body's not giving enough time to regenerate
you lift weights
you gotta sleep 8 hours to build muscle
all this stuff
I've been doing it my entire life
and it's something that I own
it's a decision that I make
but what if that's not the case
like what if I didn't choose to be
a late night person
and oddly enough
a morning person as well
but
how much
I guess I'm
kind of getting
off track here
but I'm thinking like
how much of our lives
are dictated by us
how much of our lives are dictated by
environmental factors
or genetic factors
but you know the decisions we make
but then how much
like a simple
habit of waking up at the middle of the night
to get a snack
did Sophia start doing that
on her own
and then
see this creature
see this entity one night
and it just happened that way
that's possible
but
Jodi does add in her narrative
that after they got rid of the chair
Sophia
slept through the night
she once again
every night after that
slept through the night
and no longer needed
a midnight snack
so
does the world of the paranormal
have a day to day impact
on even simple habits
we have
because again
it's not like
she woke up
and she saw this thing
and she goes
next night I do that again
we play
I believe this entity
was waking her up
and making her hungry
both of those things
needed to be accomplished
for her to come into the living room
if she just woke up
she wouldn't be able to go
in the living room
her parents would put her back to sleep
she had to be woken up
and be made hungry
so they would have time to talk
because she would eat this stuff
like someone would eat a bowl of crackers
that's going to give you a good
10-20 minute conversation
depending on how many crackers
this spirit
this demon whatever it was
woke her up
and made her hungry
that is
it's weird because you
you go
sure a demon possessing a guy
and turning him into a mass murderer
that is worse
that takes a huge amount of power
it does
I'm not diminishing
I'm not diminishing all the
demonically possessed murderers out there
I'm just saying that
this would take a lot of energy as well
and to what
end
what was this spirit's goal
why was it waking up this one year old girl
and making her hungry
so she would be in the living room with it
and they could have a conversation
what was the end game there
fascinating story
it really at first glance
it just seems like this is the story of a creepy kid
but it really has to
but it really opens up that
whole question of how powerful is the world of paranormal
and how much of an effect does it have
on our daily lives which is funny
because that's what ancient cultures
used to believe 100%
like the paranormal is constantly interfering
in the daily lives of the humans on the planet
and over time
we either say this stuff doesn't exist
or it's rare
but what if some of the habits you have
that I have
that we think we've developed on our own
are actually the work of spirits
and I think there's a case to be made
when you can look at stuff like porn addiction, gambling addiction, drug addiction
that there's a demonic element to those things
I think that there's an art
we've talked about those on the show
I think any sort of addiction where you
forgo your family
and you forgo your job
and you forgo your own health
to pursue something you
know is destructive
but you just keep doing
I think you could definitely argue there's a demonic element to that
but eating crackers in the middle of the night
did this spirit just want some company
and was stuck in the darkness
and decided to use what little energy
it had outside of that chair
to wake up a child so it would have a conversation
so it wouldn't be so lonely through the eternal nights
well if that's the case
what did she see on that last night
what frightened her so much
if this was a benign spirit
what did she see
[music]
(upbeat music)