An alien story that hits uncomfortably close to home.
You're home, the aliens are at its right now.
Look out.
And then we attend the aftermath of a little girl's birthday party.
After all the children have left and the house returns to peace and quiet,
all that remains is a little bit of birthday cake.
But then something knocked on the door.
Today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Carpenter, I'm having a great day.
Hope you guys are having a great day too.
We're coming up to the end of season 20, just two more episodes, this one and one more.
And then I will be back at the beginning of April.
First week of April, we will be back.
I know it seems like a long time away,
but I just am not going to sugarcoat it, it's a long time away.
It's about two and a half week break.
Normally I only take two weeks breaks, but I'm getting ready for the Oregon Ghost Conference in Seaside, Oregon.
I hope you guys can join me there on March 24th, 6 p.m.
I will be giving a presentation called, "Why Are There No Fat Ghosts?"
And I can't wait to do it.
Basically be a live episode.
We're not recording it either.
So be there or be scared.
Or don't go and don't hear much spooky ghost stories and then maybe you won't be scared.
It's not the best slogan.
I also wanted to say, check out, like in the meantime there's a bunch of other podcasts you can check out obviously,
but I recently was interviewed on the Paranormal Encounters podcast.
I will put that in the show notes, you can click on that.
It's an interview talking about a lot of my personal ghost stories, personal ghost experiences.
Dr. Kelly Schutze was interviewing me on that show and it was a lot of fun.
So I'm going to put that link in the show notes, check that out, check that episode out.
There's a lot of good interviews on there too.
It's a lot of interviews with other paranormal researchers.
So go ahead and check out that podcast, Paranormal Encounters.
But someone who's always checking stuff out, he's a paper, he's a paper, he's a big ol' pervert.
He's flying into Dead Rabbit Command. You're not a pervert.
Okay, let me give you another intro.
But someone who's not a pervert, floating, I don't know why you're floating,
but floating into Dead Rabbit Command right now is known non-perverted Patreon supporter, Radio Lunch.
Woohoo, yeah, come on in.
That's binoculars hanging from his neck.
Come on, put those away. I just said you weren't a pervert.
Radio Lunch, you're going to be our captain, our pilot this episode.
If you guys can't support the Patreon, you don't want to get insulted live on air, that's fine too.
Just help spread the word about Dead Rabbit Radio.
That really helps out a lot.
If you can't help the show financially, spreading the word is another way you can help the show grow.
Radio Lunch, I'm going to go ahead and attach the keys to the Dead Rabbit Dune Buggy.
We're leaving behind Dead Rabbit Command. Let's burn rubber all the way out to New Mexico.
[Demonstration of the Dusty Plains]
Driving through all the dusty plains of New Mexico, we're passing the Plateaus.
I'm like, dude, look at that. That is a flat mountain.
[Demonstration of the Dusty Plains]
Look at that. That's a bird. That's a bird flying behind me.
The most annoying guy to take a road trip with. I was like, did you see that? Well, golly.
I think I just saw a squirrel walk by.
Santa Fe, New Mexico is where we're headed.
We're about to meet a young woman. Her name is Sarah.
It's not a real name. It's a name that I gave her. She posted this anonymously.
Sarah, she starts off by telling the story. She goes, I've had a lot of alien encounters throughout my life.
And when we talk about alien stories, there's basically different types.
There's a broad spectrum of people who believe in aliens.
There's a lot of people who go, oh, I'm sure they're out there. The universe is so huge that I'm sure there's aliens out there.
But have they ever reached here? Probably not.
You have those people, then you have people go, no, no, I think that they do visit us.
But I think it's mostly for scientific missions.
Every so often they'll abduct someone and talk to them about stopping nuclear war or cleaning up the environment.
And you know what's funny? You notice that they never abduct military officials or people who own greenhouse companies.
Because they're experimenting on them. They're like, we're going to teach you to ruin the environment.
They're like, I don't make greenhouse gas. I just make greenhouses. That's what I do.
I build greenhouses for gardens. They're like, paper ice. They're like, that doesn't matter.
You know, people like polluters. They're never like, oh, you are the oil man.
You're the guy who runs all the oil. He's like, well, that's not actually a job.
His eyes dart from side to side. He's like, how did they know? I controlled the world's oil.
They're like, stop polluting. Stop polluting. Stop making plastics and stuff like that.
They never abduct. They always abduct like a farmer. But then your question is, or do they?
I wonder how many times generals wake up in the middle of the night and they're like, they're like, they're like, hey, Barry, hey, Glenn, these aliens are walking by.
They're like, we told you our name was ZipSorb, calling us that. We're going to tell you that nuclear war is coming.
And the general's all yawning. He's like, this is the best sleep I get. My wife snagging me all the time.
You guys are just some aliens snagging me about nuclear war.
Maybe generals and like CEOs of companies do get abducted. They just don't tell anyone about it.
Because if a farmer said, yeah, I was out toiling through the field with my tractor and I got abducted by an alien and he told me that we needed to make peace with the USSR and dismantle all of our nuclear weapons.
People are like, what? Why would they abduct you? Like, do you know something about this stuff?
He's like, no, I don't know why they abducted me there. I don't know why they did that.
But then he would go on the next day just farm in his field. Locally, he'd be known as a kook.
There was definitely a disinformation like anyone who reported UFO stuff back in the day.
It happens to a lesser extent now, a way lesser extent back in the day.
There would have been like a smear campaign against them. But at the end of the day, you know, he would just go back to meet a farmer.
If a general ran into the Pentagon tomorrow and he goes, guys, guys, we have to dismantle all of our nuclear weapons.
The aliens told me that. The 100% would lose his job.
He's like, oh man, I'm probably shouldn't have said all this. I'm probably should have left off the part about the aliens abducting me.
I probably could have just said, hey, we should dismantle our nuclear weapons. Even that!
He'd be like, what are you? Are you some sort of trader?
So I wonder how often high ranking officials, what was I even talking about?
Oh yeah, we're in New Mexico. We're in New Mexico.
You have people who believe, let me get back to this, you have people who believe that aliens are fairly scientific or hands off to humanity.
Sometimes they abduct people. Sometimes they're doing breeding experiments.
But then you have people who are like, we are currently being invaded by aliens.
Like this is not a hands off mission. The interbreeding process isn't so they can save their own race.
It's to take over Earth, the forced impregnations of women and the raping of human men by alien females.
That is so they can invade, not because they can't reproduce properly on their home planet.
And reptilians are here in force. We are actually in the midst of an invasion and have been for the past 50 or 60 years.
And in between there's a spectrum.
But Sarah is one of the, we're currently being invaded by reptilian.
You're like, what is Sarah? I totally forgot about that.
You're like, Jason, the show flies by like a breakneck.
Sarah is the woman in New Mexico and she says she's had several alien encounters throughout her life.
And she said at this point, she traveled to Santa Fe, New Mexico to work at different hotels as a housekeeper.
And you know, when I read this story, I go, I see a lot of parallels between Sarah and myself.
While I have had not alien encounters, while I have ghostly encounters and demonic encounters,
and I've had some weird ones, we've talked about them before on the show, I'll put a couple in the show notes.
I honestly could see, and I talked about some of them on the interview I did on Paranormal Encounters as well.
I could definitely see if I had taken a different path in life, I could have ended up like Sarah.
Like had I thought through my, not necessarily the ghost encounters, but through my demonic encounters and the time where I saw an angel,
imagine, I'll put that in the show notes, imagine if I let those events dictate my life.
Imagine if I began to think that I was special in a way other than my mom telling me I'm special.
You know, imagine that I thought I was this holy warrior sent out to destroy the forces of evil.
It would be hard to maintain a job.
It would be hard to walk into J.C. Penney's every day to sell pillowcases, and you're like, I should be out smashing evil.
But instead of smashing prices on these pillowcases, step right up.
I have like a little stage built like that dude from Pete's Drag and I'm doing a song every hour.
People are like, oh, I'll take all the pillowcases you got. Good sir.
It would be hard. I could see like had I not been able to suppress the, what's the thing that makes you feel super important?
Is it the id, the ego, or the super ego? I don't remember. Or all three. I don't know.
But had I not been able to go, okay, well, you've had these interesting experiences, but it doesn't necessarily mean that you yourself are interesting, quote unquote, interesting in a cosmic way.
So don't quit your job. You make a lot of money and you're still hunting for that dragon, that dragon that's running around J.C. Penney's.
Just, you know, you know what I mean? Like you can see people who have paranormal experiences like it really shaking things up.
And so when I read Sarah's story, I could see myself kind of traveling down this path.
She, too, she's working at multiple hotels. I don't want to read too much into the fact, and I do read a lot into this story.
I'm trying to keep it short, but the fact that she's working at different hotels is a housekeeper.
I don't know if that's normal. I don't know if when you're a housekeeper or a maid, isn't that the term?
At a hotel, that's your job, right? You work at Motel 6. I think there's enough, there's enough filth there to keep you busy.
I don't think you have to work at multiple hotels. What I would, and I could be wrong on this, but I would read that as saying she's going to Santa Fe knowing full well.
She's going to get fired from. She's going to get fired from a couple of these hotels. She's like, make some map out.
She goes, I'm going to work at this hotel, and then I'll get fired in a couple of weeks. Then I'll work at this hotel, and that will last a month.
Then I'll eventually get fired and da-da-da. Or maybe it's normal. Maybe maids work through four different hotels at the same time.
It'd be embarrassing if you showed up to a Hotel 8, still wearing your Motel 6 uniform. It's all covered in cockroaches.
You're the one that's spreading. You're the typhoid Mary of New Mexico.
You're actually spreading disease from filthy hotel to filthy hotel anyways.
So yeah, at this particular point, she's been in New Mexico for three weeks, and she declared Santa Fe as the quote, "Most alien-infested place I've ever been to."
She said when she first arrived in Santa Fe, something fell off spiritually. She felt a little weird, and then she started having this thought loop.
This intrusive thought where it's- well, and seeing her mind it was an intrusive thought. It was an actual communique from a higher power, but she keeps hearing this phrase repeated in her head.
"There are reptilians here. There are reptilians here." I don't know if it was that constant. She's trying to eat salad. She's watching young Sheldon.
"There's reptilians here. There's reptilians here." She's brushing her teeth. "There's reptilians here."
You know what would be creepy if it was that constant, and then she walked into like Barnes & Noble and it says, "There's reptilians."
And then she steps out. "Reptilians here. There's reptilians." That would be creepy, right? The absence of the message.
But again, I don't think it was on a constant loop. You'd stick ice picks through your air drums. If that's all you heard, there's reptilians here.
But anyway, she had this constant loop playing through her head. And I mean, like literally, this is like right when she gets into town, she could feel them everywhere.
So she found an old church nearby, and she sat outside. That's weird. You know what Jason? Okay. That's what's weird.
This woman is hearing someone go, "There's reptilians here." But the fact that she sits outside a church, this woman's wacky.
Well, I figured she'd go in the church. Figured she'd go in the church. But anyways, she's outside the church and she prays.
She's praying for peace. She goes back to the hotel room, because I guess that would make sense, right? Like you would work in a hotel.
I don't think they'd make you pay for it. You're staying at a motel six and you're working at a hotel eight. You probably stay in a hotel room.
Well, that doesn't make sense, because there are some hotels that have like huge staffs, right? Like Downton Abbey. I know that wasn't a hotel, but or was it?
I don't know what to think about that show. Does the staff stay there? You're like, "Hey, King Dutchman, I'd love for you to come out to my Downton Abbey.
It's only $89 a night, but sorry that we hired too many butlers, so there's no free rooms." I'm sure that like a regular like cheap hotel, I don't know, do you get to stay there?
That'd be a pretty snazzy job. Well, anyways, and it would make you not want to quit, because you're like, "Oh, man, on the one hand, I hate this job, but I'm free HBO and I'm in the pool every time I'm not working."
She goes back to her hotel room. She begins blasting gospel music. She cranks it all the way up. Jesus is wonderful. Yeah, Jesus is the best. Jesus is the best. Jesus is the best. Oh, Jesus, you're the best.
It's not the best. It's not the best song they've ever written, right?
But anyways, she's a huge fan of the song "Jesus, He's the Best," and she's blasting it at full volume, and she goes, listening to this brilliant Christian song, gave me a sense of peace and protection.
But imagine you're in the hotel room next to you. You're just sitting there laying in bed reading a book. You're reading the Bible. You're like, "I should check this out. Free Bible. I'm going to open this up," and you start reading, and then you all of a sudden, muffled through the wall, you hear, "Jesus is the best. Jesus is the best. Jesus is the best. Jesus is the best. Jesus is the best. Jesus is the best."
"I am, I am, I am, I am, I am, I am, I am, I am, I am, I am, I am, I am, I am, I am, I am, I am, I am, I am, I am, I am, I am, I am, I am, I am, I am, I am, I am, I am, I am, I am, I am, I am, I am, I am, I am, I am, I am, I am, I am, I am, I am, I am, I am, I am, I am, I am, I am, I am, I am, I am, I am, I am, I am, I am, I am, I am, I am, I am, I am, I am, I am, I am, I am, I am, I am, I am, I am, I am, I am, I am, I am, I am, I am
It's going to take forever, but I find this so fascinating, because at this point when I was reading the story, I said, this is why it takes me so long to research stuff sometimes. I was reading the story and I go, I wonder what the connection is between meth use and religion.
And now I'm not saying that Sarah does meth. She does seem to have some meth-adjacent issues. I'm not saying that she uses meth, but she's listening to me. I've hung out most of the time involuntarily with meth users, and the playing the music super loud.
A lot of people do that, but not everyone sees reptilians everywhere. You're like, "Oh, you know my nephew plays his music quite loud. Does he see reptilians?" No. She's listening to music. I think the reason why she was outside the church praying, because it was probably like three in the morning, she's up late.
But again, I don't know. I'm not saying that Sarah does meth at all, but she has some meth-adjacent habits.
And so that question popped in my head, so then I started researching. I thought this was interesting, because what would you think? I asked the beam this. I'd already looked it up. I already knew all the answers. But I go, what do you think the crossover is between meth use and religion?
Now, meth is considered even by meth users as a satanic drug. I knew that going in, because we've done episodes about that in the past. It's very closely linked with satanism and satanic pornography.
Meth use. On the other hand, I would say most of the meth users I've known personally were highly religious, very conservative people.
So that's why I was like, I wonder if that was just because I grew up in, up and down California, but most of the meth users I knew weren't from Orangevale, which is a rural community in Northern California near Sacramento.
I go, maybe it was just that area. Is there a correlation between meth use and Christianity? Because all the ones I knew, they'd be like, what? Bill Clinton's a scumbag. I'm voting for George Bush this election.
Smoking meth? I was like, really? Are you for limited government? Where is this coming from? And very religious. Not like they went to church. Not like they went to church all the time. They all believed in Jesus and all of that.
Christianity. So was that just the people I knew? Was that anecdotal? I found a medical journal article called What's Faith Got to Do With It?
Religiosity among women who use methamphetamine. People have actually studied this. Back in San Francisco, they did a study. They did a study of 321 women, meth users in San Francisco.
74% of them that used meth regularly also had high levels of religious beliefs. So not specifically Christianity, but 74% of meth users. Well, not Satanism. Not Satanism. They're like, yeah, yeah, where's the Satanism?
Religious beliefs they did other studies among weed marijuana users, right? They have the highest connection to religion. People who smoke weed regularly, 84% of them believe in one form or another of an organized religion.
Not like, oh, I believe that hippies and spirits and all that stuff. No, they're talking about like religion as an organization. The lowest drug, the lowest drug that you have religious people use was cocaine.
Just so that was interesting side note. So again, I'm not saying for the future defamation lawsuit, I'm not saying Sarah's doing meth, but that did jive with it. I go, okay, the meth users I've known have tended to be very religious and Christianity specifically.
Anyways, we're back to Sarah. Sarah says that while she was in Santa Fe, she was hanging out with a coworker and there was a statue. Some of you guys may know of this statue. She could have just hallucinated it. I don't know.
When you get a bunch of emails from Santa Fe, they're like, Jason, that statue doesn't exist. Apparently somewhere in Santa Fe, this is like a where's Waldo for you locals out there. There's a statue of a skinny man in a loincloth and his butt cheeks are exposed.
You're like shaking your head. Jason, that's not a statue. And I'm kind of disappointed. That's some psychotic woman mentioned it. You're like, check out this landmark. You totally believe it. I don't know. Apparently, there's a statue of a man in a loincloth with his butt cheeks exposed.
And she climbs on top of the statue. She goes, this is a broad daylight apparently. She climbed on the start of the statue and started spanking the statue. Like I said, meth adjacent, right? I'm not saying she uses meth, but she's doing a lot of stuff. Meth people do.
She jumps up and she begins spanking the statue. Later, they go back to her friend's room. I don't think we're ever going to get to that cake episode. I'm sorry. We go back to the friend's room and her friend falls asleep and she's sitting there in the dark and these aliens show up.
These glowing white aliens show up. And the reason why was because she spanked the statue. She was spanking the statue's butt. So as she's sitting in this room all by herself, these glowing aliens just show up and she goes, they look so disapprovingly at me. They're just glaring.
And not just these glowing white aliens, there was also a dark figure, like a shadow standing there with huge horns on his head and he's also like, mmm, mmm, mmm. And then eventually she just fell asleep.
This is one of those, I don't mean to keep overanalyzing it, but I just find this so bizarre that imagine this. You are this woman, you're Sarah's friend.
Let's say that you're hanging out with your coworker and you're like, hey, you know what? We should go downtown. They're walking around, musical montage, checking out shops, trying out sunglasses.
And then there's a statue and your friend climbs up on the statue and starts spanking its ass. And you're like, oh, Sarah, that's really cool.
And then you go back to your place and you're watching a movie and you fall asleep.
It's a normal day for you, right? I mean, other than the statue getting spanked, it's a pretty normal day for you. But imagine the person that you've been hanging out with, like, while you're sleeping, is having a full on.
One of two things is happening, right? It's either aliens were upset that she spanked the statue.
For whatever reason, why four glowing aliens and a figure from the bowels of hell would pop up in a motel six bedroom?
Those definitely, those are always there. Those hotels are so disgusting, they're basically built on the hell mouth. That's just normal.
But imagine they're there because you spanked the statue. Now, it could be a real paranormal event. That's 100% true.
But in this case, let's say that it's not. You're blissfully asleep next to your coworker and they're basically having a psychotic breakdown next to you in bed.
Like, how scary would that be? How scary would it be to fall asleep next to someone you kind of know they're like your friend?
And as you're dreaming, they're seeing these figures standing over them just glaring.
There's something creepy about it, right? There's something totally creepy about it. And you wouldn't know.
You'd wake up the next morning and it's not like, you're like, Sarah, how was your sleep? Oh, it was great, except for when that horned demon showed up with his four glowing compadres.
You'd be like, what? Now, if it's a real paranormal experience, you pick your poison. What would be creepier? Someone hallucinating that?
Or it's being a real encounter. You figure if it's a real encounter, you're like, well, no skin off my back.
I wasn't the one climbing up on that statue and spanking it. I mean, I guess. That's pretty blasé.
Imagine if you woke up and the hotel was filled with blood. These entities just ripped Sarah into pieces because she spanked the statue and you wake up, you're like, oh, man, I'm the maid.
I'm the maid of this hotel. I got to clean up this room, oh, Sarah. Why'd you have to be so full of blood?
If it's a real entities and they're really mad, I mean, you don't want that. But it would also be creepy if she was just hallucinating this.
Sarah said after these entities left, she just fell asleep. And she, this is so weird. Like, this is just so weird to even type this out, to even put this in a word so other people could digest her.
Like, what? It's so bizarre. She said, quote, I fell asleep in my co-worker's room. This is after seeing four entities, five, really, four glowing entities glaring at you and then this dark horned figure standing amongst them.
She says, quote, I fell asleep in my co-worker's room and had a fun dream. I mean, even that, you're like, well, wait, what?
I fell asleep in my co-worker's room and had a fun dream. I was swimming in clear ocean water with otters.
Is it just me? I mean, like, again, that just seems so, it seems like such a bizarre segue. And it adds nothing to the narrative other than to paint the person who's telling this story as someone completely disconnected from reality.
It's so bizarre. Imagine if the story of Travis Walton, he was like, yeah, I was abducted by this, I was on this hunting trip with my friends and I was abducted by these aliens and I saw him do these horrible things to people and they were going to do horrible things to me.
And I escaped from the ship and that night, that night I dropped, I was hanging out with Captain Crunch, we were in the Amazon hunting for a bow constrictor.
And he was like, what? What does it have to do with anything? What are you telling me about your dream? It has nothing to do with anything. It would make him sound crazier.
It would make, what's so interesting, that's such an evocative dream too. Like, you can totally picture it. When I read that, I was swimming in clear ocean water with otters. Like, it is, it's beautiful.
In any other context, that would be like, oh, that's really, that's a really cool visual.
But in this context, after just unleashing the spirits of Santa Fe upon you, because you spanked a statue, it makes negative sense. It doesn't make zero sense. It makes less than zero sense. I don't get it.
I don't understand it at all.
I know that I've pushed back that haunted birthday cake story. This will be the second time I've done it. I have not gotten to the alien part yet. We've still got more stuff to cover.
Radio lunch though, I want to get you in that carbonar copter this episode. So let's toss you keys to the carbonar copter, fly us around scenic, sunny Santa Fe.
As we land at yet another hotel, another hotel in the same area. Sorry, bro. I got to get you in the carbonar copter this episode. I can't split it up.
He's all buzzing the buildings flying really close. He's all beeping Tom. He's trying to fly the helicopter, looking at people's windows. I was like, stop it, bro. Stop it. Radio lunch.
You have to be such a pervert. He's been a page on the board for years. I'm so sorry, bro. He's all flying around Santa Fe. The police. We got five wanted stars now. The police are hot on our tail.
But speaking of tails, let's finish this one. So she goes the very next day. So she had this dream of the beautiful imagery of her swimming in the clear ocean with otters.
The next day, the next day after the entities in the room and the dream and all that stuff, she's working at a hotel. She's moving her cart, her working, like cleaning cart.
There's no room to maneuver it. She's kind of like trying to turn it around and she can't get it when suddenly a woman is right behind her.
And Sarah goes, that's weird. How did somebody get behind me? That in and of itself is odd. It's not like hotel hallways are long.
I'm lined with doors on every side. And it's almost impossible to not be standing behind somebody at any given point.
Sarah realizes this woman standing right behind her and all of a sudden a thought races across Sarah's mind. Reptilian.
She turns around. She knows what she's going to see. She's going to see a reptilian, but not a reptilian that you could point and go, everyone look. It's a reptilian. She's not a dummy.
She knows she's slowly turning around. She knows what she's going to look at is a reptilian in a disguise.
She turns around and she sees this woman who she describes as very tall.
She doesn't say very tall. I mean, it's not like Manu Bull or something like that. Just a tall woman, a tall slender woman, but at the same time seemed physically powerful.
She says that she turns around and she looks at this woman. She's tall. She's slender. She's powerfully built, but she also looked. This is an exact quote. She looked, quote, just like a human snake, but with a very crappy human woman disguise on.
She's convinced that this woman is a reptilian. Now, again, here's the interesting thing. This is what I love about these types of stories is she's either turning around and she's clearly seeing an alien invader from another reality.
A reptilian either from beyond the stars or from another dimension that has entered our own and is part of this global plot to take over the planet. She's either seeing that and this, for whatever reason, this reptilian.
Sometimes they're the queen of England. Sometimes they're the head of the stock market. Indistinguishable from humans, but this one, as she's getting ready to invade Earth, they're like, here's your suit.
She's like, what? This doesn't fit. It has a tag on the back. It's like a plastic human face. Like a little kid wearing a Halloween store.
And they're like, yeah, you know, we're trying to invade Earth pretty rapidly these days. We haven't been keeping up on our mask making abilities. And she's like, oh man, how am I supposed to invade Earth in this crap?
It looks like a crappy human suit. I still look like a big old snake. They're like, well, you gotta go. You gotta go to Santa Fe. We got a mission for you.
Oh man, these aliens either have the ability to transcend time and space to get here in an instant or simply walk from one dimension to another, but their mask making abilities have gotten really bad because before they were indistinguishable from an ordinary human.
She either turns around and she sees an alien low enough on the totem pole that it gets a crappy disguise or, and again, like this is, yes, it would be creepy to think that reptilians are slowly take or quickly at this point taken over the planet, but it would also be creepy to meet someone who looked at you and thought your skin was fake and you were a reptile.
I think that's creepier in a way. I can shoot a reptilian in the stomach with a shotgun and be like, go back to wherever you came from. Where did you come from? By the way, as he's bleeding out, I was like, are you interdimensional? Are you from another planet? He's all, you should have asked me that before I died.
I can kill a reptilian. I mean, I guess technically I could kill a human too. My point is that imagine like you're walking on the street and someone looks at you and they think you look like a reptilian in a bad disguise.
So not only are they having this paranoid delusion where they think you're an invader from another planet, it's actually quite insulting as well. You're like, what? Oh, come on, man. I'm not that ugly.
My skin doesn't look like a bad disguise.
And you imagine this has happened to all of us at some point. You know, if you're out and about in the world, we've all come across someone who may have. I wouldn't say all of us at some point. That's probably high balling it a bit, but it's happened to some of us at some point.
We're walking around and someone might have seen us and they were in the middle of a paranoid delusion and they thought we were a shadow person or we thought we were a gangstalker. They thought we were a reptilian.
Like that's creepy. Creepy to think about. She turns around, she sees this woman, this reptilian standing behind her and it's her room that Sarah needs to clean up.
And she goes, she doesn't want to go in the room, obviously, right? You wouldn't want to go into the snake queen's lair. You'd be like, oh man.
And she goes, she goes in there and she's cleaning up and the whole time the woman's on the phone saying quote unquote weird things.
She doesn't really go into detail what the weird things are, but she does say at one point the woman goes, she's here.
In relation to Sarah, I guess being in the room or something like that.
And to kind of bless the area, to kind of like keep herself mentally sane and safe, Sarah begins to pray to God in her mind. She's like silently praying.
Which listen, I'm not mocking the thought of prayer. I pray. I'm not laughing at that.
But we know enough of Sarah at this point in her story that she goes for a minute. I was praying and eventually the reptilian woman just said, that's enough. Get out of here.
And in Sarah's mind, she probably thought maybe my prayers were emanating through the reptilian hive mind.
Maybe even though I was praying simply in my head, it was blessing the area around me and the snake woman can't deal with that.
What is more likely is that Sarah came to a complete stop and just stood there as she's praying.
I don't think she was continuing to clean up. Plus who do maids come into your room when you're there?
But anyways, I just imagine Sarah is perfectly still standing there.
The woman like, okay, can you just leave? You're obviously not cleaning up. I don't know what you're doing.
But maybe, maybe right, maybe the prayers were reaching through the universe to neutralize the reptilian's power because Sarah goes, as I was leaving, I said, the woman said, get out of here.
As she was leaving, Sarah goes, okay, okay, have a blessed day.
And she goes, the woman looked at me like I had thrown acid on her.
She recoiled. She recoiled at the words blessed day.
She goes, and then I just walked away and she goes, I haven't had any experiences since.
On line, she posts on the name Twilight Zone Survivor and it's one of those things that, again, a lot of times when I find these stories to try to look online to see what their posting history is, if I can.
This was an interesting one because on the one hand, like if you're looking for a story that's made up, no one's going to make up that story, right?
It looks so foolish. But again, there's always this air of tragedy behind it.
Like I do believe that, I don't believe she's making it up.
Whether or not what she's experiencing is real is different than whether or not she's making it up.
People who make it up, it's just wasting my time and I don't want to waste your time so I don't cover it.
But, like, I think she's experiencing something.
Is she actually seeing reptilian agents on Earth?
I mean, I can't completely discount the possibility of it.
I don't believe there's a fall on reptilian invasion, but I do believe that reptilian aliens may be one of the races out there that are interacting with humans.
I don't think they're taking over the planet, though.
It's possible, right? In the world of paranormal, I can't say no, that's impossible.
That's totally impossible. Now let's talk about this ghost cake.
But on the other hand, this story, it does seem like she's having some sort of mental issues.
Just because of the way everything is laid out.
And again, I mean, like, who's to say, right? I could tell my stories a hundred times and you're like, well, Jason, it sounds like you have some serious mental health issues.
It's just fair to say, right?
But she tells these other stories and again, they're just tinged with sadness.
Let me take, I found this one.
Found this one she posted as well. She said back when she was around four or five years old, she's not for sure.
She was at her stepfather's grandma's house.
And this grandma was quite the hoarder.
Which would be chaotic, right? To grow up in, to grow up in a hoarder's house would be so awful.
You're like, oh no, you're playing with marbles.
You're like, yay, Jimmy, I knocked all your marbles out of the circle.
Jimmy's like, well, now what? All of our marbles are underneath 20 years of newspapers.
Yeah, we should probably play a game that doesn't involve physics.
We should probably play a game that the pieces never move. You're all rolling dice.
Like, come on, you're all be sorry.
You're all the dice. It rolls underneath a pile of twine.
You're like, okay, I guess that's the end of that game. You didn't even get to play.
You just have to play Candyland because the cards are the dice.
It'd be chaotic. You wouldn't be able to play with paper airplanes.
Nothing. You would just sit on a pile of all those papers you're like, oh.
I don't know if Eisenhower's going to get reelected according to this headline.
You're just sitting on the paper and be chaos.
Poor Sarah. She's at her stepdad's grandma's house who was a hoarder.
And Sarah's trying to go to sleep. Sarah's trying to fall asleep.
I don't know if she was vacationing here or if she lived here, but even then, it's not funny.
I don't know what's worse because if you lived there, you would at least be used to the garbage, right?
You're like, oh, I'm the king. I'm the king of discarded cat food mountain.
You'd at least stand in all these empty cans of wet cat food.
I don't know what's worse because on the one hand, you could just own the mess.
You would have like, let's go to cobweb cove.
It's cobwebs that my grandma bought at a dollar store for Halloween decorations back in 1982.
They're very thick. They're surprisingly strong as we crawl through cobweb cove.
What would be worse? Living in a hoarder's mess or just visiting occasionally.
I think if you lived there, you'd get used to the smell. You'd get used to everything.
But if it's like, hey, we're going on vacation, yay, to grandma's house, they're like, oh no.
Not again. Kids are like wearing oven mitts. They're totally having to protect themselves.
Using baking pans as body armor because who knows what you're going to get in a hoarder's house.
You have no idea what she possibly could have collected.
You have no idea what she could possibly have collected in between the last time you saw her and now.
But you would be like, please don't take me to grandma's house. That would be so funny.
But anyways, this episode is running way too long.
I'm going to talk to her with that. You would have to go to grandma's house.
You guys could place bets. You'd be like, I bet you she really started collecting red solo cups.
And the brother's like, uh-uh-uh. I'm betting on catalytic converters.
You're like, oh no. My poor feet. I didn't even wear shoes.
I'm going to step all over catalytic converters the whole time. Why did she wear shoes? I don't know.
Sarah's four or five years old. She's at her stepdad's grandma's house who's a hoarder.
She's trying to go to sleep when all of a sudden she felt something on her.
She felt something crawling on her and probably against better judgment.
If you're at a hoarder's house and you feel something crawl across you, just ignore it.
That would be my advice. Just let it go.
Because the worst thing I think you could do is know what it is.
But again, I mean, pick your poison. Would you rather feel something and just be like, it was just the wind?
Or would you rather turn on the light? Well, Sarah turned on the light and the entire room that she was sleeping in,
the entire room was covered in hundreds of cockroaches.
She said when she turned that light on there were so many cockroaches crawling through the room.
She goes, she actually could see, she goes, it looked like the wall was vibrating. She was actually watching.
There was no wall. There was nothing but cockroaches all on the wall and she saw the wall move.
And if you think that's an exaggeration, that happened to a college professor of mine.
She used to be a social worker and she goes, yeah, I went into this house and I turned on the light and she goes, I watched the floor shift.
Like I watched the whole floor move and my brain couldn't make sense of it.
And what it was was the entire floor was covered in cockroaches. Like when the light came on, my brain did not know how to, because floors don't move.
It didn't make any sense. But then once I started processing it, hundreds upon hundreds of cockroaches, and she actually, there was an elderly person in there who was elder abuse.
Like she was there doing some social work and she got the people sent to jail for that.
Like they had this old person like sitting there in the darkness and a recliner and the cockroaches, there's so many cockroaches, you could see everything shift.
Anyways, so not an exaggeration. I could totally see being that many cockroaches you turn the light on and it seems like the walls are moving.
And what happened was Sarah sees this, she looks over and she sees all of these cockroaches, hundreds upon hundreds of cockroaches, and then suddenly she's floating outside of her own body.
She is now floating above her body. She goes, I see the silver string leading from my human body's belly button to this spirit form of mine.
And I'm hovering over my own body and I'm watching these cockroaches swarm all around the room.
Now I 100% believe that happened. Like that was a separate post she made. I believe that this little girl went into shock.
And she left her body. Like it was that bad of an experience. You're already helpless. You're four or five years old. You're, by definition, helpless.
You're at your grandma's house. It's a disgusting place to be. You're trying to get a little shut-eye and you wake up. You don't even fall asleep.
You feel something crawl over you and then you see hundreds upon hundreds of cockroaches. She left her body. She basically disassociated to the point that her soul left.
The cockroaches are climbing up. The cockroaches are like, "Uh-uh. They're climbing up the silver cord." It's like, "No, no, you're not supposed to be here. We're everywhere."
The cockroaches said, "I 100% believe that happened." And you wonder, like, if this is the type of story, this could be a one-off story.
It could be a one-time traumatic event. But remember, she said she's had alien encounters over the years. I wonder if she had such a chaotic childhood.
Because I doubt this was the first time she was at her grandma's house and I definitely doubt it was the last.
"Dad, do you have to go spend the night here last time with your hundreds of cockroaches on the walls?" Well, you know, it's free babysitter. Me and your mom want to go see Splash.
We don't want to go see that Mermaid movie starring Tom Hanks. But you've already seen it five times. It's not that good. No, we're dropping you off at grandma's house.
Just pretend the cockroaches are toys that have their own thoughts and feelings and they like to crawl all over humans. Ah!
What if someone had such a chaotic upbringing that their mind just has a hard time dealing with reality?
Because if that's your... dude, if that young... that young, if you're seeing stuff like that, like my college professor friend, my college professor,
she was like in her 30s or 40s and she had a hard time comprehending what she was seeing. You're four or five and I doubt that was the only horrible thing that happened to her as a kid.
I'm not saying her entire childhood was terrible, but it maybe it was. That's a bad starting point.
Is it possible that she just experienced so much trauma growing up that now she's at a point in her life that she gets these intrusive thoughts?
I'll put that episode in the show notes because everyone gets them. That when she hears them, she believes them because she's just been beat up by life.
Is it possible that she's just having these psychotic episodes because of this horrible stuff that's going on? Or went on as a kid and probably still...
I don't forget all the meth stuff, but maybe that's a factor. Maybe it's not. Maybe she's never done drugs. I don't know.
Maybe she's had a very chaotic life and now she's just... when she believes something, she believes it.
When she really thinks there's a reptilian in the room, she turns around and her mind changes what her eyes see to make it look like a reptilian because this is the universe she's created for herself.
Or is it possible that she has had such traumatic life experiences throughout her life that it didn't break her brain but fixed it?
Is it possible that the rest of us are under the spell? That the rest of us are believing the lie?
Is it possible that the rest of us want such a comfortable lifestyle that we can look at someone who's clearly not human?
For us to believe that, for us to actually recognize the person standing in front of us as a reptilian, is for us to not only believe that aliens are real, but that they're here, that they're invading,
and that they can look like us to the point that no one else can see them but you.
So we can select few others like Sarah.
To accept that as truth, to look at someone, look at a stranger in a hotel, and realize, oh my God, that's not a real person.
That looks like a reptilian wearing a human suit and you turn to your friend and you're like, do you see that?
And they just see a person standing there but you look back and you can clearly see that's a reptilian.
So instead of believing the truth, you, like everyone else, would say, oh man, I must have not gotten any sleep last night.
I must have had a bunch of cockroaches on me and went over to Grandma's house.
Cockroaches are pouring out of your pockets.
I'm going to believe the lie because to believe the truth, to believe that reptilians are actually invading, means that you give everything up.
Would you be able to go back and work at the bank knowing your boss was a reptilian?
Would you be able to take part in politics?
You're watching the debate, it's just two reptilians on stage.
And it cuts back to the panel, the debate panel, and there's two humans and one reptilian asking the questions.
If you believed in it, you would believe in it.
You'd end up leaving everything behind, just moving from place to place, making enough to get you to the next place.
You're not on a holy crusade to stop the reptilian menace.
You've already tried telling your friends and family that the reptilian's out there and they don't believe you, they all think you're nuts.
So all you can do now is hope to survive.
Not like some camper out in the middle of nowhere roughing it, you don't have that skill set.
You just take odd jobs here and there to make enough money to eat, you get a place over your head, and just survive.
That's the consequence of admitting that what you saw was real.
But then in the back of your head, you're always wondering, was it real?
Is the entire world crazy or am I?
Are the reptilians invading or have I just lost my mind?
And that's a question you ask yourself every once in a while as you're at a bus stop, ready to leave this town for the next.
As the bus pulls up and you get ready to board it, head it off to another city, you have to ask yourself, is what I'm seeing real?
And even if it is real, wouldn't it be better if I could just go back into believing it wasn't?
Wouldn't my life be so much easier if I could just go back and believe the lie?
[Music]
DeadRabberRadio@gmail.com is going to be our email address.
You can also hit us up at facebook.com/deadrabberradio.
TikTok is @deadrabberradio.
DeadRabberRadio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast.
You don't have to listen to it every day, but I'm glad you listened to it today. Have a great day, guys.
[Music]
[BLANK_AUDIO]