They truly are like family to us.
We are so lucky to have these people that just care.
At Ann and Robert H. Lurie Children's Hospital of Chicago,
we know that caring for your child takes more than medicine.
They're not just treating the disease.
They're caring for Olivia.
They know my baby's name.
They make me happy.
And they make me feel better.
With cutting-edge treatments and kid-friendly care,
there's a reason Lurie Children's has ranked the number one
Children's Hospital in Illinois.
I would always recommend Lurie Children's, always.
A bizarre sighting in the middle of the woods.
A conspiracy that involves America's favorite pastime.
And then we take another trip to the conspiracy theory iceberg
to look at the bizarre theory that demonic activity
is closely connected to the blue light
coming out of your cell phone today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
(upbeat music)
Hey, everyone.
Back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Carpenter.
I'm having a great day.
I hope you guys are having a great day too.
We got a lot of stuff to cover.
We got three stories.
First off, I wanna give a shout out
to our newest Patreon, Swain on Discord.
Swain on Discord.
Thank you so much for supporting the show.
Really, really helps out a lot.
I wanna say this about Swain real quick.
There's gonna be a link in the show notes.
Today I'm putting it above even my Patreon link.
I want everyone to check this out.
A long time ago, Swain took my Thomas Dick episode.
And made a proof of concept little animation
of that episode.
It's maybe like 40 seconds, a minute long.
Ah, dude, I think it's so funny.
Actually watching this video, watching this cartoon,
made me realize how my style of presenting it,
it was really kind of a wake up call.
It was kind of weird to see myself doing the show.
'Cause this was pretty early on.
I think this was in the first 100 episodes.
It was really, really cool.
I'd been meaning to share it with you.
And then I forgot who sent it to me, honestly.
And then I've lost the link.
But when he hit me up on the Patreon,
I was able to track it down.
So there it is.
I recommend all you guys checking out his channel,
checking out that video.
It's super funny.
It's a little animated version of that episode.
Awesome.
Thank you so much, Swain.
Thank you so much for doing that.
If you can't support the Patreon, that's fine too.
Just help get the word out about the show.
That really, really helps out a lot, guys.
Swain, we're gonna toss you the keys
to the Jason Jalopy.
First off, we're headed out to the middle of the forest.
(humming)
We're getting married, apparently.
What's that song from?
Some old timey thing.
Doesn't matter.
Music box music.
We get to the middle of the forest.
Now this is totally unsourced.
This was a post from the export
that was screen-shotted and then presented on Reddit.
So that's the providence of this story.
Or providence, providence.
It doesn't matter.
Providence.
This is the providence of this story.
We don't have a source.
We don't have a location.
We don't have anything like that.
But I still find this story interesting.
We're gonna take a look.
Okay, so slow down the car, Swain.
We're pulling up into the forest.
Get out.
We got on our hunting caps.
We got our rifles.
We're walking around.
And we're gonna join a man hunting with his grandfather.
What happened was there was a kid.
He was 19th birthday.
He was out hunting with his grandpa.
A little father, not father-son,
by the name of the activity.
Grandfather-son, by the name of the act.
No, they're not.
Whatever, two dudes are hanging out in the woods, right?
And they see a deer walking, walking around.
And this is what they came here for.
This isn't that Rihanna song.
This is what they actually came here for.
They're gonna kill this deer.
And the deer stops and looks at a rock.
And they get their guns ready.
Do both of them shoot at the same time?
I've never been hunting.
Do you take turns hunting?
Like, do I have it?
And I'm like, okay, I'm gonna shoot it in the neck this time.
And you're like, no, you numbschool.
I'm gonna do it.
You guys are wrestling over the gun.
If there's two people with guns, do they take turns?
Do they both shoot at the same time?
Whichever bullet hits it first wins?
Anyways, they're sitting there with their guns.
This is, I'm a city boy.
They're sitting there with their guns.
And they see this deer.
And the deer is like just standing there
looking at this rock.
And then slams its head into the rock.
And the grandpa and the son, the son's not there.
The grandpa, the son realizes a disturbance.
The grandfather and the grandson look at each other.
And they look back at the deer.
And the rock is covered in blood.
And the deer looks at the rock.
(gasps)
Smashes its head into the rock again.
(imitates gunshot)
One of the antlers break off.
It's like 3D.
It's coming right at the grandpa and the grandson.
Well, they dodge.
(imitates gunshot)
Crash, crash, crash.
Smashin' its head into the rock.
Harder and harder and harder.
The deer rears its head back up.
And brains are shooting out of the deer.
Swains thrown up in the corner.
(imitates gunshot)
Sorry, Swain.
He's holding his hair back.
Smash, smash.
The deer keeps smashing its head into the rock.
Brains are just leaking out.
And then the deer stands up on two legs, looks around,
starts walking towards the river on two legs.
And then just doot, doot, doot.
Raging river, doot, doot, doot.
Walking deeper into the water, doot, doot.
Grounds.
The grandpa and the grandson,
the birthday party's canceled, right?
Grandfather actually moved out of the area.
He went to go live with his grandmother in Florida.
Not his grandmother.
She went to be like Betsy Ross.
He goes to live with his wife in Florida.
I don't know whether they separated before.
He's like, honey, please take me back.
I've seen the air of my ways.
Plus, I've seen pure Cthulhu level horror.
Please, I want another chance.
He moves in with his ex-wife, his grandma.
Not his grandma.
What is up with you?
The point is that grandfather moves away
and the grandson never went back to the forest.
So that story was posted.
It's creepy, right?
It's pretty disgusting.
Some people have had, first off,
let's assume the story's true.
Could totally be fake, could be creepy, boss.
But let's assume for the sake of argument, that's true.
Some people on Reddit goes,
it could be chronic wasting disease.
It could have had like Khrushchevill's Jokub disease.
It's the Mad Cow disease,
but it's the deer version, Mad Deer disease.
It could have been that they had like a,
like some sort of obviously mental deficiency
and smashed their brains.
It could be that they were having some sort of disease
that was eating away at their brain.
And the itch was so bad
that they were smashing their head into the rock.
Doesn't explain why they walked up on two feet.
I guess deer sometimes can walk on two feet,
not for a super long distance,
but they have been known to do that.
There's video footage of them walking like that.
But yeah, a bizarre story.
I mean, obviously I'm covering it
not just because it's bizarre,
but because it's almost like,
it is like a Cthulhu level thing,
like an animal killing itself very calmly.
Like it was smashing its head,
but it wasn't crying out in pain.
And then once it had already knocked out a good chunk
of its brains, it stood up and walked away into the river.
Now that obviously sounds fake.
Another person on Reddit was saying,
they worked at a farm.
Oh, by the way, if you love animals, rewind it.
Don't listen to this first story.
But sorry, I should have said that earlier.
This one guy said he was working on a farm in Australia
and there was massive wildfire.
And he remembers seeing kangaroos
that had been caught on fire running towards their fence line.
They had a metal fence line around their property.
And he says the kangaroos were burning.
They were on fire.
They're killing themselves.
They began smashing their heads into the metal fence line
to kill the pain was so unbearable.
Which is interesting because I didn't know animals
were that smart.
Like, I didn't think an animal was smart enough
to kill itself.
Like, yeah, sure, lemmings, you know, that's not true.
You know, lemmings don't really run off cliffs.
That's a weird thing.
Walt Disney's, that was from a documentary
that Walt Disney made.
And they're like, I don't know if they just needed
a climatic ending or something like that.
I guess lemmings kind of do that.
But they, the producers of that documentary pushed them off.
They were like, it wasn't like off screen.
There was a intern like throwing them off the cliff.
But they edited the footage
and made basically like herded them off the cliff.
I think it is a real thing, but not to the scale
that it really is.
And then that movie was a meme, made it a thing.
But anyways, like, how does a kangaroo,
so you're on fire, this is super grim,
but let's say I'm a kangaroo and I'm smoldering.
Not like I'm super sexy, I'm literally smoky.
And I see a pillow, a metal stake, and a tree.
And I have to smash my head into one of those three things.
I didn't think animals were smart enough to go,
pillow out, just take a nap.
The metal stake will go through my brain
and that tree will take a long time for me to smash my head.
'Cause they don't know what metal is.
I didn't know that animals knew the difference
between like minerals and stuff.
Like, I didn't know, like if you put a kangaroo
and you had like, let's say you had a cliff.
You were like, Jason, please, please,
just stop talking about it.
You had a cliff and there was like a bunch of water
at the bottom of one cliff and then a bunch of water
and some jagged rocks on another cliff.
Swain's like, give me my money back.
Why am I here for this episode?
He's erasing the cartoon, he deletes it from me too.
You have a cliff, you have a water.
You have a cliff, you have water with jagged rocks
and then you have a cliff with like a pavement underneath it.
Wouldn't the kangaroo go to the first cliff and go,
that's just water, I'll probably swim.
But it will put the fire out.
And then he jumps to the other one
but he still wants to kill himself
because he owes the mob a bunch of money
and he can't pay him back and he's on fire.
So he goes to the other cliff and he sees the jagged rocks
and he goes, hmm, that will kill me but maybe not.
Maybe I'll fall in between the jagged rocks
and dive very slowly and then he goes to the other cliff
and sees the pavement and goes, that is pavement.
In my kangaroo brain, it knows
that that will kill me instantly
because the reason I know that if I jump off a cliff
and if I land on pavement, I will die
is because people have told me that.
I don't genetically know, I never genetically knew that.
You didn't know that.
We don't know that if you fall off a distance, you die
unless somebody tells you or you see it happen.
If I, kangaroos aren't walking around with watermelons
and they don't butterfingers in, they're like, oops.
And they watch the watermelon splat on the ground
and the kangaroo goes, that will happen to me.
If I fall, that's not how animals think, right?
So how did the animals know?
How did, why wasn't the deer smashing his head on a tree?
How did he know a rock was going to do the job?
Like, how did they figure that out?
So anyways, the kangaroos, they sell on metal spikes
which to me makes me think that they know minerals and stuff
'cause then they'd be like, that's like soft soap rock.
What's that rock that's like pumice, the kangaroo's on fire.
You see he's a bunch of pumice.
You guys get it.
I'm not gonna keep naming.
I'm not gonna keep coming with hypothetical situations.
How does the kangaroo know that the metal would do it?
Like, did they jump past another fence
then it was just like wood and the kangaroos are like,
sure I'm burning to death, but that won't do the job.
I know another 50 feet there's a metal fence line.
So there you go.
I did not intend for that to be another evolutionary rant
but it turned out to be one.
Swain, let's go ahead and leave behind Australia.
That's where we ended up in that story.
Let's hop in the carpenter copter.
We're headed back to America.
This is a really short one.
I've had this on deck for a while.
That was very interesting
'cause I talk a lot about real conspiracies,
conspiracies that are provable that matter.
And this conspiracy you can argue
whether or not it matters.
I think it matters to a large group of people though.
And I gotta give a shout out to Chris Thompson
for Dead Spin, the website Dead Spin.
He wrote this article a while back in July of 2019
and all of my research comes from this article.
To give you a little background of the story,
you have Major League Baseball, MLB.
Recently, back in 2019, had purchased Rawlings
and they're the ones who make the baseballs
that are used in professional level baseball games.
So originally they are two separate companies
but now Major League Baseball bought out Rawlings.
And then we have this quote
from Houston Astros pitcher Justin Verlander.
He was speaking to ESPN and he had this quote
and he's gonna be referencing a man named Rob Manfred.
He's the Major League Baseball Commissioner.
So that's a little bit of background to this.
I think this is an interesting conspiracy.
And so what Verlander's beef is,
is he believes that Major League Baseball
is messing with the baseballs themselves
because now they own the company
that manufactures the baseball.
He believes that Major League Baseball
is actually gooseing up the balls.
They're making it so they can just hit homer
after homer after homer.
Look at this quote, I found this interesting.
It's an effing joke, Verlander says.
It's an effing joke.
Major League Baseball's turning this game into a joke.
They own Rawlings and you've got Manfred up here saying
it might be the way they center the pill.
Some baseball term, I don't know what that means,
but you might.
Back to the quote, they own the effing company.
If any other 40 billion company
bought out a 400 million company
and the product changed dramatically,
it's not a guess as to what happened.
We all know what happened.
Manfred the first time he came in, what do you say?
He said they want more offense.
All of a sudden he comes in, the balls are juiced.
It's not a coincidence, we are not idiots.
Then they're asking, do you think that this is intentional?
Do you think that these balls are making it easier
to hit home runs?
He goes into this quote, yes, 100%.
They've been using juiced balls in the home run derby forever.
They know how to do it, it's not coincidence.
I find it really hard to believe
that Major League Baseball owns Rawlings
and just coincidentally, the balls become juiced.
Manfred had a response to this and he simply said,
"The balls have not been changed in quote,
"any meaningful way."
So the balls have been changed.
I think that's an interesting conspiracy theory.
It's one that affects millions of people, baseball fans.
It definitely also affects money.
So it's an interesting conspiracy theory.
It's one that is probably true, right?
It's one that involves a corporation
manipulating the outcome behind the scenes.
It really has all the hallmarks of a conspiracy theory.
You have a truth sayer who's putting his career on the line.
I'm sure that his coaches got several phone calls
after this interview.
I'm sure he got pulled in his coaches office
and all this stuff.
It's all the hallmarks of a conspiracy theory.
I find this type of stuff very fascinating.
It's a reminder that there are conspiracy theories
happening all around us.
They're like miracles.
They happen all around and we don't know how they work,
but they happen.
Very, very fascinating story.
I don't really cover many sports on this show,
but I thought that was an interesting one.
So Swain, let's hop in that carbonar copter
one last time this episode.
We're headed out to Britain to start this adventure.
(imitates flying)
We're flying out of Houston, Texas.
Supposedly, we'll cover this in a later episode,
but supposedly there's supposed to be a massive hurricane
hitting Houston, Texas on August 10th, I think it was.
We'll be covering that.
It's possible that a time traveler is using TikTok
to warn people of the future.
However, he's also selling t-shirts.
So I'm a little skeptical of his time travel claims,
but Beatrice Leyva sent me that story.
We'll be talking about that later in the week.
That's a little teaser for that.
(imitates flying)
We're leaving behind.
Beatrice is like, "No, no, the hurricane's coming.
Save me, save me.
What, we can't hear you over the carbonar copter.
We can totally hear her.
We're just leaving her behind.
Wait, no, I'm a loyal listener."
We're flying away.
So she's a loyal listener, but we're still leaving her
to the hurricane that won't happen.
But we're flying out.
We're flying out to Britain.
So this is from the Conspiracy Theory iceberg.
It's just a simple phrase on the Conspiracy Theory iceberg.
And again, thank you, some weirdo from Twitter, aka Jack,
for making this Conspiracy Theory iceberg.
Spreadsheet has really made a lot of this stuff helpful
to look at.
We're flying to Britain because there's a Conspiracy Theory
iceberg phrase, "LED attracts demons."
And that means light emitting diodes.
So we're talking about all sorts of LED lights,
which includes flat screen television sets,
which will include your cell phone,
includes computer monitors,
which includes devices all over us.
These things invite demonic activity.
So before we get into this, we're gonna go to Britain.
We're gonna travel back to the year 1907.
And LED light has a interesting provenance
of different things.
I see I learned, I learned, I learned from my mistakes.
When it was basically invented and then forgotten
and invented and forgotten.
But it was originally first invented in the year 1907.
That's the first time that you're able
to create a solid state light,
which is different than gas light or filament lights.
Now back in 1907, this is like people are still walking
around in old-time Victorian clothing.
The tripods haven't even shown up yet.
So we're talking about like old-timey stuff,
but they were still working on a solid state light.
And now it's everywhere.
But you know, like it was invented and lost,
invented and lost.
1907, guess who invented it?
Marconi Labs.
Now I don't know if that's the same Marconi related
to Marconi systems that we covered on Friday,
that a bunch of people were brutally suicided.
A little weird coincidence, right?
I don't know how many Marconi Labs are out there,
but maybe it's different.
Maybe it's the same people.
It wouldn't make sense though,
because Marconi was pushing limits of science
even in the 80s.
But LED lights are all around us.
It's very, very efficient.
They don't use a lot of energy.
They don't put out a lot of heat.
The problem is that they're very, very damaging to our eyes.
But it allows us to have flat screens.
It allows us to have super bright cell phones
and all that stuff.
It can make your poison.
It could cause permanent eye damage.
We don't know yet.
But let's take a look at this phrase here.
LED attracts demons.
LED attracts demonic activity.
It's kind of a spooky phrase,
because I know that I personally stay up late
in bed with my cell phone, reading nonsense.
And the light is comforting, right?
You're in a dark room.
You have that light.
You feel safe.
But what if the light is actually attracting the darkness?
What if right now while you're lying in bed,
listening to this podcast and your phones off in the corner,
giving you a little bit of blue light?
What if that's not a safety net?
What if it's actually a beacon for dark forces?
I think it's interesting on one level
because light is always,
light is the opposite of darkness.
The book of Genesis starts off
where there is nothing but darkness.
And then God says, "Let there be light."
And that's like the creation.
There was nothingness,
and then light is the first thing created.
That's if you believe in the story of Genesis.
But even if you don't,
I think you still get the symbolism.
Even if you look at the book of Genesis as a myth,
you still understand the symbolism.
It's light coming into darkness.
It's something coming into nothing.
I think when we think of light,
we also think of the heat, of the warmth.
And even a light bulb, an old light bulb,
an old filament light bulb was hot to the touch.
So you couldn't have light without other forms of energy,
i.e. heat.
But what if you're able to have light
but you're able to not have the heat?
Which is what an LED does.
Or it has such an insignificant amount of heat.
What if it's not the light
that actually keeps the darkness away,
but the heat that does,
it's not the light of day
that keeps demonic forces at bay.
It's the heat of the life-giving sun.
It's the oil lamp.
It's the candle.
It's the flame.
Even if it's just the flame being put out by a filament,
we were confused.
It wasn't the light itself,
but the heat behind the light.
Now that we've been able to create a world of light
with no heat,
we've basically taken that natural defense away.
So we are in the darkness,
even though there's light.
We're still surrounded by darkness.
So when you're already in a dark room
and you pull out your cell phone late at night,
that blue screen pops up.
Something knows that you are not protected.
It knows where you're at.
And it knows that the heat,
the life-giving energy is gone.
Replaced with a false light.
Lucifer is described as,
Lucifer literally means light bringer.
But is it a false light?
That was always the thing.
Lucifer brings false light.
Very, very esoteric.
I mean, obviously this is what we do
with the conspiracy theory icebergs.
We take these phrases,
we examine whether or not there's any truth to the phrase.
We put on our conspiracy caps full board.
We discuss this.
So that's one saying of it could have a literal meaning
like that,
that having LED lights attract demons
because it is a false light.
We think we're safe, but we're not.
We're the opposite of safe.
We're sending out a beacon.
I mean, that's always the thing.
When you cry for help,
you could be attracting a savior
or you could be attracting a predator
knowing that you're unsafe.
You're scared.
So let's flip this around for a second.
Maybe the blue screen isn't attracting them
to us in the external world.
Maybe the demons have already infested cyberspace.
They're already existing in this virtual world.
And when we pull out our phone late at night,
turn it on and begin surfing the internet,
as your kids call it.
They find their way from the virtual world
into our world.
That's interesting theory.
Let's take a look at this.
You'll see this if you look this up.
So I have to address this.
There's a man.
He's the Reverend Jim P's.
I have to give him his due.
He's a man of the cloth.
A Reverend Jim P's borough.
He wrote a book called "Devil and the Machine."
He's a minister down in Georgia
and he was interviewed in this newspaper.
You'll see his name pop up
on a ton of very reputable paranormal websites.
He wrote a book called "Ghost and the Machine"
about how demons can possess computers.
He doesn't exist.
He was originally mentioned in the weekly world news.
The book doesn't exist.
He doesn't exist.
So if you start researching this
and he pops up immediately,
just move on to the next article
'cause that doesn't exist.
What does exist?
So I had to address that
'cause he's the most popular.
What does exist though is there is a man named Rizwan Horshi.
And he wrote two books.
They're both called "See and Control Demons and Pains"
from my eyes, "A Sense and Theories."
And then he had book one and book two.
He had an interesting,
I haven't ordered the books.
I was just reading the excerpts
and they have the Google x-ray thing.
But I think I got the gist of it.
He has this theory that demons do possess computers.
He actually believes that there is a separate type of demon
that is what's known as an electronic demon.
And he says they're basically completely digital,
but not digital in the sense that they're ones and zeros.
Like they don't exist, they exist in an electronic form.
Their bodies are electric.
Their brains are electric.
They are a completely different strata of demons.
And these demons use the electrical impulses
of our brains to hack us.
Now this obviously sounds completely bizarre, right?
But let's again put on our conspiracy caps
that also protect our brains from being hacked.
The idea of a spiritual possession is a demon
taking over your body.
Your soul is trapped in your own body.
So you can kind of observe what's going on,
but the demon has control over your body.
If you had to explain hacking to a caveman,
that is pretty much what you would say, right?
That your computer is being controlled by somebody else.
Now obviously it gets more complicated than that.
You could say, well, your computer is not controlled.
It's this particular subset program that's running,
and it's overwriting this program
that should be doing it and so on and so forth.
It has back there.
You can go into the real technical side of it,
but you will just say,
the hacker has control of your computer.
You talk to a computer specialist,
they'll be like, well,
they have control of this particular thing
in this path, and stuff like that.
So the idea of a demon not necessarily having
a soul possession, but simply hacking into your brain,
your brain is nothing but electrical impulses
and gray matter.
And so the idea that something could interfere
with the electrical impulses would make sense.
And how do most people get hacked?
Not all, but most people get hacked
by messing up themselves,
by inviting something into their computer.
Opening an email, clicking on a link,
winning, quote unquote, winning a sweepstakes
and following the prompts.
That's how a lot of computers get hacked.
It's rare that you just turn on your computer.
If it possible, I'm sure it's possible,
but it would have to be a specialized attack
where you turn on your computer,
you do nothing and it gets hacked.
And so what do we always hear about people getting possessed?
They invite the spirits in.
They're using the Ouija board.
They're going to these haunted locations.
They're putting themselves at risk of being possessed,
i.e. hacked.
So it's less paranormal and more like a new program
overriding the brain.
And because these demons exist in an electronic form
or an electrical form,
they can move through the internet.
So it's not like you're pulling your cell phone
up late at night and there's a demon
out in a graveyard somewhere and flying through the sky
and it's sitting outside your window.
It's the other side.
It's in the system already.
And you're going through the internet
and you're seeing a link and you're clicking on it
and something in the system sees you.
That blue light to us is a display,
but it's really a one-way mirror.
On the other side of that screen,
of that big screen television set of your laptop,
of your phone, there's something watching you,
influencing you, hacking you.
I find this theory very, very fascinating.
Very fascinating.
I believe that there's another phrase
on the conspiracy theory iceberg
that I've tried looking into.
I haven't really found much on it.
It's enchanted websites.
I believe, and I mentioned this before on the show,
I believe that websites can be haunted.
I 100% believe that if a place,
if a location can be haunted,
what is a website but a digital place?
We even use terms like digital storefront.
Why couldn't there be haunted websites?
Haunted porn websites that make you seek out
more extreme pornography until the next thing you know,
the feds are kicking in your door.
You just went too far.
You couldn't get that feeling again.
It was addicted.
A haunted gambling website.
You end up blowing your family's fortunes.
There was a guy recently who met a cam girl in Russia.
He embezzled $250,000 from his father.
And when his family finally had an intervention for him,
he killed his brother, his mother, and his father.
He's in prison now for the rest of his life for a cam girl.
I'm not saying the cam girl is a demon,
but I'm saying that you can't tell me
there's not demonic influences on the internet.
You find a gore website,
and then you're trying to find even gore-er things,
and then you wanna try it out for yourself.
Now millions of people could go and watch gore videos
all day long, but you went to that site
that had another force behind it.
You went to that site and something reached out
and interfered with the electrical waves of your brain.
You didn't even notice it,
but you knew you needed to go back to that site.
Maybe you were at work the next day and you felt,
I need to go see if they've updated that.
I wanna see what that's new going on.
I wanna see this and you keep going to it
over and over and over again.
You're building those neural pathways.
You're opening the door to this thing.
Riz Juan also says that based on his theory,
we should never build robots
with the capability of killing humans,
because guess what?
These electronic demons can possess the body of a robot.
So it may not be that we have to worry about the AI,
over Lord, or maybe a demon will masquerade as an AI.
Humanity will think they've created this amazing,
advanced intelligence system,
but it's really an age-old demonic force.
The darkness itself that was pushed away
when the light came into existence.
Sitting in a computer, leading humanity.
And what does LED stand for, light emitting diode?
What is it's spell?
LED causing a person to move in a direction.
Now I've made fun of other people
who've made such connections in the past
and feel free to make fun of me,
but I do find that to be an interesting coincidence.
Is it possible that these devices we have in our pockets
that we use for entertainment,
that you're probably listening to this podcast on
this very moment, is actually a beacon
that brings us, every time we use it,
one step closer to the darkness.
We think it connects us as a civilization.
And it does, but it may be connecting the civilization
to something much darker, much older,
and much more evil than we could ever comprehend.
(upbeat music)
DeadRabbitRadio@gmail.com is gonna be your email address.
You can also hit us up at facebook.com/deadrabbitradio.
Twitter is @deadrabbitradio.
DeadRabbitRadio is the daily paranormal conspiracy
and true crime podcast.
You don't have to listen to it every day,
but I'm glad you listened to it today.
Have a great one, guys.
(upbeat music)