Geico asks, "How would you love a chance to save some money on insurance?"
Of course you would!
And when it comes to great rates on insurance, Geico can help.
Like with insurance for your car, truck, motorcycle, boat, and RV.
Even help with homeowners or renters coverage.
Plus, add an easy-to-use mobile app, available 24-hour roadside assistance, and more.
And Geico is an easy choice.
Switch today and see all the ways you could save.
It's easy.
Simply go to geico.com or contact your local agent today.
How would you do if you were asleep in one night, catching some z's?
When all of a sudden, you realized something was watching you.
And then we take a look at the story of the puppy named Eddie.
A curious little guy who's found stranded on the side of the road.
But when a family adopts Eddie and brings him home, they have no idea he's going to
become a gateway to the world of the dead.
Today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Garvin, and I'm having a great day.
I hope you guys are having a great day too.
I hope you guys are having tons of fun out there in the world doing whatever you're
doing.
Don't forget it's coming up to the end of season 20 and we are about to take a break.
I don't think there's going to be any classic episodes this time.
I know that I always say that we're going to do them.
There's so much more work.
I need to do them at the beginning of the season and I say that every time too.
But we will have more classic episodes for you at some point in the future of Dead Rabbit
Radio because I do love doing them.
I'm just done.
You know, by the end of the season, I'm so overworked.
And also a quick reminder, March 24th, 6pm in Seaside Organ at the Oregon Ghost Conference.
I will be giving a presentation.
Why are there no fat ghosts?
And I would love to see you guys there.
It's $15, but that's not just for my speech.
$15 gives you three days at the Oregon Ghost Convention or Oregon Ghost Conference.
I guess I should say the name right.
You're walking around.
Here's a big sign that says Oregon Ghost Conference.
You're like, "Oh, Jason said it was the Oregon Ghost Convention."
So I'm not walking in there.
Oregon Ghost Conference in Seaside, Oregon, it's three days and lots of fun of people
talking about the world of the paranormal.
So I can't wait.
I'm going to be stopping by a lot of other speeches.
I want to hear that.
I might attend a workshop or two.
And I hope to see you guys there.
That'll be really cool.
Someone who's always cool whether or not he goes to the Ghost Conference or the Ghost
Convention walking into Dead Rabbit Command right now is one of our newest Patreon supporters.
And give it up for Lazy A Farms.
Woohoo!
Yeah!
Come on in.
An entire plot of land, an entire farm is coming into Dead Rabbit Radio Command.
Lazy A Farms, you're going to be our captain, our pilot this episode.
If you guys can't support the show financially, I totally understand.
I really do.
Just help spread the word about Dead Rabbit Radio.
That helps out so, so much.
Lazy A Farms, everyone, let's walk around on his plot of land.
You're like, Jason, clearly that's a business.
You understand that a farm itself is not supporting the Patreon.
I don't know.
Weird things have happened.
We're walking around with hoes and pickaxes and we're like tilling the soil.
A bunch of cows are giving us orders, telling us what to do.
It's a pretty cool place, Lazy A Farms.
But while we're doing that, I'm going to go ahead and bury the keys for the Dead Rabbit
Dune Buggy in the soil.
Lazy A Farms uses those keys somehow.
I don't know.
Grow some vines.
Drive us all the way out of Dead Rabbit Command.
We're headed out to a little boy's house.
Ding, ding, ding.
It's a nice little speedy drive across the world.
We don't know where the story took place.
We don't really even have a timeline.
But it took place in the past.
It took place sometime between Earth cooling and evolving life on it.
And today, this was written, posted online anonymously.
We're going to go in and call the guy Fred.
And Fred said this story happened when he was eight or nine.
So we'll figure it minimum 10 years ago.
I'd probably say it's in that time period, 10 to 15 years ago.
Fred said that he was spending the weekend with his cousins and having a lot of fun.
He actually didn't have that having a lot of fun part.
But you know, I can do a little bit of editorializing.
I'm sure it wasn't terrible.
Well actually, not that I think about this story.
He's kind of terrifying.
He was spending the weekend with his cousins and he was sleeping on the couch.
And this was the house of his aunt and uncle and their kids.
And we'll go ahead and call him Uncle Jack.
This is the other named character in the story.
He goes to the house, Uncle Jack's house.
The way it was laid out was you had a front door.
Obviously, he's like, no, he had a climb up sheet rope where you could only enter on
the second floor.
Had a front door.
And the way that the front door was set up was there was a window at the top of the door
frame.
And then above it, you have a nice big window to let the sun in.
And that would not be notable in any house.
Right, obviously, he's pointing that out for a reason in this story.
You're like, what?
That's weird.
I've been in a dozen houses like that.
No one's ever been, hey, when you visit, make sure to check out the window above the front
door.
He's like, what?
Is that the best thing about your house?
They're like, yeah.
There's a window above the front door.
So anyways, Fred is spending the weekend here.
He's sleeping on the couch.
His eyes are closed.
His little eight or nine year old eyelids are tightly shut.
But he sees, well, it's like that weird thing.
You know when your eyes are closed and someone's shining a light?
Probably me.
You're trying to get a nice sleep on top of you with a flashlight.
I was like, wake up, wake up.
You know how when you have your eyes closed, but someone turns on the light, even though
your eyes are closed, you can kind of see the light through your eyelids?
You're like, before you even wake up, you're kind of annoyed that the light's on.
It's that.
That's the sensation he's having.
His eyes are shut, but he kind of wakes up in the middle of the night because he senses
a light is on a very bright light, a very bright green light, which would be more alarming.
There should be far more alarming.
You may think, no, it's not.
You may be a leprechaun and you're like, oh, my lights are green.
Imagine if you woke up in the middle of the night and there was, you shut off all the
lights and all of these scenarios are terrifying.
I always make up the scariest.
Imagine all the lights in your house are off.
You wake up in the middle of the night and you can see underneath the crack of your bedroom
door that your hall light's on.
That'd be spooky.
But imagine, you're like, Jason, no, I don't care what color the light is.
If I shut them all off, I woke up in the middle of the night and it was a strobe light.
Well, see, that's the thing.
It'd be scarier because then you'd think aliens are in my hallway.
If it was a green light coming from underneath your doorway, you would go paranormal.
If there's a red light, you'd go demons.
You would associate different light with different phenomenon.
All of them would be equally terrifying.
But if you were over at your uncle's house, an unfamiliar house, and there was a green
glowing light, you'd think, oh, maybe someone has a really bright alarm clock.
Maybe someone's experimenting with radiated rods nearby.
But whatever it is, whatever's going on, it's annoying.
And Fred's trying to sleep and he opens his eyes up and he sees, of course, like he thought
with his eyes closed.
The entire living room is bathed in a green glow.
And then he almost immediately realizes the source of the glow.
It's not a alarm clock.
It's not radiation.
Well, it might be radiation.
I can't really think about it.
But he realizes, like, he looks around and his eyes settle on that window above the front
door.
And what he sees is so impossible.
He goes, I must just be dreaming.
That's not possible.
I'm going to go back to sleep.
So he closes his eyes.
He holds them tight.
And the green glow is continuing to permeate his eyelids.
And then he begins to get this sensation that he is being watched.
That tried and true sensation we've all been through where we feel like someone's watching
him.
And now he's like, OK, this isn't fake.
It's impossible.
But it's real.
He kind of takes his eyes.
He's kind of squinting.
He's kind of, like, barely looking.
He doesn't want it to know he's awake.
Fred does not want this thing to know that he is terrified.
What Fred saw when he first opened his eyes was a massive green eyeball floating outside
the front door window.
So the front door itself is what?
We're talking about six, seven feet tall.
Six feet tall.
We've bumped our heads all the time.
It's about seven, eight feet tall, right?
So this giant eyeball is floating about nine or 10 feet off the ground.
It's giant.
If it was a normal sized eyeball floating 10 feet off the ground, you're like, ah, whatever.
I'm trying to attack it with a place water.
But it's giant.
It's a giant green floating eyeball.
It's taking up almost the entire window.
So you imagine it's floating about nine feet off the ground.
And you could say it's maybe four feet in diameter, maybe a little bit bigger than a
basketball.
You're like, what basketball do you play with?
That's actually huge.
Four feet in diameter would be a massive basketball.
The globe trotters are like, ah, yeah, it's funny looking, but we'll hurt our backs if
we try dribbling that thing.
Big, big eyeball floating.
And when he first saw, if you saw a giant eyeball, if you woke him in the middle of
the night, there's a giant eyeball floating outside your house, you would go, I must be
dreaming, that's impossible.
If you saw what looked like an intruder, if he had just seen the green glow, he probably
would have been more curious of what was out there.
Giant eyeballs don't exist, but when he tried going back to sleep, when he shut his eyes,
that's when he felt the eyeball was watching him intently.
And so Fred is laying on this couch and he has his eyes closed like he's pretending to
sleep, but he's kind of squinting through them because he wants to like double check.
Is that what I saw?
Is there really a giant eyeball out there?
And he said, when I was squinting and I'm looking at the eyeball, the eyeball twitched.
It had a physical reaction as if it knew for a fact that Fred was looking at it.
He said it made a physical movement and I felt now that it knew that not only was I
awake, but I was steady in it.
I was trying to figure out what it was.
And Fred just begins screaming at the top of his lungs.
He's being screaming at the top of his lungs.
He starts the middle of the night and his uncle comes storming down the stairs.
Not like, oh no, I got to protect this blood of mine.
I got to protect this nephew.
He's one of the pack.
No.
He hears a little boy screaming and he's pissed off, which is fair, right?
You're not going to assume, oh, the burglar must have gotten into my house and is killing,
killing my nephew.
You would be running down the stairs being like, great, I have a little kid over here.
He's in a new house and something scared him.
The burglar, the burglar.
Yes, he can be scary kids, but as long as he just steals the stuff we don't use anymore,
everything's okay.
Uncle Jack comes downstairs and he's actually really upset because he just woke up.
He was deep asleep.
All of a sudden he heard this little kid scream and it's not even yours.
And Uncle Jack enters the room and grumpily says, what is it?
And Jack just points at the window and goes, look.
And Uncle Jack follows the finger and looks at the front door and looks at the window
and takes a step backwards.
He's startled by what he sees.
He has a physical reaction to it.
This wasn't just the nightmare.
This wasn't just the hallucination or the trick of the light.
Uncle Jack sees it too and he steps back.
Uncle Jack's like, what is that?
And Fred goes, it looks like an eye.
And it's still just floating there.
Now there's two witnesses who are watching this phenomenon.
And Uncle Jack, to his credit, walks towards the eye.
I don't know if I would have done that.
I might have scooped the kid up and ran upstairs and fucked all the torus.
I don't know.
Maybe I would have walked towards the eye.
Maybe I'm braver than I think.
But Uncle Jack walks towards the eye and he puts his hand on the door handle and he opens
the door up and right when he does that, the eyeball vanishes.
Uncle Jack shuts the door and then we have probably the most realistic conversation that
can happen in one of these situations.
We run into it all the time.
If you're an experiencer of the paranormal, this is something you run into all the time.
If you're a fan of paranormal, I'm sure you've read accounts like this as well.
Or wondered, hmm, why did they do that?
Jengrean eye, floating nine feet off the ground, bathing the entire room in green light.
Two witnesses, an adult and a child in two different parts of the room.
One's much taller, one's laying down.
It's not a trick of the lights, not a hallucination, not a dream.
Jengrean eyeball, door opens up, it disappears.
Fred goes, what was that?
And Uncle Jack's exact quote, what Fred told us he said was, quote, "I don't know.
It's gone now.
Go to sleep."
And then Uncle Jack just left.
Uncle Jack just left the living room, walked up the stairs and went back to his bedroom.
And Fred was like, dude, I can't do that.
What are you talking about?
There's Jengrean eyeball out there.
And he goes, I spent the rest of the night just looking at the window.
I couldn't go back to sleep.
He goes, it never showed back up.
And the next morning, when we were sitting around the breakfast table, I asked my uncle,
what was that?
Like, what was up with that giant eyeball that was floating in?
And Uncle Jack goes, I must have just been a trick of the light.
It must have been something 100% explainable.
It's interesting because when you do look at accounts of the paranormal, people will
do things, but they'll have these extraordinary events and they'll go back to sleep.
They'll have these extraordinary events.
And then they continue about their day.
They'll go shopping and then they'll come home and then they will hit them.
The terror, the excitement, whatever they actually went through.
People act in interesting ways and most of the time, it's avoidance.
Yeah, it's like, that can't be true.
And that's what Fred did at first too.
Remember, he saw it.
He was deep asleep, saw the green light, then saw the eyeball and goes, I must be dreaming.
That's not real.
And then the event intensified from there.
It was the same thing with Uncle Jack.
He's like, it was nothing.
Like, even though he clearly saw it and he had a physical reaction to it, like he, it
scared him.
He stepped backwards.
He was scared and then he walked to it, opened the door and it went away.
And his first thing was, I don't know what that was, but it's gone.
Go back to sleep.
It's super interesting, isn't it?
It would have been one thing if Fred was the only witness.
Uncle Jack would be like, just go sleep.
It was a nightmare and Fred could be like it.
But to this day, I know it was a nightmare.
No, there were two witnesses.
And even though the adult saw it, he goes, whatever, whatever, it's probably some eyeball
from another dimension.
Just ignore it.
And then the next day, he'd completely dismissed it.
He's definitely the, the uncle's not posting online being like, you won't believe what
happened.
I was 30 years old and a giant eyeball.
No, you just went on with his life.
Maybe he thought about it later.
Maybe he didn't.
And what's interesting too is I found when I was looking more into this, there were a
couple of different people who also described giant floating eyeballs.
You'd see other people comment on the story and one girl said she opened up her closet
once and there was a giant floating eyeball in her closet.
Another girl said that she would wake up.
This one was particularly creepy.
I mean, no, I'm not like a giant eyeball in her closet is anything to sneeze at or outside
your house.
But she goes, this one seems more malicious.
She goes, I would always sleep with my bedroom door kind of cracked open.
And one night I woke up and there was a giant eyeball floating in the hallway of the house
that also gave off a green glow.
But she said this one floated in such a way that it looked like it was trying to peek
over the top of the open bedroom door.
Like it was making an attempt to spy on her.
Like it was kind of like looking around like a pervert in a Walmart dressing room.
And the reason why I pointed out, you could go, well, Jason, the first eyeball was looking
at a sleeping eight year old boy.
I mean, that's pretty perverted too.
When you have paranormal phenomenon, sometimes it is like my experience with the shadow people,
the shadow men, I'll put it up in the show notes.
They were completely aloof.
They didn't care.
My experiences with them was they did not care that you were there.
They didn't care that you observed them.
It was basically the same thing as a squirrel sitting on a rock watching the river.
The river doesn't care.
It's simply a phenomenon that it neither hates nor loves the squirrels.
It's simply happening in this place and time and it's being observed by the squirrel.
So an eyeball floating outside of a house could be a neutral phenomenon.
It didn't like being looked at for sure and it disappeared when the door opened.
But that's fairly neutral.
The eyeball kind of angling for a better view of a little girl sleeping in her bedroom.
That seems creepy.
To be fair, they're both creepy, but you know what I mean?
One of them, the one floating in the closet, that seems fairly neutral, a neutral phenomenon.
Then you can have helpful paranormal phenomenon, which I think happens so often we don't even
recognize it.
Sometimes it's super dramatic and we'll talk about guardian angels, but I think sometimes
it's just you see something, you walk down the road and you see something that makes
you smile.
You see giant green eyeball being dribbled by the Harlem Globetrotters and you're like,
"I think sometimes good paranormal events are so minor they just kind of lighten our mood."
You get home and your favorite television show, you didn't miss a minute of it, right?
When you got home, "Jason, no one does that anymore, you boomer."
We all watch stuff on streaming.
You know what I mean?
I'm sure there are little paranormal things that happen quite often that we just account
to luck or being like, "Wow, everything just kind of worked out.
I think you could qualify that stuff as good paranormal, evil paranormal stuff obviously,
you know, murders, people getting chopped up by demons, people falling deeper and deeper
into addictions or depression and completely destroying their lives and the lives of their
family, all that stuff.
That would be more of the negative.
Even I think a spooky ghost floating around your house, they don't, he's like, "I'm sorry
to make you aeronetic.
I'm just a spooky ghost.
You have such high standards, Jason.
I just wanted to float around and be spooky and now I got to take you down to the casino
and you sit in front of a slot machine for 10 hours, dude.
You can have just spooky ghosts, spooky noises, things to scare you and then things that actually
ruin your life.
Yeah, but again, I think it's interesting because the glowing green eye, how malicious
is it and how widespread is it too?
It's really interesting when someone comes out and says, "Hey, here's the story I have."
And then you see other people talk about it.
Some of them could be made up because they're kind of hanging on to the story, but some
of them, a story like this, like again, we talk about this all the time, they show where
to classify it.
It's not a ghost, it's not a UFO, it's not a cryptid.
There's dedicated organizations for those.
So if you see an alien kill your dog, like we talked about on Friday and Monday's episode,
you contact MUFON.
If you see Bigfoot, you contact the Bigfoot Research Group.
If you see a ghost, you contact ghost researchers, but who do you call for a giant green eyeball?
So who knows how common this is?
Probably not super common, but it may have happened more than just a few times it was
posted here.
And Fred went online by the name FitzyTheArtist.
That was the name they posted this on.
I wanted to give them credit for that.
But interesting story, what is the phenomenon and is it going to be watching you tonight?
Like, I hope so.
You buy some new underwear, you're like getting all sexy before bed, you're like, "Oh, I have
that green eye spies on me."
Lazy A farms will do it and leave all these perverts, leave all these eyeball perverts
behind.
The rest of you get on board the world of famous carbonar copter at Lazy A farms.
I'm going to touch you the keys, catch them in your corn stock.
We are leaving behind Uncle Jack's house.
Take us all the way out to a road.
The whole time he's like, "This road is like, no, no, not that road."
We're going to a specific road.
In another story, we don't have a location for or a time.
And this story might pull on your heartstrings a little bit.
So if you're currently going through a bout of depression, be warned.
Also if you love talks, like Jason, what is it?
Just got done with closing counters of a canine kind of week.
Let's take a look at this story.
I find this story beautiful.
But let's take a look at it.
It doesn't start off beautiful.
It starts off quite grim.
We're going to take a look at Joey's family.
All these names, except for the dog's name.
The dog's name is real.
But all these names we've had to create are supposed to be anonymously.
Joey tells this story.
He said, "One day my stepdad, Phillip, was driving down the road and he sees a little
lump on the side of the road."
A little lump.
He's like, "Oh, that's my favorite.
That's my favorite Fergie song."
He's all humming it as he's walking up to the lump.
He's like, "My humby, humby, humbs.
My lumps.
My lovely lady."
And then he looks and the lump, it's not a lovely lady lump, although that would be
disgusting too.
There's just a boob sitting on the side of the road.
He's like, "Ah, that's not what I expected either."
What he sees is a puppy.
But this puppy's not in good shape.
This puppy, because you're my friend, I'm not going to go into detail.
But apparently what it seemed like, okay, I'm not going to tell you that, just the puppy
is not in good shape.
And Phillip goes, "Philip's all set in imagining in great detail.
What could have happened?"
And he's like, "I'm not going to tell anyone that."
Phillip takes the dog to the vet and he goes, "Hey, this isn't my dog.
I found him by the side of the road."
And the vet's like, "Dear God, you know what happened to this dog?"
And he starts talking about it.
And Phillip's like, "I don't know.
Just fix the dog.
Just fix this dog, please."
And the vet goes, "We will rebuild this dog."
And so they did.
They spent a lot of money, but Eddie was ready to go.
They were like, "Back to the road, buddy."
He's like, "Ruff, ruff, ruff, ruff."
And they named this puppy Eddie and Phillip goes, "You know what?
We did spend a lot of money on this dog.
Let's take him home.
Let's consider him an investment.
I'll write him off for my taxes."
Let's bring good old Eddie home.
So they take Eddie home and at this time Joey is a little boy.
And Joey and Eddie kind of start growing up alongside each other going on little adventures.
He's like, "You want to go for a walk down the road?"
And he's like, "Ruff, ruff, ruff, ruff, ruff in."
And they're like, "What?
I know you can talk."
Joey and Eddie are growing up together.
But Eddie, although he loves hanging out with everyone, he is Phillip's dog.
He loves Phillip so much.
And Joey goes, "We all had our time to sit and pet Eddie, chase him around."
Eddie is constantly hanging out with Phillip.
And wherever you found Phillip, you found Eddie right next to him.
It was like a true bond.
But everyone, it wasn't like he growled at everybody else.
But you know, Phillip comes home from work and a little puppy's walking next to him.
He was to have the coal mine too.
He has a little hat, a little hard hat on.
His face is all dirty.
When Phillip comes home from work, Eddie runs up to him, sits in his lap.
And they sit there and they watch the news together.
Price is right, whatever.
And that's just life.
That's life for Eddie.
He's found his home.
He's found his family.
He's found his dad, Phillip.
Little Eddie loves this family.
And Joey eventually, it's time for him to go to college.
And when Joey is at college, he gets a phone call from his mom saying Eddie passed away
last night.
And obviously Joey's heart broken, right?
Like, this was like a member of the family.
He grew up with Joey.
And in the back of his mind, he's thinking, "Oh my God, what about my stepdad?"
Like, "It hurts me.
It hurts my heart that Eddie has passed, but I can't imagine what my stepdad's gone through.
Like, it was like, he rescued this puppy.
This puppy was going to die.
And my dad just happened to pull over and pick him up and not only save his life, but
then bring him home and make him part of our life.
And Joey says, "This happened so suddenly."
Him dying and then being buried in the Pet Cemetery.
He goes, "I felt like I didn't have a chance to say goodbye.
I definitely didn't get a chance to be with him in his final moments."
And he doesn't say how Eddie died, but you know, probably natural causes.
I think he would have included if he involved a road.
But anyways, he just says that Eddie passes away.
And it all happened so quickly.
He didn't get to say goodbye to Eddie either while he was getting sicker or even after,
you know, like at the funeral ceremony for the dog and all that stuff.
So he felt that he had lost something when, a piece of the grieving process.
Joey felt like he wasn't, he wasn't part of that, you know.
He said a few months later though, Joey's still in college and he has a dream.
He has a dream that he's standing outside in a fairly unfamiliar place.
He just knows that it's this outside location.
And there's this trail.
And trotting down the trail is Eddie.
And he sees Eddie come towards him and he's so relieved.
He's like, "Eddie, oh my God, oh, I've missed you so much."
And he looks down and Eddie is a little worse for wear.
But he's happy.
His tail is wagging.
He's doing a little puppy dance.
His hair is matted and dirty.
And as Joey is petting Eddie, he realizes that Eddie's flesh is also a little rotten.
I probably, I probably stopped petting him at that point.
Dream or no dream.
But he realizes like what he's looking at is Eddie is dead, even in the dream.
But Eddie is so happy and so excited it doesn't matter.
Joey's going to take this moment to be with Eddie just a little bit longer.
And they begin walking down this trail.
And the whole time Eddie is just wagging his little tail.
So happy.
He's back with his buddy Joey, his brother Joey.
And Joey said, "The farther we got down the trail, the more excited Eddie got."
He's started prancing a little bit more, tail wagging even more.
So excited to be on this journey with Joey.
Until eventually they come to this giant wall of mist.
Joey said that it covered the entire horizon.
You could look both ways.
It would go on forever.
And when he looked up he saw it reached far past the sky.
The wall of mist was silent, peaceful.
There was a beauty to this barrier.
But Joey knew that this was the end of the trip.
Eddie walks up to the wall of mist and then turns around and walks back to Joey.
Joey reaches down to pet Eddie again.
Eddie just licks Joey's hand.
Joey picks up Eddie.
They do a couple little nose kisses.
And he sets Eddie back on the ground.
And Eddie begins to whine just a little bit, just for a moment.
Eddie looks back up at Joey, walks back towards the wall of mist.
And as he gets to the mist he begins doing his little happy dog dance again.
His little prance that Joey had seen so many times before.
In the moments when Eddie was the happiest he would do this little dance.
Eddie walks through the wall of mist to the point that now it's just a silhouette of a
dog.
All detail has been lost to the fog.
This little dog is dancing around in the mist and begins jumping up and down as a humanoid
silhouette shows up.
Joey sees Eddie jump up and down as this shadowy apparition appears next to him.
Joey takes a step forward himself.
He wants to see what's beyond the mist, what's on the other side of this unending wall.
He reaches out and he puts his hand against the mist.
And his cell phone goes off.
He wakes up, his cell phone's ringing.
He reaches over, looks at the number, answers the call.
It's his mother.
She's sobbing.
Phillip just died of a heart attack.
It's a fascinating on so many levels it has what we expect from a traditional ghost story.
It has all of these elements in it.
The idea of dreaming of a dead loved one coming back to visit you one last time.
Very traditional ghost experience.
We've had a couple stories this week.
I didn't plan it this way.
I definitely didn't plan all the dead dogs in the past two weeks.
But we covered the boss at the work site.
Nobody knew he died but they saw his ghost.
The story has that element as well.
The implication is that the humanoid figure on the other side of the mist was Phillip.
It's never explicitly said but I think that's the implication.
That was this dream and Eddie was going.
He was excited for multiple reasons to see Joey again but Eddie also was there to walk
with Phillip in the afterlife.
They were inseparable and now they would be together in paradise.
This is one of those stories.
When you look at it, when you look at this person's posting history, they haven't posted
in a long time.
But it's not a ton of spooky stories.
It's not a ton of...
Actually it's zero.
This is the only one.
Otherwise they're just constantly walking around Reddit.
Every so often they're in a subreddit called "RetKond" which is actually a new version
of the Mandela effect.
I've been spending a lot of time on that subreddit.
There's some interesting stuff coming out of there.
But you know what I mean?
He's not on the creepypasta subreddit.
He's not like "and then the next day Eddie returned and he had a watch, a magical watch
that allowed him to control a UFO.
He's not constantly adding to the narrative.
It could be made up but it's also possibly true in the world of the paranormal.
Nothing in the story is out of place.
For the most part it just seems like a traditional ghost story.
And it's one that I think depending on your point of view is either sweet or sad.
Because I think you can hear the story and go "well that's just so sad that you know
like Eddie and Philip are dead" or any story involving a dead dog is sad.
I don't know why you can't get that through your head Jason.
Listen I love dogs.
I don't eat dogs.
I think the story is sweet.
I think the story is a reminder that death is not the end.
I think that's the reason the appeal of a lot of ghost stories.
I think even when they come back as monsters, they're like "death is not the end and I'm
gonna haunt you until you're death and then I'm gonna keep haunting you because death
is not the end and I'm gonna bully you in the afterlife as well" you're like "ugh".
You know what I mean like to know that there's something after this.
I think it's a sweet.
I think it's an endearing thought.
I think it's calming in a way.
And I know there's not everyone's like that.
Some people go "I think it's more intriguing to think that this is all that there is and
when you die it's over."
I mean to each their own.
But and they may hear this story and they may go "well it's really the story about a
kid whose dog died and then his stepdad died and everything else was a hallucination.
Everything else was just a dream."
Jason this whole thing took place in the dream.
Like what's the paranormal aspect?
It's funny now that I say that the only paranormal aspect of the dream is the fact that he knew
well actually okay this is super interesting because this is part of this.
This show has no script.
If you guys haven't guessed that, thinking about it this way and I could go on forever
so we're gonna have to wrap this up because I just thought of this.
There is no element in this story that is paranormal.
Zero.
Not saying that it has to be.
Someone's like "oh no my kid died" I was like "well but did they get killed by a
ghost?"
They're like "no" I was like "ah don't tell me about it."
I was reporting on it as a paranormal story and I made all of these.
The way I read it was it was the ghost of Eddie coming back to say goodbye to Joey one
more time and then led Joey to the wall that separates the world of the living and the
world of the dead and on the other side of that wall was now Eddie and then a humanoid
figure appeared who Joey at no point, I'm gonna double check because I don't even know
if he specifically says "I think that was my stepdad."
Let me double check that here.
It says then he turns around again and starts to do that happy dog prance toward the wall
until he finally passes through it.
I can sort of see his outline jumping up and down excitedly next to a human shaped figure.
I jog after Eddie and reach my hand out to touch the wall hoping I'll be able to pass
through it too.
That's when my cell phone rings in real life waking me up.
When I answer it my mom is on the other end crying.
My stepdad has just died of a heart attack.
So he never even makes that claim.
And that interesting, the way I read the story was that the dog had come back from the afterlife
to greet, say goodbye to Joey and then Phillip showed up and was on the other side of this
wall and that's why Eddie was doing such a little happy dance.
And then Joey wakes up and finds out that his stepdad is just out of a heart attack.
And this is interesting because as a paranormal guy, as a paranormal researcher, I defaulted
to that because it had so many hallmarks of a paranormal story.
But it wasn't a paranormal story.
Was it just a dream?
Could you argue the humanoid figure wasn't him knowing in advance even just by a few
seconds that his stepdad was going to die?
Like I'm assuming the stepdad died, the mom wasn't calling him as he was having a heart
attack.
I'm assuming the stepdad had died and the ambulance just picked him up and all that stuff and
then they get the phone call.
But who knows?
It's an interesting story now to think about it.
It may be a paranormal story of ghosts and premonitions of death, even if it's just by
a couple seconds, a couple minutes before that phone call, right?
It's still a premonition.
It could be a story of that or it could just be the story of a dream.
And the humanoid figure on the other side of the wall was not Philip.
It was just another guardian spirit there with Eddie.
That's super interesting.
That's just, I think, looking on that, that's an insight into how I read things, my psyche,
right?
It was posted, someone asked the question, "What is the most paranormal or unexplainable
event you have ever witnessed?"
And people were responding to that question.
So it wasn't unexplainable.
You could say it was unexplained.
You could say it was paranormal.
My view on life after death, which I believe in, if you asked me what exactly is that,
I don't know.
Like, I don't know.
I don't know how it works.
I don't know if it's reincarnation.
I don't know if it's heaven, like a literal place called heaven, if it's some sort of
paradise world.
Who knows?
I don't know.
But so this story, I read it and I go, "Oh, these are the things that I already think
about the after."
There's going to be a lot of dancing dogs.
That better be.
Fascinating story, though.
Ghost story, unexplained event, or just simply a dream that I've read.
Not only did I read too much into it, but I told it in such a way that led it to maybe
you also going, "Oh, this is about ghosts."
I think I even said in the beginning, this ghost brings home, opens a portal to the other
world or whatever it said in the beginning.
So that's interesting.
I almost feel like this is a meta commentary.
How did you experience that story?
Because the whole time you think, "Oh, it's just a dream," or, "Oh, Jason's making a joke
about dogs on roads again.
Come on, dude."
Just tell the story, but fascinating.
And it shows kind of my view of the world and how I can lead.
Like again, if you weren't predisposed, I don't want to get too meta, but if you weren't
going to be predisposed to hearing that story and thinking it the way I did, did I tell
it in such a way that you didn't have an option?
That's all real fascinating stuff.
But not as to me, not as fascinating as the story.
I really love the story of Eddie and Phillip.
And it's a story that love lives on even after death.
Love does not die with death.
I truly do believe that.
And so does Eddie.
DeadRabberRadio@gmail.com is going to be our email address.
You can also set it up at facebook.com/DeadRabberRadio.
Tiktok is @DeadRabberRadio.
DeadRabberRadio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast.
You don't have to listen to it every day, but I'm glad you listened to it today.
Have a great day.
Bye.
(upbeat music)